RUBY: Previously on Good Girls...
You ladies got passports?
He wants us to pick something up for him
in Canada.
We just need a car.
RUBY: We should just borrow a Car.
What's going on?
It's, uh, the craziest thing.
We got hit.
You guys, they know about the car.
Who are you?
We're the volunteers.
Oy, Gloria,
are you ever not pregnant?
(BOTH CHUCKLE)
Oh!
Because if kids
like you all are our future,
God help us all.
I'll go clean out my locker.
What did Stan say?
I can't tell Stan.
I gotta get something else going first.
Where's your uniform?
I left it at work.
DOCTOR: Your daughter had a seizure.
Her kidney's basically non-functioning.
We have a business proposition.
To clean your fake money.
Let us do it right here.
Fake money in, real money out.
You want all this back on a card?
Cash is fine.
Morning, Mrs. Boland.
You know this guy?
Uh... No.
I have cancer.
(ROCK MUSIC PLAYING)
DR. HARPER: So, with the high PSA
and the biopsy,
it's cancer in your prostate.
There's no question.
(POLICE RADIO CHATTERING)
(SPEAKING INDISTINCTLY)
DR. HARPER:
There are so many treatment options
these days.
External radiation,
chemo.
We even do robotic-assisted surgery,
if that's something you wanna consider.
How much is all of this gonna cost?
(RADIO CHATTERING INDISTINCTLY)
Sir.
(ROCK MUSIC CONTINUES)
I'll see you after the exam.
(DOOR CLOSES)
Couldn't make it sound
a little more serious?
It's cancer.
Cadillac?
Buick.
New?
New to you.
(SINGING)
J Fresh dressed like a million bucks
(STAN BEAT-BOXING)
I Threw on the Bally shoes
and the fly green socks
f Stepped out the house Stopped short
- Oh, no.
S / went back in I forgot...
I My PAYGO S So then I dilly
- BOTH: Dally, I ran through an alley
I bumped into my old girl
t Sally from the valley f Sally... Valley
f This is a girl playing hard to get
(BEAT-BOXING)
F So! said, "What's wrong?"
F 'Cause she looked upset
BOTH:
S Now, what was I to do?
J She was crying over me
f And she was feeling blue
I said, "Don't cry."
- "Dry your eyes"
< "Here comes your mother
f "with those two little guys"
J Her mean mother stepped up
- said to me, "Hi"
J "Hy"
J Looked Sally in the face
and decked her in the eye
f Punched her in the belly
ft and stepped on her feet tS Feet
S Slammed the child on the hard
BOTH:
- Concrete f
Boom!
(IMITATES CRASHING SOUND)
(IMITATES LASER BEAMS)
Hills in effect!
(MIMICS LASER BEAMS)
That was awesome.
You want some breakfast?
(SIGHS)
I can put on a movie.
Secret Life of Pets.
Yeah.
Yeah?
Maybe later.
(SIGHS)
Are you still okay to stay home with her?
I'm at the diner all day.
What? Again?
Yeah.
Tony hired some high school idiot
that only lasted an hour, so...
See now,
if I didn't know you like I do,
I'd think something shady was going on.
Please. As if.
Leaving early, coming home late.
All right.
Where'd you meet him?
He taller than me?
He's a little taller.
(CHUCKLES)
Oh.
And Harry's teacher wants to talk about
his listening skills.
Okay, well, he's got none of those,
so that should go pretty quick.
Well, he gets it from you.
I'm sorry. Did you say something?
(LAUGHS)
Oh.
You're funny.
You should take that on the road.
Hey, look.
Don't burn yourself out, okay?
We need you in one piece around here.
Okay.
Bye, babe.
Bye.
BETH: Here's your cut.
This is nothing.
It's more than we had last month.
Sara's on home dialysis now.
Plus the new medicine.
This is barely gonna make a dent.
Ugh, you suck.
My custody lawyer billed me
for messaging her questions on Facebook.
Why would you think you
wouldn't get billed for that?
Because we're friends on Facebook.
I've never worked so hard for so little.
And I worked a service job.
(SIGHS)
I say we get out.
Are you serious?
We're risking everything,
including our lives.
We barely see our families.
And for what?
For the money.
It'd be one thing if
we were making mad bank.
But this?
This isn't mad bank, you guys.
I say we cut our losses now,
before we get caught.
Or shot.
(SWING CREAKING)
Please stop that.
Guys, this place is so familiar.
I'm having, like, deja vu.
(CREAKING)
Oh, please stop.
Okay.
(SIGHS)
Just chill.
It's gonna be fine.
(SCOFFS)
How do you figure, Ruby?
We tell them the job wasn't for us
and that we're moving on.
ANNIE: Right. Yeah.
I'm sure he'll be totally cool with that.
We didn't sign a contract.
Dude, we've been laundering fake money
for a street gang.
So?
So,
it's not a college internship.
We can't be like,
"Thanks, bye.
I learned so much."
There is no getting out.
RIO: Out of what?
RUBY: We've, um...
We've been thinking...
(CLEARS THROAT)
Just about,
you know, your whole operation
and our small role in it.
And we've learned so much.
But it's not working for us.
How so?
We need more.
(SOFTLY) What?
BETH: We've been clearing about, what,
a hundred grand every few weeks for you?
We're gonna need
five times that amount
to turn a profit
and make it worth our time.
You wanna clean 500 Gs?
We can do it.
(GASPING)
Can we?
You don't get more time.
That's not a problem.
(VOICE BREAKING)
Isn't it?
Go big or go home, right?
Brought that mama van with you?
Load 'em up.
"Go big or go home"?
I don't know. It's something
Kenny's coach always says.
Yeah.
When he says it, he means home.
As in, your house,
not the big house.
Okay.
What were you thinking?
I was thinking about our future.
We didn't come all this way to just quit.
I robbed a grocery store.
I didn't do it for nothing.
God. When did you get so cool?
You guys, we can do this.
We just need some extra hands.
You wanna bring
other people into this now?
We've got a system that works.
If we could just do it on a bigger scale.
What if they get caught?
They won't.
We haven't.
This cash is that good.
So, what?
I just ask Harry's Spanish teacher
if she wants a side hustle?
I mean, she probably does.
Teachers make next to nothing.
We know tons of women
who could use extra cash.
This isn't Mary Kay.
You can't just serve
a bitch a mini muffin
and invite her to join you
in a life of crime.
What if they didn't know it was a crime?
(UPBEAT MUSIC PLAYING)
So, what's a secret shopper?
Well, stores hire companies
like the ones we work for
to send in people
to pretend to be shoppers.
That way they can tell
how good or bad the customer service is.
Mini muffin?
Yes.
So, you'll pay us to buy a bunch of stuff
and then return it?
They're mostly interested
in the customer experience.
So, every time you make a return,
you fill out a survey and you get paid.
It's that easy.
(CHUCKLES)
Crazy, right?
(CHUCKLES) So crazy.
How long does the survey have to be?
Oh, that's entirely up to you.
Do we get reimbursed for mileage?
Ooh. Good question.
ANNIE: I will definitely
bring that up with corporate.
(MOUTHING)
Well, I, um...
I have to ask my husband.
Yeah.
Oh. Henry will freak
if this takes me away from the kids.
WOMAN 1: I can't get someone
to watch my kids all day.
I should talk to mine, too.
No, no. No, no.
It's called
"Secret shoppers."
Gotta stay secret.
And, you guys,
this isn't about your husband
or your kids.
I mean...
I get it.
You feel like you've gotta put everyone
in front of you, right?
But you don't.
We are giving you an opportunity
to make your own money,
to do something just for yourself.
This is about being
a strong, independent woman.
Well, I'm not a woman.
I think you guys are getting
a little caught up in the details.
ANNIE: Yeah.
BETH: I don't have all the answers,
but I will tell you this.
Ever since I started this,
my perspective has changed entirely.
Ain't that the truth.
You guys, we're in this together.
I mean, when women support other women,
incredible things happen.
Plus, the shopper of the year
gets a new Corvette!
What?
A Corvette?
(CHUCKLES)
Why didn't you say that before?
(ALL CHATTERING EXCITEDLY)
WOMAN 2:
I'm down for that.
Oh, they'll never remember.
I'm gonna top all y'all.
WOMAN 3: Whatever.
(WOMEN LAUGHING)
DEAN: It's, uh, Agent Turner, right?
Jimmy.
You, uh...
You in the market?
'Cause we've got some sweet deals.
What are you driving now?
An unmarked government-issued sedan.
(CHUCKLES) Well, that's...
That's no fun.
Go ahead. Take a ride.
The Bureau doesn't like flashy.
Oh, I'm pretty sure that J. Edgar Hoover
used to rock a feather boa.
All right, well...
(CAR DOOR CLOSES)
So, what can I help you with?
Well, I'm hoping we could help each other.
Cops found that SUV you reported stolen.
They did? Where?
Bottom of Cedar Lake.
Oh, was there an accident?
No.
(CHUCKLES)
Who steals a car to sink it?
I have no idea.
You know who might, though?
Who?
Your wife.
Maybe we should step into your office,
Mr. Boland.
BETH: That better not be
Halloween candy, mister.
Well, uh, my science teacher says
that chocolate's good for the heart.
Ready, Mama.
BETH: What's with you and pants?
Are you just morally opposed to pants?
Are you on a pants strike?
EMMA: No pants!
KENNY: Where are my shin guards?
BETH: Probably in Dad's car.
KENNY: Dad?
Dean.
Huh?
Shin guards.
Oh, uh...
I'll look.
EMMA:
Leave me alone.
You feeling okay?
What's on tap for you today?
Carpool, cleaners, grocery store.
The usual.
Is that it?
It's tuna fish.
Keep it in the fridge.
Fridge. Yeah.
BETH: All right, everyone, let's go.
Let's go.
Emma.
Hey, hey, hey.
Knock it off.
Thank you.
Have a fine and frugal day.
Ma'am, I'm ready if you are.
They never carry the mints I like.
Do I Know you?
Uh, no. No, I'm not...
BOOMER: Nana?
What are you doing here?
I would've brought the ham salad to you.
It is you!
(CHUCKLES NERVOUSLY)
Oh, my God. It is!
I didn't know you worked with my Leslie.
She works for Social Services, too.
Well, it's really more of a volunteer
kind of a thing, you know, but...
Well, she and all her friends
cleaned my whole apartment.
Yeah.
I bet they did.
She's a very sweet girl, Leslie.
Oh, yeah.
Big heart, this one.
You know, it's funny you didn't mention
Fine And Frugal when you came over.
Oh, uh...
BOOMER:
That is funny, Annie.
Now why do you think that is?
Hmm. Uh, I don't know, Leslie.
Maybe it's just because
your nana and I had
so much to talk about.
(BOTH CHUCKLE)
For example,
how's your fiancee, Jessica Alba?
Oh, I showed her that beautiful picture.
Fine, yeah. No, things are fine.
Yeah? Now, she's
in LA, though, right? Ugh.
Well, it must be really tough.
You know, the distance.
We make it work.
Glad to hear it.
You know, you left so abruptly that night,
I was hoping you'd come back again.
Oh, I wanted to, Marion. Really.
I just... I've been
so busy lately. You know?
Yeah, Annie has a whole life
outside of this store, Nana.
You would be real shocked.
It was just nice to have someone
to talk to.
BOOMER: I mean, you can talk to me, Nana.
Oh, that's different, Leslie.
A woman needs the companionship
of other women.
What about your friends, Marion?
They're dead.
TYLER: Yo, Annie.
Uh, yeah.
You got a sec?
Yeah, what up?
I bought all the merchandise
and filled out all the surveys,
just like you guys said.
Okay.
And it was super chill
and they didn't even know I was
a secret shopper,
just like you guys said.
Okay, great.
And then I went
to return it all, you know,
just like you guys said.
And what happened?
Some of the stuff was stolen from my car.
But your windows aren't broken.
The locks are, though.
Yeah.
Well, how much did they take, Tyler?
Um, well...
a lot.
Well, how much is a lot?
Pretty much all of it.
We gave you $20,000.
Yeah.
You guys could just call corporate,
right?
I! mean, this stuff
must have happened to them before.
You know? They're probably insured for it.
You know? Man, I generally think
the best in people.
He lost all of it?
Oh, yeah.
All gone.
So...
This is for you.
Remember her?
RUBY: Uh, I'm sorry.
What's this?
And this is...
BETH: What are you doing?
...for you.
Now, we're gonna need a Sharpie.
No. Uh-uh.
Not happening.
Because we can't
have any more of these
pesky orange tippies poking through.
We are not robbing another store.
Or any more little old ladies.
Well, I actually agree with that.
Marion came into the store earlier,
and it was like Driving Miss Daisy,
only sadder.
Okay, then.
So I figured
we could rip off a check-cashing place,
because...
We're not robbing anything!
Fine. We'll just stiff the gang.
Hey. Do you guys know what, uh, happens
when they need to dump your body
in an oil drum?
They soak you in lye
and they make you into soup.
And then the cops can't tell
if you used to be a human or a large dog.
That's really not necessary.
Well, actually, it is,
'cause oil drums are real small.
Just waiting on suggestions over here.
I have an idea.
Oh, do you?
I do.
Love to hear it.
We pay the gang back in full.
And how do we replace the 20 grand?
We stiff our secret shoppers instead.
We can't do that.
At least we don't end up in an oil drum.
No, just prison when they report us
for fraud.
Yeah, and it wouldn't be enough.
We would have to dip into our profits
to cover it.
And that would basically leave us
back where we started.
!am not going back there.
Me either.
So... (VOCALIZING)
Stop it.
We don't need that.
Then how are we supposed to get
the money back?
We don't need the money.
We just need the merchandise.
(UPBEAT MUSIC PLAYING)
(KNOCK ON WINDOW)
RUBY: Oh, my God.
My name is Randy.
I'm raising money
for our school trip to...
No, thanks. Go away.
It's an opportunity for my class
to visit our nation's capital.
And it's only $2
for a chocolate bar.
Okay, whatever. Give me one.
Awesome. Okay.
It's three for five and six for ten.
That's a way better deal.
Okay. Fine. Give me six.
Wow. Um, okay.
What flavors do you want?
I have caramel, plain...
Oh, my God. I literally
do not care, Randy.
Okay, um... uh...
You gave me nougat?
(UPBEAT MUSIC CONTINUES)
Thank you.
(ALARM BEEPING)
Oh. I'm sorry.
Is that me?
I'm gonna have to see your receipt.
Yeah, okay.
Oh, you know what?
I completely forgot
that I tried that on.
Uh, here.
Let's go.
We got returns to make.
DEAN: How was the meeting?
(COIN CLATTERS)
Mrs. Rubin's on a tear
about trans fats in the cafeteria again.
That woman needs a hobby.
(CHUCKLES)
I Know.
I'm gonna take a shower.
Maybe after,
you can tell me why you stole a car
and ditched it in a lake.
You wanna sit down?
No.
The FBI guy, he came back. (SCOFFS)
What did you tell him?
Uh, I told him that I cheated on my wife,
and (CLEARS THROAT)
she freaked out.
So she took my car
on a joyride and trashed it
after she went on
a mini-Canadian shopping spree.
Did he buy it?
Yeah.
He did.
(SIGHS) Good.
I don't.
So...
What the hell were you doing?
It's hard to explain.
How about you try?
I... I...
Were you smuggling drugs?
I didn't know what it was.
How do you not know?
You stole a car and went over the border
with something illegal inside of it.
You... you could go to prison for that.
We have kids.
We needed the money and we needed it fast,
and I didn't know how else to get it!
Well, uh, maybe you get a job.
It was a job!
I meant, like, Panera or something.
Don't yell at me.
(SCOFFS) Sit down!
(YELLING) Sit down!
Was it that bounce-house guy?
I mean, did he put you up to this?
What?
You know, those guys, they just...
They prey on good, innocent people.
They just rope 'em in.
I mean, is that what happened, or...
That's exactly what happened.
(SIGHS)
(INHALES)
I'm sorry I yelled at you.
But, look, everything's gonna be fine.
Okay.
Okay? I'm gonna take care of this.
Nothing bad is gonna happen to us.
Okay?
Okay.
(SIGHS) Just stay away from that guy.
Dean.
Yeah?
Thank you.
Hey, boo-boo.
How you doing?
Okay.
I brought Chinese.
Uncle Tony brought food.
What?
(INDISTINCT CHATTERING)
STAN: There you are.
Hey, Tony.
Hey.
I heard about Sara being in the hospital.
STAN: Yeah, he brought enough food
to feed a marching band.
TONY: Well, I feel terrible
about everything.
That's so sweet.
If I had known what was going on
with your family...
It's okay.
...I would've never let you go.
Place isn't the same without you.
I told him not to worry, that you've been
keeping yourself real busy.
RUBY: /was gonna fell you as soon as
I got another gig.
Ooh, surf and turf.
That's what I've been doing
the past few weeks.
Just, you know, looking for work
all day long.
God, he really went all out, didn't he?
I was SO embarrassed
that I blew a perfectly good gig,
that I couldn't tell you.
No fries?
I'm sorry, babe.
I really am.
Why they gotta be crinkle cut?
Would you stop with the food, Stan?
Ruby, what do you want me to say?
I don't know.
Anything.
All right. (SIGHS)
I don't believe a word
that just came out of your mouth.
How about that?
(CRIES SOFTLY)
Is it me, or are the Salisbury steaks
getting smaller?
You're just not a little boy anymore.
(CHUCKLES)
Nana?
Where do you keep your money?
Somewhere safe.
Well, you should think about a bank.
I mean, that's safer.
I don't trust banks.
(SCOFFS) Well, you know,
I don't like you keeping
a bunch of cash lying around.
You know, you live alone.
You got people coming in now.
Medicare or whatever.
Bring these
to work for Annie, will you?
Seriously?
Well, her little girl loves
oatmeal raisin she said.
Well, yeah. I like
oatmeal raisin. (SCOFFS)
She's a single mom.
Did you know that?
How she volunteers
on top of it is beyond me.
Yeah, well, believe me,
she's no saint.
That's not very nice.
Yeah, well, she's not very nice.
Okay?
She's a loser,
Nana. She is a loser and a liar,
and just a bad person.
Mildred had a magazine called Us Weekly.
Jessica was in it.
There was a picture of her
coming out of a gas station.
Apparently, she's such a big movie star
that...
that people pay to see her
coming out of a gas station.
Yeah, well...
You know, I'm...
I'm really proud of her.
They said she's married
to a man named Cash Warren,
and has adorable children,
Honor and Haven.
It's a, uh...
It's a blended
family situation.
She was never your fiancee, was she?
I just... I didn't want you
to worry about me.
Well, I do.
You've always had trouble meeting people,
and I always thought
it wasn't your fault.
It's not. (SCOFFS)
(SIGHS) Oh, I love you, Leslie.
I do.
But Annie's not the loser here.
(SIGHS)
(PEOPLE CHATTERING INDISTINCTLY)
(TELEPHONE RINGING IN DISTANCE)
Turner!
Hey, Jimmy.
Hey, what's going on with the case?
When are we gonna move
on these bitches, man?
(DOOR HANDLE RATTLES)
Turner. Jimmy.
Come on, buddy.
This thing's locked.
Is this soundproof?
Sir, step away from the glass.
It's cool. We actually work together.
Hey. Can you, uh...
Wait. Wait! Jimmy!
You need to leave.
We work together.
Now.
Twenty years of marriage,
Stan has never looked at me like that.
Oh, honey, I'm so sorry.
Like, ever.
At least he doesn't know everything.
Dean does.
What?
The FBI found the car, you guys.
When?
I don't know.
But Dean covered for us.
Deansie covered for us?
Well, then we're good.
He thinks I'm some naive idiot
that got taken advantage of, so...
Of course he does.
So what are you gonna do about it?
Let him think it.
RIO: How'd it go, ladies?
It's all there.
Half a million dollars.
Let me ask you something.
How do you not get caught?
School ain't in session right now.
BETH: Hey, come on.
We just cleaned half a million dollars
for you.
I flip my game.
What does that mean?
It means I flip my game.
She knows all those words individually,
but not, like, in a row.
Say we're talking herb.
Now, you could move
nickel bags all day long.
Nickels move fast, 'cause everybody knows
the nickel bag man, right?
That's why his dumb ass is
always getting popped.
Now, the smart ones,
they turn nickels into dimes.
Dimes gets you to pills.
And now you're moving up the chain.
Before anybody knows what's going on,
you're on the TVs and whatnot.
And while they all got their back turned,
I'm over here
with a bunch of suburban bitches
selling Monopoly money.
(ZIPPER CLOSING)
We'll see where that takes me.
Your cut.
Count it.
It's all there.
Trust me, 60 Gs.
We up your drop next time?
Say $750,000?
Why?
'Cause you delivered.
(POP SONG PLAYING)
(ANNIE WHISTLES)
Just call us the mailman.
Why?
'Cause we deliver.
He just said it.
Can someone explain to me
what "flipping a game" means?
I did not process a word of that.
(CHUCKLES)
Not a word.
And then I was too embarrassed
to ask again.
(CHUCKLES)
Well, you can't ask again.
No.
Oh, I used to get high in this park.
I have planned everything out.
RUBY: I am also planning.
ANNIE: On?
Two more of these.
Ooh.
Okay, well, mine is a business plan.
Ooh! Watches CNBC once.
Six months
and we're out.
Hmm.
By then, we will have enough money
for all of Sara's medication
and any extra medical fees.
We will have more than enough
for your custody lawyer.
And my bank accounts
will be in the black.
And...
we will have a honeypot.
What is the honeypot for?
We invest in something legit,
and that's our safety net.
So, no matter what happens,
we don't have to rob
a grocery store again.
(SIGHS)
Hey. You know what you just did there?
Uh, flipped our game?
Correct-a-mundo.
Yeah, you did.
(ALL LAUGHING)
Excuse me. Can we get
another round, please?
Yeah, can we?
Thank you very much.
Thank you.
Okay. Six months and out.
Cheers.
Cheersies.
Guys,
what am I gonna tell Stan?
(SIGHS)
RUBY: I did something.
It was stupid and risky.
All right.
So stupid and risky,
you would've had my head examined.
Which is why I couldn't tell you.
Well, that's not how
this is supposed to go, you and me.
I Know.
You know, we handle what we gotta handle.
So, here it is.
Are you ready?
I started a business.
Okay.
And...
I didn't wanna tell you
because I was afraid I'd fail.
I didn't fail.
I'm crushing it.
You made all this?
I did.
Legitimately?
Well, what's the business?
Secret shopping.
It's very lucrative.
Yeah, I... I see...
I see that.
How much is that?
Almost 20 grand.
And that's yours?
Well, it's ours.
Can I touch it?
Go ahead.
Whoa.
That's heavy.
That's nice.
You can smell it, too.
(INHALES AND EXHALES)
Smells good.
Smells fresh.
Yeah, it does.
Smells better than our debt.
(CHUCKLES) Way better.
Do you know what we can do with this?
Everything.
No, no, no.
Ring, ring, ring.
Hello?
Uh, do you know what we can do with this?
Everything.
(LAUGHS)
Come here.
What?
(SIGHS) Oh, my God.
(CHUCKLES)
(SNIFFS) I'm sorry.
I just can't...
(SNIFFS) I can't stop smelling it.
(SNIFFS)
Can't stop, won't stop.
It's So good.
(SNIFFS)
(DOORBELL RINGS)
Hi!
Oh, come on in.
Come on in.
I didn't know
when you were coming back,
so I started a little list of chores.
(SIGHS)
What's wrong?
Um...
Look, Marion, I...
(SIGHS) I'm not with Social Services.
Are you with Medicare?
No, um...
Medicaid?
No. Marion...
Meals on Wheels?
Uh, I'm...
I'm not with anything helpful.
The truth is,
we came here to rob you,
'cause we thought you'd be an easy target.
(SIGHS) Um...
So I just wanted to
return what we stole.
I, um...
I couldn't find the little drummer boy,
so I got you the accordion player
instead.
(CHUCKLES)
Marion, I'm...
I'm really, really sorry.
Are you rushing off to your daughter?
Uh, no, she's...
She's out of town with her dad.
Because Gloria had a baby.
(CHUCKLES)
I was gonna toast her
with some of Raymond's nice bourbon.
I'm sorry. Just to be
totally clear, you...
you understand that I stole
from you, right?
Did you have a good reason?
I hate to drink alone.
(CHUCKLES)
So, what is this for Gloria? Four? Five?
Six!
Six?
(BOTH LAUGH)
You're killing me, Gloria!
BOOMER: Darren.
Got a minute?
I swear I haven't been double-bagging
since you said not to.
Oh, good job.
That... That's good.
Uh, hey, what if I told you
I was looking to, uh, party?
Party?
Oh, party supplies.
Aisle nine.
Yeah, the thing is,
uh, I'm a little more
interested in party favors.
Oh, they're also on aisle nine.
No.
Different kind of favor,
if you Know what I mean.
I... I don't, Mr. Petersen.
(CHUCKLES)
Drugs, Darren.
Oh, cold and flu's aisle eight.
Listen. I got your number, son.
All right?
Nobody who bags groceries
drives a Range Rover.
So unless you want me
all over your business
in the parking lot,
I suggest you hook a fella up.
I got cola, Tina, molly, oxy, K, addys,
and fat bags of herb.
I'll take it.
What do you...
What do you mean?
I'll take all of it.
Hey.
(CROWD CHEERING ON TV)
Unbelievable.
My keys didn't work in the front door.
I had all the locks changed.
Hey, did you get milk?
We're out.
Why'd you do that?
I want you to feel safe in your own home.
Oh, and by the way, Fred from work,
he's gonna close for me from now on.
Didn't he just have a baby?
Twins. They're super cute.
I just don't like the idea
of you being home alone.
You don't have to come home early.
I just wish we could turn
that bounce-house guy in.
He's not a bounce-house guy.
I know. But still...
And you can't turn him in.
Look. He's not gonna mess
with you anymore, all right?
Not on my watch.
(CHUCKLES)
What's so funny?
(CHUCKLES) I mean, who says that?
"Not on my watch, young lady."
(LAUGHS)
Dangerous people took advantage of you.
Yeah. Yeah, they took advantage of me.
Hey, I...
I don't see anything funny
about any of this.
How did they take advantage of me, Dean?
Am I so naive and innocent?
I must be.
I... I never said that.
I! must be dumb, too.
Just a little lamb to the slaughter?
I didn't say that.
You didn't have to.
How little you must think of me.
They didn't take advantage of me.
It was a choice.
I wanted to.
And you have no idea
what I have done,
or even who I am.
And that little wifey of yours
who lived to make you dinner
has left the building,
and she is not coming back.
I mean, I'm sitting here
watching... (GRUNTS)
What is this?
Where did...
Where did this come from?
Yeah, I did forget the milk.
Beth, what the hell is going on?
And let Fred go back to his babies.
I'm not afraid of the dark.
(POP MUSIC PLAYING)