RUBY: Previously on Good Girls...
I handled the mortgage.
But how did you do that?
This is a robbery.
No, I'm turning you in.
ANNIE: Boomer, please.
No, please. No!
(GLASS BREAKING)
(MUFFLED SCREAMING)
You can't leave me here forever.
There he is.
She's gonna cut his penis off.
(CAMERA CLICKS)
What are you doing?
Texting a picture
of your penis to my daughter.
No.
If you go to the cops, so will I.
Oh, hell, no.
I mean, it was either
you or my 11-year-old, you know?
Hostage peen.
(LAUGHS)
It'll put the vroom vroom vroom
back in your engine.
Do you think he's sleeping around?
Your child bride wears
very expensive underwear.
I was stupid.
Nancy and I are suing you for custody.
Eculizumab.
It improves renal function.
It's also 10 grand a month out of pocket.
You're short.
You're an idiot.
We're normal people.
How many jujubes did Jen take from Sam?
Thirty-six.
Kenny!
Go inside!
Your friend's helping me.
Maybe there's something
you could help me out with.
What's that?
You ladies got passports?
He wants us to pick something up
for him in Canada.
What?
I thought we were done with this.
Says it's better if we don't know.
Mmm.
Mmm-hmm.
I mean, come on.
Guys, seriously...
Just say it!
Drugs. Up our asses!
What?
Oh, yeah.
Otherwise you got to swallow the baggie,
which, frankly, seems
even more uncomfortable,
you know. I'd almost rather...
No, uh-uh.
That's not gonna happen.
Oh! You'd rather just
declare a kilo at customs?
I don't want to smuggle drugs at all.
Don't say kilo.
Okay. When are we supposed to do this?
Friday.
ANNIE:
Well, I can't Friday.
I have a home visit for my custody case.
So you're gonna tell the man
with the crying skull tattoo
that Friday doesn't work for you?
Fine, but we have to
be back in time for me to clean up
and get all the drugs out of my cavities.
He didn't say it was drugs, you guys.
It could be something else, okay?
Like what?
Guns?
How is that better?
Can't fit up your ass.
EMMA: Mama?
I had a nightmare.
Same.
I'm sorry, Bubba.
I'll come rub your back, okay?
Mmm-hmm.
You guys, he said if we do this,
he'll forget about the money.
And we're done.
It's over.
What if we don't?
That didn't seem like an option.
Come on, sweetie.
Let's go to bed.
You ever seen Locked Up Abroad?
No.
Good.
(SLURPS)
(WHISPERING) Sadie.
Sadie, Sadie, Sadie,
Sadie, Sadie, Sadie...
Kids need sleep to grow.
Ooh, wah.
Hey, hey, hey.
Hey, hey.
So, what do you think
they're gonna ask on
this home visit thing?
(SOFTLY) I don't know.
No, but like, what do they want to know?
Just, like, if you're a good mom.
(IN IRISH ACCENT)
So I shouldn't speak to them
in my wee little leprechaun voice, then?
Do you think that
I'd embarrass my favorite child?
(CHUCKLES) Yeah.
(INNORMAL VOICE)
Yeah, okay.
(SIGHS)
Just know your dad and Nancy are gonna be,
like, wearing slacks.
His and hers Dockers.
(GIGGLING)
Ew. Totally.
(SIGHS)
Nancy's planning a menu.
Wait, they're serving food?
Scones, like at tea or something.
Since when are they 80 and British?
(EXHALES)
Hey, don't worry.
I'm gonna totally slay this thing.
You better.
I like it here.
(KISSES)
Hi... Hey. What do I owe this pleasure?
$4,000, we owe.
The mortgage.
We're going to default again this month.
Want to tell me how you paid
for it last month?
No, thank you.
So I'll pool everything together,
open all new accounts
in my name, and I'll start fresh.
That's a great idea.
Thank you.
I mean, it would be if it was possible.
I have good credit.
Yeah. I mean, you haven't had a job
since high school in the DQ.
So...
Because I've been raising four children.
But trust me, if I was the guy
handing out credit, I...
I mean, I would give you
all the credit in the world.
Look, I'm...
I'm working on it.
Like, our sales are up,
and I feel really good.
If you just, you know,
if you give me some time.
You look so skinny.
I was.
You look happy.
Well...
I gave it 20 years.
RUBY: That bad, huh?
You have no idea.
I also think we should cross the border
at Windsor.
Their border patrol's super nice there.
How do you know?
Let's just say I made a lot of field trips
to Canada in high school.
Why am I not surprised?
Anybody else?
(SIGHS)
No, I'm cutting back.
Now is not the time.
So we have the passports
and we have directions.
Now, we just need a car.
I would say we could take mine,
but it got the boot.
How many tickets?
Six is apparently the cutoff.
Now we know.
Well, Stan needs ours for the kids.
I don't want a bunch of heroin in my car.
I drive my kids in that car.
Good point.
Could be residue.
We should just borrow a Car.
Or we could just steal one.
Or we could borrow it
and bring it back, Bonnie.
From who?
(IMITATING LADY FROM COMMERCIAL)
We've got Chevys.
We've got Fords.
We've got Chryslers, too.
No.
So come on down to Boland
Motors and we'll put the...
No, no, no...
BOTH: Vroom vroom vroom
back in your engine.
I said no.
(BEEPS)
Which one should we take?
(SINGSONG) Oh, Ken doll!
Barbie's home.
Yeah, that won't attract
any attention at all.
We got to keep it low-key.
Ugh, fine.
If we were good people,
we'd take a hybrid.
RUBY: Oh, but we're not.
BETH: Ooh, responsive headlights.
Dork.
No, this is so helpful at night.
Hey, check it out, you guys.
Making it rain.
(CAR ALARMS BEEPING)
ANNIE: I hit the panic button.
BETH: Well, stop hitting panic!
Turn them off!
Push the same button!
You push the buttons, then!
(OVERLAPPING SHOUTING)
(ALARMS CONTINUE BEEPING)
(SONG CONTINUES IN BACKGROUND)
(ALARMS WAILING)
Here are your coupons.
Have a fine and frugal morning.
Saw you put in for a personal day.
Hey, your bites are almost gone.
We're doing inventory tomorrow.
I was hoping they'd get infected
and eat your face off.
So you can't have the day off.
Unless...
Unless what?
Tell me what you're doing tomorrow.
It's personal.
That's why it's called a personal day.
Are you gonna hit a bank next?
I mean, what, you think
you're freaking Ocean's 11?
Well, guess what?
The all-girl version
of that movie is gonna suck.
Yeah, because we all Know girls
aren't funny.
WOMAN: Oh! Mr. Petersen!
We haven't seen you around much.
Oh, I took a bit of a camping trip.
We love camping.
Oh. Who doesn't?
Hey, you should show them
the pictures from your trip.
I didn't take any.
Oh. I'm sure you did.
Actually, my hands were pretty tied up.
ANNIE: Huh.
What about that one
that you sent to my daughter?
WOMAN: I'd love to see it.
(CHUCKLES)
I don't want to hold up the line.
Okay. Come on through.
Hey, thanks again
for tomorrow, by the way.
Really appreciate it.
MAN: Because I Know God has a plan for me.
(ORGAN PLAYING)
And if I'm being honest...
Look alive, baby.
I'm up.
...probably does not involve tequila.
PASTOR: Amen. Amen.
(SCATTERED APPLAUSE)
PASTOR: Bless you, brother.
God is good...
ALL: All the time.
Truly, God is good.
Is there anyone else
who wants to testify today?
Anybody at all?
Right here. I would.
Brother Stan.
(CLEARS THROAT)
Hi, everybody.
Uh...
I Know you all been praying
for our little girl, Sara.
It's been a long, hard road,
and, um, we just want to say thank you.
Because we needed a miracle
and, uh... And we got one.
Our baby girl's doing
much better now and that's
'cause the money...
The money that we needed
to help her just, um...
(CHUCKLES)
You all know I'm skeptical now.
You know, I'm skeptical,
but that cash just showed up.
It just appeared.
All right.
Other people want to talk.
And, um, we've been
coming here for a long time,
so I don't know
if the person who did this for us is here
today in this congregation.
But I hope someday I'll get the chance
to meet you
to say thank you
for saving my family.
All right, don't hog the mic.
(ALL CHEERING)
The Lord is good!
MAN: Amen!
PASTOR: My, my, my, my.
WOMAN: It broke my heart.
I couldn't see your little girl
so sick like that.
Sheila, are you for real?
I... I don't want a bunch of attention.
(CHUCKLES NERVOUSLY)
STAN: Well, it's too late,
you angel. Come here.
No. (CHUCKLES)
Come here.
(SCATTERED APPLAUSE)
PASTOR: Praise God, praise God!
Amen.
Let the church say Amen.
Thank you.
You saved our baby.
PASTOR: Miracles do happen.
Let the church say Amen.
Amen.
The woman gave us 10 grand.
Oh, yeah?
What does she get for 20?
Show me how I was supposed to do it.
Show me!
No.
She wants a piece and you know it.
Oh, come on!
Yeah, since high school.
And she's so fake with that
"I don't want attention."
Bitch, please.
Look, are you hearing yourself right now?
And then you had to invite her over?
What am I supposed to cook?
Cook her spaghetti!
What? What is wrong with you
is what I'm asking.
Do not call me crazy.
Well, if the shoe fits.
Okay. I'm gonna make this woman dinner.
And when she comes over here,
if she wants another hug,
I'm gonna give her one of those, too.
Okay, Ruby?
She saved our kid's life.
Stan...
We couldn't.
Am I wrong?
Come on, Ruby.
No, you're not wrong.
You know, you need to have some fun on
your girls' trip, 'cause...
You really need to chill.
Don't hold the wheel like that.
How am I holding it?
Like you already have
the drugs up your butt.
AUTOMATED VOICE:
You're about to cross
the border into Canada.
Please have your passports
and all necessary documents ready.
Do they pull you over on the way in?
ANNIE: Well, if they do,
it's not like we have
anything in the car, do we?
I brought Stan's gun.
What?
Relax. It's in my purse
and it's not loaded.
ANNIE:
Why would you do that?
RUBY:
I thought it was smart
to bring protection.
We're committing a crime
in a foreign country.
ANNIE: It's Canada.
We're not meeting
El Chapo in Guatemala here.
El Chapo's actually Mexico.
(SCOFFS) Jesus.
Whatever.
What are we doing, you guys'
This is So crazy.
Yeah, it is.
What if we get caught?
I mean, it's not like
we have a choice, right?
There's always a choice.
ANNIE: And then what?
What happens when he shows up again?
In front of our kids?
Dude, it's never gonna end.
Unless we end it.
Tell me to turn around.
BETH: Please say it.
Please. Please, someone Say it.
(CAR HORN HONKS)
(INDISTINCT CHATTER OVER PATROL RADIO)
(CAR HORN HONKS INSISTENTLY)
Passports, please.
Here you go. Have a nice day.
Still think it's drugs?
Worse. Scrapbooking.
He said to go around the back.
(SINGING)
I went to the doctor
I went to the mountains
I looked to the children
I walked through the valleys
(MUMBLING)
There's more than one answer
to these questions
And it...
(TURNS RADIO OFF)
Wow.
What's your problem?
We're not at Lilith Fair right now.
Mmm, but wouldn't you rather be?
Mmm... Tough call.
Damn, someone's in a mood.
(SIGHS DEEPLY)
Going through something with Stan.
What, he rub your feet too much?
Been hugging on you too hard?
Some woman at church
took credit for the money.
Wait. For Sara?
What? Who?
Some thirsty skank who's been after Stan
for years.
(CLICKS TONGUE) Damn.
I mean, it's Stan.
It's not like she actually
has any kind of in.
Yeah.
But it's the fact she has the nerve
to think she does,
and that's enough to bug.
I feel you.
(INDISTINCT CONVERSATION)
All right.
This doesn't look good.
(EXHALES)
(CAR DOOR OPENS)
So? What happened?
He doesn't have it.
What do you mean he doesn't have it?
He doesn't have the package for us.
He doesn't have it
or he won't give it to you?
Why wouldn't he give it to me?
(SCOFFS) Maybe he wants
to keep it for himself.
You think?
(SCOFFS) Canadians.
What's his name?
Mike.
Wait. What are you doing?
Handling it.
BETH:
He really seemed like he didn't have...
Well, what does she think she's gonna do?
(INDISTINCT CHATTER)
Hey, beautiful day, en?
MIKE: Mmm.
ANNIE: Big Mike?
Can I call you Big Mike?
No.
Look, I already told your friend. I don't
have what you want...
No, I know, she's so lame.
She's not the one
to talk to about this, okay?
I Know you see us, you think, "Hey."
You think we're some
low-hanging fruit, right?
Little... Little payday.
A side hustle for ya?
Yeah. What are you gonna do about it?
(SIGHS)
Hey, Mike. Just...
Just humor me, okay?
For a sec here'?
Do you have sisters?
Two.
Okay. All right.
Well, what do they do?
(CHUCKLES)
One's a receptionist, one's a teacher.
Okay, well, they sound like
really nice, normal people.
So just, for a second,
just picture them in our position, okay?
They are terrified.
They're in way over their heads,
and they just need somebody
to give them a break.
Okay? Otherwise they are totally screwed.
Don't you want to give
your sisters a break, Mike?
(PATS MIKE'S ARM)
You don't want to screw your sisters.
I don't get it.
I thought we were connecting.
I mean, I...
I was SO nice.
All right, well, nice isn't gonna cut it.
(BOTH EXCLAIMING)
Are you serious?
Don't point that at me.
Relax.
I'm just gonna scare him a little.
Damn, gangster.
Who are you?
I'll be right back.
So, Mike, I...
(GUNSHOT)
(BOTH SCREAM)
(ALL SCREAMING)
(MIKE GROANING)
(RUBY SCREAMING)
(ALL CLAMORING)
Oh, my God!
You shot him!
I didn't mean to.
I didn't mean to!
I thought you said it wasn't loaded!
There must have been one in the chamber.
You shot me in the foot!
Oh, Big Mike!
What can I do?
Stay away from me.
Just stay away from me.
Take what you came for
and get out of here.
The box is back that way.
Okay, come on.
(MIKE SCREAMING IN PAIN)
Forgive me, Lord Jesus.
Have mercy on me.
I did not mean to shoot that man.
I pray to thee for forgiveness for
all my past transgressions.
It just needs a Band-Aid.
It was just a graze.
In the foot.
He's being a baby.
He's gonna live.
He may not walk again but...
He's about to get
the best free care socialized medicine
can buy.
We should all be so lucky.
I shot a man.
(INDISTINCT YELLING)
Passports.
Quick trip?
Yeah, just a little shopping.
Have all the receipts for your purchases?
That should be everything.
(KEYBOARD CLACKING)
Everything looks in order.
Pull on over to Lane 3.
Is that the express lane?
Search and seizure.
Just need to verify
your purchases, and you're good to go.
(DOG BARKING)
(INDISTINCT CHATTER OVER PATROL RADIO)
Hi, little baby.
Miss. Please do not engage the dog.
No, no, no, no.
Hey, Brian!
Box cutter.
RUBY: Jesus.
(ALL BREATHING HEAVILY)
MAN: What's that?
ANNIE: Oh, Jesus.
Oh, Jesus, Jesus.
MAN: Give me.
Right there.
Be cool.
(INDISTINCT CHATTER OVER POLICE RADIO)
What did they say?
(QUIETLY) I don't know.
(INDISTINCT CHATTER OVER PATROL RADIO)
(SHUDDERS)
Have a Safe trip home.
Thank you for your patience.
That dog would have smelled drugs, right?
Yeah.
What is it?
Get in there.
Come on.
Is there something inside?
I don't see anything.
No, I don't think so.
ANNIE: Guys...
RUBY: It's got to be inside then.
It's wrapping paper.
It's just wrapping paper.
What?
(ENGINE SHUTS OFF)
This is it?
Are we supposed to knock or something?
(SOFTLY) Okay. Okay.
(INDISTINCT CHATTER)
Holy mother!
RIO: All right, ladies.
This is what's gonna happen.
Hang on.
Tell them we're at capacity, okay?
They don't want to hear that.
I don't care if that's what
they wanna hear or not.
It's gonna be happening.
Look at this place...
Excuse me.
We're moving double what we did...
Hi.
...six months ago and we're good.
Excuse me.
I'm tired of dealing with him.
I don't want to deal with him anymore.
No, no...
I just need to know we're good.
If not, we renegotiate.
Okay? Start at 40 crates,
go up only as needed.
MAN: Forty?
RIO: Yeah.
I need you to make a tally
every 100,000...
No one's gonna show up at my house.
No guys, no guns.
I could find 10 different guys
to do what they do.
MAN: I'll get on top of it.
All right.
No, guys, in the back.
Let's keep it going.
Let's keep going.
Yep, yep, yep.
It's all good.
Just make sure you keep an eye
on your stacks.
It's all gotta be tight, tight, tight.
I want 100s here, 50s here, okay?
Separate them.
I don't want what happened
last time, okay?
No, I'm going to need to hear you Say it.
We're good.
(CLEARS THROAT)
WAITRESS: Can / get you anything else?
Oh, yeah. We're going to take
another round of these
pineapple margaritas, please.
Extra strong this time.
And then we also want one of those
fried onion things that has,
like, the arms that stick out.
You know those?
Nachos!
BETH: Yes, Nachos and, um...
The poppers, jalapeho poppers.
Two orders of those, please.
She's a lightweight.
Are we celebrating today, ladies?
Oh-ho!
I would certainly say so.
Yeah.
WAITRESS:
What's the special occasion?
Oh, we just smuggled
a bunch of counterfeit money
over the Canadian border
and escaped a violent street gang.
And no drugs in our butts.
No drugs in our butts!
Yay for no drugs in our butts.
(ALL LAUGHING)
So, pretty special, huh?
I'll put that right in.
ANNIE: (IN SQUEAKY VOICE)
Thank you.
She hates us.
No, I think she loves us.
Oh, my God.
How much money do you think that was?
It was one bajillion dollars, actually.
I've never seen that much cash in my life.
I mean, fake money, but yeah.
Well, I mean, it's real to somebody.
Yeah, but it's no longer our problem.
Phew.
So here's to going back to normal life.
Yes, I'chaim to that!
(RUBY CHUCKLES)
Yeah.
To normal life.
ANNIE: To normal life.
(ALL SLURPING)
You okay?
Yeah.
I think I'm gonna, um,
call the kids, though.
Oh, boy. Reminds me, I...
We should probably
get the check with the food
just 'cause, like, you know, to be safe.
Oh, we have time.
You'll get home.
I Know. it's just...
I, like, really need this
to go well, you know?
Like, it has to.
It's gonna go great.
You are a good mom.
Just chill.
Yeah, you're right. Thanks.
(GASPS)
I shot a man.
How are the kids?
DEAN: Good. Great.
When are you coming back?
I got a little bit of a situation here.
Yeah. What's going on?
Well, um...
It's the craziest thing.
We got hit.
I mean, I don't know how many cars,
but we have a lot of
police officers everywhere.
We'll come right now.
(CELL PHONE CLICKS OFF)
You guys, they know about the car.
Check, please.
We dump it on the side of the road.
Let the cops do their job.
Yeah. I mean, they already know
it's stolen.
No one suspects a thing.
Oh, hey, there's that
empty parking lot off I-94.
You know, by the Chrysler plant?
Yeah, that's perfect.
(ENGINE STARTS)
(CAR CHIMES)
Hold up.
You synced your phone?
So? I mean, I! wanted my music
for the road trip.
So it has your name
and all of your contacts
In a car that was reported stolen.
Okay, so we just unsync it.
How do I do that?
You can't.
Of course you can.
Dean borrowed my minivan
like, once, and it still asks me
if I want to connect
to his pocket rocket.
(DINGS)
Look, there. It's wiped.
Go ahead, restart the car.
Go ahead.
(CHIMES)
Hmm.
Yeah. Hmm.
Okay. You know, I'm thinking
we may just have to
reboot the whole thing.
What are you...
What are you talking about?
Like, the actual
hard drive of the actual car?
What are you even...
I don't know. I just...
I'm just saying words
that I've heard before.
What now?
(BREATHING HEAVILY)
Well, we have to torch it.
You want to blow up a car?
We're not doing that.
It has my digital fingerprints on it.
In the middle of rush hour traffic,
you want to blow up a car?
Do you have a better idea?
(CRICKETS CHIRPING)
You know, I just...
No.
I just wanted to...
Nuh-uh.
(BURBLING)
(CELL PHONE RINGING)
(EXHALES)
Hello?
WOMAN: (ECHOING IN CAR)
Hello, did I lose you?
Hello?
Hi, it's Clare Davis.
I'm here for your custody evaluation.
Jesus. Oh, my God.
Oh, my God. Okay.
Oh, it's almost 7:00.
Hi. Hi.
I'm so sorry.
I'm just running
a little bit late, and I'm
having a little bit of...
car troubles.
Well, how far away are you?
Not far!
(SIGHS)
SADIE: This is us at Six Flags.
My mom looks kind of weird
because she just barfed.
Yeah, I always do.
After Big Blue, right?
(CHUCKLES)
She still goes on it with me, anyway.
Hi. I'm... I'm Annie.
I am So, SO, SO Sorry.
Hi.
I'm so late.
My day just got crazy.
CLARE: Oh, how so?
She does a lot of charity work.
With kids.
Yeah, I... I love kids.
You Know, sick kids, and healthy kids.
I mean, who doesn't love healthy kids?
Wow. I can't stop saying kids. (CHUCKLES)
What kind of children do you work with?
Mentally disabled.
Cancer...
Kind.
Cancer, and they are
also mentally disabled.
Yeah, so it's really sad.
Wow. Yeah, well, you must be exhausted.
Um, I'll make this quick.
(MOUTHING)
I just have a few standard questions?
Shrimp?
(STAN SIGHS)
Kids just went down.
Okay, good.
Now we got business.
Ugh.
Can we please do this tomorrow?
Nope.
I'm sorry. I overreacted.
She can come over for dinner once, okay?
Nope.
What more do you want from me?
Your hands where I can see them.
(SCOFFS)
Seriously?
Oh, yeah.
(GROANS) Babe, I'm legit so tired.
Yeah, but you just came back
from a girls' trip.
Trust me, it was not relaxing.
Oh, you could just lie there.
(SCOFFS)
I was stupid.
I Know.
I love you.
Neatest homework packets.
What does that even mean, right?
Your daughter
is one impressive young lady.
Okay, I just need to take a quick peek
in your mom's bedroom,
and then I am out of here.
SADIE: No, wait.
ANNIE: Sweetie!
Oh, my God.
What happened?
Nothing.
Okay, that doesn't look like nothing.
It's fine.
How long has this been bleeding like this?
Since I made the shrimp.
Okay. How long did you
leave her alone today?
Let's get you a Band-Aid.
SADIE: We don't have any.
I already looked.
If... If this is a latchkey situation,
I'm gonna have to report.
It's totally not.
Honey, it's okay, Sadie.
She never leaves me alone.
Sadie.
Normally I... I don't,
but today I had to.
I had something really important come up.
And I... I just lost track of the time.
Because of the mentally disabled
cancer kids?
Sadie, I have to take you to a hospital.
I think you need stitches.
(WHISPERING)
Your car has the boot.
The boot.
Um...
I'm kind of in between vehicles
at the moment.
Any chance you could give us a lift?
DEAN: Okay. Come on.
Oh, my goodness.
(GRUNTS, SNIFFS)
Your feet smell like you're a high school
football player.
Hey. I love you so much.
Do you know that?
I love you all the way
to the moon and back.
Hey.
Good night, boo.
(KISSES)
Hey. Hey, do you mind
if I steal some cold cuts?
Getting pretty tired of eating the hotel
vending machine for dinner.
Sure.
Thanks.
So how many cars did they take?
Oh, don't know yet.
Still doing intake.
Which, of course, I have to pay for.
What about insurance?
Even with the claim, we take a hit.
Sorry.
(CHUCKLES)
It's not your fault.
This is a lifesaver.
Thank you.
(CLEARS THROAT) Hey.
So... (CLEARS THROAT)
I have been thinking
about our little sitch.
And if we were smart,
we would get back together.
Just hear me out.
Okay? So look, I would totally want to
divorce my ass, too.
But in the end, I wouldn't.
I would not.
Why not?
Why not? Because of
the ancient rule of two.
The ancient rule of two.
Yes. Two houses,
two mortgages, two cable bills.
Okay.
Two water sewage garbage fees.
I! mean, that...
That's craziness.
Wow, it is so romantic,
the way you're wooing me
right now. Honestly.
I'm not wooing you.
I am begging you not to leave me.
By way of sewage fees.
Well, I was gonna mention that you are
the love of my life
and that I wish everything could go back
to the way it was
because I had no damn idea
how good I had it until it was gone.
But then, I thought
that sounded kind of cheesy.
So I decided to focus on the cable bill.
Which kind of isn't really playing out
like I thought it was gonna.
Look, I know you hate me right now.
I don't hate you.
(DEAN SCOFFS)
Good. Because...
I just don't think
we have much of a choice.
There's always a choice.
(SINGING) / was born
by the devil I was left here to die
I was hell of a ransom
Under cold summer skies
I was told not to love him
I was told not to try
I was lonely the only
'Til he said he'd be mine
He will leave me for younger
He will leave me to cry
Cut the knife A little deeper
Count the days I survived
I will run to the river
I will reach for the well
Drown my sorrows From someone
In my hope I leave this hell
I was told not to love him
I was told not to try
I was lonely the only
'Til he said he'd be mine
He will leave me for younger
He will leave me to cry
Cut the knife a little deeper
Count the days I survived
Yeah, it's written in the water
Yeah, it's everywhere I go
Telling me that I should leave you
Like I did two times before
I'll be fine if I met you
When you still Have had your own
Give me one kiss For the road boy
I guess it's time I let you go
I will run to the river
I will not be what you'd like
Yeah, it's riches for the road boy
And it's time I let you go
(KEYS CLATTER)
(DOOR SLAMS SHUT)
I'm gonna call that fancy lawyer, see if
she could get us a do-over.
No shrimp this time.
I'm going to go big, like crab legs.
(OPENS BOTTLE)
(SNIFFS)
I'm sorry.
I suck.
(EXHALES)
Do you hear me?
(IN IRISH ACCENT)
I said I'm sorry.
I suck.
Where were you?
(INNORMAL VOICE)
I had to...
Do something really, really important.
What's more important than me?
There is literally nothing
in my entire life
that is more important to me than you.
I'm going to bed.
PASTOR: Tell me the Lord
is good now. He's good.
(CONGREGATION MURMURING)
He's good, I tell you.
The Lord is good.
Amen. Is there anyone else
who wants to testify
this morning? Anybody?
I would.
You would?
Sister Ruby.
MAN: All right.
Hello, everyone.
(CONGREGATION MURMURS)
I would just like to follow up
on the other day.
To be totally honest,
I am not feeling super good about it.
Sheila, you went above and beyond
for our little girl.
I don't even know how you put together
all that money.
You're still at the salon, right?
I've saved here and there over the years.
Well, listen...
(EXHALES) I realized that I reacted badly
because I have a hard time
taking charity.
Pride is a Sin, as we all Know.
CONGREGATION: Amen.
So I would just like to say something
that I should have
said before, which is thank you.
MAN: Hallelujah, sister.
Thank you for the money.
(SCATTERED APPLAUSE)
You're welcome.
And thank you for offering
to drive the kids home from school
when I'm at work, and thanks for offering
to babysit
so that we can have
a date night and offering
to do the laundry
and, oh, my God, the groceries.
At Whole Foods, no less.
Seriously?
Because this woman...
This woman only buys organic, people.
CONGREGATION: Amen.
I don't even know what to say.
RUBY:
There's nothing to say.
But thank you.
Got it.
I Know you do.
(ALL APPLAUDING)
PASTOR: Sometimes our prayer simply
needs to be, "Lord Jesus,
"help me to learn to be generous.
"To labor and to not seek reward."
Let us all simply say...
ALL: Amen.
(INDISTINCT CHATTER)
Well, look who's finally using the pen.
Yeah, it just felt a little crispy.
Oh.
Let me try.
No, I'm sure it's fine.
Let me see.
It's legit.
Good thing, because customer's long gone.
Next time, try checking
before they leave the store.
Good pro tip.
Oh, uh...
Do anything fun on your day off?
Just hung out with my kid.
Is that all?
Is there something you wanna ask me?
Just making conversation.
(SINGING) Mama just happened
to be singing
Songs of sunlight and my daddy
Oh my daddy
He'll be right...
Back
Even though I know I know
Everything
I thought I knew I saw you
Now I know I know nothing at all
(WHISPERING) Sadie.
Are you awake?
(SONG CONTINUES)
You know the tradition is Jordans
over a phone line, right?
I only had pumps.
Fair enough.
(SCOFFS)
So what did you want to talk to me about?
(SONG CONTINUES)