BETH: Previously on Good Girls...
We're gonna rob that store.
Yes!
Oh, dear God.
BETH: You get to help your little girl.
And you get to take care
of this custody thing.
And I get to save my family.
ANNIE: Ladies and gentlemen,
this is a robbery!
Get out of the way!
(GRUNTING)
We got more than the 30 grand.
Why does a grocery store
even have this kind of money on hand?
Because it's hella shady.
We didn't know you owned the store.
You just gonna pay me back is all.
And right quick, too.
With interest.
How many chicks have a tramp stamp
that says
"All You Need Is Love"?
The cops came around,
but I didn't tell them.
What do you want?
I just get so lonely.
Stop. My sister is here.
ANNIE: (GRUNTS) No!
That's how you like it,
right, tough girl?
Get off of her!
Whoa! Hey.
ANNIE: Boomer!
Boomer, please.
We can get you money.
Oh, no, I'm turning you in.
(ANNIE SCREAMS)
Ow! (GROANS)
(WOMEN GASP)
(BOTH SCREAM)
BETH: Is he...
ANNIE: No.
Are you sure?
(UPBEAT POP SONG PLAYING)
EMMA: Mama.
Mama.
Mom!
TV's broke.
"Broken."
Uh, and...
and no, it's not. Um...
When's Daddy coming home?
Just hit, uh,
"Input" twice.
And "Satellite"
and "Menu."
I need help with math.
(SIGHS) Why can't I help you?
Because you can't do math.
(DOOR OPENS)
DEAN: (IN ITALIAN ACCENT)
Papa!
He-a gotta the donuts!
(KIDS CHEERING, SHOUTING INDISTINCTLY)
(INNORMAL ACCENT)
Hi, guys! Hey, grab your bags.
Quick, quick, quick.
(IN ITALIAN ACCENT)
This train's a-leaving the station.
Fun dad.
(INNORMAL ACCENT)
Sad dad.
I miss my kids.
You've been gone two nights.
I miss you.
Kenny goes to sleepaway camp for longer.
Let's keep it together.
What about the lawn?
I can push a mower.
At least let me show you the remote.
Input, Satellite, Menu.
That's not even close.
I'll get there.
You've got a little, uh, on your face.
Kind of looks like blood.
Um, no, it's pizza.
Go. Don't leave the kids alone.
(ELECTRO POP SONG PLAYING)
(INDISTINCT CONVERSATION)
Hey. What's with the fuzz?
We got robbed, yo.
Get woke.
Yeah, but isn't that, like, old news?
They had guns, Annie.
I threw my neck out.
It must've been really scary.
In my job, the key is
to think of yourself as already dead.
So there's nothing left to be afraid of.
Wow.
Hey, have you seen Boomer?
Why?
The cops wanna talk to him again.
But he never came in for his shift.
No, I haven't seen him.
ANNIE: They're looking for him.
Do they know he's missing?
I don't know.
Or is it just about the robbery?
I don't know!
What did you tell them?
That you bashed his head in
with a whiskey bottle.
What do you think I told them?
So, I got $18 in tips.
I had to sell Stan's
favorite set of cufflinks for $250.
Sara is playing her first soccer game
In a T-shirt instead of the team uniform,
which gives us a grand total of $343,
which means we now owe
$59,657 to the violent street gang.
Please tell me you did better.
What's going on?
There's been a development.
What kind of development?
What am I looking at right now?
What am I even looking at right now?
(MUFFLED SCREAMING, GRUNTING)
(SCREAMS AMPLIFYING THROUGH SLIDE)
He knows about the store.
He was going to the cops.
Does he know about the gang, too?
Hell no.
That's way above his pay grade.
He's like the definition
of middle management.
Oh. And he also tried to rape me.
What?
That is absolutely true.
He's a dick and a rapist.
It was self-defense.
Self-defense?
Yes.
Definitely.
How is hog-tying a man,
climbing him 12 feet above the earth
and hiding him in a tree house
self-defense?
Okay, you know what?
You weren't there.
You're damn right I wasn't there.
We are feeding him.
Oh, good.
Well, you know.
What else were we supposed to do?
If he goes to the cops, we're screwed.
No. We're screwed because of the gang
that is going to kill us
if we don't get them their money.
Okay. She's right.
First things first.
Okay, well, I make $9 an hour.
So, just give me a couple decades.
Okay. Who do we know?
To rob?
To ask for money, Annie.
Somebody rich who would care
if I was dead? I mean...
(SCOFFS) I wish.
What?
Who?
No.
What do you mean, no?
I mean, no.
No, no, no.
Annie, this is life or death.
I choose death.
Give me death!
(ROCK SONG PLAYING ON RADIO)
Which one of these houses is your dad's?
How can you never remember?
Because all these cheesy-ass houses
look the same.
It's that one.
Oh.
Oh. Mmm. Hey, Nance.
(FAKES LAUGH)
Why's she always in scrubs?
Isn't she, like, a facialist or something?
Aesthetician.
(CLICKS TONGUE)
(SIGHS) All right, let's do this.
Um, would you mind taking your shoes off?
We're trying to keep it
clean-ish in here.
Hey, how do you feel about tacos?
We could do a little cheese,
a little pico de gallo.
Yeah, I feel good.
Oh, yay! Fun. Okay.
I am off to work.
Good luck saving lives.
Love you.
(ANNIE SIGHS)
What you making?
Pico de gallo?
Yeah.
Um...
I have sort of a favor to ask.
How much?
Just, like, 60...
All right.
...grand.
It'll be more like a loan this time.
I'll totally pay you back.
What is the matter with you?
It's not like you can't afford it.
Look at this place.
There's orchids everywhere.
You have an in-ground pool.
What do you need that much money for?
For a very good reason.
You, uh, hire a lawyer yet?
Do you actually think
I would ask you for money
to fight you for custody?
Are ya?
I wasn't.
But now that you're
accusing me of it, maybe I should.
(SCOFFS)
So, can I have the money?
No, you freak!
Why do you have to be such a dick?
Because you're insane.
I mean, you never think anything through.
This is exactly why Nancy and I
should have custody.
Because you are not stable.
Yeah, because who cares
about real love and connection
when you can make a child
a fresh pico de gallo?
Why do you keep saying that?
Thank you for making me
completely humiliate myself
for no reason.
These are cold.
They're not mine.
(GROANS)
What do we do now?
I have no idea.
What is it?
You okay?
Stay here.
I got a question for you.
The two, two, and two meal.
How much is that?
$7.95.
Yeah, see, but if I order two hot cakes,
two sausages and two eggs a la carte,
it's cheaper.
You get a garnish.
Like parsley or something?
(LAUGHS)
It's an orange slice.
You tell the owner that ain't right?
Cheating people like that?
We're gonna get you your money.
All of it. I swear.
Now would be great.
We need more time to get it.
Thank you.
I'll come by tomorrow.
One o'clock good for you?
Your friend's house.
You can subtract the coffee.
BETH: How much?
WOMAN: 10 for the clubs, 75 for the rest.
So, what'd he do?
(SIGHS)
Eesh! Something bad.
It's real sterling.
$50. You can keep the picture.
Okay. I have to take home
at least 2 grand for all of this.
Okay.
It was his great-grandmother's.
How much do you hate him?
(SIGHS)
AMBER: Mr. Boland.
Mr. Martin is here
inquiring about the 2015 Mustang.
Oh. Okay.
Hi.
Hey. How you doing?
Good. How are you?
Everything is good.
So, what are you driving now?
A 2007 Celica GT.
Ooh. Well, this thing's quite an upgrade.
Fully loaded.
I mean, she handles like a dream.
She's gorgeous.
(CHUCKLES) Yeah. Right?
My Celica's been good to me,
but she's pushing 100,000 miles. So...
She's dependable.
It's sad to see her go,
but I think it's time
to change things up a bit.
I mean, I thought the exact same thing.
I'm sorry.
You know, you see something
shiny and new, and you just
forget about what you got.
Once you upgrade, those memories,
they come back and they...
they haunt you.
You know, like, uh,
road trip with the kids.
I don't have kids.
The fun stuff you did
in the... in the back seat
in high school.
I haven't had it that long, so...
The crazy thing is, you thought you were
the one sick of her,
and now you'd do anything
to get her back.
You do sell cars here, right?
Don't give up on your Celica.
Maybe... Maybe if we test drove it...
You'll regret it.
Yeah. Uh, okay.
(SPECTATORS CHEERING)
STAN: Come on, baby.
Let's go! Let's hustle!
Pace yourself!
Don't be a hero!
Run, baby!
Get the ball!
You want some water?
Time out! Time out!
Water break!
STAN: She needs some water.
COACH: Come on, girls!
Get back in the game.
Excuse me. Can we keep it together,
please?
She shouldn't overdo it.
She's doing great.
She's fine.
Look at her.
Yeah, I see.
But what about when we can't afford that
damn drug anymore?
What happens then?
Cops get real good insurance.
You're not a cop yet.
Yeah, I will be.
Yeah, in six months, babe.
Okay. Okay.
Look, I know you're not used to this.
Used to what?
Neither am I. I mean,
we haven't been here in a long time.
What are you talking about?
This. Right here, right now.
That's what winning feels like, babe.
The girl's strong enough
to run and play in the sunshine
for the first time in years.
I don't Know about you, but...
I'mma drink in this moment.
Fine. Drink up.
Oh, I'mma need a little bit more
than that.
Excuse me?
I'mma need you to say it.
You're crazy.
Say it with me.
"We are winning."
We're winning.
Yeah, I'm sure you could do a lot
better than that.
We are winning.
Mean it.
Come on, baby.
(CHEERILY)
We're winning.
(LAUGHS) Yes!
That's what I'm talking about!
We're winning!
Yes!
Come on, baby!
Let's go!
We're winning, baby!
We are winning!
Let's go!
No, we're not!
I'm sorry, baby, I know.
I know, just stay focused, baby.
Stay focused.
We are winning.
Get back inside, Coach.
My bad.
Stay in the game, baby.
Stay in the game.
(CLAPPING)
(EXHALES)
That's 19.
You know what?
This is some bull right here.
Them coming at us
with guns, dropping by my job.
Uh-uh.
We have families.
We have children.
We have lives.
And we gotta end this now.
Great. How?
The way I see it, we got two issues
we need to take care of.
One is your boy up in that tree house.
Excuse me.
He's not my boy.
And the money.
Yeah.
So, two birds, one stone.
Y'all are already
getting charged for kidnapping.
We might as well ransom his ass, too.
(GASPS)
(BOOMER SLURPING)
Just let me go already.
Yeah. So you can run to the cops?
It's not like you're gonna kill me.
ANNIE: And how do you know?
'Cause you don't have the guts.
You're not killers.
(SCOFFS)
You're just a dumb checkout girl.
And you're what, a housewife?
Thought you'd pull a fast one, hmm?
Make a quick buck?
Now, you guys are freaking out
because you are in way over your head.
Just shut up.
Only reason I'm up here
is 'cause you don't know
what to do with me.
Just shut up!
You have no idea.
'Cause girls like you,
you never think things through.
No, he's right.
You do do this.
I mean, you've done this your whole life.
I mean, you make these big messes,
and then, you just expect everyone else
to clean it up,
and then, you just ignore it, for hours.
Hours become days, and days become weeks.
Yes, and weeks sometimes turn into months.
You're so right.
I do do that.
Mmm. Fatal flaw.
You can't leave me here forever.
Oh, we wouldn't mean to.
No. Right.
But like you said,
we don't have the guts to kill you.
And it's just, we're in
so far over our heads,
I feel like it's gonna take us
a really, really long time to figure out
what to do with you, and by then...
The animals or just Michigan winter
would probably just
take care of it for us.
I'm just a dumb checkout girl.
And I'm just an idiot housewife.
His grandma's loaded.
ANNIE:
And she doesn't trust banks.
So she keeps all of her cash at home
like Scrooge McDuck.
Where should we have her bring it?
Well, they always do the drop
in a park in Law & Order.
So, how about Beaman?
All right. Check out
this app I downloaded onto his phone.
AUTOMATED MALE VOICE:
(SCOTTISH ACCENT)
We have your grandson.
Deliver $60,000 to Beaman Park
by 5:00 p.m. or he's dead.
Is that Sean Connery?
No, it's just
"Scottish Man."
Here.
Sounds hot.
What about...
HIGH-PITCHED VOICE:
We have your grandson.
Deliver $60,000...
She wouldn't get that.
Okay, let's see here.
ROBOTIC VOICE:
We have your grandson.
Deliver $60,000 to Beaman Park
by 5:00 p.m.
or he's dead.
That's good.
Yeah?
I think that's good.
Yeah.
All right.
Phew. Okay.
(LINE RINGING)
BOOMER'S GRANDMA'S VOICEMAIL:
You've reached Marion Petersen.
I'm not home right now.
Please leave a message.
Try later.
(LINE RINGING)
VOICEMAIL: You've reached
Marion Petersen...
(LINE RINGING)
VOICEMAIL: You've reached
Marion Petersen.
I'm not home...
(LINE RINGING)
You've reached Marion Petersen.
(RUBY GROANS)
I'm not home...
Marion, where you at?
(SIGHS)
I mean, if she's out for the night...
Everyone has to use their own toothbrush,
and no one goes in the backyard tonight.
Just sprayed for bugs
and it's covered in very toxic chemicals.
I won't be late.
I just have a thing with
my sister and a friend.
Oh. A girls' night?
Yeah.
(ELECTRONIC DANCE SONG PLAYING)
(SONG PAUSES ABRUPTLY)
Ugh. Of course.
It's a security door.
We don't have a code.
All right, will you just be cool?
I hate it when you say that.
This is So much easier
than the grocery store.
She's not even home...
Here we go.
(SONG RESUMES)
(MAN ON VIDEO SPEAKING INDISTINCTLY)
Just go back to the part
with the second pin thingy.
I'm trying.
Stop flipping it around.
Just hold it one...
What is taking so long?
It's buffering.
That unlimited data plan sounds real nice
right about now, doesn't it?
Can I help you?
Marion.
You're up and about.
That's great.
We were told that you would be bedridden
and to just let ourselves in.
Who are you?
We're the volunteers.
Medicare automatically
enrolls you to receive
a number of services.
Tidying up, meal prep,
companionship, whatever you need.
Should we come back
another time, or is this a bad time?
Well, I suppose not.
You are an incredible liar.
Right?
Thank you.
(SONG CONTINUES)
(SONG ENDS)
Got any family in town, Marion?
My husband passed last year.
ANNIE: Oh.
I'm so sorry.
Such is life. (SIGHS)
We had 40 years.
Five children, sixteen grandchildren.
Wow, that must keep you busy.
Every one of them moved away.
Can you believe that?
They're just too into their own lives.
Except Leslie.
He's my little boy.
(CHUCKLES)
Oh, and this is his fiancee.
Isn't she pretty?
Very.
(MOUTHING)
Jessica Alba?
I Know what you're thinking,
but she's only half.
How about some of this
no-calorie lemonade?
Marion, where's your restroom?
Oh.
(ENGINE CRANKING NEARBY)
(MUFFLED SCREAMING)
(ENGINE STARTS)
Help!
(POP SONG PLAYING OVER EARPHONES)
(MUFFLED SCREAMING)
(SONG CONTINUES PLAYING)
(SONG CONTINUES)
(SONG FADES)
(CELL PHONE VIBRATING)
Are the kids okay?
(KRISTEN SPEAKING INDISTINCTLY OVER PHONE)
No. It's Input, Satellite, some...
You know what?
Tell them there is no TV.
It's too late.
What? Wait, wait.
What's that noise?
No, that noise.
Where's that coming from?
Be sure that you really get back
in that corner, now.
You gonna make the white girl
clean something?
Or does she just get to eat?
ANNIE: Mmm.
Doug looks so skinny here.
Oy, Gloria.
Were you ever not pregnant?
(BOTH CHUCKLE)
Right? Here.
Hand me that...
We gotta go. Now.
Sorry, Marion.
ANNIE: You didn't take it?
I told you, Dean is in my backyard.
I can't do this.
No, we're doing it.
Stop!
Why didn't you take the money?
I couldn't do it.
You couldn't rob
the sweet old racist lady?
She had this life.
She had this full life that she loved.
Come on.
We're robbing lonely old people?
Is this who we are now?
What we are is screwed.
Because you choked.
Beth.
We needed that money.
I Know. I'm sorry.
I gotta go.
Okay. Yeah. We'll just
talk about this tomorrow
when we're all dead!
(SIGHS)
I told you not to mow the lawn.
Well, good thing I did.
'Cause guess what I found back there.
What?
Moles. Those tiny little
rat thingies that build tunnels.
Oh, we got them, like, really bad.
No, I have them.
I have the moles.
Okay.
In my backyard, in my house that
I paid the mortgage for,
and am perfectly capable of handling
all the aspects of,
including the lawn.
And the remote control.
And the...
What happened to your ring?
I took it off.
For how long?
I don't know.
Oh.
You can
throw a chewed-up
bubble gum into the mole hole
and they'll choke and die.
That's terrible.
I Know.
Dean.
Thank you.
It's the middle of the night.
I'm making lasagne.
In the middle of the night?
You have to reheat at 350. Okay?
What, you plan on going somewhere?
Where would I be going?
You tell me. You're the one
acting like you're not gonna
be around to feed us no more.
Oh.
An island sounds good.
Oh, an island.
With one of those huts, mmm?
Where you could
see the ocean through the floor?
Mmm. Yeah.
(CHUCKLES)
I might come.
I'm sorry.
It's my imaginary island.
An island for one?
Maybe you can make conjugal visits.
(CHUCKLES)
Hey, hey.
(INTERRUPTS)
You'd tell me if something was
going on, right?
Yes? Baby...
I'm just making lasagne.
Why don't you come on back to bed?
And bring some of that salt with you.
(BOTH CHUCKLE)
(REFRIGERATOR OPENS)
EMMA: Where were you?
Oh, honey, it's so late.
Why aren't you in bed?
I woke up and you were gone.
Where was Kristen?
She's always sexting her boyfriend.
It's scary when you wake up
and I'm gone, huh?
Well, there's something
you need to know about mommies.
Sometimes they go away.
But guess what?
What?
They always come back, no matter what.
Okay?
Come on.
Did Kristen teach you that word...
"Sexting"?
Mmm-hmm.
I'm glad I gave her a raise.
(THUNDER RUMBLING)
Um, she sleeps with a nightlight.
What?
Sadie, she sleeps with a nightlight, okay?
She's 11 years old.
Yes, I know that.
That's why you just turn it on
and you walk out of the room
so you don't embarrass her.
What time is it?
And she doesn't like to swallow pills.
So you have to make sure
that you get her the gummy vitamins, okay?
What... What are you doing here?
And she's gonna need
to start wearing a bra soon.
So don't get her anything too girly.
Just get her something like
tank tops or something so that she can...
Annie, Annie, Annie, Annie. Annie.
I'm not gonna fight you for custody.
Seriously?
Why... why not?
Because I'm dealing with some stuff and...
I just can't.
And she's a kid, you know?
Uh-huh.
So, don't make her take off her shoes
in her own house.
Yeah.
How much is there?
Same as yesterday.
ANNIE: Costa Rica?
(BETH AND RUBY SIGH)
Bugs.
We cannot run.
We have families.
ANNIE: Right. China?
RUBY: Earthquakes.
(SIGHS) That's your big issue with China?
You have a better problem with China?
(SCOFFS)
Language barrier.
Human rights violations.
Communistic rule.
We are staying here
and we are facing this.
Air pollution, swine flu, and...
They don't have Indian food.
I need to go some place
where they have Indian food.
(LAPTOP CHIMES)
India?
God, no.
Who keeps IM-ing you?
Oh, I put Hans up on eBay.
Who's Hans?
The little drummer boy
I stole from Boomer's granny.
Annie, that is an heirloom.
Who's she gonna pass it down to?
Alba? Or her only-one-quarter-Mexican
grandchildren?
(LAPTOP CHIMES)
Holy mother.
What?
Hans is up to 8Gs.
Shut the front door.
Did you take anything else?
You're short.
No, we're not.
Yeah. You are.
Actually...
We're over.
See, these are super-rare collectibles.
Treasures.
Yes, sister.
You are correct.
That's a better word for these.
Because these super-rare treasures
go for 10 to 15Gs on eBay.
How much leg work is there, right?
But the truth is, it's very little
because we have done
the lion's share of the work for you.
Ruby.
These are the usernames
and passwords for our eBay accounts,
plus auction tips to
maximize your profits.
You want me to sell your dolls?
Tell him about Hans.
Oof. Our little drummer boy,
the pride of Hamburg.
(LAUGHS)
You see, Hans here, is one of only 12
in the entire...
(DOLL SHATTERS)
(SCREAMS)
Eleven in the world.
This some kind of joke to you?
I'm done playing with you guys.
(OBJECTS CLATTERING)
(SCREAMS)
What are they doing?
Making it look like a home invasion.
So they can kill us.
Please, don't do this.
Wait! Please wait!
We can get you the money.
I swear. Please.
We have families, we have kids.
(BOTH WHIMPERING)
(VOICE BREAKING)
You're an idiot.
Beth!
What, are you gonna blow our brains out
all over the room?
'Cause that's how it works, right?
Someone shorts you and they get tossed out
like trash,
and no one cares, and no one even notices.
Your problem this time is, that's not us.
We're normal people.
We pay our taxes and...
we take our kids to P.F. Chang's,
and we take orange slices
to soccer games.
And when bad things happen to good people,
everyone else goes crazy.
It's all over the news.
And there are all these
hashtags and movements.
Because if it could happen to us,
it could happen to anyone.
So, if you want to
invite all that attention
over a few grand,
then you're not the smart businessman
you think you are.
Now, roll the dice,
tell him to pull the trigger.
See what happens.
(SOBBING) Please.
Oh, my God.
(GASPS)
(WHIMPERS) Sweet Jesus.
(DOOR OPENING)
This was my favorite sangria bowl.
Well, it could have been your face.
LL 'chaim.
To life.
Dude...
ANNIE: Hey, looks like we got a Survivor.
(MUFFLED GRUNTING)
(MUFFLED LAUGHTER)
Split three ways,
it's two weeks, plus overtime.
(GRUNTS)
Could you go faster?
I'm going the speed limit.
Uh, are you joking?
I am not gonna get a ticket.
Why, you don't wanna mar
your perfect record of
armed robbery and kidnapping?
He couldn't have gone that far.
His hands are tied.
I mean, remember that
Gulf War vet on our block, growing up?
He ran marathons with both his arms
blown off.
How is that helpful?
You brought it up.
Damn, that was amazing.
I mean, can we just find this guy? Okay?
Yes, I'm trying.
Then what? We shove him
back up in the tree house, like Rapunzel?
Oh, there he is!
Where does he think he's going?
BETH: Oy, this is hard to watch.
Oh, okay. Oof.
I got this.
Wait. What are you gonna do?
(GROANING)
(WHIMPERING)
(CHUCKLES) Okay.
Wait, wait, wait.
What are you...
What are you doing?
(GRUNTS)
She's gonna cut his penis off.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no.
(BOOMER GRUNTING)
There we go.
(YELPS) What...
Yikes.
Mmm-hmm.
Oop.
(CAMERA SHUTTER CLICKS)
What are you doing?
Texting a picture of your penis.
Why are you doing that?
Actually, you're doing it.
It's your phone.
And, there. Sent.
To my daughter.
Who's 11.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no.
Oh, yeah.
Wait, why?
Well, because now,
if you go to the cops, so will I.
Have a nice night.
Wait. Wait. No.
I don't get it.
What did she do?
(CELL PHONE CHIMES)
Oh.
Oh, hell no.
(ANNIE LAUGHING)
Really?
You're a Sick, sick woman.
It's true.
Will someone tell me what happened?
I mean, it was either you
or my 11-year-old, you know.
Hostage peen.
(LAUGHS)
(SIGHS)
Can we go?
Told you I had it.
(SLOW POP SONG PLAYING)
Feeling good, feeling strong.
And taking requests.
Minions!
TV on.
Streaming box on.
Input 1, 2...
Arrow up, arrow left.
Select.
(ALL CHEERING)
Where's your brother?
Outside.
KENNY: "...Jujubes,
and gave one half to Kyle.
"Kyle kept eight of the Jujubes and gave
the last 10 to Kim.
"How many Jujubes did Jen take from Sam?"
MAN: Thirty-six.
You know how many
she'd have taken if Sam had a gun, though?
How?
Zero.
KENNY: Whoa.
Kenny, go inside.
I don't wanna.
Now.
Your friend's helping me.
Stop with the homework
and go inside and watch TV, now!
Listen to Mama, Kenny.
You know you should really
get him a tutor, right?
You want the rest
of the money, we'll get it.
Nah, let's forget all that.
Then why are you here?
I keep thinking about what you said.
About being a basic bitch and whatnot.
That's not exactly what I...
Maybe there's something
you could help me out with.
What's that?
You ladies got passports?
(POP SONG PLAYING)
(SONG CONTINUES)