NARRATOR: Previously on Good Girls...
DOCTOR: I would suggest
we put Sara ona list for a transplant.
A girl in Madison just got hit.
She's a perfect match.
Are people pulling your pants down?
SADIE: They want to know what I am.
We could send her to St. Anne's.
She's an atheist who enjoys a bow tie.
I don't think that
Catholic school is a good fit.
DR. HARPER: It's cancer in your prostate.
Couldn't make it sound
a little more serious?
Can I call you Big Mike?
(GUNSHOT)
(SCREAMS) Oh, my God!
You shot me in the foot.
Just stay away from me.
Take what you came for
and get out of here.
MARY PAT: We'll just put the whole thing
on the,
"I'm what's keeping you
out of jail account."
Would you ever wanna grab a coffee?
I had fun tonight.
MARY PAT: Should I put on some tea?
BOOMER: Yeah.
RUBY: Who's the boy?
It's that fool we arrested.
He's ours now.
They have him!
The FBI! And he is talking to them!
You think I need you?
Ain't nothing but a damn charity case
to me. Go home.
I don't see how you're gonna
let me do that.
You're sure he's coming for us?
We know too much now.
ANNIE: Maybe we should turn ourselves in.
It's better than waiting to be murdered.
He's the one who should be in jail.
Then let's put him there.
ANNIE: We hire a hitman.
Seriously?
We don't need him dead.
We need him in jail.
Let me finish.
We hire a hitman,
and then we frame Rio
for the murder that the hitman commits.
Oh, well, when you
put it like that, then...
Who's the hitman gonna hit?
A random innocent?
Someone who cuts in line
at the Starbucks?
Oh, there are candidates.
I'm sure there are.
Look, nobody said
this was going to be easy, okay?
If it was, the FBI would have done it.
Mind control.
Turns himself in.
And, I'm done.
It's called brainstorming.
You throw stuff out, you see what sticks.
I've got something in the morning.
More important than being murdered?
We're meeting with the finance people
from the hospital.
What are you gonna do?
Say we can pay for that kidney.
No problem.
Write a bad check
and hope they don't realize
until she's open on the table.
It's a good plan.
Go with God.
(SIGHS) I'll call you tomorrow.
Park in your garage, just in case.
Yeah, and don't let anybody
pull up next to you at a stoplight.
How am I supposed to do that?
Just keep inching forward.
You know what?
Don't even stop.
Yeah, run the reds.
Do you want to just...
I'll tell Stan I drank too much.
It doesn't have to be a lie.
ANNIE: Yeah, you can crash on my couch.
(DOOR OPENS)
(BELLS JINGLE)
No, thanks.
I'm not staying.
If you waiting on my boy,
you're wasting your time.
He ain't coming tonight.
Yeah, so, if I were you,
I'd go back home to that beautiful family
in Baltimore.
You know, let's just
call this thing what it is, yeah?
I! mean, not that I mind
having my picture taken,
but it must be getting pretty old
for you people
chasing my ass all over the city,
and not coming up with jack.
I think I'll talk
to Eddy myself, if you don't mind.
(SCOFFS)
Good luck with that.
Her match was removed
from life support late last night,
so I'd say we're in a 24-hour window.
(EXHALES)
Once we hear,
you sign consents,
you deposit the payment,
and Sara goes straight to surgery.
Um, how much of that
does insurance cover?
Your out of pocket was
20% after deductible.
And, that's what now?
$87,400.53.
Okay.
Specific.
(CHUCKLES)
So do you all need us to write
a check now, or...
That'd be great.
Yes, right now is...
Yeah. Fantastic.
Can do.
Not a problem.
Yeah. You got that.
All right.
(STAN CHUCKLES SOFTLY)
Of course, my pen runs out.
It's not...
Babe, do you have a...
You Know what, I think I do have a...
No, wait.
You're not a pen.
(BOTH LAUGH)
RUBY: You cannot write with that.
You could try.
It's not gonna happen.
You can use mine.
STAN: Here we go.
Okay.
Yeah.
Uh...
This can be a really anxious time.
So just be sure you take some time
to practice self-care, okay?
Oh, yeah, yeah, yeah.
We are all about that namaste.
Yes, regularly, yes.
Great.
How much is in there?
$3,500.
GoFundMe?
Hang on.
But I think about $1,000.
Okay, Well, we still got options.
Like what?
If corporate comes through,
call him again.
I already did.
And GoFundMe's at $800.
(SIGHS) I thought you said $1000.
I was wrong.
(SIGHS) Okay.
All right. Well,
church could do another car wash
or a rummage sale.
I can pass the hat at the station.
Hell, we can go door to door,
but people are gonna need to step up.
They already have.
Well, they need to step up the step-up.
Stan.
(SIGHS) This check
is gonna bounce so hard.
I Know.
No, it's not just
gonna bounce, it's gonna ricochet.
I Know.
It's a three-year felony
for writing a bad check,
Ruby, you can go to jail.
You can go to jail for a lot of things.
Well, then we might as well
just rob a bank.
All right.
Just calm down.
(SIGHS AND GROANS)
Okay?
Mm-hmm.
Breathe.
(BREATHES HEAVILY)
Where'd you get French fries?
KENNY: Under the seat.
Give me one, please.
Thank you.
Nom, nom, nom.
Delicious.
Hey, guess what Wednesday is.
Trash day.
Hey.
You Know who that is?
Um, I don't know.
Maybe the Lee kid.
Just never seen him before.
Hmm. Wednesday is Our anniversary.
I Know.
Yeah, it's our 20th anniversary.
I could make a reservation.
I mean, we gotta eat.
Dean...
Look, I just... I think that
we have to decide.
Like, if we're not gonna be...
Then we just...
We got to call it.
Because right now, we're stuck.
We're, like, in this weird limbo.
And I guess, like, I'm...
I'm saying that, I just... I got to know.
I'm sorry. You need to know what?
Is it our anniversary
or just another Wednesday?
Buckle up, guys.
Hmm. How bad is it?
It's only been a week.
You hate it.
It's fine.
(SIGHS)
Do all the girls own horses?
Does the gym teacher wear a habit
or does she have nun shorts?
We don't have gym.
Hey! It's not all bad.
Like I said.
Look, Dad and Nancy just
get to make the decisions for right now,
but I promise you,
you do not have to stay here
for much longer, okay?
I gotta go.
Hey.
You look dope in the suit.
Love you.
BOTH: Never put no one above ya.
BOOMER: Annie-bananie.
I want you to meet Sally.
I am grooming her for assistant manager.
When did you start here, Sally?
Three days ago.
ANNIE: Huh!
Quite a promotion.
Well, you know,
some people are born leaders,
and, uh, others aren't.
And, you know, I'm going to need
to start, uh, delegating
a bit more now.
Why is that?
If you must know, I am, uh, dating someone
very special.
Is she Jewish?
Is she?
Uh, so, Annie's drawer
was 78 cents short last night, Sally.
Let me show you how we fix that
around here, Sally.
Watch and learn.
Mm?
Mm! Mm.
Seventy eight.
Then... (SIGHS)
(SYSTEM BEEPS)
Mm, mm, mm.
(COINS JINGLE)
Bada-bing.
Yeah, so, you're gonna
need to stay on the check-out girls.
Especially this one.
So that the vault matches
end-of-day receipts.
Now where things can go really wrong
is the seafood counter.
Now, those guys think
anything on ice is a fresh catch,
even if it's been
sitting around since Christmas.
Sally, I can't tell you
how many potential lawsuits
I have settled over crab salad.
Hey.
What's going on?
You're scared the hell out of us.
I have an idea.
You cannot text 911...
When we have a literal fatwa
on our heads right now.
...unless it's an actual 911.
Let me know when you guys are done
and it's my turn.
What is the one thing
that we know about this guy
that the cops don't?
He wears his hoodie funny.
Like half on, half off.
Yeah, make up your mind, bruh.
That's correct.
But he also launders money at my work.
Which we found out the hard way.
Hello.
People go to jail for that.
We can tell your FBI guy.
And what do we say
when he asks how we know?
We can't exactly
say we robbed the joint
and got more than we expected.
We don't have to tell him anything.
We just have to give them a reason
to look.
Oh, hell no!
It's already familiar territory.
It's right up there with the hitman idea.
But all we have to do
is get the vault open
and the cops will do the rest.
My God, mind control
never sounded so good.
They'll never see it coming.
I mean, nobody hits the same place twice.
Yeah, because it's stupid.
But it does get you your kidney.
We would have to take
just enough for Sara,
and then leave the rest for the Feds.
I mean, we could take a little more.
Okay.
(TUTS)
Hello, old friend.
All right, so the store has gotten
some major security upgrades.
How major?
Three new eyes in the sky.
Oy-vey.
Mm-hmm.
And a brand-new vault,
which is very high tech.
What about your boy from the tree house?
Okay, still not my boy.
And he's not working nights,
because, apparently, he's in love.
Ew!
With what?
(SCOFFS) Right?
What about Tyler?
No upgrades on Tyler.
Although, he did lose seven pounds,
so he might run a little faster.
But he just discovered pho.
It's pronounced "fuh."
What does pho have to do with it?
Longer dinner breaks,
because he does the whole
ceremonial Vietnamese thing.
BETH: All right.
That helps.
And there's panic buttons
at each register now.
Wait, what?
Yeah.
That call the cops?
Or SWAT, National Guard.
I don't know.
We've never used them.
But whoever they are,
they guarantee response in ten minutes.
And new linoleum floors.
Very slippery.
Okay. Is that it?
ANNIE: Yes.
Except for the motion detectors
at the loading docks,
which are infrared.
Oh, sweet Jesus.
But that's it.
Except for...
Oh, my God.
What now?
(CHILDREN LAUGHING)
DEAN: Hey, what is that sound
of crazy footsteps?
What?
You only love me for the candy.
Please, put the candy back.
Put the candy back.
Please, please put it back.
Surprise.
Can you drop the kids off
at your mother's tonight?
Yeah, what...
what's going on?
And maybe you should stay there, too.
Are you in trouble?
Yeah.
I! mean, is it bounce-house guy?
Oh, my God, Beth.
But I've got this.
I'm gonna fix it, and it'll all be over.
Well, let me help, please.
I mean, I... I've got
to do something to help.
Why don't you make
that dinner reservation?
Really?
Yeah, okay. I will.
I can do that.
Yeah.
I love you guys.
CHILDREN: Love you, too, Mom.
DEAN: Say goodbye to Mom.
CHILDREN: Bye.
DEAN: Bye.
EMMA: Bye!
KENNY: Bye.
I'm done.
You barely touched it.
Can I have pizza?
Me, too.
No. Baby, this is all
you're allowed to eat
before your surgery.
I'm not having surgery.
(SIGHS) You know what?
I don't even know what
y'all are talking about,
'cause I'm getting
notes of hickory up in here, just...
honey chipotle, maybe a little garlic.
Mm. Mm-hmm.
Mm. Right?
Yeah. I've got, like, a smoky, citrusy,
oregano thing going on.
Mm. You know what this tastes like?
Straight up pizza.
Mm-hmm.
Pepperoni and pineapple.
Salty, sweet goodness.
I wanna try some.
Back off, man.
Theirs is way better.
All right.
Knock yourself out.
(CLEARS THROAT)
So, I got some good news today.
Oh, yeah?
Yeah. Uh...
Corporate's gonna come through
with that advance.
It's going to be a bitch to pay back.
But they want to help.
Yeah?
Yeah.
(SNORTS AND LAUGHS)
Hey, you know what that is right there?
What?
That's that boomerang
of yours coming back.
Well, the accounting office is in Dayton,
so I'm going to head down there tonight
and, uh, get the money first thing.
Mm. I don't want you driving
all night alone.
It's fine. Beth said she'd come, so...
HARRY: I don't taste pizza.
(RUBY CHUCKLES)
And one day,
they gonna realize how far
you go for them.
Uh, you think? (SIGHS)
(POP MUSIC PLAYING)
Nobody move, this is a robbery.
We're gonna make this quick and easy.
Do what we Say, nobody gets hurt.
Who's in charge here?
Come on. Come on.
Come on.
I said who's in charge here?
BETH: Somebody better start talking.
ANNIE: It's me.
I am.
BETH: Come on.
Come on. Over there.
Come on. Come on.
Let's go!
Let's go! Let's go!
All right. All right.
Okay, Okay.
Okay, that's it.
Come on. Come on.
RUBY: Hey!
Uh-uh, not you.
Why?
Because you're gonna open the cash vault.
Sally, I need your keycard.
Sally, don't be a hero.
Just give them what they want.
Hey. It's going to be okay. Go on.
BETH: All right, everybody, down!
Face to the ground.
Come on, you guys.
Not like that.
Come on, you guys, like this.
Like, nap time, okay?
Come on.
I don't want to see any eyes.
If I see any eyes, I swear to God,
I will put a bullet between them.
Let's go, bitch!
Ow!
Really, with the excessive force.
Oh, my God, I was a character.
Well, Mr. De Niro, now I'm gonna have
a bruise.
We got to make it real.
Come on.
I'm trying, okay?
I'm going as fast as I can.
Well, which one is it?
It's this one.
But it's got like a ring within a ring
situation,
and there's all these
library cards on it.
Just let me try.
No, you have gloves on.
Just chill.
And you have no nails.
So, just let it try it.
God, chill!
(KEYS CLATTERING)
(BEEPING)
BETH: Keep your heads down!
I'm watching.
(BEEPS)
There it is.
You sure?
Yeah, I'm sure.
I'm looking right at it.
It's like it fell into a furry salad.
Can you reach it?
Dude, it's way down there.
But you got those long sauce arms,
baby, come on.
How much time do we have left?
Six minutes.
Doesn't anyone else have a card?
(COUNTRY MUSIC PLAYING ON SPEAKERS)
(INHALES)
Come on, whip that lasso, girl.
I'm trying.
Put your hips into it.
Now, you're talking.
Yeah. With my butt.
I'm really bad at this.
(CHUCKLES)
That's fun, anyway.
You're fun, anyway.
RUBY: Can... (GROANS)
Three minutes.
Oh, my God. I can feel everything.
Dude.
Oh, my God. Oh. (GROANS)
No!
Who's got that... (EXCLAIMS)
(GASPS)
Sauce arms forever!
Yeah!
Yes!
Nobody move. Count sheep.
Good to go.
(SIRENS APPROACHING)
(SOUL MUSIC PLAYING)
Annie, what are you doing?
Where did you get that?
I'd like you to put
all that money back now.
Do you remember the time
you broke that window on that Prius
because you thought
there was a dog in the back seat
that was gonna die from the heat,
but it was actually just a leather jacket?
Yeah.
Well, I didn't tell anyone about that.
It's not the same.
But couldn't it be?
Put it back, Annie.
(SOUL MUSIC CONTINUES)
OFFICER 1:
We got to take them.
Come on, let's go.
Go. Go. Go.
(INDISTINCT CHATTER)
Go, go, go.
Clear.
OFFICER 2: Let's go.
We gotta move.
Everybody out.
Let's go.
Go, go, go, go, go!
All right, folks.
You're safe, ladies.
Let's go. Let's go.
(SOUL MUSIC CONTINUES)
Tyler, please.
You don't want to do this.
I don't have a choice.
I'll split it with you.
I don't want it.
I'll be your girlfriend.
I'm gay.
Huh.
Tyler, please.
There has to be something that you want.
Anything.
(POLICE OFFICERS CHATTERING IN DISTANCE)
OFFICER 3: Let's go.
OFFICER 4: Let's go.
Please.
OFFICER 5: Check the back.
It was like his body
just knew what to do, you know?
Like some reflex that
lay dormant until called upon.
Like Van Damme meets Bruce Lee,
but more lethal.
She's exaggerating a little bit.
(CHUCKLES)
No, (SPUTTERS)
I just can't believe
that this whole time,
I was working next to a hero.
I'm just pissed they got away.
Congratulations.
Oh, thank you.
Thank you, Sir.
Good work.
Thank you.
You did good, son.
You did good.
Thank you.
Hey, how you doing?
OFFICER: Right this way, sir.
(COUNTRY MUSIC PLAYING ON HEADPHONES)
What's that sound?
(DISTANT BEEPING)
Is it one of your toys?
Where are those robots
that Daddy got you?
Is it you that's beeping?
(BEEPING CONTINUES)
What is it?
Come here, baby.
(BEEPING)
(GRUNTS)
Okay.
Two, three, four...
(INHALES)
That's $87,500.
Sorry I don't have smaller bills.
Oh, it's...
Do you need the check for your records?
Just shred it. Thank you.
Okay.
How'd she do?
Oh, baby girl's a warrior like her mama.
Can we go see her?
Nah, they're gonna
call us in when it's go time.
(EXHALES) I can't believe we're here.
Believe it.
Doctors, urgent care,
what, it's all gonna stop now?
No, you'll find something to worry about.
(BOTH CHUCKLE)
I always do.
(SIGHS)
And 40 years /ater, the blizzard of '78
Still has people...
WOMAN: (ON RADIO)
...a Grand Rapids woman
speaks out after her personal information
was used fo e-file a fraudulent...
(TURNS RADIO OFF)
(SIGHS)
(INDISTINCT CHATTER)
(CHILDREN CHATTERING)
(SADIE CHUCKLES)
MAN: (ON TV)
Experts are warning to file your taxes...
(REMOTE CLICKING)
WOMAN: (ON TV)
More I-75 closures
coming your way
as the river bridge project
continues to expand south.
(KNOCK ON DOOR)
Travelers should expect
just one open lane near...
(TURNS TV OFF)
(KNOCKING AT DOOR)
(KNOCKING CONTINUES)
I don't know if he's FBI or CIA or...
Jesus, Mary and Joseph.
I feel so stupid, you know?
Where did you meet him?
At church.
But you didn't say anything, right?
No, I don't think so.
I don't know.
I trusted him, you know?
I mean, I...
Like, I liked him.
(BREATH TREMBLING)
I'm such an idiot.
No, you're not.
There. That's him.
Mary Pat.
What?
You are going to need a drink.
It's 3:00 in the afternoon.
Then, let's have a double.
(HUMMING)
Mr. Boland.
Someone wants to test the Maserati.
Oh, uh, can you do it?
I gotta get home.
You got a hot date?
Mm, uh, maybe.
(SINGING ON RADIO)
My darlin'
(SINGING)
Turn the radio up
For that sweet sound
Hold me close Never let me go
Keep this feelin' alive
Make me lose control
(HORN HONKING)
(INDISTINCT ANNOUNCEMENT ON PA)
Mrs. Boland?
Yes.
He's gonna be fine.
Oh, God. Thank you.
Just a couple of bruised ribs.
Minor whiplash.
Can I see him?
He's up in imaging.
We're running a CT just to be safe.
This is for pain.
And this won't interfere
with the radiation?
He's on so many things now
because of all the side effects.
Uh, I'm sorry.
The side effects of what?
Of the cancer.
Did you take his blood?
Yes, we did.
Could I get some water?
Of course.
(ROCK MUSIC PLAYING)
DEAN: I have cancer.
BETH: When will you know more?
DEAN: We'll know more
after the appointment.
BETH: What did the doctor say?
DEAN: There's no question.
DR: HARPER:
He has cancer.
DEAN: I just wanna say thanks
for letting me come home.
BETH: He lives here!
ANNIE: Since when?
BETH: Since he got cancer.
MAN (ON TV):
... following the robbery
in an Ashfield area, Fine & Frugal.
Local authorities working with the FBI say
the men laundered money
through several small businesses
in Wayne County,
including the Fine & Frugal chain.
According to authorities,
they were able to charge the defendants
after a tip left by the robbers
led investigators to the gang's illegal
financial activities.
(ROCK MUSIC CONTINUES)
(MUSIC PLAYING OVER STEREO)
I did something.
You know where my mind goes.
I Know, baby.
Like it's PTSD level.
That tree house really messed me up.
Do you want to hear this or not?
(CLEARS THROAT)
So, I'm on the freeway this morning
and instead of taking the Gratiot exit,
I just keep driving.
And I go all the way to the border.
And then I go all the way
to that craft store.
You did a pop-by on Big Mike?
Oh, my God.
How's his foot?
What? What did he say?
Well, I go straight up to him.
He's up on this, like, forklift thing.
And I say, "Listen,
just because Rio's out of the picture
"doesn't mean that we have to be."
And he gets down,
and he reaches into his pocket
and he pushes a big fat gun
to my forehead.
And he says, "I don't want
to deal with new players in Detroit."
And I said, "Bitch.
"We are Detroit."
(SOFTLY) Bitch.
He could've shot you.
Yeah, well, he really
didn't like what came next.
So, I gave him a choice.
I said,
"You're either with us,
"or you're on your own."
So what's it going to be, Big Michael?
BOTH: Big Michael.
And he just looks at me,
for the longest time.
And I'm like,
"All right, here it is.
"At least I'll go in a blaze of glory."
And then,
he shook my hand.
And he loaded up the car.
You guys, I have six huge boxes
of wrapping paper in that car.
Yo, Daddy, I told you she got cool.
Who are you right now?
(LAUGHING)
You should see your faces right now.
Wait. What?
Yours is whiter than usual.
(LAUGHING)
You made all that up?
Even the forklift part?
Man, can you imagine?
I mean, I got to say,
I'm kind of sad it's not true.
Well, it could be.
We got robbed.
Again.
And I am PO'd, pardon my French.
How much have you had to drink?
I need to...
(SIGHS)
Listen.
I am gonna blow your mind
about something, okay?
You smell like a brewery.
These women.
I Know you're in some kind of
shady business with them,
but they are not good people.
In fact, they are criminals.
I... What did they do?
They... they hit my store.
For a second time.
Oh my gosh, that is...
SO Crazy.
I know this is a shock,
and God knows you don't deserve this,
but you fell in with a bad crowd.
What about Annie?
That one is garbage.
Is that why you tried to rape her?
(SCOFFS)
Uh, who told you that?
Was it that piece of trash?
Because that's not what happened.
What happened?
(SCOFFS) It's complicated.
Well, I want to know.
We...
We sort of had a thing.
You dated her?
I mean, she flirted with me constantly.
You see the way she flaunts her goods.
Uh, the low cut blouses,
that tattoo of hers.
I mean, it's a walking billboard for...
S-E-X.
So you raped her?
No, no. (SCOFFS)
See, I... I feel like
you're not even listening to me, okay?
Uh, Annie...
(SCOFFS) I mean, she's no...
She's not like you.
She's not a good Christian like you.
I mean, girls like that,
they want that kind of attention.
Rape?
No!
Just...
The rough stuff.
Look, there's a difference.
You know me, I'm a gentleman.
But when a tease like that
pushes my buttons,
and you know what button
I'm talking about,
I'm apt to give her
what she came looking for.
And I'm sorry if that's not
pretty or romantic,
but it's human nature, you know?
It is science.
(SCOFFS)
Do you have anything you want to add?
You recorded me?
Why would you do that?
I could ask you the same thing.
That was before.
Before what?
Before I liked you.
I think you better go.
I want that back.
Just because you want something,
doesn't give you the right to take it.
(DOOR SLAMS)
Went old school
Cinnamon Schnapps.
(GASPS)
My personal favorite.
That's like bat mitzvah old school.
Oh! Sadie's almost that age.
(EXHALES) Damn!
We old.
Dude.
She just looks so happy, you know?
Stop.
It was like there was
this whole other planet
called St. Anne's,
that she never knew about
where everyone's cool with her.
They play hacky sack.
I've literally been keeping her from it.
She's there now.
She could've been there months ago.
Do you promise you won't be a dick?
No.
Maybe I'm not the only person
who knows what's best for her.
I'm... I'm sorry.
Say that again?
Dick!
(CHUCKLES)
I just wanna make sure
it's not the Schnapps.
She needs you, too.
Not the Schnapps.
That is literally
exactly what I needed to hear.
"Not the Schnapps."
Well, we just did it in two seconds,
what they pay lawyers for in blood.
Leveled up.
Like some grown-ass folk.
Yeah, except grown-ass folk
don't use the term
"grown-ass folk."
Mm. True.
I should go.
Me, too.
Chocolate shakes, chocolate chip cookies.
Mm-hmm.
Burgers.
What's the one that comes
on a doughnut, Mom?
The doughnut burger?
Those look nasty.
I want one now.
Mm-mm.
RUBY: Okay, okay.
Now, your new kidney's
gonna quit before it even takes.
Yeah, let's not do that.
Can I have more Jell-O then?
Jell-O is good.
You can eat Jell-O,
till your ears turn blue.
I'll get the nurse.
I love you, Boo-Boo.
I love you, Mama.
(SIGHS)
I got this.
You can stay with hungry-mungry.
What's wrong?
You know that guy
that I collared a while back?
The one with the goofy mustache?
Excuse me.
Yes?
Can we get some Jell-O for 111?
NURSE: Of course.
Yeah, the, uh, the Feds and the DPD
took his gang down last night.
That's good.
(SIGHS)
What?
Tell me what to do here, Ruby.
I don't...
See we got them,
because they were laundering their money
through this grocery store,
and, uh, we wouldn't
even have known any of it,
if, uh, these two women
hadn't robbed the place
a couple nights ago.
That's lucky.
Mm.
I don't think we should leave her alone.
It's the same store Beth's little sister
works at.
Oh, my God, was she there?
That's how you're gonna play this?
I mean, I haven't talked to her...
It's the same damn store,
the same damn night,
that you and your friend, Beth,
were going down to Ohio
to collect 87 grand in cash.
Hang on. You think...
There's no business, is there?
No corporate.
All this was just a bunch of BS.
How could you think I would ever do that?
Your face.
Right now.
I did it for us.
I'm a cop, Ruby.
I had no choice.
What the hell am I supposed to do?
I don't know.
You asked what it would take
for me to walk out the door.
You knew the answer.
(BREATH TREMBLING)
And you did it anyway.
RIO: Hi, honey, we're home.
Would have been here sooner,
but I got tied up.
Surprise.
I'm sorry, Beth.
He didn't do anything.
RIO: Oh, he tried.
(CHUCKLES) He tried.
Got more fight in him than I thought.
Ain't that right, champ?
Oh, I'm sorry.
Does this...
Does this bother you?
Let him go.
What, you can't even handle
a little blood?
I thought you wanted to be me.
I mean, that's what all this is, right?
You're trying to put me away and all.
You must got big plans.
But see, you didn't think things
all the way through.
It takes balls to do what I do.
You want to be the king,
you got to kill the king.
This stuff's medieval, darlin'.
Please, don't do this.
Please, don't kill us.
(LAUGHING) I...
I ain't gonna kill nobody.
Nah, man, you are.
(COCKS)
So, what you think?
You got what it takes?