BETH: Previously on Good Girls...
BETH: Who is that guy?
He works for me.
Where am I?
I'm a friend of your friend's.
You wanna bring
other people into this now?
We've got a system that works.
WOMAN: So, what's a secret shopper?
The more you buy and return,
the more money you're gonna make.
You think you could slip in
fake cash with the real
and I ain't gonna notice?
No.
We would never do that.
Maybe it was one of the women.
I mean, how would
you know that I turned in
the exact same cash?
I don't know what you've gotten me
involved in,
but it's something super-shady.
TURNER: An arrest you made this week
gave us a man on the inside.
Did you get to put on the cuffs?
Uh, maybe.
(BREATHING HEAVILY)
I got cola, Tina, Molly, Oxy,
K, Addys, and fat bags of herb.
BOOMER: /'I/ take all of it.
Wow. I didn't think you had it in you.
$10,000.
So, we're good now, right?
Yeah.
Till next month.
(DOG WHINING, CHEWING)
(SIGHS)
(DOG CONTINUES CHEWING)
(DOG WHINING)
(WHINES, GROANS SOFTLY)
(INSTRUCTOR SPEAKING INDISTINCTLY ON TV)
(PANTING)
(INSTRUCTOR CONTINUES INDISTINCTLY)
Where is it?
Huh?
The money, Dean.
Where is it?
What are you talking about?
The cash that was all over the kitchen,
it's gone, it's all gone.
Okay, calm down.
Did you take it?
No.
Are you seriously accusing me right now?
You don't have the best track record
with money, Dean.
I didn't touch your stupid money!
Okay, who took it?
I don't know.
Who knows about it?
Jeez, Beth!
(INSTRUCTOR CONTINUES SPEAKING
INDISTINCTLY ON TV)
(GRUNTS)
Why did you take my money?
RIO: Mmm-mmm.
My money. Mine.
We're gonna be shutting things down
for a while.
What does that even mean?
One of my associates got picked up.
When I feel heat, I don't mess around.
My bad.
Do you want some?
No.
You sure?
They put the...
They put the hash brown
on the inside of this thing.
I don't understand.
(CHUCKLES) Me neither, like...
And they're still so crispy.
No, I'm talking about the shutdown.
Mmm.
Yeah.
Yeah, you closed for business.
But you took all of it.
So?
So part of that was our cut.
We worked our asses off for that money.
What you want me to say?
It's a company-wide shutdown.
And if I got closing costs,
everybody feels the pain.
You can't just mess with people's lives
like that.
You wanna know what I can't do?
I can'tdo 5 to 15
in FCI Milan
'cause some bitches
need their pocket money.
How long?
Excuse me?
How long are we shut down?
Till further notice.
How long?
I don't know.
Like a week?
If you had to guess.
Okay, six months.
Six months?
BETH: I don't know!
I mean, when are we
gonna put a man on Mars?
A couple years, tops.
I just feel like we're close, you know?
So, what are we gonna do
about the secret shoppers?
We tell them corporate's
revamping the program.
Okay, yeah, I guess I'd buy that.
And what about our friendly neighborhood
blackmailer up our ass?
Well, we just paid her,
so at least we have some time.
What about us?
Well, I mean, what are we supposed to do?
Go back to working like dogs
and barely scraping by?
I guess, we go legit for a while.
(SIGHS)
So, the dogs and the scraping?
I like the word
"legit" better.
(KIDS CHATTERING)
WOMAN 1: I mean, seriously,
how long has it been
since we've had a playdate?
WOMAN 2: Forever!
WOMAN 1: (CHUCKLES)
Bethie's always so busy.
WOMAN 2: Yeah.
WOMAN 1: Right?
Beth?
(ALTERNATIVE POP SONG PLAYING)
Not anymore.
You Know, there is so much
that we need help with
at the school right now.
Oh, pancake breakfast!
And, um, a fall cleanup.
Silent auction.
Oh, do you know what Taft did?
What?
They let you bid on a parking spot
close to the school.
That is genius.
So convenient.
Higher, Mommy, higher!
(POP SONG CONTINUES PLAYING)
(BOOMER GRUNTS)
Well, I mean, the urinals could use
a little more love.
I just started in here.
No one excused their way to the top.
Speaking of...
Urinals?
I was hoping I could
maybe pick up a couple more shifts.
I'll take graveyard or whatever you have
is fine.
Why?
What's going on?
I need the money.
Was the bling ring not panning out?
Here's what I like.
(CLEARS THROAT)
You've been, uh, passing the drug tests
with flying colors.
One day ata time, right?
And you've shown a real willingness
to take on new challenges.
So, that's all good.
My concern
is still the overall attitude.
I'll work on it.
Yeah?
Yeah.
And, hey, come back in an hour
and I'll have this place
shining like fine silver.
Look at you, Annie Bananie.
You've come a long way.
(SOFTLY) Thanks.
And I'll, uh...
try to get you on the schedule
a little more.
Urinals.
You just talk to local businesses,
see what they might be willing to donate.
It's a chance to be really creative.
Bolton Travel donated...
(MOUTHING)
...a hot-air balloon ride last year.
WOMAN 1: No way.
WOMAN 2: What if I hadn't asked?
Thank God you did.
Welcome to Dandy Donuts.
What can I get for you?
(WHISPERS)
"Dandy Day."
(MOUTHING) What?
(WHISPERS)
"On this dandy day."
Sorry. What can I
get for you on this dandy day?
(MAN SPEAKING INDISTINCTLY OVER PHONE)
Can you repeat that?
Three glazed, a maple bar, and a coffee.
You heard?
Three glazed and a maple, stat!
How could you hear that?
Thank you.
Whoa, whoa.
Did they ask for extra Sugar?
They could have.
But did they?
Dude, it literally sounds like
they're speaking Mandarin
with a stutter out there.
Okay, we don't do extra sugar.
Okay.
Come on, hustle.
The line is backing up.
(POP SONG CONTINUES PLAYING)
Thank you.
Dandy day!
Have yourself a dandy day.
How much?
$1,900.
(SIGHS)
Is that it?
It's all I can spare right now.
Same.
I can try and squeeze
a tiny bit more out of Dean.
I'm getting an allowance again.
Don't look at me like that.
He offered it and I took it.
Hey, I am not throwing stones.
Last night, I got donut fat in my eye.
I found a dead cat in a produce truck.
Not that it's a competition.
Well, it's not 10 grand,
but still a payday in my book.
BETH: I mean, do you think she'll take it?
She'll take it and she'll like it.
Screw this, bitch.
I am so tired of this trick.
We are shut the hell down.
What does she want? Blood?
Hey! Hey!
Over here!
(ALL CHEERING, APPLAUDING)
Who is that?
I don't know.
Let's go.
Must have me confused with someone else.
Well, we do all look alike.
(CHUCKLES) Right?
Ruby, hey!
Okay, she don't look confused.
Hi.
Oh, wait, I do know her.
Oh, yeah?
From school?
No...
Hi.
Yeah. Hello.
It's good to see you.
Hi.
(CHUCKLES)
Which one is yours?
Uh, in the yellow.
Well, they're all in yellow.
(BOTH CHUCKLE)
No, our daughter.
She's on the bench down there.
She's not feeling too great.
MARY PAT: Oh.
Hi, I'm Stan.
Mary Pat.
MARY PAT:
Oh, she's so sweet.
Yeah, which one is yours?
Well, Benji here might be starting soon.
We're just gonna, kind of, check out
the program.
Mmm-hmm.
Hey, mister, did you
ever hear of a napkin?
Oh, come on. Don't...
(CHUCKLES)
Gosh, I hope I have some wipes. Um...
Could... Do you mind?
Actually, just like...
Yeah.
Oh, wait.
Found some.
(CHUCKLES) Phew!
(CHUCKLES)
So, I guess this little guy here's
gonna be a few years
before he gets his cleats, huh?
That's right.
You didn't tell me that you were married
to a police officer.
Oh, he's not a real cop yet.
Oh, okay, now.
Almost there.
Well, thank you, Stan, for almost
protecting our city.
(LAUGHS)
She's funny, this one.
She'll keep you on your toes.
Hey, can I, um...
Can I ask you about a police matter?
He's off duty.
What if somebody,
um, stole money out of my mail?
STAN: Yeah?
How much?
Uh, about 8,000 bucks.
STAN: Seriously?
Wow, that's federal level.
You know, I was really
counting on it, too.
STAN: Mmm.
They left me a little bit,
but not nearly enough
to get through my bills and everything.
Come on, mister.
You're making this much harder
than it needs to be.
(CHUCKLES)
Does anybody have
any hand sanitizer, or...
You need me to hold
something else for you...
No, it's just, like,
really caked on here for some reason.
Give me your hand.
Maybe it was a misunderstanding.
The money in your mail thing.
You know, I don't think so,
because I feel like I was pretty clear.
Yes, I was, wasn't I?
Mama was so clear.
(CHUCKLES)
Hey, that make you wanna try for a third?
Hey, um, what if I think
I know who did it?
STAN: Could file a report.
Oh, can I do that with you?
Yeah, sure.
Come on down to the station.
Super.
STAN: Yeah.
I just might do that.
Come on, now.
Let's bring it home!
Come on, let's go!
(SPECTATORS CHEERING)
Well, it was really nice
to meet you, Officer.
You too.
All right, let's go, come on.
STAN: Wait, your diaper bag.
Gonna need that before the day's over.
(CHUCKLES)
Thank you.
Come on.
Ooh, she is an odd bird.
You have no idea.
What does Minions
mac and cheese taste like?
Mac and cheese.
What about Ninja Turtles?
So...
(DOOR OPENS)
We gotta pay her. Now.
Before she ruins my damn life.
What are you talking about?
Mary Pat.
She showed up to Sara's soccer game
and threatened to tell Stan.
Wait, what?
What?
Yeah, and if she tells him,
he's not gonna look the other way.
He's not Dean.
No, he's a good person.
RUBY: He's a cop, you guys.
He'll leave me so fast
he'll leave tread marks.
Then we've gotta get her her money.
How? I'm working seven days a week,
doubles and graveyards,
and I still can't afford
all the multiple genres of lawyers.
You don't have to tell me.
I hate to Say it...
Wow.
Hmm?
What else are we gonna do?
I'm just surprised that you wanna rob
something again.
I don't want to.
But you don't not want to.
I want to stay ahead of a bad situation,
and I'm not just talking
about the Mary Pat thing.
Every cent I saved went towards those
damn hospital bills.
BETH: Exactly.
And my mortgage is paid now,
but what about next month?
So, what are we talking about here?
I was thinking
something kind of low stress,
like a 7-Eleven.
I can get behind that.
Except for the one on Lynwood,
because I got him to sponsor the school.
Good for you.
Well, I'm out.
You're out?
It's just not a good time for me
to get back into crime.
Well, can we sync up iCals
so I know when is?
(GROANS) I'm facing a felony drug charge.
I gotta keep a low profile.
Well, you bitches
didn't ask me if I wanted
to kidnap a dude.
That's true.
It's different.
(CELL PHONE CHIMES)
Well, now it's my turn,
and I ain't asking.
Come on!
(SIGHS)
You know what all this is?
No.
'Cause your principal says
that you and some girls shoplifted this
and tried to sell it at lunch.
Hey, eyes up here.
STAN: Is that true?
No, I...
Uh-uh.
The other girls...
Nope.
I didn't...
Try again.
Will you please let her speak?
Well? Speak.
It's not mine.
Then how did this box
end up in your locker?
She said it wasn't hers.
So it just magically appeared?
Harry-Potter style?
Well, not all of it's mine.
Damn it.
Uh-uh.
Keep talking.
Kendall sells the makeup.
Madison does the candy.
And I...
I move the fidget spinners.
You stole fidget spinners?
She moved them, Stan.
Our child moves the fidget spinners.
All right.
Easy now.
Our child speaks
the language of the streets.
Why?
Baby, why would you do that?
The other girls do it all the time.
RUBY: So, if they jumped off
a high-rise, you would do it?
Ran across a busy freeway?
Mom.
Robbed a bank?
Okay. Okay.
Just because other girls do crazy,
stupid-ass stuff,
doesn't make it okay.
You wouldn't do those things,
so why in the hell would you do this?
They used to make fun
of the oxygen tank weirdo.
Now they don't.
I'm dope.
Stealing doesn't make you dope, Sara.
It just makes you a dope.
She's right.
You ain't dope.
Now go to your bedroom.
I need to talk to your mom.
Now.
(SIGHS)
You really need to get a hold of yourself,
you're scaring her.
Good.
Babe,
she messed up, okay? Agreed.
She didn't just mess up.
She's a criminal.
Strong word.
Right word.
I'm just saying,
you know, we gotta keep
a level head here.
You're a cop, for God's sake.
Yeah, and before that,
I was mall security
and I saw kids do this stuff all the time.
Okay? It's just a phase, baby.
Phases become habits,
habits become problems.
And then suddenly our little girl's giving
handies on the street
for a fidget spinner.
Oh, my God.
You gotta breathe.
Okay?
Just, with me, now.
Take a deep breath.
(BREATHES DEEPLY)
She's gotta return everything. All of it.
No doubt.
Apologize to the store owner.
She'll do that.
Write letters to the teachers.
She's gonna wash the dishes
for at least a month, maybe six.
She's gonna do the leaves.
We will do whatever it takes, just...
Yeah.
We will do whatever it takes.
Yeah, we will.
Oh, hi.
MAN: (ON TV)
Who is it?
It's carol singers!
(CHRISTMAS CAROL PLAYING ON TV)
It's a CD on a boombox.
It doesn't even sound like real carolers.
Just suspend your disbelief.
Not to state the obvious here, but, uh,
you're aware that's
your best friend's wife, right, dude?
Mom.
What?
I'm just saying.
Extremely wonderful cue cards or not,
he's a scumbag, and he shouldn't be
hitting on her.
Well, I mean, she's not innocent, either.
She kisses him.
You guys are maybe the worst people
to watch a movie with.
I'm gonna go do homework.
(HESITATES)
(SONG CONTINUES)
(SIGHS)
How you been?
Fine. You?
Fine.
Great.
What's new at work?
Nothing much.
Got me peeing into a cup.
That sucks.
Yeah.
Hey, you know what else sucks?
Hmm?
Supervised visits with my own child.
It's not my fault.
(SCOFFS)
Nothing ever is, is it?
Look, if you wanna talk about it,
we should just talk about it.
Mmm. What do you wanna talk about, Gregg?
You know what I! wanna talk about.
I wanna talk about what happened.
If you wanna talk about it,
let's talk about it like adults.
(SCOFFS) Please.
Why start now?
Because this is...
(CHUCKLES)
Hey.
(CLEARS THROAT)
Oh, my God!
Did you get to the cue card scene yet?
Ugh, I love that part.
(CHUCKLES)
I bet you do.
Yeah, apparently it's quite controversial.
Really?
Yeah.
Oh, I wish I didn't have to go to work.
Ugh! Is there a zit only you can pop?
(CHUCKLES)
Actually, we just opened
a third location. It's crazy.
But I love helping women
feel good about themselves.
So, If you want,
I could help you with
that little divot in your
forehead there, just...
(MIMICS POP)
One shot.
(CHUCKLES)
I'm good.
NANCY: Okay.
Oh, actually, um...
Do you mind not leaning
all the way back on the couch?
Sorry, I know it's weird.
It's just, um, your...
your hair oils, they tend to get
on the pillows.
I'm sorry?
I noticed it last week
when you were here.
It's this...
It's this stupid fabric.
It is impossible to clean.
(PATS COUCH) Yeah.
Normally, I would...
I would never say anything, it's just...
the covers and the shams,
they're... they're new.
It's just 'cause they're new.
NANCY: Yeah, we just bought them.
Mmm.
Okay, well, have so much fun, you guys.
Mmm-hmm.
I love you, Mister Man.
(CHUCKLES) Ooh...
(SIGHS)
(CHUCKLES)
"I love you too!"
Okay.
(CHUCKLES)
Bye.
(SIGHS)
(KNOCKING ON DOOR)
Do you know what time it is?
It's showtime, baby.
Hey, have you ever heard of hair oils?
Is that, like, a thing that people say?
I mean, it's definitely not, right?
What is going on?
We're not robbing no 7-Eleven.
RUBY: You wanna hit a day spa?
She just opened a third location.
And I'm telling you,
these places are flush.
Can't find your K-Cups.
Maybe it's the universe
saying you've had enough.
(GASPS)
(SINGING)
Dark magic!
You Know!
So, won't Nancy see us?
No. I signed her up
to be Sadie's chaperone on a field trip.
So, okay, check it.
All three mall locations
have the exact same layout.
So, I figure we split up
and we hit them all simultaneously.
You know, just like boom, boom, boom!
Hang on, Boom, boom, boom.
What happened to
"I have a felony drug charge"?
Well, if we don't use guns,
is it even really a crime?
Yeah.
Or...
is ita gentle redistribution of wealth?
Plus, Nance has it coming.
So, wait. How do we
get past security if we don't have guns?
These places don't have security.
They don't even have cameras.
No cameras?
It's a Spa.
Everybody's naked, yo.
So?
So, I was thinking more along the lines
of an ATM.
But...
suck it, Nance!
Suck it, Nance!
(ALTERNATIVE SONG PLAYING)
(INAUDIBLE)
So, where do they keep the cash?
Everybody pays with credit cards.
How do we get the money?
Oh, we're not going after the money.
(SONG CONTINUES)
(SONG ENDS)
Smooth, right?
Like taking candy from a baby.
Okay, where's Annie?
(TIRES SQUEALING)
(GLASS VIALS CLINKING)
AUTOMATED FEMALE VOICE:
Please insert ticket.
(PRESSING BUTTON)
I did insert my ticket, you dick.
What the...
(LINE RINGING)
Come on. Come on.
Yeah, hi, your machine
ate my ticket and I need to leave.
MAN: (ON RECORDING)
You have reached the parking office.
No one Is available to take your call.
(SIGHS) Oh, God.
(LINE RINGING)
She's not answering.
Come on, Annie.
(VIBRATING)
You're insane.
All I'm saying is I don't get the hype.
But it's objectively good.
You can't say
something is objectively good.
(WOMAN SIGHS)
At least Miss Saigon had a helicopter.
Oh, my God.
It's a million songs at a desk.
Wha... What?
I'm at a desk, yo, and I'm writing, yo.
I gotta...
(BOTH SCREAM)
ANNIE: Roll it down!
Come on!
Please don't hurt us.
We don't have any cash.
I need your parking ticket.
BOTH: What?
(SHOUTS) Give me your parking ticket!
WOMAN: Okay, okay.
ANNIE: Come on, hurry up!
WOMAN: Right there.
ANNIE: Hurry! Hurry up!
All right, now,
put your head between your legs,
and count to ten!
BOTH: Okay.
ANNIE: No, make it 20.
BOTH: (WHIMPERING) Okay.
BOTH: One, two, three...
(SIGHS)
What'd you do?
Stop for burgers?
What are you, the punctuality police?
Jesus. Come on, let's just pool the loot.
Here.
DARREN: Yo, A-Dawg.
(BICYCLE APPROACHING)
(TIRES SCREECH)
That's your connection?
He looks like
he just came from S.A.T. prep.
ANNIE: Chill, it's all been arranged.
'Sup, D-Man?
These are my colleagues.
(SOFTLY) Yo.
BETH AND RUBY: Yo.
So? What do you got?
Before we talk business,
I got a question.
How rich is rich enough for you?
Depends.
What are we talking, like, 401k-rich?
Asset rich? Cash rich?
Mmm. Give me the dream.
(SIGHS) Oh, man.
Okay, well, uh...
Place on Nantucket with a catamaran.
ANNIE: Mmm.
Couple of show dogs, you know.
Pimping hard like Larry Ellison.
You know?
Tight. Tight.
We'd like to help you get there.
Hell yeah.
What I got in here
is more addictive than Oxy.
Costs more per ounce
than Bolivia's finest,
and is as pure as a glacier stream.
Feast your eyes.
(VIALS CLINKING)
What... What am...
What am I Supposed to do with this?
Move it, baby.
I can't sell this junk.
Wait. What?
Okay. Look, my...
my clientele
isn't really into, um, personal upkeep.
I thought you talked to him, Annie.
I thought it was prearranged.
It was. Uh, Darren,
I'm not understanding
what's changed since our convo
in the frozen foods aisle,
'cause you were in.
You said injectables.
These are injectables.
I thought you meant heroin.
(SCOFFS)
Oh, no.
Look, I... I wish I could help you.
Just...
You know, the cosmetic stuff, not my jam.
Just sell allergy medication to
people without allergies!
Yeah, they use it to make meth.
This shiz is medical-grade.
People are gonna pay top dollar.
I'm really sorry for the miscomm.
Oh, my God!
(SCOFFS)
Is this gonna make things weird
between us at work?
Yeah, maybe.
(SIGHS)
Well, um, nice meeting you guys.
I'm just gonna...
(CLEARS THROAT)
Bye.
RUBY: What are we gonna do?
We still owe that bitch 8Gs.
I! wonder how much we can get for it.
30, maybe 40 grand.
We got nothing 'cause we can't unload it.
So we hit a snag.
"Don't worry.
Done deal.
Piece of cake."
What am I leaving out?
"Easy peasy."
I would never say
"easy peasy."
So sue me, I didn't Know I'd come down
to drug-dealer semantics.
There is a difference
between injectables and injecting heroin.
Well, this is how we learn.
I can't believe you made us do this
for nothing.
ANNIE: Oh, I made you?
That's rich, coming from you,
Miss I I-Ain't-Askin'.
And you, with your judgy face
that I can feel from here,
I cannot.
'Cause we all know
that this month has been killing you.
It has not.
Oh...
You've been crawling out of your skin
like a frog in a slow boil, baby.
She's not wrong.
Oh, great. You too?
Pile it on.
Oh, it's all so banal,
the P.T.A., the playdates, the yoga.
Each day, the flame grows
a little hotter.
She's been missing that hood life!
(SCOFFS) Right?
Peace.
Whoa, whoa, wait, you're just gonna
leave us here with this?
You know what?
I did my part.
You handle this.
(RUBY SIGHS)
(DOOR OPENS)
(DOOR CLOSES)
Wait, wait, wait, you're leaving too?
I gotta haul Sara's fast ass
down to the station
and scare her straight.
Why?
'Cause that little heifer
has been slinging stolen fidget spinners
on the playground.
Sara?
Like mother like daughter, I guess.
Hey, you know that's not the reason why.
Yeah, right.
Love you.
(DOOR OPENS)
OFFICER DENISE:
So, you just want me to
scare her a little, right?
I want you to put the fear of God in her.
Cuff her, tase her,
pepper spray, whatever it takes.
(CHUCKLING)
I'm dead-serious.
Look, I get it.
I worry about my kid, too.
She's gonna be fine.
You guys are great parents.
She has good role models.
Yeah, right.
You ready to see how this works?
Do I have to?
She's ready.
You like bunk beds, Sara?
Oh, she's been begging us for bunk beds.
Ain't that right?
I want you to think of this
as an opportunity
to grow during the downtime.
A chance to really
flip your game in a way that,
if it's not completely legal,
it is totally F.D.A.-approved.
Mmm-hmm.
This is essentially liquid money.
I mean, it's literally liquid, but...
It's garbage.
This stuff's poison.
Not any more so than the substances
your guys deal.
Who would I even sell it to?
Don't you know someone?
That rolls with a bunch of
middle-aged ladies?
Nah, man, not so much.
(CHUCKLES)
How's your rotten egg?
I don't know what you're talking about.
You said you handled it.
I did.
Then why you trying to play me
with this side-hustle stuff?
I told you we're shut down.
(PLACES VIAL ON TABLE)
And I told you I have expenses.
I have four children, a mortgage.
I can't just shut down.
Whoa, whoa, whoa.
She got you on the hook now, right?
I said I'm handling it!
Okay. (CHUCKLES)
You think you're a boss now, huh?
Your lily ass does two jobs,
and all of the sudden,
you think you run the whole game?
Let me tell you something,
you ain't no boss.
And on the real,
you ain't gonna be nothing
till you get your house in order.
And you best not
put that stuff in your face.
You don't need it.
(DOOR OPENS)
OFFICER DENISE:
When you're in my house,
you mind your business.
You're sharing your space
with gangbangers, murderers,
people you don't wanna mess with,
let alone sleep next to.
So, they just put everyone in
all together?
There's not like
a separate white-collar cell?
One big melting pot.
You okay, Mom?
Yeah, you know, it's just hot in here.
You got chow at 7:00,
clean up at 7:30,
and then you gotta shower.
And what does she shower in?
A group.
You make a circle,
then rotate under the shower head.
No, I meant, like, shower shoes?
Your shoes are your shower shoes.
You don't wanna get them wet?
You take your chances with the fungi.
And don't expect hot water, neither.
And what if she has to, um, use the...
There's your bathroom,
your kitchen,
your sink,
everything.
Wait. So, people
just go right there, like,
in front of everybody?
Even number...
All the numbers.
(RETCHES)
And most of the time,
there won't be toilet paper.
Okay. Thank you, Denise, but...
I think...
I think she gets it.
There are things you can do for a square,
but you don't wanna.
Yeah, well, we really need to get home.
You're home with me, ladies.
(LAUGHS NERVOUSLY)
Welcome home.
Okay, we gotta get out of here.
No can do.
It's not rec time.
Oh, my God, let me out of here!
(BANGS CELL DOOR)
(KEYBOARD CLACKING)
Hey.
How was your day?
Has our credit rebounded enough
to qualify for a loan?
Well, we put a dent
in our debt, that's for sure.
Yes or no?
No.
(INHALES SHARPLY)
Look, I Know you don't wanna tell me
what's going on...
I need cash. Fast.
How much?
10 grand.
Does that have anything to do with
the many vials of liquid hashish
I just saw in the garage?
It's not liquid hashish.
Oh. Well...
(CLEARS THROAT)
What is it, then?
(KEYBOARD CLACKING)
Why don't you let me help you?
I don't know that you can.
Maybe not.
But what do you got to lose?
Mr. Boland, I don't have you down
for an appointment today.
Hey, got a minute?
I'm with a patient.
It's slow-growing.
You'll be fine.
How's that Buick treating you?
Fine.
(VIALS CLINKING)
You know any dermatologists?
(CRYING)
I can't believe it was all three.
You know, like, I would get it if it was
just one, you know, but...
Oh, God.
You know, I'm just...
Hey.
Want some more water?
(SOBBING)
I'm just...
What are we gonna do?
I mean, 'cause I just...
Oh, no, um...
Of course. Yeah.
Sure. Um...
Thank you for letting me know.
Yeah, you too.
Okay, bye.
(SNIFFLES)
Sorry. I was just gonna...
You okay?
Yeah, I'm fine.
(SIGHS)
I mean, your insurance
is gonna cover it, right?
What are you talking about?
Sadie told me you got robbed.
(SCOFFS) That's, like, the least of it.
Do I look like a total raccoon right now?
No.
You look great.
My God, it's like...
Ugh, it's these hormones.
I'm, like, shooting up like a junkie.
And for nothing,
because apparently,
I only make these, like,
crappy unicorn embryos
with, like, horns or something.
How long have you been trying?
Ugh, this is, like,
our fourth round, or like, fifth.
I honestly...
I can't even keep track.
It's been so...
And I literally cannot stop crying.
I can't... (SOBBING)
Stop, stop, stop!
(SIGHS)
You're blocking me in.
You're leaving?
Why did you tell me
to get extra anchovies?
God!
You're a dick.
What?
Just move your car.
All right?
Whoa, what the hell's wrong with you?
How long have you been doing I.V.F.?
Oh, God.
Yeah.
(STAMMERS)
I was gonna tell you.
When? Mid-bone?
(GROANS) Gross.
You were having sex with me
while your wife was
injecting herself full of baby hormones.
I didn't plan on it.
Obviously, it just kind of...
happened.
You were there.
No.
A solar eclipse just happens.
Two people decide
to sleep with each other.
What am I supposed to do,
leave her and marry you?
We tried that, it didn't work, remember?
What do you want me to do, Annie?
I want you to move your car.
(SIGHS)
MARY PAT:
Door's open! Come in!
Okay, guys, 10 more minutes, okay?
And then it's homework time.
(BABY FUSSING)
Hey.
Is it all there this time?
It's all there.
Can you hand...
Thanks.
I'm not an evil person. Okay?
Okay.
It's just, um, Jeff left me with, like,
a mountain of debt, so...
I have literally nothing to lose.
Now you do.
(BABY CRYING)
If we get caught, you're going down, too.
I think it's called an accessory.
So why are you doing it?
Same reason.
You sure about that?
(BABY CONTINUES CRYING)
Have you ever heard the theory
that they always
look like daddy when they're born?
Some caveman evolution thing,
so men know it's theirs
and they don't leave.
Well, this one's Jeff's twin, So...
All four of mine looked
exactly like Dean.
Go figure.
(BABY CONTINUES CRYING)
BOY: Stop it!
Mom, he hit me!
MARY PAT:
Boys, homework!
I swear to God!
Well, you've got your hands full.
Hey, listening ears,
you wanna put them on?
It's like I'm not even here.
Imagine if you were in prison.
Hey, Beth?
I'll see you next month.
(TELEPHONE RINGING)
(INDISTINCT RADIO CHATTER)
So, uh, hey,
you think it worked?
She got her wake-up.
Yeah?
(CHUCKLING)
Well, I'll tell you what.
Ooh!
Listen. If she is half the woman
that I got in front of me right now,
she's gonna be something else.
(PHONE RINGING)
Will...
Will you chill?
You are at work.
What? Come on, we undercover.
We undercover.
Ain't nobody watching.
(CHUCKLING)
What's that?
Oh, the guys are just busting my chops.
I mean, who's the boy?
Oh.
It's that fool we arrested.
RUBY: That's him?
STAN: Mmm-hmm.
He's young.
Yeah, he's dumb, too.
He's ours, now.
What does that mean?
He's part of some gang
that the feds got their eye on,
and, uh, we put him to work
for the good guys.
Cool. Very cool.
That's right.
It's all 'cause of your man.
DEAN: Hey, uh, you mind
if I use the shower?
Kenny's got, like,
a million action figures in the tub,
and I keep stepping on them.
Sure.
Thanks.
I'll be...
I'll be quick, I promise.
Hey.
How'd you unload all that stuff?
Friend of a friend.
Not gonna tell me, huh?
No, I am not.
I probably deserve that.
You don't deserve anything I did to you.
(SIGHS)
We wash counterfeit money for a gang.
We buy stuff with fake cash
and return it for real.
We get 12%.
But I'm gonna ask for 15%
when we're up and running again,
because we're smart,
and we work hard, and we deserve it.
(SCOFFS)
Do you think I'm insane?
I think you're incredible.
(DOORBELL RINGS)
I'm gonna...
(SOBBING)
(SLOW POP SONG PLAYING)
(DOOR OPENS)
They have him!
What?
The kid...
The gangbanger.
The one bleeding up in Emma's room.
Who has him?
The cops.
The F.B.1.
And he's talking.
He is talking to them.
Wait, what?
Oh, my God, you guys,
there's... there's no toilet paper.
And... and you have to
go right there in front of everyone.
Oh, my God!
The place is literally for animals.
Oh, and drink up,
because jail wine...
(GAGS)
Jail wine is brewed in a toilet
with ketchup and bread.
Bread?
Bread is where I threw you?
The toilet you're good with?
The toilet I understand
because have to have
somewhere to put the...
Bread is yeast, so it ferments.
We have to tell Rio.
You don't think he knows?
That his boy is talking to the F.B.1.?
No way!
If we tell him, he'll kill him.
I mean, right?
That's how they do.
Okay, SO we don't tell Rio.
No, we do.
We have to.
It's that kid or us.
(SONG CONTINUES PLAYING)