SARA: Girls today can be anything.
CEO, Olympic golden medalist,
even a Supreme Court Justice.
We've finally broken that glass ceiling
and, wow, it sure looks good
from the top.
(POP SONG PLAYING)
(GIGGLES, SQUEALS)
KENNY: Stop!
Hey, go brush your teeth.
Wipe her face.
Did you find your homework?
And you, my little friend,
you need pants.
Mom, can! stay home from school today?
Nobody's staying home.
I feel sick.
What hurts?
My spleen.
Specificity is good,
but that's over the top.
Next time, try "tummy."
It's go time. Let's go.
Okay, everyone's going to school.
Mommy has something important to do.
AMBER ON TV: Oh, look.
KENNY: Guys, look.
Daddy's on TV again.
AMBER: So what are you waiting for?
A pig to fly?
All right, let's go.
Line up.
Train's a-leavin'.
Bye.
Love you. Love you.
Bags in the back.
Love you.
Tuna fish. Keep it in the fridge.
SADIE: Stop, stop, stop! Mom!
ANNIE: You make your dad
drop you off all the way back here?
I don't know.
What's the girlfriend drive?
Porsche Turbo.
(MIMICS RETCHING)
Oh! I'm so sorry.
Did you need this?
(ANNIE GIGGLES)
Love you, Sadie.
Can I have lunch money?
Ugh, come on.
Did those kids take it again?
God, those douchebags.
That was a $20.
Well, small price to pay
for the bone structure of my face.
That's very true.
I don't wanna leave you without cash.
Excuse me, who is the adult here?
Don't answer that.
So, why aren't there
any of these awesome women
in my history book, huh?
I'll tell you why.
Sister made the mistake
of getting her period.
They say, "Behind
every great man, there's a great woman."
Well, I say that's some bull right there.
Well, none of these
nasty women I just told you about
stood behind men.
(MIMICS POP)
They stood right beside them.
So, we gotta
get it done ourselves, ladies.
Am I right?
You get it, girl!
You get it!
We're gonna burn this patriarchy down!
Whoo!
(LIGHTER CLICKING)
Ain't nobody gonna stop her?
(CHUCKLES NERVOUSLY) Okay.
Okay, I'm out of here.
What's going on?
You got an early shift?
Um...
I figured, you know,
we could use the extra.
Mmm, I figured the same thing,
'cause I'm about to
pull a double at the mall.
I'll make it work.
You always do, boo.
I do.
(POP SONG CONTINUES PLAYING)
(TIRES SCREECHING)
I cannot believe you.
Chill, sis. I'm, like, two minutes late.
(SIGHS)
How was Sara's thing?
Oh, she was so good.
She's so smart.
I worry about mine.
(CHUCKLES)
Stop it.
All right.
Y'all ready for this?
(SIGHS)
Now or never.
Let's do it.
ANNIE: All right!
Everybody be cool, and nobody gets hurt!
Ladies and gentlemen, this is a robbery!
Oh, my Lord!
(WAX STRIP RIPPING)
(EXHALES)
Maybe we don't have to do
the full Brazilian.
A Brazilian would put you in the hospital.
This is just brush control.
Yeah, I probably don't get in here
as much as I used to.
(SARCASTICALLY) No.
My husband and I aren't having
a lot of S-E-X right now.
Maybe he just can't find it.
Kids are back to school.
I'm swamped.
He's always working late.
Plus, there's so much on the DVR,
it's really kind of hard to schedule...
(WAX STRIP RIPPING)
Ow! Okay!
Mrs. Boland?
Your card was declined.
Are you sure?
I ran it twice.
I'm sure he just forgot to pay the bill.
He's been very distracted lately.
Hey, there.
Amber here,
over at Boland Motors.
(KISSING)
We've got Chevys.
We've got Fords.
We've got Chryslers, too.
(MOUTHING)
Have we got the car for you?
Do you think I could make it in L.A.?
DEAN: Mmm.
Mmm-hmm.
It's not like Michigan.
They have really good actresses there.
You're gonna win
one of those fancy awards.
Like a People's Choice.
I don't need all that.
I just wanna be super famous.
AMBER ON TV:
So, come on down to Boland Motors,
where we'll put the vroom, vroom, vroom
back into your engine.
Annie Bananie.
Hey, you, uh...
You got any plans later?
My church is having
a "Bring a Friend" night.
You know, I'm just not really
much of a church person.
You're definitely a stuck-up bitch.
(CHUCKLING)
I'm just kidding you.
Now, see, the old me totally
would've meant that,
but, you know,
born-again Boomer don't judge.
This, uh, came
from your register last night.
Know what it is?
Hmm. This is a tough one.
It's a curling iron?
We in the biz say "counterfeit."
Now, see, I Know it's counterfeit
because I use the pen.
Did you use the pen?
Boomer, I don't remember if I...
I'm guessing you didn't,
because if you had,
you would have known it's counterfeit.
Which is why we have the pen.
So, unfortunately,
I'm gonna have to dock this
from your paycheck.
Whoa, whoa. Wait.
Boomer, that's, like,
a whole shift for me.
Well, maybe next time
you'll take security more seriously.
Oh, come on.
What security?
(SIGHS)
(PEOPLE SPEAKING INDISTINCTLY)
(MAN COUGHING)
RUBY: Excuse me,
how much longer is the wait?
'Cause we've been...
DOCTOR: What I'm most concerned about
right now
is Stella's kidney function.
Sara.
What?
You said "Stella."
Her name's Sara.
Okay. So, what about her kidneys?
(EXHALES) One is failing.
The other one's right behind.
I would suggest that
we put Sara on a list for a transplant
as soon as possible.
Carla, you just can't
throw files like this.
CARLA: We just got 10 walk-ins.
I've been doing some reading.
Okay.
'Cause she can barely make it through
the school day right now.
DOCTOR: It's all willy-nilly over there.
She can barely...
Okay? No.
...make it through the day,
let alone soccer.
You might wanna
keep her home and get a tutor.
Are those last week's blood draws?
Well, my husband and I
work all the time...
Here, Carla.
...SO we Can't.
And...
DOCTOR: Take them all away.
And the transplant lists
can take months, right?
DOCTOR: Separate.
Thank you.
And there's this new drug...
DOCTOR: Thank you.
...that just got approved...
Take everything out.
Oh, my God!
Can you please
just listen to me for one damn minute?
Shame on you.
Shame on all of you. (CRYING)
(SIGHS) Eculizumab.
That's the name of the drug
you're talking about?
Yes.
It does.
It improves renal function dramatically.
It's also 10 grand a month out of pocket.
And I'm guessing
that may not be an option.
Well, I'll talk to my husband.
We might be able to swing it.
Okay.
BETH: And she was only
halfway through my wax.
So, what happened?
Well, now I'm very uneven.
RUBY: I don't even wanna know.
(CHUCKLES)
Dean maxed out their credit card at
some lingerie store.
Do you think he's sleeping around?
Don't nobody want Dean.
It's a Christmas gift.
BETH: In October?
Maybe it's your anniversary present.
He already gave me
100 coupons to Bed, Bath & Beyond.
Ew. Really?
Son of a bitch.
No, I really do love it there.
No. That old guy is stealing your tip.
He can't even walk.
Go get it.
(RUBY SIGHS)
Shady S.0.B.!
Huh? Mmm-hmm.
RUBY: Shady.
At my old job, we got robbed all the time.
So I got the sixth sense now.
Are you serious?
I mean, it's no big deal.
All the stores I work at
eventually get hit.
You could get shot.
Ugh. One can hope.
These guys, they don't wanna
hurt anybody.
They just want the money.
So we let them have it.
Nobody's trying to be a hero.
Do they get caught?
(SCOFFS) Yeah, the dumb ones do.
'Cause they park
in the front by the security cameras.
You gotta put your getaway car
in the back by the loading dock.
And you never
dick around with the registers.
The real money is back in the vault.
You've really worked this out.
I'm just keeping my options open.
How much is in the vault?
30 grand, give or take.
Damn, I could use that money.
Oh, my God. Me, too.
So, when you wanna do this?
Well, I already bought three automatics
and filed off the serial numbers.
SO, really, name a day.
(LAUGHS)
You should see your face.
It's whiter than usual.
(ANNIE AND RUBY LAUGH)
ANNIE: I'm gonna
need you to all get on the ground!
Get your cell phones out of your pockets,
and keep your hands where I can see them.
All right, good.
Now, I need you to get
your manager up here.
I said you need to get a manager
up here right now.
Hey! Where's y'all's boss at?
(ANNIE GROANS)
(SHOUTING) All right.
Better get a manager up here right now
or I will start Capping people!
I'm not even joking, mother...
(PEOPLE SCREAMING)
You the manager?
Over there.
Hey.
Hey, you. You.
You, squirmy.
Hey. Hey. Hey.
(WHIMPERING)
Are you in charge here?
(STAMMERING)
Yes. Yes, I am.
BETH: Okay, then, you listen to me.
You're gonna put on your big-boy panties,
and you're gonna tell your customers
to stay calm,
and this will be over real soon.
ANNIE: Get out of there.
Everybody stay calm, okay?
Now, you're gonna take
my friend here to the cash vault.
Move it before I shoot your face off!
Let's go!
Now! Now! Now!
BETH: Oh, my God.
Hey, Deadpool, you wanna...
Ugh.
Seriously?
You won't call me back.
I was busy.
So, here I am.
Well, I'm pretty sure
I'm supposed to be helping customers,
not chatting with my ex, So...
So, now I'm a customer.
Nancy and I are
suing you for custody.
(SCANNER BEEPS)
Club card?
There's a hearing next month.
You should probably get yourself a lawyer.
You know, if you sign up now,
you get 10% off your purchase.
Annie, we were 17
when we decided all this stuff.
Sadie would be happier with us now.
How do you figure, Gregg?
We could send her to private school.
St. Anne's.
She's an atheist
who enjoys a jaunty bow tie.
I don't really think that Catholic school
is a good fit.
We could get her therapy.
She doesn't need therapy.
She's figuring out who she is.
Yeah, that's all great,
but she's getting bullied, Annie.
Yes, by dickhead kids that need therapy.
Who's watching her now?
It's after midnight.
The neighborhood girl.
She's very good.
The one who got the DUI?
She lives within walking distance.
Buy her a new computer.
Hers has been broken for a month.
Well, why didn't she tell me that?
Because she said she didn't wanna
freak you out.
ANNIE: Why is it SO crazy?
I mean, it's a victimless crime.
The store is insured.
Plus, you know they make us work
through lunch?
So it's basically tit for tat
when you figure in the lost wages.
Oh, that'll hold up in court.
Hey, no pop before dinner, sweetie.
But she gets it.
That's because I am a grown-up.
Technically.
Okay. You know, can't you
just have my back on,
like, one thing ever?
This isn't me telling
Mom and Dad that you smoked pot.
Which was incredibly lame, by the way.
This is me helping you
not ruin your life.
Oh, because your life is So great.
I should want this life?
I didn't say that.
You're, like, this Stepford mom
without a pulse.
I never said that.
You're cutting chicken fingers
into stars.
They're already fingers.
And, I mean,
not to pile on, but look who you married.
It's 20 years and 4 children.
Marriage sometimes takes a little work.
(SMACKS LIPS) Wow.
That is so romantic.
You could lose your daughter.
Has that occurred to you?
Well, seeing as Gregg is
suing me for custody
and I can't afford to fight it,
yes, actually.
The thought has crossed my mind.
I didn't know.
Now you know.
Hey, there. Amber here,
over at Boland Motors.
Jeez. Who'd this chick
have to blow to get on TV? (SCOFFS)
So what are you waiting for?
A pig to fly?
So, come on down to Boland Motors,
where we'll put the vroom, vroom, vroom
back into your engine.
Is your babysitter free?
Mmm. They took away her license.
She's always home.
It's this charge right here.
Could you just tell me
exactly what was bought?
It's against policy to divulge information
on previous purchases,
for privacy concerns.
Oh, but it's on her bill, so...
Then she should remember what she bought.
Well, I remember that I bought it
for a friend.
And she loved it so much,
she really went nuts for it. Um...
But then, she was in an accident.
With a driver.
Texting.
Yeah. Well, it was
the other driver texting,
not my friend.
She would never do that.
But, anyway, she's been in
a coma ever since,
and her brain is,
like, 10 times the size it should be.
Um, I just thought,
"Wouldn't it be a nice gesture,
if she wakes up..."
Hey. When she wakes up.
Stay positive.
Yeah.
"...to have her
favorite pair of undies waiting."
'Cause she was actually wearing
the last pair
when she got in the accident.
Mmm-hmm. Mmm-hmm.
And the paramedics had to
cut them off of her,
you know, jaws-of-life style.
Darn it, if I cannot remember
the size that I got.
And I obviously
feel stupid asking her family.
Mmm. Can't do that.
So could you just look it up?
Okay. Just give me one second, please.
Damn. That was a good sell.
This is So crazy.
It's obviously gonna be
something for you.
Here it is.
This was it?
Okay. Yeah, that's...
probably not for you.
ANNIE: Okay.
It's gonna be okay.
We're gonna have a drink.
Oof, we're gonna have 10 drinks.
Uh, hey, do you know the difference
between a Manhattan and a sidecar?
I always forget.
Something about the vermouth...
(DOOR OPENS)
...whispering...
RUBY: Hey!
(SHUSHES)
RUBY: Guess who found
those caramel bugles at Kroger?
What is going on?
The Bachelorette is on.
Hello.
(MOUTHING)
Dean is having an affair.
(MOUTHING) What?
(WHISPERING)
Dean is having an affair.
Huh?
(WHISPERING) Dean is...
Son of a bitch.
Oh, honey.
What can we do?
How about a screwdriver?
A sledgehammer.
What?
(GRUNTING)
You planning on stopping this?
Nah. You?
Nah, I'm good.
What is it?
Oh, my God.
What, does he have another ho?
(DOOR OPENS)
(DOOR CLOSES)
(DEAN SIGHS)
(REFRIGERATOR OPENS)
BETH: If you're looking for the vodka,
I drank it.
What are you doing in the dark?
Guess I'm used to it after 20 years.
What does that mean?
It means your child bride wears
very expensive underwear.
What happened to us?
I was stupid.
I was stupid and...
Doesn't even matter.
Why do we have
three mortgages that we haven't paid?
Why do our credit cards
all have advances on them
and we have hardly anything
in our accounts?
Look, I made a few bad decisions at work.
Oh, my God.
I tried to fix it with
a couple of investments
and I should've been...
I should've been more careful.
I just... I panicked.
We have four children.
I Know.
Are we going to lose this house?
Look, I dropped the ball.
That's all.
Are we going to lose the house?
No.
I mean, I don't know.
Maybe.
We might.
We could lose everything.
(CRYING)
I'm so sorry.
We're gonna rob that store.
What?
Yes!
Have you lost your mind?
(POP SONG PLAYING)
RUBY: We were just kidding
about the store, Beth.
Hey, I wasn't.
Well, I was.
Why? You need it just as bad as we do.
We just do it once.
And we get some money.
Oh, dear God.
You get to help your little girl.
And you get to take care
of this custody thing.
And I get to save my family.
And we're done.
We never do it again,
and we don't sit back
and let everything be taken away from us.
No one's gonna fix this.
We have to do this ourselves.
(GRUNTS AFFIRMATIVELY)
(SONG CONTINUES)
RUBY: What is taking so long?
BETH: I don't Know.
(GIRL WHIMPERS)
Hi.
How old are you?
Let me guess. Six?
Do you watch Doc McStuffins?
(CHUCKLES)
Uh, yeah, we, um, used to
watch it in the big house.
ANNIE: Move it, you little weenie!
Ow! Uh, I'm going as fast as I can.
Come on!
Get out of the way!
(ANNIE GRUNTING)
(ROCK SONG PLAYING)
ANNIE: Stay right there!
Holy crap.
We gotta go.
We gotta go!
Oh, shit!
Let's go!
Nope. Turn around!
(SHOUTING INDISTINCTLY)
RUBY: Let's go. Come on!
RUBY: We gotta go!
ANNIE: What?
BETH: Go! Go! Go!
Go, go, go!
Gotta go! We've gotta go.
They're out there.
They're going out the back!
(PANTING)
Get them!
(WHEEZING)
BOOMER:
Get them!
RUBY: Beth?
Hello?
Are you okay in there?
What's your name?
I robbed a grocery store.
RUBY: Who's Secretary of State?
Who is Secretary of State?
We robbed a grocery store.
Oh, we totally did.
And we actually got away with it.
Like some smooth criminals.
(LAUGHS)
Uh, how much did we get?
Please tell me we got the 30.
Uh...
We got it.
(BOTH SIGH)
Thank you, God.
We got more than the 30 grand.
How much more?
(SIGHS)
What in the hell?
How is this even possible?
Count it again.
I counted it right.
Count it again!
You said there would be 30.
I said,
"30, give or take."
I guess it was give.
Why does a grocery store
even have this kind of money on hand?
Because it's hella shady.
I told you this was a bad idea.
ANNIE: You guys are missing the point.
We just won half a million dollars!
We didn't win anything.
Half a mil, bitches!
We didn't win it!
We stole it!
And maybe the cops
don't follow up on $30,000.
They damn sure
follow up on half a million dollars.
What do we do?
Nothing.
We divide it up and we sit on it.
Until we can come up with a way
to get rid of it quietly.
Without looking like, you know...
Criminals.
RUBY: Yeah.
Okay?
Yeah.
Okay.
(CLICKS TONGUE) Okay.
(HIP-HOP SONG PLAYING)
Hey.
What is this?
Turbo S.
You know, it's similar
to the model that douche-face Nancy has.
But more features, more cylinders.
You know, more cooler.
Why don't you check under your seat?
ANNIE: Oh, yeah.
Hmm?
Who are you? Oprah?
You get a laptop, and you get a laptop,
and you get a laptop!
I don't get it.
Uh, how to have fun?
Yes, I can see that.
No. How you have money for all this.
Would you just let me worry about that?
But...
Who is the adult here?
Mom.
Who is the adult?
Who's the adult?
(SIGHS)
Come on.
Let's go tailgate some old people.
(ENGINE REVVING)
Hey, Mrs. Boland.
Nice weather we're having.
Afternoon, Mrs. Boland.
I'm gonna have to call you back.
Uh, Mrs. Boland.
Hi. What are you doing here?
I'm here to clean up a mess, Amber.
What mess?
You. Sit.
Don't worry.
I mostly blame him.
He should know better.
You're obviously stupid.
Oh, it's not a knock.
We all have our strengths and weaknesses.
You're a beautiful dummy.
It doesn't make you a bad person.
So...
here's what's going to happen.
You're going to
quit your job and my husband,
effective immediately.
Trust me, they're both a dead end.
This is 5 grand.
Enough for a plane ticket
and a little to get you started in L.A.
I do wanna warn you
about something, though.
What's that?
Those folks out there,
they take one look at a person like you,
the pretty, the dumb, the self-hating,
and they figure...
"Perfect for porn."
Mrs. Boland?
Why are you doing this?
Because we both deserve
more than a liar in a pig suit.
Me more than you, but still.
That's the nicest thing
that anyone's ever said to me.
Wow.
Really?
Uh, Mr. Boland?
(ENGINE REVVING)
(TIRES SCREECHING)
(LAUGHS)
Whoo!
Oh, no.
(SERENE ORIENTAL MUSIC PLAYING)
Doctor, I know you're busy
and I won't waste your time.
But I've been doing a lot of research here
on different drugs and things.
Just, um...
It has, like, this crazy-ass name.
Um, but I know it's all out of pocket.
Um, you're touching me.
Why are you touching me?
Because you've been here for 10 minutes
and you've barely taken a breath.
(BREATHING DEEPLY)
The new med's a great option.
Definitely worth trying
before we go down the transplant road.
I've got some samples.
We'll start her on it
and see how she does.
In the meantime,
let's doaCT, creatinine clearance
and an ultrasound.
Cover all bases.
Mom.
(INTERCOM CLICKS)
Can we get some water in here, please?
MAN ON INTERCOM:
Yes, of course.
Oh, is cucumber-infused okay?
Oh, my God, yes.
Can I get lemon, too?
(WHISTLES)
(KNOCKING AT DOOR)
Annie Bananie.
You forgot your paycheck.
Lot of money in here.
(CHUCKLES)
Thanks.
Hey.
How did you have the balls to do it?
What, you and the girls
get all get coked up
or something beforehand?
What?
I saw your ass tat.
I don't know what you're talking...
How many chicks have a tramp stamp
that says
"All You Need Is Love"?
It's a very popular song.
Okay.
Well, then, uh,
I guess you won't mind
if I go to the cops then, right?
I mean, if it wasn't you,
I'm Sure you got some explanation
for how you bought all this
on minimum wage.
I didn't say nothing.
The cops came around,
but I didn't tell them.
What do you want?
(BREATH TREMBLING)
You want money?
It's not like that.
What's it like, then?
I got your back.
I'm gonna keep my mouth shut.
Thanks.
I mean, I'm really gonna try.
I am. I...
I hope I can.
(INHALES DEEPLY)
I don't know.
I just get so lonely, and...
Well...
I'm sorry to be crass here, but, uh,
horny...
too.
I just wanna shoot my mouth off.
Talk and talk till I'm...
satisfied.
(BREATH SHAKING)
(BOOMER KISSING)
Can we just get it over with, okay?
Oh, but, hey, hey.
I'm not some wham-bam-thank-you-ma"am.
You know?
I need a little romance.
(SIGHS)
Mom?
Hi, honey.
I thought you were asleep.
And here it is.
Found it.
He lost some change in the couch,
so I was just helping him find it.
Thanks. Thank you.
Yeah, no problem.
Oh, Sadie, honey, this is
my, uh...
Boomer.
I work with him at work.
You know, So...
But he has to go now,
because he was...
He has to...
I have to use the quarters
on the vending machines.
Or maybe fill a meter, too,
you know, to surprise someone.
Hey, that's nice.
Yeah.
Pay it forward or whatever.
(WHISPERS)
Just go.
BOOMER: You know, uh...
since I have all this bus fare now,
I'll probably be back real soon.
(DOOR OPENS AND CLOSES)
Morning.
I'm gonna need the PINs and passcodes
to the accounts.
Mortgage, bank, credit cards.
Uh, it's "2Fast2Furious."
It's the number two.
You know, like the movie?
I Know it's a movie.
That's for all of them?
Yeah.
I handled the mortgage.
But how did you do that?
I handled it because you couldn't.
And this thing that we do
where you bring home the bacon
and I don't ask any questions,
that's...
that's over.
Does that mean we get to stay
in the house?
It means I get to stay
in the house with the kids.
You get to go to a motel.
Your clothes are in the car.
Still no leads on
last week's armed robbery
of Fine & Frugal.
A rep from the local...
You don't think it's weird?
What?
Our GoFundMe page has been up for years.
Some anonymous donor
rolls in now with all that cash?
It's a miracle.
Why question it?
(KIDS LAUGHING)
See this?
I do.
(LAUGHING, CHATTERING INDISTINCTLY)
Our girl's coming back.
Yeah.
Hey. Okay, bruiser.
All right, ease up on him.
You got him.
(SARA GRUNTS)
STAN: Look at you.
(WHINES)
Hey, buddy.
What's wrong?
You need to go potty?
You need to peepee?
Nah, he's good.
(SCREAMS)
We already took him out.
What do you want?
Oh, relax, sweetheart.
I just need you to call
your lady friends over
SO we Can all have...
a little talk.
About what?
Oh, about the money you stole from us.
Yo, this backsplash is dope.
Hey, what's it made out of, marble?
Yo, you ever get any problems with
staining back here?
Like, if you're cooking
a big pot of spaghetti sauce
or something like that?
No, I don't think so.
No?
(CHUCKLES)
We didn't know you owned the store.
I look like some kind of
grocery store manager to you?
Or, like, Rotary Club or something?
No, let's just say that
we got certain arrangements
with some local businesses.
And we help each other out
and whatnot, you know?
Like money laundering for drugs?
(WHISPERS)
I told you it was shady.
Why don't you stop
worrying about my business dealings
and start figuring
how you're gonna pay me my money back.
We can get it back.
Oh, that'd be great.
Most of it.
Sorry, what?
ANNIE: (STAMMERS)
Some of it, for sure.
(SCOFFS)
Oh, what?
Like, you guys didn't spend a dime?
How much, Annie?
I don't know.
I probably spent, like,100...
grand.
BOTH: What?
I'm gonna shoot you myself.
Nah, you just gonna pay me back is all.
And right quick, too.
With interest.
(BREATH SHAKING)
MAN: So, we'll see you real soon, yeah?
You know, you really
got to be careful, ladies.
I mean, with citrus on marble,
like lemon and whatnot,
that stuff will erode like crazy.
KENNY: Why can't Daddy come home?
Your daddy and I love you so much.
And I know it's confusing.
Daddy's gotta stay here
while he and I work on
some grown-up stuff.
You can have whatever candy you want
from the vending machines, okay?
KIDS: Yay!
Hey.
Pick the kids up from school
and bring them straight back here.
Don't go to the park or anywhere.
I can't have the kids here.
I've got, like, one twin bed.
You have to.
You just have to.
What's going on?
I can't tell you.
Wait. Uh, stop.
Are you okay?
Just take care of my babies.
Hey, who wants, uh...
Who wants pizza?
KENNY: I do!
(KIDS CHEER)
I would've picked you up
down the block, but your cell was off.
SADIE: Where's the Porsche?
I sold it.
I had to.
Is that a cassette deck?
What?
And manual roll-down windows?
Yas queen!
Mmm-hmm.
Cloth interior. Nice.
Leather burns your ass.
How did you get to be so awesome?
Don't ride in Porsches.
(DOORKNOB RATTLING)
Who is it?
(RATTLING CONTINUES)
I said, who is it?
STAN: Me.
(SIGHS) Stan!
(LAUGHING)
What the hell are you doing?
I want an alarm system.
And can you please fix the back gate?
I said I would.
Yeah. You said it,
but it just sits there wide open.
Got your bat out.
You know, you could've
gotten the knife out of the drawer, baby.
All right. All right.
I'm sorry. Calm down.
(GROANS) Oh, God.
I'm sorry. You scared?
Your heart's beating.
Come here.
Breathe. Breathe.
What did I tell you?
All this right here is all the security
you need, baby.
Hmm.
You don't need no wiffle bat.
Is that so?
Yeah, that's so,
because your man here, you know...
is no longer gonna be trailing teenagers
at the Great Steak & Fry.
You applied to the police academy?
I did.
Yeah. I didn't tell you
in case I got rejected.
Brother ain't get rejected.
Detroit's finest, baby.
Protect and serve.
Give me some.
BETH: Where are we at?
RUBY: Short.
BETH: By how much?
Over 60 grand.
(SIGHS)
What about the car?
I took it back.
Lost over half its value, B-T-dubs.
Well, maybe you shouldn't have bought it
in the first place.
My, what a helpful contribution!
Let me just grab my time machine.
Oh, my God.
We should just go to the police.
ANNIE: Wait. What?
RUBY: We haven't done
anything that bad yet.
We don't have records.
ANNIE: Uh, yes.
Now we do.
RUBY: If we just explain to them that...
Explain what, that we meant well?
"Gee, Officer, we're sorry.
We didn't mean to piss off the gang.
"We just wanted to rob
the grocery store."
Okay, I'm just trying not to die, okay?
If you have a better plan...
Actually, yes, I do.
We should take it from somewhere else.
We'll just steal it
and then we'll pay them back
and then we'll just
put the whole thing to bed.
Bitch, are you out of your mind?
It's the best possible plan!
BETH: Enough!
Enough!
Enough.
We're gonna get that money.
We're gonna figure it out.
Because we are strong
and we are resourceful.
And we've accomplished
way harder than this.
I once made 300 damn cupcakes
in one night,
and they were both nut- and gluten-free.
Kid still had an allergy attack.
And you don't always have to
fact-check me, okay?
(BETH SIGHS)
I'm gonna take a shower.
I smell like booze and crime.
RUBY: Call you tomorrow.
(FRENCH POP SONG PLAYING)
(SHOWER RUNNING)
(KNOCKING AT DOOR)
(SIGHS) Boomer.
I...
Oh? Bad time?
Very.
Hey, come on.
Don't be rude.
Oh, God. Boomer, you're wasted.
You know, I was just thinking about
how we didn't finish what we started.
Boomer, it's not...
Stop. Stop.
(CHUCKLES) What?
Why don't we just have
a little bit of fun?
Boomer.
Hey, hey. Stop.
My sister is here.
Yeah? Is she hot?
I'll be fast, I promise.
(GRUNTS)
Did you just hit me?
No! No!
(GRUNTING) No!
ANNIE: (GRUNTS)
Stop! No!
You're hurting me!
That's how you like it,
right, tough girl?
Come on.
You're gonna rob a store, right?
Get off of her!
Whoa! Hey.
Hey, hey, easy.
All right. No need to get upset.
All right? No need to get upset.
Oh, do I look upset?
Why would I be upset?
Because every man in the world
thinks he can do whatever he wants
whenever he wants?
Okay, okay. Hey, we were
just having a little bit
of fun. All right?
Oh, was that what that was?
'Cause you see,
when a lady screams "Stop,"
it is usually because
she is not having the time of her life.
But what do I Know?
Now, you're gonna pull up your pants
and you are gonna
get the hell out of here.
Get out!
Is that a...
toy gun?
No.
(SCOFFS)
Yeah, it is.
No, it's not.
Okay, then.
Shoot me, hmm?
(WHIMPERS)
You stupid bitches.
You're going down.
Boomer! Boomer, please.
You need money, right?
We can get you money.
Oh, no, I'm turning you in.
Boomer, please. Please!
You know how fast
they're going to lock you up
and take away your loser kid?
No, Boomer. Please.
Yeah, your dumb-ass sister, too.
The two of you are so done.
You're gonna rot in jail.
Yeah, you think you're so much better
than everyone.
Well, now you are finished.
It is over!
No, please! (SCREAMS)
Ow! (GROANS)
Oh, my God!
(GROANS)
(GASPS)
You...
(WOMEN GASP)
(BOTH SCREAM)
(ANNIE SOBS)
Is he...
He's not.
No.
Are you sure?
(SHUDDERING)
What do we do now?
Well, we're not going to the police.
(FRENCH POP SONG CONTINUES PLAYING)