Previously on Hannibal...
Can I have Carlo slaughter you a hog?
A token of my appreciation
for all that you do for Margot.
Was Will aware of your intention
to get pregnant?
I'm all you have.
Will understands that
Hannibal Lecter can help him.
What Will understands is,
if you can't beat Hannibal,
join him.
Freddie was investigating a story
about Will and Hannibal
committing murders together.
She was a slim and delicate pig.
You slice the ginger.
Among gourmands, the ortolan bunting
is considered a rare
but debauched delicacy.
A rite of passage, if you will.
Preparation calls for the songbird
to be drowned alive in Armagnac.
It is then roasted
and consumed whole in a single mouthful.
Ortolans are endangered.
Who amongst us is not?
I haven't been gorged, drowned,
plucked and roasted.
Not yet.
Traditionally, during this meal,
we are to place shrouds over our heads,
hiding our faces from God.
I don't hide from God.
Bones and all?
Bones and all.
After my first ortolan, I was euphoric.
A stimulating reminder
of our power over life and death.
I was euphoric
when I killed Freddie Lounds.
Tell me, did your heart race
when you murdered her?
No, it didn't.
A low heart rate is a true indicator
of one's capacity for violence.
Your design is evolving.
Your choices affect
the physical structures of your brain.
Killing is changing the way I think.
Yes.
You must understand that blood and breath
are only elements undergoing change
to fuel your radiance.
Just as the source of light is burning.
Orthodontics confirmed.
It's Freddie Lounds.
A little bit of kerosene,
incendiary journalism.
See? No scabrous crust on her chin.
She was dead before the match was struck.
Blood's already pooled
to the lowest parts of her body.
She's been dead at least 24 hours.
Freddie had a longing to be noticed.
She was noticed.
Freddie Lounds' ultimate failing
was her inability to keep herself
out of her own stories.
You know, there's more to this story.
Check it out.
Severely-burned bodies
tend to split along lines of musculature,
but that looks like an incision.
That is right. He cut out her psoas muscles
with what looks like a hunting knife.
A peculiar trophy.
Why did he burn her?
How many people has Freddie Lounds
burned in her career?
Whoever did this was not striking out
against Miss Lounds'
exploitative brand of journalism.
This is something else.
This is something sacred.
Freddie Lounds had to burn.
She was fuel.
Fire destroys and it creates. It is mythical.
She won't rise from the ashes,
but her killer will.
He's the one to be noticed now.
There's no baby.
It isn't even an embryo yet,
but here I am, feeling maternal.
You conspired with your unborn child
to liberate yourself.
You've made Will an unknowing accomplice.
I got what I wanted from Will,
but I didn't understand what I was taking
until the strip turned blue.
I'm not proud of myself.
Nor should you be.
- You said...
- I lied.
Did you know?
I was aware of Margot's goal
of having a child.
I was not aware
you were the means to achieving it.
- What do you want from me?
- Nothing.
Or as much as you'd like to give.
As much as I would like to give?
I always thought men were an optional extra
in childrearing, so...
I'm not opposed to a male influence.
As long as it's not my brother.
He's not good with children.
Come along, children.
What's your name?
Franklin.
Do you like horses, Franklin?
Whoa!
Where do you stay, Franklin?
With Mama and Shirley.
Mama is not your real mama, is she?
She's my foster.
- Do you love Mama and Shirley?
- And Kitty Cat.
And Kitty Cat, yes.
Franklin,
you can't stay there anymore
with Mama and Shirley and Kitty Cat.
You have to go away.
- Who says?
- The government says.
Mama lost her job
and her approval as a foster home.
You can't see her after this week.
You can't see Kitty Cat after this week either.
Why not?
Maybe they just
don't want you anymore, Franklin.
Is there something wrong with you?
There is, isn't there?
Oh, here. Here now.
Here we go.
Can you put your head back?
Just like that. Perfect.
Yes.
Perfect.
Have a chocolate.
Do we do friendly visits anymore?
This isn't a friendly visit.
What kind of visit is it?
I guess I'm trying to
convince myself of something.
You're worried I killed Freddie Lounds.
Did you?
What do you think?
I think that's the wrong answer
to tell somebody
who is already wondering
what you're capable of.
I told everyone Hannibal was a killer,
and no one believed me.
Just like no one would believe you
if you said I was a killer.
I don't think Hannibal is good for you,
and I think your relationship is destructive.
Hannibal's good enough for you.
You should be afraid.
I want you to have something.
Whoever you are afraid of,
don't be afraid to use it.
It takes 9mm rounds.
Buy a box,
find a range.
Practice.
Please.
I would like to tell you about camp.
It was a wonderful childhood experience
that keeps coming back to me.
Papa paid for the whole thing,
every summer,
all 125 campers on Lake Michigan.
Your father was a generous man.
I've continued his charitable work today.
Most of the campers are unfortunates
who will do anything for a candy bar.
Maybe I took advantage.
Maybe I was rough with them.
I'm not holding anything back.
It's all okay. I got a walk on the charges.
What was your penance?
I got 500 hours of community service.
I worked at the dog pound,
and I received some court-ordered therapy.
Was therapy helpful?
I got the doctor involved
in something unethical,
so he'd cut me some slack.
That's not helpful.
Papa called it "altruistic punishment."
Mason. Please.
Papa was a prodigy in the field of meat,
but his real genius was for human nature.
He could look at a man
and see his weakness.
Your father's dead.
A boy's illusions
are no basis for a man's life, Mason.
Margot is the only family you have left.
My sister loves me, Dr. Lecter.
She has to or she's destitute.
Vergers are noted expansionists.
And I am the sole Verger heir.
Unless biology provides another.
"Thou preparest a table before me
in the presence of mine enemies.
"Thou anointeth my head with oil,
my cup runneth over.
"Surely goodness and mercy
shall follow me all the days of my life
"And I will dwell
in the house of the Lord forever."
I'm here to mourn Freddie Lounds.
Can't imagine that's why you're here.
There's all sorts of reasons
why I'd go to Freddie Lounds' funeral.
It's common for a killer
to revisit their victims after death,
attend funerals, return to crime scenes.
- Anyone suspicious?
- Besides me?
That was implied.
You were expecting me.
It's common for a killer
to revisit their victims after death.
I'm not here to dance
on Freddie Lounds' grave,
if that's what you're getting at.
You're not here looking for her killer, either.
You don't seem
particularly interested in the crowd.
Are you profiling me, Dr. Bloom?
I'm here because
my psychiatrist suggested
it would be therapeutic.
I've been so preoccupied with taking a life,
I'm having trouble
wrapping my head around making one.
When men become fathers,
they undergo biochemical changes
that affect the way they think.
You said the same thing happens
when men become killers.
Fathers can be killers.
What sort of father would you be?
I'd be a good father.
How quickly we form attachments
to something that does not yet exist.
No. I'm not attached.
I'm only anticipating attachment.
We have a deep-seated need
to interact with our children.
It helps us discover who we are.
Have you ever been a father?
I was to my sister.
She was not my child,
but she was my charge.
She taught me so much about myself.
Her name was Mischa.
Was?
She's dead.
Abigail reminded me so much of her.
Then why did you kill her?
What happened to Abigail had to happen.
There was no other way.
There was.
But there isn't now.
Would you protect this child
in the way you couldn't protect Abigail?
I still dream about Abigail.
I dream that I'm teaching her how to fish.
I'm sorry. I took that from you.
Wish I could give it back.
So do I.
Occasionally, I drop a teacup
to shatter on the floor.
On purpose.
I'm not satisfied
when it doesn't gather itself up again.
Someday perhaps, a cup will come together.
Extra parts were harvested onsite.
Just one night in the ground,
that beats Jesus by 48 hours.
Never thought Freddie Lounds would
make it to heaven, much less get deified.
This killer is trying
to get somebody's attention.
He has direction.
His chaos is getting more orderly.
So first, he burns effigies,
and now he's assembling them.
Burning Freddie Lounds
wasn't his first effigy.
Whoever killed Freddie killed Randall Tier,
mutilated him, dismembered him
and put him on display.
Randall Tier and Freddie Lounds
have a connection.
Will.
Randall Tier was his suspect
and Hannibal's patient,
and Freddie Lounds
was investigating his murder when she died.
Freddie Lounds was investigating
a lot of things when she died.
This psychopath
was incubating fantasies about killing
and is building himself up.
Or someone's building him up.
He has a benefactor
who admires his destruction.
Shiva is both destroyer and benefactor.
He's being guided.
Is this some kind of signpost?
Maybe Freddie's killer didn't do this.
Maybe his benefactor did.
Why?
It's a courtship.
Good morning!
Riding agrees with you.
Puts color in your cheeks.
You've got a bloom. Really.
It's chilly.
You're frequently chilly, Margot.
I was lying in bed,
composing in my mind,
like the deaf Beethoven,
and it occurred to me that for a family
who owns breeding stock,
we don't do much of it ourselves.
I'm concerned about the next generation
of Vergers. Aren't you?
I'm just trying to survive this generation.
Meat is, at base, a people business.
Nobody understood that better than Papa,
except now for me, of course.
Papa would take me out of school
for weeks at a time
while he conducted my real education
in livestock, slaughterhouses.
I need to share this wealth
with a little Verger.
- "A little Verger."
- Don't you want an heir, Margot?
I want a baby Verger.
My own baby.
I have viable sperm.
I think I'd have a son. It'd be your heir, too.
Auntie Margot.
I think a child,
it may be what we need
to bring us closer together.
Maybe it is.
I've said it before, you've got a bloom.
Rosy.
Positively radiant.
What is your secret?
Every creative act
has its destructive consequence, Will.
The Hindu god Shiva
is simultaneous destroyer and creator.
Who you were yesterday is laid waste
to give rise to who you are today.
How many lies have had to be sanctified?
How many consciences devastated?
As many as were necessary.
You sacrificed Abigail.
You cared about her as much as I did.
Maybe more.
But then, how much has God sacrificed?
What god do you pray to?
I don't pray.
I have not been bothered
by any considerations of deity,
other than to recognize
how my own modest actions pale
beside those of God.
I prayed
I would see Abigail again.
Well, your prayer
did not go entirely unanswered.
You saw part of her.
Will.
Should the universe contract,
should time reverse
and teacups come together,
a place could be made
for Abigail in your world.
What place would that be?
You've lost a child, Will.
It seems you're likely to gain one.
God is beyond measure in wanton malice
and matchless in his irony.
No, no, no. Cancel that one.
I remember
walking the swine fairs with my father,
looking over the competition.
Papa's little silver knife ever ready
to slip out of his waistcoat
and stick into the back of a pig
to check the depth of fat.
Your education was an odd one.
Those were good, funny times.
Papa would stab 4-H show pigs
who thought everyone was their friend,
scrubbed in milk and baby powder.
Such coddled little things.
Part of a show pig's consideration
is its happiness.
If we were truly considerate
of a pig's happiness,
we wouldn't eat them.
What about Margot's happiness?
Papa taught me how to stick the knife in
only as deep as necessary,
to test the thickness of her skin.
You miscalculated.
Struck a nerve.
Margot would love to stick a knife into me,
and it wouldn't be to test
the thickness of my skin.
She tried to kill you once already.
"To a male heir
confirmed as my descendent..."
It's a very clever loophole
she's found in Papa's will.
Clearly, he did not take into account
how resourceful she is.
Neither did you.
I can be resourceful, too.
If she's not pregnant, she will be.
Margot's very tenacious that way.
This child would be a Verger.
You would have an heir
to carry on the family name,
to carry on your name.
I'd have an heir only if I die.
One observes only things
which are already on the mind.
What's on your mind?
I'm feeling pressure
to believe something I don't trust,
and that pressure is making me paranoid.
Who's pressuring you?
Will.
We'll never really be alone, will we?
He'll always be in the room.
Do you feel like you're helping him?
Making progress?
Will is finally finding himself.
He's getting better.
Doesn't seem to be getting better.
Are you questioning my therapy?
I'm questioning everything.
It's all blurry and subjective.
I feel empty,
like I've given blood.
Alana, you've given more than blood.
Have you been firing a gun?
I told you, I was feeling paranoid.
Poor Margot.
You just can't win.
I have to remove this temptation.
They're going to find something wrong
with your lady parts, Margot.
Or so the record will state.
The doctor will advise me that it's best
if they take
everything.
I'm afraid the only person
you'll be celebrating Mother's Day with
is me.
The most terrifying thing in the world
can be a lucid moment.
What are you up to?
I'm not sure I know
what you're talking about, Dr. Bloom.
I think you know.
You're not fooling me, Jack.
- I'm not trying to fool you.
- You're lying.
You're all lying.
Will. Hannibal.
You're lying to each other,
and they're lying to you.
Tell me what you believe is happening.
What do I believe?
What do you believe?
Do you believe Will killed Freddie Lounds?
No, I don't.
Do you think Dr. Chilton's
the Chesapeake Ripper?
- There was overwhelming...
- Stop lying, Jack!
You think you've moved
your pieces around so cleverly.
What's changed, Alana?
I have no confidence
that I know Hannibal Lecter anymore.
Even with as much as you know
or think you know Hannibal,
you don't know him either.
You don't know Will.
You are going to lose, Jack.
If you haven't lost already.
I want you to come with me.
How was my funeral?
Carlo?
Carlo, I don't think they've had enough to...
You must be the baby daddy.
Excuse me if I don't offer you a cigar.
I'm gonna feed you to my pigs.
Carlo!
Do you think it was Margot's idea
to have an heir?
You think it was your idea
to take it from her?
My idea to come here and kill you?
The only thing that you, your sister and I
have in common
is the same psychiatrist.
If Dr. Lecter had his druthers,
you'd be wrapped around a bullet right now.
Dr. Lecter is the one
you want to be feeding to your pigs.