Previously on Hannibal...
This killer doesn't think
like anyone else, Jack.
You'll have to find someone who
doesn't think like anyone else to catch him.
- There's no evidence I did this.
- Let him go.
You're making a mistake, Jack.
I know what it's like
to point at a killer and have no one listen.
You pointed in the wrong direction.
Don't lie to me, Dr. Lecter.
I believe my brother won't stop.
If you really want
to kill your brother, Margot,
wait until you can get away with it.
Or find someone to do it for you.
You're Hannibal Lecter's therapist.
I believe you.
Which answer is it you want to hear, Will?
What's happening now
and about to happen is an answer.
I want an admission.
I want you to admit what you are.
Must I denounce myself as a monster
while you still refuse to see
the one growing inside you?
Why not appeal to my better nature?
I wasn't aware you had one.
No one can be fully aware
of another human being
unless we love them.
By that love we see potential in our beloved.
Through that love,
we allow our beloved to see their potential.
Expressing that love,
our beloved's potential comes true.
I promised you a reckoning.
Here it is.
That smells wonderful.
Sacromonte omelet
with liver and sweetbreads.
Sacromonte was
the Gypsy hood of Granada.
I visited Granada when I was a young man.
- I've never been.
- No?
I fell in love with many things,
in particular, this dish.
I remember my time there so vividly,
like I frescoed the walls of my mind.
I used to be afraid of losing my memory.
What I wouldn't give to forget
a thing or two now.
My compliments
to the Gypsy hood of Granada.
Memory gives moments immortality,
but forgetfulness promotes a healthy mind.
It's good to forget.
What are you trying to forget, Jack?
Doubt. I let doubt in.
About me?
About Will.
I can no longer discuss
Will's state of mind with you
or anyone else without his consent.
Will's officially my patient.
He employs me now, not the FBI.
Well, let's hope your therapy works.
Therapy only works when
we have a genuine desire
to know ourselves as we are,
not as we would like to be.
Do you have any regrets?
With every choice lies
the possibility of regret.
However, if I choose not to do something,
it's usually for a good reason.
I'm...
Riddled with regrets.
A life without regret would be no life at all.
I regret what I did in the stable.
Then you were lucky I was there.
No, no, no.
Being lucky
isn't the same as making a mistake.
The mistake was allowing you to stop me.
So, it's not pulling
the trigger that you regret...
It's not pulling it effectively.
That would be more accurate.
You must adapt your behavior
to avoid feeling the same way again, Will.
Adapt.
Evolve.
Become.
Yes.
I want you to close your eyes.
Imagine a version of events
you wouldn't have regretted.
What did you see?
A missed opportunity...
To feel...
Like I felt when I killed Garret Jacob Hobbs.
To feel like...
Like I felt when I thought I'd killed you.
And what does that feel like?
I felt...
A quiet sense...
Of...
Power.
Good.
Remember that feeling.
I tend to walk out of this building
in a very similar state.
You must be a patient of Dr. Lecter's.
I'm sorry?
You look familiar.
I either know you or I know of you.
I'm the guy who didn't kill all those people.
We all have a gauge
for humanity that twitches
when we see other people.
Tell me, Margot, what twitches
when you see your brother?
Not my gauge for humanity.
You don't recognize in
your brother basic human traits.
You dehumanize him
as much as he dehumanizes you.
At least, I'll never be
the worst person I know.
The tendency to see others as less
human than ourselves is universal.
My brother is less human.
And you are less human from it.
Did you just dehumanize me?
Psychiatrists who dehumanize patients
are more comfortable
with painful but effective treatments.
I met a patient of yours. Will Graham.
Wonder what sort of painful
but effective treatment you prescribed him?
What do you imagine?
You're very supportive
of me killing my brother.
And I appreciate that support, I really do.
But I can only imagine
what you'd be supportive
of Will Graham doing.
What kind of psychiatrist are you?
You already had my reputation
and bona fides verified.
You know what kind of psychiatrist I am.
I'm beginning to.
Since when did the FBI get involved
in animal attacks, Jack?
When there's somebody holding the leash
of whatever it is that's doing the killing.
Esophagus is destroyed.
The bite almost severed his head!
Whatever it was, it's not afraid of humans.
Not anymore.
So I'm thinking a bear or a wolf.
Wolves or bears don't eat where they kill.
It'd have dragged him off.
There's no eating here.
We're gonna find everything.
The viscera's exposed, the belly's laid bare,
but there's no sign
of rutting or gnawing, Jack.
A rabid animal attacks victims at random
and doesn't eat any part of them.
Found the same wound patterns
on a series of livestock mutilations
in the area.
Evisceration, dismemberment,
yet everything accounted for.
Livestock mutilations... That was practice?
He's going to kill again.
And he's gonna get better at it.
And he's urbanizing his animal,
moving it closer to the city...
Adapting it for bigger prey.
And he's not denying its natural instincts,
he's evolving them.
It's blood sport.
A wolf or a bear?
Hey, this is Kevin.
Try not to stare
or they'll take him away from me.
Sorry.
It's okay.
Bear. Wolf.
Do bears and wolves hunt together?
You could train a bear to be a wolf,
or a wolf to be a bear.
Train them long enough,
and they will hunt together, feed together.
Okay.
Enough time...
There's a great deal
I could train even you to do, Will.
That kind of friendship can
keep you on your toes.
Animals, they do have...
They have friendships just like us.
We're the same.
Yeah, I'll try to remember that.
Please, don't blame the animals.
- No.
- Don't.
Man is the only creature that kills to...
Kill.
It's not an animal.
It's a man who wants to be an animal.
Does he believe he's an animal?
It's not what he believes,
it's what he imagines.
Well, what does he want?
He wants to maul.
Nothing personal about this.
He doesn't know them.
He doesn't need to know them.
They're just...
Meat to him.
Prey.
This kind of psychosis
doesn't just slip through the system.
Somewhere,
someone would have noticed this.
If it is psychosis,
he got inside of it somehow,
tamed it,
made a suit out of it.
He's an engineer...
Or he understands engineering.
He knows how to build.
He built his beast.
He is a student of predators.
"No beast is more savage than man,
"when possessed with power
answerable to his own rage."
It's not rage.
Rage is an emotional response
to being provoked.
This is something else.
What is it?
Instinct.
- It's the way he thinks.
- The way any animal thinks
depends on limitations of mind and body.
If we learn our limitations too soon,
we never learn our power.
His victims are torn apart,
I'd say he learned his power.
He claimed his power.
Can you imagine tearing someone apart?
Or would you prefer to use a gun?
Guns lack intimacy.
You set an event in motion with a gun,
you don't complete it.
You fantasized about killing me
with your hands.
Wouldn't that be more satisfying
than pulling a trigger?
Yes.
When you sent the man to kill me,
were you imagining killing me yourself?
Living vicariously through him as if...
Your hands tightened
the noose around my neck?
Or were you simply hiding?
I wasn't hiding from anything
the first time I tried to kill you.
You were hiding...
Behind the gun.
You must allow yourself to be
intimate with your instincts, Will.
The closest comparative bite radius
we could match
to the victims' wounds is a cave bear.
Even the dire wolf,
which is the largest species
of the genus Canis,
is itty-bitty by comparison.
But a cave bear did not do this.
Mostly because they're vegetarian,
and have been extinct for 28,000 years.
Mostly because the bite force
relative to the skull size
doesn't match the kind of damage
we've been seeing.
What could?
Pull-ratchets and pneumatics, maybe.
Pretty sophisticated ingenuity
for any kind of animal, man or beast.
Animals are far more like humans
than we ever realized.
And humans are far more like animals.
One thin barrier between us.
And for some, that barrier is way too thin.
Hello, Dr. Lecter.
How does something like this present?
Someone affected by
this kind of species dysphoria
typically has other conditions.
Mood disorders, clinical depression,
- schizophrenia.
- Typically?
They may not present at all.
Your killer could have
built a bridge between
who he appears to be and
what he now knows he's become.
He didn't build a bridge, Doctor...
He built a suit.
What he seeks is transformation.
Have you ever seen
anything like this before?
This threatens to be a violation of
doctor-patient confidentiality,
so I will tread carefully.
You've seen something like this?
Years ago, I treated a patient
who fits the profile.
A teenage boy who suffered from what
I would describe as an identity disorder.
This boy fancied himself a beast?
During our therapy,
he reported a moment of clarity.
He understood in that moment,
he was an animal
born in the body of a man.
He kept a solitary life.
He would hide and behave in ways
resembling animal behavior.
- He was delusional.
- Not necessarily.
He didn't believe metamorphosis
could physically take place,
but that wouldn't stop him
from trying to achieve it.
He'd be a grown man now?
And as he grew in wisdom and confidence,
he would no longer feel he had
to meet his needs in hiding.
What are his needs, Dr. Lecter?
Savagery.
Museum's closed.
Hello, Randall.
Dr. Lecter.
You will always be ruled
by your fascination with teeth.
That's what you said to me
when they brought me in your office
the very first time.
Is that what I said?
Yeah.
I was crying.
I was dreading telling you
what was wrong with me and...
You made it easier.
Other visits too.
A therapist's life is equal
parts counsel and curiosity.
We set a patient on a path,
but are left to wonder
where that path will take them.
You've come so very far, Randall.
A long time since you treated me.
Which is why I wanted to talk to you
about your wonderful progress,
just for a moment, privately.
I've seen what you've done.
What have I done?
You bore screams...
Like a sculptor bears dust
from the beaten stone.
That crying boy doesn't
cling to you anymore.
What clings to you now?
What clings to your teeth?
Ragged bits of scalp...
Trailing their tails of hair like comets.
Beautiful.
They are looking for you.
I don't think I can stop.
I don't want you to.
But they will find you, Randall.
When they do,
it's important you do exactly what I say.
- You wanted to speak to me?
- Randall Tier.
Special Agent Jack Crawford with the FBI.
This is Will Graham.
Did you... Put all that together?
- Yes, I did.
- Nice work.
- What is that?
- That is a cave bear.
You put together
a lot of cave bears, do you?
Yeah. I put them together, take them apart,
put them back together again.
You understand their mechanics
and how they're engineered?
We understand a lot about cave bears.
Their fossils have been found in the tens
of thousands, all over southern Europe.
Very common.
The reason I ask is because a...
A cave bear skull...
Was used recently as a murder weapon.
Prehistoric jaws and claws
are designed to do what they do best.
The victims were torn apart.
Used the right tool for the job.
Well, look inside the skull
and you'll find what the job is.
You have a history of trouble
with things inside your head.
Isn't that right, Mr. Tier?
Is that what this is about?
You think I killed someone with a fossil?
I had an identity disorder.
The doctors told me the internal map
of my body didn't match reality.
Do you know what it's like
when the skin you're wearing doesn't fit?
I can imagine.
I know who I am now.
And I'm doing much better.
I'm socializing. I take my medication.
I'm employed. And I work very hard.
And I'm proof that
mental illness is treatable.
Hi. I don't know if you remember me,
but I met you outside of Dr. Lecter's office.
I remember it. How did you find me?
Well, as it turns out, you are famous.
You're not exactly anonymous yourself,
Margot.
Did you sneak a peek
inside Dr. Lecter's calendar?
That is exactly what I did.
It's cold. Do you have any whiskey?
What is the heir to
the Verger Meat Packing dynasty
doing at my door?
My brother is the heir, not me.
I have the wrong parts and
the wrong proclivity for parts.
You didn't answer my question.
Came for a character reference.
Patient-to-patient.
What do you think of Dr. Lecter's therapy?
It depends what you're in therapy for.
I'm in therapy for all kinds of reasons.
The Vergers slaughter 86,000 cattle a day
and 36,000 pigs, depending on the season,
but that's just the public carnage.
What's your private carnage?
I tried to kill my brother.
Well, I assume he had it coming.
Did he ever.
What's your private carnage?
I tried to murder Dr. Lecter.
Did he have it coming?
What do you think?
I can't say that I know.
Neither can I.
We have some very similar issues.
Although I doubt that Dr. Lecter
gave you the same advice
on murder that he gave me.
And what's that?
He said...
"If at first you don't succeed, try, try again."
I'm curious what would happen
if your patients started
comparing notes, Dr. Lecter.
What would Randall Tier have to say to me?
What did Randall Tier say to you?
He said he was much better now,
that mental illness was treatable.
Randall Tier is a success story.
You believe he's innocent?
I believe...
Your therapy was successful.
You can be persuasive.
How many have there been?
Like Randall Tier?
Like me?
Every patient is unique.
Your psychiatrist came to visit me
at the hospital before my trial.
Dr. Du Maurier.
She told me she believed me.
She knew there were others like me.
Fascinating.
Did you kill her?
No.
What do you think about
when you think about killing?
I think about God.
Good and evil?
Good and evil has nothing to do with God.
I collect church collapses.
Did you see the recent one in Sicily?
The facade fell on 65 grandmothers
during a special mass.
Was that evil? Was that God?
If he's up there, he just loves it.
Typhoid and swans,
it all comes from the same place.
Does Randall Tier believe in God?
Perhaps you should have a more
personal conversation with Mr. Tier
and ask him what he believes.
The solitude of what you do
is to be respected,
and I intend to honor that.
I've only come to offer
words of encouragement.
You are becoming, Randall,
and this beast is your higher self.
Your bodies, voices and wills are one.
Revel in what you are.
Hey!
Buster! Buster!
I'd say this makes us even.
I sent someone to kill you...
You sent someone to kill me.
Even Steven.