Previously on Hannibal...
I hallucinated that I killed her.
Will Graham, you're under arrest for murder.
Four of the lures are made from
materials including human remains.
According to the evidence...
I killed Abigail Hobbs.
I feel wounded.
I guess you dodged a bullet with me.
I kept pushing him
because he was saving lives.
I told you not to put him out there!
I didn't kill any of them.
And somebody is making sure
that no one believes me.
You catch these killers
by getting into their heads,
but you also allow them into your own.
- I'm trying to help you, Will.
- I know who I am.
I'm not so sure
that I know who you are anymore.
Are you a killer, Will?
Will.
- Hello, Will.
- Hello, Dr. Lecter.
This course is called Mukozuke.
Seasonal sashimi,
sea urchin, water clam, and squid.
What a beautiful presentation, Doctor.
Kaiseki.
A Japanese art form that honors
the taste and aesthetic of what we eat.
I almost feel guilty about eating it.
I never feel guilty eating anything.
I can't quite place the fish.
He was a flounder.
I last prepared this meal for my aunt,
Murasaki.
Under similarly unfortunate circumstances.
Well, what circumstances were those?
A loss.
This is a loss.
Will is a loss and we're mourning a death.
Will's death is on me, not you.
It's on both of us.
I can't stop thinking that Will
may be convicted of five murders
while I am only maybe convicted of one.
But you're not on trial.
I will be.
In the halls of the FBI.
And so will you.
I mean, according to Will Graham,
this was all you.
Will was your bloodhound.
You can't ignore where he points.
I'm not ignoring it.
You have to investigate me.
It's in my best interest and yours.
Yes, it is.
But I also can't ignore
the fact that my bloodhound went mad
before he pointed in your direction.
We can't define Will
only by his maddest edges.
We can't define Will at all.
What did you say?
I said, how does that make you feel?
That makes me feel like
I'm sitting in a dunking tank
and you're lobbing softballs,
hoping to make a splash,
but you keep missing the target.
Fortunately, I have time for a few more lobs.
You are in my hospital.
You're my patient now, Will.
I'm not talking to you, Frederick.
I want to talk to Dr. Lecter.
According to Dr. Bloom,
you were warned against putting someone
with Will Graham's issues into the field.
Yes. That's correct.
Were you aware that Dr. Bloom
would be filing this report?
Yes, she told me what she was going to do.
Did you advise her against it?
I told her she should do
whatever she felt was necessary.
Evidently, she felt it was necessary
to file the report.
These are allegations of misconduct.
It's damning stuff, Jack.
I never stated anywhere
that this was misconduct.
In my opinion, it was a lapse in judgment.
A lapse in judgment is misconduct.
There'll be an internal investigation.
There should be.
A federal examiner is someone
who arrives at a battlefield
after the battle and bayonets the wounded.
You have wounded Agent Crawford.
Who do you think
is gonna be getting the bayonet?
There is a general desire
to see this go away,
quickly and quietly.
In light of that, Dr. Bloom,
I would greatly appreciate it
if you would recant your report.
No. Will Graham's life has been destroyed.
How that happened
has to be a matter of record.
I'm sorry, Jack.
Dr. Bloom is not easily swayed.
This is going to get ugly.
It already has.
Was there a storm?
It looks like someone's
blasting beaver dams again.
Man!
It smells real bad down here!
Probably dead beavers!
Get me out of here!
Go!
Will Graham has asked to see me.
I would like to see him.
I continue to be curious
about the way he thinks,
despite all that's happened.
He's still influencing you.
Will Graham asking to see you
betrays his clear intent to manipulate you.
And if I agree to see Will?
It betrays your clear intent
to manipulate him.
I miss him.
You are obsessed with Will Graham.
I'm intrigued.
Obsessively.
And he will take advantage of that.
Will is my friend.
Why?
Why is he your friend?
He sees his own mentality
as grotesque but useful.
Like a chair of antlers.
He can't repress who he is.
There's an honesty in that I admire.
I imagine there's an honesty
in that you can relate to.
What can't you repress, Hannibal?
Hello, Will.
Dr. Lecter.
Lost in thought?
Not lost.
Not anymore.
I used to hear my thoughts inside my skull
with the same
tone,
timbre, accent,
as if the words were coming out
of my mouth.
And now?
Now...
My inner voice sounds like you.
I can't get you out of my head.
Friendship can sometimes involve
a breach of individual separateness.
You're not my friend.
The light from friendship won't reach us
for a million years.
That's how far away from friendship we are.
I imagine it's easier to believe
I am responsible for those murders
than it is to accept that you are.
Sure is.
Your inner voice can provide a method
of taking control of your behavior.
Accepting responsibility
for what you've done.
Giving your thoughts words
encourages clarity.
I have clarity.
About you.
Our conversations, Will,
were only ever about you opening your eyes
to the truth of who you are.
What you did to me
is in my head,
and I will find it.
I'm going to remember, Dr. Lecter.
And when I do,
there will be a reckoning.
I have huge faith in you, Will.
I always have.
I'm amazed what falls off the best of us
when moving through a room.
Lessons learned from cellular decay.
Enjoy the world while we have it
and give a little bit back.
When possible,
I try to leave an indelible mark
wherever I go.
Hopefully not with your DNA.
How long will you have my suits?
You might want to think about
supplementing your wardrobe.
I frequently do.
You know, this is just a formality.
Nobody expects to find anything.
Except for maybe Will Graham.
He'll have to be disappointed.
The beauty of what you do, Ms. Katz,
is in its certainty.
It'll be your evidence that convicts Will.
Well, I found enough of it.
No need to infer or intuit or trust.
So much simpler than psychiatry.
Will is doing his best
to understand where he is
and why.
You were supposed to protect him.
From himself?
Yeah.
I'm not mad at you.
Not anymore than I'm mad at myself.
We all missed it, whatever it was... Is.
We all are not suspects.
You're not a suspect,
you're the new Will Graham.
Thank you for coming, Dr. Lecter.
Jack, what can I do for you?
I was hoping you would help me
with the psychological profile.
We found another body.
This way, Doctor.
This is the fourth body
we've recovered so far.
There's at least one more down there.
How long have they been here?
Hard to say,
but someone went through a lot of trouble
to make sure that they were well preserved.
They've been coated in some kind of resin.
The big one was partially sealed,
rotting from the inside out.
The other three look like
they were embalmed.
Whatever he's doing,
he's still figuring out how to do it.
Were they injected with silicone?
They were injected with something.
Silicone?
A technique for making
resin-coated models out of fish.
Helps the body retain shape in death.
He's making human models.
You make models of things
that you want to keep.
These were tossed in the river.
Maybe they were imperfect.
These are his discards.
I'm giving you informed consent
to discuss me as your patient.
With whom?
Jack Crawford.
Disclosure of patient information
should be limited
to the requirements of the situation.
What is the situation, Hannibal?
Will Graham made accusations.
Jack's only being thorough.
You're keeping Agent Crawford close.
We share an obsession.
I got to be Will Graham today.
I consulted at an FBI crime scene.
I stood in Will's shoes,
looked through his eyes and I saw death.
How I imagined he would see it.
Why would you be inviting
the scrutiny of the FBI?
I'm being as open and honest
as I know how.
You maintain an air of transparency,
while putting me
in the position to lie for you.
Again.
You're not just lying for me.
How far will this flirtation with the FBI go?
It would seem Jack Crawford
is less suspicious of me than you are.
Jack Crawford doesn't know
what you're capable of.
Neither do you.
Come on! Come on!
How are the dogs?
Good.
Well, Winston keeps running away,
but the others are adjusting.
Where does Winston go?
Home.
Well, he's not gonna find me there.
Not today.
But maybe someday he might.
With the right defense.
I don't currently have legal representation.
You keep firing your lawyers.
Yeah, they're the FBl's lawyers.
Then I'll find you a lawyer
who's not affiliated with the FBI.
What defense do you think I have?
Automatism.
Allows a defendant to argue
they shouldn't be held criminally liable
for their actions due to unconsciousness.
Unconsciousness?
Will,
your mind was on fire.
You had no control of what you were doing,
much less remember doing it.
What if I could remember?
What if I could remember
how this was done to me?
What if you could remember how you did it?
You believe Hannibal.
I believe the Will Graham
standing in front of me now
is incapable of that violence.
I believe you lost your mind,
and for periods of time,
you weren't the Will Graham I know.
I hear Hannibal's voice
in the well of my mind.
I hear him saying words
that he's never said to me.
It isn't my imagination. It's something else.
Have you ever helped
a patient recover memories?
Close your eyes.
Feel the heaviness in your limbs.
Imagine yourself in a safe
and relaxing place.
Safe to relax completely.
No matter how deeply you go
my voice will go with you.
This isn't working.
What did you see?
Will...
Salted and ash-baked celeriac
with foraged sel fou.
Frederick, you have tested me.
It's rare that I cook a meatless meal.
I lost a kidney.
I have to watch my protein intake.
You didn't lose it, Frederick.
It was taken from you.
I remain impressed with your recovery.
One can grow to love beets.
Alana Bloom
was visiting with your former patient today.
Will was never my patient.
The irony is that he is my patient,
but he refuses to speak to me.
Makes me feel like
I'm fumbling with his head
like a freshman pulling at a panty girdle.
Will is going to be a challenge
for any psychiatrist.
He is so lucid, so perceptive.
He's trained in criminal psychology,
and he is a mass murderer.
He's a prize patient.
Or should be.
How was Dr. Bloom's visit?
He asked her to hypnotize him,
so he could recover his memories.
This is delicious.
Was he successful?
Only in playing Dr. Bloom.
It's sad to see a brilliant psychiatrist
fall for such hoary old chestnuts.
She wants to believe him.
I do too.
You do realize you're his favorite topic
of conversation.
Hannibal, Hannibal, Hannibal.
Not with me, of course.
But with everyone else who'll listen.
He tells everyone that you are a monster.
Well, in that case, you are dining
with a psychopathic murderer, Frederick.
You have nice skin.
Dental and medical records
placed the six.
All adults, both men and women,
different ages, different ethnicities,
all from different states.
Nothing in common
except they all disappeared
from their homes with their vehicles.
And they all had large amounts
of heroin in their systems.
Enough to be the cause of death?
And then some.
What's this strange
skin discoloration on these bodies?
We found traces of BHT,
which is a color preservative.
He wants them to look alive.
Shot them up with a little China white,
injected them with preservatives,
then filled the bodies
with silicone so they don't emaciate.
Then he seals them
with, like, a hard resin shell.
What are these puncture wounds?
Those are like eyelets.
Something was threaded through.
They were strung up, mounted, presented.
So how's he choosing them?
We got nothing.
Appears to be random,
but if this is the discard pile,
I'm curious to know
how many were keepers.
All right, I want a list
of any missing persons
that disappeared along with their vehicles
in the neighboring states.
Got it?
Got it.
It's good to see you.
Don't know how I feel about seeing you.
I'll let you know when I do.
Does Jack know you're here?
No, but he shouldn't be surprised.
I'm surprised.
I'm compartmentalizing.
There are a lot of people missing.
- You have the file with you?
- Yes.
And pictures?
Yes.
The first six bodies
were found in the same place.
Dumped in a river, caught in a beaver dam.
What does he do to them?
He targets them, follows them home,
abducts them and preserves them.
You want to know
how he's choosing them, don't you?
I thought you would have some ideas.
These are DMV pictures
of people who are still missing
under similar circumstances
from three different states.
Tell me what you see.
It's a color palette.
Hi, Winston.
Come here, boy. There you go.
I suppose you blame me too?
Hello, Jack.
You need to take better care of this dog.
I feel horrible.
I got all the dogs chipped,
but at least they're not running away
to anywhere I can't find them.
He's just looking for Will.
Yeah.
Isn't that why you're here?
Listen...
I understand why you felt
you had to file that report.
You questioned my judgment
when it needed to be questioned.
Yes, it did.
And it will help in Will's defense
if it's in the record.
Declaring Hannibal's guilt
is more important to Will
than establishing his own defense.
Hannibal's not guilty.
Neither is Will.
But he's clinging to the hope
Hannibal did this so
he doesn't have to face what he did.
Convince me he didn't know
what he was doing.
I would really like to be convinced, Alana.
A psychopath wouldn't be
so scared of the truth, Jack.
Will's terrified, but that's not
stopping him from trying to find it.
Somebody's got to find the truth, Winston?
If Will doesn't remember what he did,
he'll never accept the truth.
Will?
Hey, Will.
Hi, Jack.
Where were you just now?
Gone fishing.
What are you doing here?
I needed to remind myself
of who you once were.
You know, that man
whose classroom I walked into months ago.
I remember that man.
Memories are all I have.
Imagine how nice it is
to stumble on a new one.
I was
almost certain
Hannibal Lecter did this to me.
And it's a funny thing, doubt.
I had nothing to prove to myself
or anyone else
that Hannibal was responsible
not even a memory.
You have something now?
You've recovered a memory?
Yes.
That's meaningless.
Not to me.
He did it so well.
There wasn't an orgy of evidence.
There was just enough to convince you.
We investigated your claims
about Dr. Lecter, Will,
thoroughly.
We went over every fiber
of every stitch of clothing.
We took his DNA.
We took his fingerprints.
We found nothing.
You let the fox into the henhouse.
You stood over
Cassie Boyle's body in that field
and you described yourself to me.
No, I described Hannibal Lecter.
I can't hear this anymore.
I am not the intelligent psychopath
you are looking for.
Goodbye, Will.
You may not believe me now.
You will.