Previously on Hannibal...
I'm a good fisherman, Jack.
You hook him, I'll land him.
Never seen pigs like these.
They're a special breed.
Riding agrees with you.
You've got a bloom.
I don't get a legacy.
Unless you make one.
She's pathological.
I'm sure she's told you
horrible things that I've done.
They're going to find something wrong
with your lady parts, Margot.
You must be the baby daddy.
Dr. Lecter is the one
you want to be feeding to your pigs.
Can you explain my actions?
Can you posit my intentions?
What would be your theory of my mind?
I have an understanding
of your state of mind.
You understand mine.
We're just alike.
This gives you the capacity to deceive me
and be deceived by me.
I'm not deceiving you, Dr. Lecter.
I'm just pointing out
the snare around your neck.
What you do about it is entirely up to you.
You put the snare around my neck.
Why did you tell Mason Verger
I want to kill him?
I was curious what would happen.
It's true, isn't it?
You do want to kill him.
Or you want me to kill him.
Either way, you'd like him dead.
I'm just
giving you a little nudge.
Mason is discourteous.
And discourtesy is unspeakably ugly to me.
Are you thinking about eating him?
Whenever feasible,
one should always try to eat the rude.
Free-range rude.
Would you join me at the table?
Mason Verger is a pig
and he deserves to be somebody's bacon.
Maybe you should kill Mason
during your next session.
He may be intending to kill me
during our next session.
Then you'll have to kill him first.
You said you were curious
what would happen.
I want you to close your eyes, Will.
Imagine what you would like to happen.
What did you see?
Good.
Garbage.
Shall we talk about
what happened to poor Margot?
- We can get to that later.
- We can get to it now.
Family affairs are best left
to the family, Dr. Lecter.
You interfered.
I provided counsel.
You subverted me.
While you were subverting
the underprivileged children
at your summer camp,
what did you learn?
Keen student of the Bible that I am,
I learned about suffering.
Not mine, mind you, but the general conceit.
God's choices in inflicting suffering
are not satisfactory to us,
nor are they understandable,
unless innocence offends him.
Clearly, he needs help
in directing his blind fury
with which he flogs this earth.
Margot's happiness is more important
than her suffering.
You say that as though
the two are mutually exclusive.
I believe they are.
Can never say to a certainty.
It is one of those things that is hid,
as the Bible says.
Papa taught me how to hide
all sorts of things.
This was his knife.
I carry it around with me
to remind me of him.
Whose fat are you planning
to measure today, Mason?
Mine?
No fat on you.
Take more than a flesh wound
to make you squeal.
What game of chicken
are you and the sperm donor
playing, Dr. Lecter?
Don't get me wrong.
I play chicken with Margot all the time.
I just don't tell her I'm playing.
I'm good at chicken, Dr. Lecter.
I never blink.
Just send me the bill.
I'm so sorry.
He could have done
what was done laparoscopically,
but my brother told them to leave a scar.
He branded you.
Mason wants you to know
this can never be undone.
Mason can be undone.
Not without taking
everything I have with him.
He's all I've got now.
That's exactly what he wanted.
He won.
He always wins.
This won't make you human, Margot,
so much as give you the ability
to make yourself human and move on.
There's no resolve to this.
There's no resolution.
Moving on isn't just a distraction.
It's a rebuke.
Show your brother how strong you are.
Survive him.
Hannibal has a certain personality style
we can all learn from.
In moderation, of course.
All I want to do is catch him.
He's given me nothing, Jack.
Nothing actionable.
He has confessed to nothing.
He's acknowledged only vagaries.
I need more than vagaries.
You have killed someone, Will.
Who was trying to kill me.
I don't know if I can prove that.
You mutilated the body.
We made a public spectacle
of Freddie Lounds' death.
I'm out on a limb here,
and the limb is going to break.
I've only told the OIG
what they need to know.
Now, what haven't you told me?
Hannibal is trying to manipulate me
into murdering one of his patients.
Mason Verger.
But I can manipulate Hannibal
into killing him instead.
What's Verger done?
Hannibal considers him rude.
It's motive enough.
It's as though committing murders
has purged him of lesser rudeness.
We're talking about putting
a man's life in danger.
You know, sometimes, Jack, a good plan
is less about finding the best alternative
than it is about finding one that works.
Don't let empathy
confuse what you want
with what Lecter wants.
I told you, Jack, I'm a good fisherman.
We have to use the right bait.
When Hannibal tries to kill Mason Verger,
I'll arrest him,
and you'll have two witnesses.
We might have three.
I'm a good fisherman too, Will.
They tell me you were hard to find.
That was the idea.
Thank you
for visiting me in the hospital
and for what you said.
I didn't say enough.
And now's your chance to say it all.
You've been granted immunity
from prosecution
by the US Attorney from District 36,
and by local authorities
in a memorandum attached,
sworn and attested.
Let's talk about Hannibal Lecter.
Some psychiatrists are so hungry for insight
that they may try to manufacture it.
How deadly that can be
for the patient who believes them.
You were Dr. Lecter's psychiatrist.
He wasn't yours.
I told myself that,
but I was under Hannibal's influence.
What he did to you
made that abundantly clear.
You were attacked
by a patient who was formerly
under Dr. Lecter's care.
That patient died during the attack.
Report said he swallowed his tongue.
It wasn't attached at the time.
How
exactly
did your patient die?
I killed him.
I believed it was self-defense.
And to a point, it was.
But beyond that point,
it was murder.
Hannibal influenced me
to murder my patient.
Our patient.
You weren't
coerced?
What Hannibal does is not coercion.
It is persuasion.
Has he ever tried to persuade you
to kill anybody?
He will.
And it will be somebody you love.
And you will think
it's the only choice you have.
How would you catch him?
Hannibal can get lost
in self-congratulation
at his own exquisite taste and cunning.
Whimsy.
That will be how he will get caught.
We're maintaining our position
on the event horizon of chaos.
Your veneer of self-composure gives
a strong sense of the surreal.
So much about this feels like a dream.
Dreams prepare us for waking life.
It's one thing to dream, it's another to
understand the nature of the dream.
You're waking up to who you are.
That's all you need to understand.
There are extraordinary
circumstances here, Will.
And unusual opportunities.
For whom?
For both of us.
Mason Verger is an opportunity?
Mason Verger is a problem.
Problem solving is hunting.
It's a savage pleasure, and we are born to it.
A pleasure we can share.
You're fostering codependency.
Is that what I'm doing?
Isn't that what you did to Abigail?
Got her to take a life so she'd owe you hers?
I bond with Abigail,
you take her away.
I bond with
barely more than the idea of a child,
you take it away.
You saw to it that
I alienated Alana,
alienated Jack.
You don't want me
to have anything in my life
that's not you.
I only want what's best for you.
Please.
Every moment of cogent thought
under your psychiatric care
is a personal victory.
You're applying yourself to my perspective
as I've been applying myself to yours.
You're right.
We are just alike.
You're as alone as I am.
And we're both alone without each other.
So you managed to avoid prosecution.
I gave you every opportunity
to tell the truth, but you ran.
How do you think
the FBI could have protected me?
You couldn't protect Will Graham.
You still can't.
Nothing makes us more vulnerable
than loneliness, Agent Crawford.
Will's not alone.
No, he's not.
Hannibal thinks Will is a killer.
Do you still believe he is your killer?
I have to believe.
Hannibal's only crime I witnessed
was influence.
Influence works best when we're unaware.
Will Graham has been very aware.
Meaning?
Meaning maybe Mr. Graham
doesn't know himself
as well as Hannibal does.
Will has more reasons
to see Hannibal caught
than any of us.
If you think you're about to catch Hannibal,
that's because he wants you to think that.
Don't fool yourself into thinking
he's not in control of what's happening.
Kholodets.
A Ukrainian dish whose outcome
can never be predicted.
The Latin word "gelatus"
translates as "frozen."
Here, the aspic provides
a three-dimensional canvas
in which one may stage a scene.
The eternal chase.
An evocative shape,
in that at a certain point,
it becomes unclear who's pursuing whom.
Well, in isolation,
a moment can't really speak
to motive, intent or aftermath.
Aspic is derived from bone
as a life is made from moments.
So, tell me, Hannibal,
what moment are we in now?
You, me, Will?
Still harboring doubts about Will?
Alana Bloom isn't harboring any doubts.
She's convinced
that he murdered Freddie Lounds.
And you?
I am convinced of
my general lack of trust in other people.
Lack of trust in other people
increases the need for religion.
If you can't rely on others,
you have to rely on God.
I'm relying on myself.
And yet in this moment,
I have to confess that
I don't know who's pursuing whom
any more than these fish do.
Whomever is pursuing whom
in this very moment,
I intend to eat them.
All right, guys. Eat up.
Mr. Verger wants your company.
Please, come with us.
Matteo.
He shouldn't have done that.
You are Sardinian.
If you have to be kidnapped for ransom,
a wealthy Italian will tell you
it's better to fall into the hands of the Sards.
And you're a professional revenger
as well, I suspect.
With you
it is personal now.
I take it Matteo didn't make it.
Did he foul himself?
I imagine he smells worse than you by now.
Kill him and you will get no money! Carlo!
Carlo!
Those little piggies are gonna go
"whee" all the way home.
Yes!
The swine may be shy
with starting with the toes,
so we need to encourage them
with a little sauce.
So we're gonna cut your throat.
Padrone, he killed Matteo.
We can give Matteo's family
Doctorone's cojones for comfort.
Capisci?
He likes to cut low.
You are an odd psychiatrist.
We could've had
some good, funny times together.
It's a damn shame!
I've muzzled the dog.
Now, it's time for you to put him down.
Don't bleed him out! Just...
Just a little nick.
Just enough to give the pigs a taste.
Carlo!
Mason, I must ask you to be quiet.
You'll frighten the animals.
Piggy, piggy, piggy, piggy.
Piggy, piggy. Here, piggy, piggy.
What?
What have you given me?
A variety of psychedelic compounds.
Psychedelic, so named from the Greek
for "mind revealing."
You need to write me
a prescription for this, Doctor.
Patients rhapsodize about
the life-changing insights they achieve.
I am enchanted and terrified.
The world presents itself
as a cacophony of sights, sounds, smells,
and recollections.
I want you to recall your education
in stockyards and slaughterhouses.
Show me how Papa would check
the depth of a pig's fat.
Here, piggy, piggy, piggy.
No, Mason.
No.
Show me on you.
Hey, Winston.
Where's everyone else?
I just love your dogs.
How is that? Is that good?
Do you want another piece?
How about you? That's a good girl.
Sit! Sit!
Mason?
I adopted some dogs from the shelter,
two dogs, that were friends.
I had them in a cage together
with no food and fresh water.
One of them died hungry.
The other had a warm meal.
I should have put you
in a cage with Dr. Lecter.
I'm curious what would've happened.
What are you feeding my dogs?
Just me.
Sit. Sit.
What Mason is experiencing
isn't restricted to reality.
So reality has to be forced to adapt.
He fed his face to my dogs.
He broadened their palates
as I broadened yours.
Murder or mercy?
There is no mercy.
We make mercy,
manufacture it in the parts
that have overgrown our basic reptile brain.
Then there is no murder.
We make murder, too.
It matters only to us.
You know too well you possess
all the elements to make murder.
Perhaps mercy too, but murder
you understand uncomfortably well.
I'm hungry.
Eat your nose then.
Eat my...
Eat my nose?
I have a taste and consistency
that's similar to that of a chicken gizzard.
Taste is housed in parts of the mind
that precedes pity.
Pity has no place at the table.
I'm full of myself.
I'm not gonna kill him.
So full of myself.
He was going to feed you to his pigs
after he fed them me.
Weren't you, Mason?
I was.
He's your patient, Doctor.
You do what you think is best for him.
Good afternoon. Agent Crawford?
Yes. Good afternoon, Mr. Verger.
What a magnificent creature.
Oh, thank you.
It's a Muraena kidako.
Its common name is Brutal Moray.
Would you like to see why?
No, thank you.
I don't want to take up too much
of your time, Mr. Verger.
I realize that you probably need
to get your rest.
But I would like to ask you
just a few questions about
what happened to you.
Took a tumble in the pig pen.
Broke my neck.
Embarrassing, really.
Clumsy, clumsy, clumsy.
If my sister hadn't found me,
the pigs would have eaten
more than my face.
Pigs did this to you?
Yes, the pigs certainly did.
Mr. Verger, you are a patient
of Dr. Hannibal Lecter, isn't that right?
Dr. Lecter, yes, yes.
Have you ever seen or met
another patient of Dr. Lecter's,
a man called Will Graham?
Will Graham.
The man that didn't kill all those people.
- That Will Graham?
- Yes.
Can't say that I've had the pleasure.
Do you find that Dr. Lecter's therapy
has been helpful to you?
I've benefited greatly
from Dr. Lecter's therapy.
I'm still benefitting from it.
I will always be grateful
for how he's helped me.
I only hope that I may repay him one day.
Now, if you don't mind, I am rather tired.
Thank you for your time, Mr. Verger.
Is it time to talk about what Margot wants?
What Margot wants
is to take care of you, Mason, dear.
Just as you took care of me.
Achilles lamenting the death of Patroclus.
Whenever he's mentioned in The Iliad,
Patroclus seems to be defined
by his empathy.
He became Achilles on the field of war.
- He died for him there, wearing his armor.
- He did.
Hiding and revealing identity
is a constant theme
throughout the Greek epics.
As are battle-tested friendships.
Achilles wished all Greeks would die,
so that he and Patroclus
could conquer Troy alone.
Took divine intervention
to bring them down.
This isn't sustainable.
We're going to get caught.
Jack already suspects
you killed Freddie Lounds.
If Jack told you he suspects me,
that means he suspects you.
I know.
You should give him what he wants.
Give him the Chesapeake Ripper?
Allow him closure.
Reveal yourself.
You've taunted him for long enough.
Let him see you with clear eyes.
Jack has become my friend.
I suppose I owe him the truth.