This morning,
the phone guy comes in
and he shows Michael that our
phones have a PA function.
And then he just left.
This is your
captain speaking.
The office will be flying at
an altitude of two stories.
Look out your
left-hand window
and you will see
Vance Refrigeration.
I am the ghost
of salesmen past.
Do not come near me.
Yes, Michael Scott
for Dr. Johnson, please.
Hello, Doctor. I was just
following up about my mole again.
Now, I was looking online
about sebaceous zits.
I have not been
squeezing it.
Could I stick it
with a pin?
Toby Flenderson to
the principal's office.
Your mother called and it appears
that you wet the bed again,
so you have to get home to wash
your sheets because they're yellow
and they're wet
with your urine.
And, at 6'6",
from the University of North
Carolina, Jim Halpert!
That's pretty funny.
Hey, you know what? Did I drop my...
What the heck?
Is that...
You find it?
I didn't. I'll look
somewhere else.
All right.
Would you like
fries with that?
Please drive around.
Hello?
Good morning.
You ready?
And we're off.
Like a herd of turtles.
Well, Pam and I
have eloped.
Actually, we just
robbed a bank
and we are on the lam.
No, seriously,
I am on a lecture circuit.
Apparently, Scranton has the best
sales of any regional branch,
so David Wallace has asked me
to go to all the branches
except Nashua.
Still a little bit raw there.
Um... But I am going
to these branches
and I am telling them
my secret recipe for success,
my 11 business herbs and
spices in a sales batter.
Oh, that.
Well, that is Pam.
Pam is coming along as my assistant
and my driver so I can focus.
And I like to pack heavy.
He brought a sled.
No, that is a toboggan.
You never know when you're
going to find a snowy hill.
So...
Every magician
has a hot assistant
and every rock star
has a roadie
and Pam is my hot roadie.
Yeah, I love being
on the road,
but I especially love
the time and a half pay,
24 hours a day
for three days.
'Cause I have a mortgage now.
Got to bring home the bucks.
No, don't say "bucks."
It's not ladylike.
Here we go. Okay, so what
we do is we drive all day
and we stay in hotels together at night.
Separate rooms.
Well, that goes without saying.
I'm gonna say it anyway.
Hey, look at what
you're wearing again, Pam.
Have you ever seen a magician's
assistant? That's...
This is a new cardigan.
Kind of blech.
Maybe you could tie it
around your waist
or lose the shirt
underneath or something.
No.
No? All right.
Hi, Kelly.
Screw you.
Excuse me. That is no way
to address a superior.
Oh, yeah?
Screw you, too.
Whoa. What was
that all about?
You forgot her birthday.
It was yesterday.
Go ahead.
You do it.
Okay.
I insist.
Basically, after Phyllis
blackmailed Angela,
Michael asked them
both to step down
from the Party Planning Committee
because there was too much drama.
What he said was...
Just... Easy.
...there was a problem with having one
head of the Party Planning Committee.
She becomes too powerful,
so he appointed two heads.
Party planning?
I am a paper salesman.
This is literally
the stupidest thing
I've ever done in my life.
This is humiliating.
That's on my side.
So this is fun.
My birthday was yesterday,
and everybody forgot.
I got really dressed up and
excited and no one said a word.
There wasn't
even a party.
I think sometimes people are really
mean to the hot, popular girl.
Can I turn on
the radio?
No, I need silence or
Sam Kinison to prepare.
But then you fall asleep and
there's nothing for me to do.
Then listen to your iPod, Pam.
That's dangerous.
Well, then... Hey, you know what?
Let's just talk.
That's okay. I can...
I'm fine.
I'll just play a song
in my head.
You nervous about
seeing Karen again?
Since she was
the other woman?
Actually, you were
the other woman, so...
No, that was
a long time ago.
Is that why you're
wearing makeup today?
No, I'm not even
wearing that much.
I hate the idea that someone
out there hates me.
I even hate thinking
that al-Qaeda hates me.
I think if they
got to know me,
they wouldn't
hate me.
But Karen knows me and she
still hates me, so...
Oh, this is
a nice office.
You don't have to lie.
Through here.
Um, Phyllis?
Who's that?
She's out of your
league, Andy.
For your information, I've been
with lots of beautiful women.
Sexually?
This conversation is over.
I am single now.
What we have here is the ultimate
smackdown between the Nard-Dog
and crippling despair,
loneliness and depression.
I intend to win.
We just wanted to say
we are very sorry.
Screw you guys.
You're dead to me.
If you say screw you
one more time...
Yeah, screw you, beet farmer, I
didn't forget your birthday.
I would never do that!
Hey! Hey!
Guys, guys, guys.
We just want to make it up to you.
What can we do?
I guess my only wish would be that
nothing so terrible would ever happen
to anyone else ever again.
Oh, God.
Okay.
In a way, it's good that it happened
to me because at least I can bear it.
What kind of cake
do you want, imbecile?
Ice cream.
Okay, point at
the Dunder Mifflin.
Hello, Rolando, how are you? Hi.
Rolando, I'd like
you to meet Pam.
She is our
receptionist.
You know what?
Maybe
you guys could go out on a
little friend date sometime.
You're late. Everyone's waiting
in the conference room.
Karen will be right here
to take you over. Okay.
Don't be nervous.
Just picture her naked.
Stop it.
That's what I do.
Steal my trick.
- Please cut it out.
- Hey.
Hi, guys.
Oh, my God.
Is that Jim's?
- What?
- Michael!
Of course not.
Okay.
Wow. Oh, man.
My head just exploded.
Whoo! Thank God
for everybody, right?
Wow, you're huge!
That's incredible.
I... God, sorry, sorry.
My head is... I'm just...
I'm trying to figure out the last
time that you and Jim had sex, and...
Let's just get this over with, shall we?
Okay. Mmm-hmm.
Ten? Ten months?
Are you kidding?
Well, I'm not done yet.
Dwight, this fits in
the palm of my hand.
You haven't blown
them up enough.
Why have you chosen
brown and gray balloons?
They match the carpet.
What is that?
"It is your birthday,"
period.
It's a statement
of fact.
Not even
an exclamation point?
This is more
professional.
It's not like she discovered
a cure for cancer.
I can't believe
how bad this looks.
Are you trying to
hurt my feelings?
Because, if so,
you are succeeding.
Fortunately, my feelings regenerate
at twice the speed of a normal man's.
Okay, good then.
Have you collected
the money from everyone?
I am working on it.
How much do you have?
$6.
That's how much you and I contributed!
Damn it, Jim!
I said I was
working on it.
Trying to see
what CDs she's got.
It's good to know the deets
about the girl you're wooing.
Uh... Ah-ha!
Feist! Yes!
No!
Oh, my God.
Oh, no. That is so awful.
That is the worst news.
I have to go. I have
to do a presentation.
I'll talk to you...
This is going to be hard
for me to speak today,
because I just learned
that my father has died.
No, he didn't.
He is alive.
And this isn't even a cell phone.
This is a calculator,
but you bought it and now
you can't return it.
Or can you?
No, you can't.
Yes, Karen?
Do you need to go pump?
Not gonna have to do that
until after I have the baby.
No, I am wondering what
are you talking about?
I am talking about how you all
need to sell an experience.
Like I sold you on the idea
that my father had died.
But now we think
you're a liar.
Would a liar bring
mini Mounds bars?
I am a theatrical person.
Growing up I always thought
I would become an actor
because I have these
memorization tricks that I use.
Um...
For instance, I learned
the Pledge of Allegiance
by setting it to the
tune of Old MacDonald.
I pledge allegiance to the flag
of the United States of America
And to the republic
for which it stands
One nation under God
With a woof-woof here
And a woof-woof there
Here a woof, there a woof
Everywhere a woof-woof
You get it.
I don't know you. But I need to
know you in order to sell to you.
That is why I've asked you to go
around and tell me your names.
I have an amazing
mnemonic device
by which I have now memorized
all of your names.
Shirty, mole, lazy eye,
Mexico, baldy,
sugar boobs,
black woman.
I have taken a unique
part of who you are
and I have used that
to memorize your name.
Baldy, your head is bald,
it is hairless,
it is shiny, it is
reflective, like a mirror.
"M," your name is Mark.
Yes.
Got it. It works!
Uh, it's very insulting.
But it works.
I would like you all to give this a shot.
What do you say?
But we already know
each other's names.
Well, then it will be
easier for you.
But I still think it's
worthwhile to give it a try.
Okay, all right, everyone.
Meeting's over.
But I still have more.
Can I please see you
in my office, please?
She is pregnant. She is knocked up.
"K," Karen.
Pam, let's go.
I can't accept
these prices, Stanley.
They just cut
our budget.
Brought you guys
some coffees.
Stanley, I know you have
adult-onset diabetes,
so I put Splenda
in yours.
Let's see, how many
did I put in there?
One, two, three, four Splendas
in your coffee, Stanley
None in yours, Julia, because
I don't know how you take it
But if you'd rather...
Four Splenda?
Are you crazy?
No, I actually
only put in two,
but that's not how
the song goes.
Are you out of
your damn mind?
You bring an angel like
that into this office
and you don't even
set me up with her.
We're not friends.
I didn't think about it.
We are friends.
Stanley, we're friends.
And you let me down.
You really like her, huh?
Yeah, I really like her
with all my heart.
Give me two clients
for her.
I grab this, and I
turn it on and I say,
"Prepare yourself for the
Utica Chain Store Massacre."
No, that is
incredibly dangerous.
No, don't worry,
the chain is off.
No, it's not.
You know, I think I'm just
going to distill all of this
and send it in
an e-mail to my team.
E-mail's not scary. This is an opportunity.
Don't blow it.
So, when are you due?
Uh, in about a month.
Wow, that is wonderful.
Congratulations.
Thank you. It just
all happened so fast.
It's really amazing.
Congratulations, Karen. Thanks.
So is there a guy
or a person
or a sperm machine
that did this to you or...
Yes, Michael.
My husband impregnated me.
Great.
His name is Dan.
This is us. We're so dorky.
That's cute.
Yes, thank you.
He's a dermatologist. We met at a bar.
Can you believe that?
What is happening there?
Oh, yeah, don't even...
That's really dorky.
It's really sweet.
No, it's really dorky.
You were right
the first time.
So how are things in Scranton?
How's Jim?
They're good.
Jim's good.
We're engaged.
That's so great.
That's great.
Thank you.
Oh, my God.
I'm so happy for you.
Oh, wow. Thank you.
Old hatreds dissolve
into new friendships.
This is really
a wonderful moment.
I have to take care
of a couple of things,
so Andy will be
taking over things here.
You are in good hands and
give my best to your mother.
So, Julia, um,
let's see.
With regards to billing,
should we send bills
to you or to your
boyfriend's house, or...
No, it can go straight
to our business address.
Oh, okay. All right.
That makes sense.
How does your boyfriend deal
with your phenomenal success?
Is he just, like, totally
threatened by you, or...
Actually, I don't
have a boyfriend.
Really? Is that...
Wow, that's so weird.
Guys, stop everything.
I'm about to ask out this girl
and I'm completely panicking.
Oh, my desk
is over...
This gal,
she's really into you?
Yeah. Yeah, I mean,
I've seen her like
three times today
and we love
all the same music
and whenever I walk into a
room she totally looks up.
All right, say no more. This
is how I got Squeaky Fromme.
No small talk. Just show
her who's the boss.
Just go right in
and kiss her.
Okay, it sounds risky.
Have I ever steered
you wrong, Jim?
Wait, what?
I would give that
lecture a solid B-plus.
Although, for the record,
Karen, wow, kind of mean.
I like her.
Really? No, honestly. Tell
me what you really think.
I'm serious.
I'm really glad I came.
Why?
Because, um...
Because I'll never wonder ever
again if I did something wrong,
and now I have closure.
She's happy,
and, I don't know,
it feels good.
Thanks for
walking me out.
Oh, my pleasure. Yeah, there's all
kinds of weirdoes out here, so...
You must be freezing.
I am about to die.
Will you wait here
while I go get my jacket?
No, it's okay.
This is my car.
Okay. Okay.
Well, listen,
you're a new client and
as one of my new clients
you will always
be taken care of
and that is
the Nard-Dog guarantee.
What's a Nard-Dog?
This is the Nard-Dog.
Whoa! What the hell?
Oh...
I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
I thought
we had this energy
and I'm a mess and I
just had my heart broken
and you came in today
and you're so pretty.
You're, like,
incredibly pretty.
I just got out of a relationship, too.
It's really hard.
Yeah, right? Wow.
Do you want to
talk about it?
Go to a mall or something,
just walk around?
No, I don't think so.
Sure, yeah, you're right.
It's too soon.
Definitely too soon
for me,
so I'm glad we got
that out of the way.
I'm going to be in touch
with you in three months.
I'm going to call you
about that order.
And maybe
about that mall walk.
Okay.
Take care, Julia.
Thank you.
Sorry I tried
to kiss...
We lost the account.
Damn it!
- Dwight Schrute.
- How old is Kelly?
Who is this?
It's Mose.
Who do you think it is?
Mose doesn't know how to use
a phone, so joke's on you.
Look, I'm at the supermarket and
they only have numbered candles.
How old is she?
Twenty-four.
Thirty-seven.
Do you think I'm calling you
for your best approximation?
I'll call you back.
I have here Kelly Kapoor's
personal and confidential file.
Allow me to share.
"Kelly Kapoor spent April
1995 to December 1996
"at Berks County
Youth Center."
Juvie.
"According to past employers, it in no way
affects her job..." Blah, blah, blah.
Are you asleep?
No.
Just thinking about
what you said.
About Karen,
about closure.
You remember Holly?
She used to work for HR.
No, remind me.
Blonde hair,
nice boobs.
Not too big,
not too small.
Perfect boobs. Of course
I remember Holly.
She was the
love of my life.
What you and Jim have times a hundred.
Just... She...
She just left
and I didn't...
I never got closure.
You know? I never
got closure with her.
I haven't talked to her since.
I haven't seen her since.
And I feel like I need to go
to Nashua and get closure.
I feel like
I need that.
Okay. Let's go.
Oh, just blow off
the lecture at Rochester?
Yeah. Screw them,
let's do this.
Okay.
I am collecting $3 from
everybody for Kelly's party.
I'd like to contribute.
Oh, great.
Here you go.