Previously on Prison Break.
It's the only building on top of those tunnels.
All we gotta do is get in there, on PI,
and dig ourselves an on-ramp.
I'm gonna find out, you know,
what it is you're doing up there.
If we talked about who had motive
to kill Terrence, we'd be here all day.
- To do with EcoField?
- Do the math. CEO gets indicted for fraud.
Investors start losing money. Lots of money.
- Call Nick Savrinn. Works for Project Justice.
- They're here.
Who's here? LJ? LJ!
- You gotta come get me.
- We can't, we're not in Chicago. Come to us.
- First of the month's coming up, John.
- Yeah. So?
I checked my balance.
It's looking deficient.
Apparently Fibonacci's
coming up for air again.
If he testifies at that hearing
a lot of people are going down,
including me.
Listen. There, uh...
there's been a restructuring.
This comes from Philly himself.
So I'm the man in here now.
What the hell are you doin'? Aargh!
Uh-oh. We got a problem.
Bellick? What's going on?
That's PI. I run it.
Not any more, you don't.
Bellick.
- Hey, boss.
- Check that volume, inmate.
We've been doing business too long.
We can fix this thing, right?
Let's get something clear. You and I haven't
done crap. Falzone's the one payin' me.
He's just an envelope. You've been
doing business with me face to face.
You think I like getting piss thrown at me?
Spit on?
Other chumps might do it for 40 grand a year
and the little uniform, but I'm not that dumb.
Falzone's envelope is the only reason
I come through that fence every day.
And it's the only reason
I'm gonna keep coming through that fence
until I have enough money
to buy a house on Lake Gray.
I'm thinking early retirement, John.
And you're interfering with that.
Hey, boss. Just give me some time and I can
match whatever Falzone's paying you.
You're out of business. Get used to it.
Hey, boss. Boss!
They're gonna find it. The longer they're
in there, the sooner they're gonna find it.
Then we gotta get back in there.
- I'm gonna say something crazy to you now.
- Surprise, surprise.
- I don't give a damn about that Fibonacci.
- You're right. That is crazy.
Because I got bigger things to think about,
like survival.
Then why are we talking about Fibonacci?
The only way I can get that room back
is if I can prove to Falzone I'm still worthy,
that I've still got what it takes. Yeah?
And the only way I can do that
is if I can give him Fibonacci.
Interesting.
You see, this is not
a me-versus-you thing any more. This is us.
An us thing, all right? It's us for the escape.
Is it? Or is this about you getting back
in good with the Mob again?
That life is over for me, fish.
I mean, they clipped my wings.
They want me to rot in here,
so I got no allegiance to them any more.
And yet you still want to do them a favour.
Falzone is desperate.
See, if Fibonacci testifies
in front of the Congress next month,
Falzone's gonna go down in flames.
But if we give him Fibonacci,
he will give us anything.
Anything. Including that very special room.
What do you say, fish?
"And the Lord said unto Satan,
'Hast thou considered my servant Job?"'
"'That there is none like him in the earth.
A perfect and an upright man."'
"'One that fears God and shuns evil."'
- Give him up.
- They'll kill him.
- Maybe he deserves it.
- That's just it. He doesn't.
Who is this guy? You told me he was Mafia.
He was working for the Mafia.
He just didn't know it.
Otto Fibonacci is... He's just like you.
An innocent man,
caught in the wrong place at the wrong time.
- What are you doing?
- You know I didn't steal from you, John.
He was management
at one of Abruzzi's warehouses.
Just a normal guy-
working class, religious.
Hey, Nicky. Nicky, Nicky, Nicky. Sh.
What did I tell you about talking?
John, please.
Johnny, please! No!
Somebody that couldn't
turn his back on murder.
He realised that Abruzzi and Falzone,
the men he worked for, were killers.
He had the key to their dealings
that could put them away for life.
And now he's in witness protection for life.
The judge asked why he was coming forward
with this information.
He said it was because
he thought it was the right thing to do.
What's the right thing to do now, Michael?
I don't know.
But if I don't give him up,
this whole thing's over.
What you're telling me is if... if I'm to live...
A good man has to die.
- Kellerman.
- You're where we discussed?
Yes. I'm still not exactly sure
why we're here, but...
- A friend of mine should be along shortly.
- A friend?
Just to see where you are with things.
We're clear on where we are.
Everything's under control.
Nothing will affect tomorrow,
if you're worried.
I'm not worried about tomorrow.
My friend is a problem solver, that's all.
He's there at your disposal if you need him.
Do me a favour,
make him feel like part of the team, hm?
Talk soon.
- What?
- She's bringing someone in.
- What does that mean?
- Something in her tone changed.
You think she knows about the kid?
We don't know that.
We shouldn't have told her we had the kid.
What is it you don't understand? We tell her
that kid got away, we are not here now.
- I swear to God, it gets deeper and deeper.
- What is that supposed to mean?
It means, if I'd have known
how this was gonna turn out,
I'd have got some crap job with the feds.
Pushed pencils.
Drank coffee all day long behind a desk.
God, that sounds good.
Keep talking like that, I'm gonna be forced
to put a bullet in your head.
As for her friend, whoever that is,
we find out what he wants,
we play nice, we deal with it accordingly.
Michael, you better see this.
Jersey! Are you putting
that carpet in the guards' room?
Yeah, I think so.
- When?
- We gotta tear up the old stuff first.
As soon as we're done with that.
Tonight, tomorrow maybe.
They're gonna find it, bro.
They're gonna find the hole.
We gotta do something.
Linc. Chow.
- What's this?
- It's for, you know...
your last meal.
Write down what you want.
Linc, you gotta write something down.
I ain't gotta do nothin'.
If you don't fill it out, all they're gonna
give you is what's on chow for that day.
- So?
- You don't want that for your last meal, man.
Hm?
In case you think of something.
Hey, Eyetie.
Something you need there, rug head?
Yeah, ajob, man.
Why don't you hit the DQ down the street?
We're not hiring.
I'll put a hundred in your kick every month.
You wanna pay me to work?
I've been in the kitchen for eight months.
I scrub one more tray, I'm gonna go j cat.
Hey! Fiorello, how about it?
Yeah, yeah.
150.
Sign me up, then, baby.
I was thinking about what you said -
that it's not a me-versus-you thing,
it's an us thing.
- That's right.
- How far are you willing to go with that?
- As far as I have to.
- Then set up a meeting with Falzone.
I wanna talk to him directly.
Falzone doesn't talk to guys like you directly.
If he wants Fibonacci, he's gonna have to.
No, no. No, you heard me right.
This kid is gonna give up
Fibonacci? Sure?
I'm definite. Only one thing,
he wants to meet with you directly.
Son of a bitch. You actually did
something right. That's good.
Guess I'll have to call off
those guys I hired to shank you.
- That was a joke, John.
- Funny.
Good. I'll come out there this afternoon.
And, John, if I come all the way out there
and this turns out to be a waste of my time,
I'm gonna castrate you.
I hope you understand that.
- Be well, my friend.
- I love you too.
He's coming.
Don't mess this up.
- Hello?
- It's me.
I know. I saw "Inmate" on the caller ID.
Remember when I said
I might be calling you on Fibonacci?
- Yes.
- Well... it's time.
- You seem distracted.
- Got a lot on my mind, I guess.
Yeah?
Have anything to do with
the people who took these toes?
- Nice flowers.
- Right.
- Do we have an admirer?
- They're from my father.
Ah.
- What's the occasion?
- It's my birthday.
- Today?
- Mm-hm.
- Happy birthday.
- Thank you.
OK.
Huh.
Nothing. Birthday's aren't usually
a sore subject, that's all.
Unless the celebrant is feeling her age,
which I don't see how you could be.
I'm 29 years old, Michael.
I'm not feeling my age.
It's just, out of those 29 birthdays,
my father has managed to see me
on precisely six of them.
So, I get flowers instead.
Flowers that end up dead
and in the trash a week later.
- That sounded bitter, huh?
- Kind of.
It's not a big deal.
You are all set. I will see you tomorrow.
OK.
I'm sorry you feel that way.
About the flowers, I mean.
- Hey, I want these in the other room.
- I got it, boss.
Hey, chill, lily white. I got it.
Come on,
I know you're around here somewhere.
- He's not doing well, is he?
- He just lost his mother.
Ten days from now, he loses his father.
How are you holding up?
You know, I...
I sort of get
what you're going through here, LJ.
No disrespect, but I don't know that you do.
No, with my dad,
I was in the same spot when I was your age.
He was in prison,
and like your dad, he was innocent.
What happened?
I mean, you know, at the end.
What I hope happens here -
he got exonerated.
- What did they say he did?
- A lot of bad things.
They weren't true, and we proved that.
Every day. Every day was a lost cause,
but we kept fighting.
I mean, what else are you gonna do when you
love somebody? Let them go out like that?
So you fight. You keep fighting.
You never give up.
We're gonna beat this thing.
OK?
- Hello.
You were expecting me?
A mutual friend arranged it.
- Yes.
- You mind if I?
Please.
Hey, how are...
- I'm sorry, I didn't get your name.
- Quinn.
Mr Quinn,
mind telling us what we're doing here?
You can probably tell just by looking at me,
I'm not a wave-making sort.
Just think of me as a supervisor
who's here to make sure things are under
control as we approach... the big event.
I wasn't aware that things were out of control.
Well, you'd be the one that would know,
wouldn't you?
Well, the reason I'm here is because
there's a discrepancy between what you know
and what you have said to the vice president.
The lawyers you tried to blow up
are still healthy as thoroughbreds.
You know it, I know it.
Same thing goes with the kid,
who you were silly enough to tell the old lady
that you were actually in possession of.
Everything that I'm saying
is boiling down to this.
You gotta hand the reins over to me now,
so that I can save your ass.
First of all...
No! No.
See, now you made me make a wave.
You and your partner are off the job
until further notice.
It doesn't come from me
or from the White House -
it comes from the company. You understand?
Your proximal and middle phalanx are
broken. Ice it for 45 minutes then splint it.
That's what a doctor would tell you to do,
so you don't need to go see one.
EcoField's SEC filings.
Steadman was murdered so information
from his indictment wouldn't be public.
Sure, but we have no way of knowing
what they were trying to cover up.
Steadman's wife said there were
hundreds of millions of dollars at stake.
So I figure we follow the money
and see where it takes us.
109 million, 212 million.
Over half a billion dollars I've found so far
in federal grants to EcoField
for alternative fuel research.
- That is a hell of a lot.
- But for what?
Not only did the company
never make a profit,
as far as I can tell, they never made anything.
No fuel sales, no patents,
no findings, nothing.
So EcoField was a sham. It was a cover.
The question is, for what?
Philly.
Sit down, kid.
So...
Fibonacci - how'd you find him?
I did my homework.
You get elliptical with me
for one more second and I will cancel you.
- You understand me?
- Give it up, fish.
Before someone's transferred to the marshals
and placed in protection,
they're guarded by a local sheriff
from the county where the trial will take place.
- Sheriff Solomon, please.
- Please hold.
Andrew Solomon here.
If the sheriff was available,
he wasn't the one guarding Fibonacci.
- Putnam County Sheriff's Office.
- Yeah, is Sheriff Pronzo there?
I'm sorry. Sheriff Pronzo's on vacation.
- Really?
- Yes, sir.
There are only four sheriffs in the county.
Since Pronzo was the only one not in his
office, and his wife and kids were at home,
I knew the only vacation
he was taking was with Fibonacci.
Watching him
till they could put him in protection.
Thing is, sometimes it takes weeks
for the marshals to set up a new identity,
so some local sheriff is stuck
in the middle of nowhere with Fibonacci.
He gets Ionely and calls home - a lot.
I called the phone company,
said I was Pronzo and I'd lost my bill.
I asked for another copy.
Mrs Pronzo was receiving dozens of calls
from an area code a long way from Chicago.
I went online,
reverse-traced the number, and voilà:
There was Fibonacci's exact location.
- How do you know he's still there?
- I have someone looking after him.
- Watching from afar, in case he moves.
- Mm-hm.
- This is about money, isn't it?
- You're an astute man.
- What?
- Your friend here is trying to extort me.
Not extortion, insurance.
I plan on being out of here one day.
I don't think my new résumé
is gonna cut it in most places.
- How much?
- 200,000.
- I'm gonna kill you.
- Quid pro quo.
You scratch my back, I scratch yours.
Well, I'll give you some quid pro quo.
Where did you get this?
Who took this?
Since you took it upon yourself to have
people watch our interests on the outside,
we took it upon ourselves
to have some people watching yours.
So who's it gonna be?
Fibonacci or your pretty little girlfriend there?
Yeah, you should be careful with who
visits you in here, fish. These walls have eyes.
If you touch her,
I'll kill you myself.
One, that is an empty threat.
You are less than a gnat to me.
And two,
all you gotta do is give me the address
and we avoid all this melodrama altogether.
The address, you gnat.
Now.
Promise me...
promise me it'll be quick and painless.
- Do you believe this guy?
- Promise me.
If the next thing that comes out
of your mouth is not that address,
there's gonna be a lot of pain...
in a lot of places.
Canada.
345 Hamilton Avenue,
Thunder Bay, Ontario.
Get outta here.
Nice work, John.
I guess the demise of John Abruzzi
was greatly exaggerated.
Thank you. I appreciate it.
Could you do me a favour
and fix this Bellick thing for me?
Yeah, consider it done.
Thank you. And Philly.
Before you pull the trigger,
look that son of a bitch in his eyes
and tell him John Abruzzi said goodbye.
"In the race toward worldwide peace
and prosperity, America will set the pace."
"Race"? Rat race, arms race...
Can you think of a word
with a worse connotation?
Fix it.
Did you send me a baby-sitter?
- This is not the time or the place.
- This is the time and the place.
Don't take that tone.
Remember who you are talking to.
I am vice president of this country.
No, actually you're Caroline Reynolds
from Montgomery, Illinois.
I know exactly who you are.
Come with me.
Just...
There is something you need to understand.
If you had done yourjob,
I never would've had to ask for Quinn.
And there's something
you need to understand.
You woke a sleeping beast
when you called these guys in.
They have a bigger agenda than us and get
nasty quick if things don't go their way.
So now no one is safe -
not you, not me.
Let's not overreact. I mean, I know everyone
is nervous about tomorrow. I understand that.
But the one thing both of us have to
remember is that we are in this together, OK?
All I'm saying is these guys are into this thing
now, and there's no going back.
That's bad news for everyone.
Sebastian Balfour?
- Yeah.
- Yeah, I'm Nestor Pollack.
Midwestern Life and Casualty.
I'm already covered. Thanks.
- No, I'm here to discuss Veronica Donovan.
- What about her?
We've been trying to track her down with
respect to the damage from the explosion.
- Explosion?
- You didn't know. Oh, I'm sorry.
It's just that her records,
they list you as her fiancé, so I assumed...
- Hold on. Is Veronica OK?
- Well, there has been a fatality.
But the medical examiners haven't been able
to identify the remains with any certainty,
so Veronica could be OK, we just can't
find her. We were hoping you could help.
Rozz.
Reese.
Burrows.
Blueberry pancakes, huh?
All right, man. You got it.
Blueberry pancakes.
341...
345.
This is it.
All right, that's it, kids.
Time for bed. Give me a kiss.
Are you OK down there?
Night-night.
All right, sweetheart. Give me a kiss.
- The kids are down.
- Thanks.
Tonight we send a message, gentlemen.
We are gonna hurt him and his family
the way he hurt ours.
- Oh, honey.
- Yeah?
- Can you change the timer on the sprinkler?
- OK.
- Love you.
- Love you too.
Freeze!
Police! Drop your weapons!
Drop it!
Down!
Hi, it's John. You wanted to talk to me?
Yeah. You hear the news?
Falzone got popped last night, up in Canada.
International gun charges, parole violation...
He's in deep.
- You threw away your flowers.
- Like I said, they don't last.
I don't think they're dead yet.
I don't like getting attached to things
if I know they won't last.
- There you go.
- Why are you so cynical?
- I think there's cynicism and there's realism.
- And there's optimism. Hope, faith.
Coming from an eight-toed guy
locked in a penitentiary?
Toes are overrated.
Thank you for trying to make me smile.
Not today.
- You never know.
- We're all set.
You and I have a lot to talk about,
don't we, fish?
Seems Philly Falzone
ran into some problem up in Canada
just because of the information you gave him.
- What kind of trouble?
- International gun charges, parole violation.
He's gonna go away for a long time.
How do you feel about that?
Pretty darn good.
- And what about PI?
- We got that back too.
Falzone paid Bellick yesterday,
so we're good. For now.
- It all worked out.
- Sure did.
Nicely done. You're a hell of an actor.
Thank you.
This helped. It's nice.
Nice shot.
Where did you take it?
It's Lincoln's from back in the day.
A camping trip or something.
- So when do we get back in that room?
- Right away.
- Well, let's get to it.
- Yeah.
Oh, there's one more thing.
You are gonna give me Fibonacci
once we're outside these walls, right?
Of course.
Thank you.
And I think I'll keep this,
as insurance.
- Juice?
- Why can't we have breakfast every day?
You should have breakfast every day, LJ.
It's an important meal.
No, why can't I have breakfast with
you every day?
Nothing would make me happier.
But your mommy and me,
we don't live together any more.
Why?
Well, uh...
sometimes that happens
with mommies and daddies.
But you know what?
You're the luckiest boy in the world,
because your mommy loves you very much
and I love you very much.
I tell you what, how about every Sunday
we have our own special breakfast?
- Just you and me. Yeah?
- Yeah.
- Little bit or a handful?
- Handful.
Handful.
Here we go.
Take a walk.
Anyone else want to walk with him?
Yeah.
- This is my game.
- Looks like our friend got his throne back.
Looks like it.
Something tells me
we may have you to thank for that.
- You don't want to know.
- Right.
Stretch your legs, old head.
Now, we got a hell of a lot
to talk about, don't we?
I got nothing to say.
You think you can play me, snowflake?
Cos you got college?
Big-school learning, huh?
Well, let me school you.
Darwin wins inside these walls.
Not Einstein, Darwin.
Yard time's over, ladies.
Let's line it up.
I'm not done with you, fish.
You never even got started.
All right.
We're through the hard part.
Another 18 inches, we'll hit that pipe.
- We'll be there by Friday.
- Friday?
- Better start making travel arrangements.
- Maricruz, here I come.
- Sardinia.
- Where are we going?
- Panama.
Panama. Darien Gap, south of the canal.
No roads, no electricity, no cops.
Nothing but white sand beaches
and ice-cold beer.
- Well, that's nice, but what about our lives?
- Well, we'll open a scuba shop.
- Hey, I don't dive.
- Neither do I.
We'll have plenty of time to learn.
Bulls.
This con says he's on ajob in here.
- I don't think so.
- You heard the paisano. Move your ass.
CO, hold on one second.
Now, are you sure about that?
Are you sure you can't use an extra hand?
You know anything about construction?
Concrete is my specialty. Can you dig it?
OK, boss. Sign him up.
You got it.
Now it looks like Darwin wins after all,
eh, fish?
I have a lot of dots,
but no way to connect them.
- Nobody's getting rich.
- What about shareholders?
Profits were all converted back to shares.
Looks like they subcontracted out
some research -
it's pennies in the scheme of things.
Nobody got early retirement.
But you can't hide $500 million
by moving a few decimal points.
In a move anticipated by many, Reynolds
announced she is running for the presidency.
She made the announcement
from her hometown of Montgomery.
The move toward worldwide peace
and prosperity is a marathon, not a sprint,
but I assure you,
America will be setting the pace.
$0.5 billion doesn't disappear.
You could run a small country with that.
The vice president is reported to have
the largest campaign war chest in history.
It is so large, in fact,
prognosticators are already casting her
as the favourite in the presidential race.
Maybe not a small country.
Maybe this one.