Previously on "Prison Break":
Think of this place like a map of the
US. Our cell over there, that's New York City.
The infirmary, our exit, that's California.
The pipes beneath us that connect the two...
- Route 66.
- Our ticket out of here.
Route 66 runs beneath that building. It's the
only building sitting on top of those tunnels.
All we gotta do is get in there,
on PI, and dig ourselves an onramp.
- Which one?
- Right there.
This goes down four feet.
Connects to the main line below.
All we've gotta do is widen it and
we've got ourselves an onramp to Route 66.
I'm gonna find out, you know,
what it is you're doing up there.
You told me that
you had been up in the crawlspace for PI,
and PI was never assigned to go there.
We got you a little get well gift.
What's your name?
There was an explosion.
Gas line. Everyone inside was killed.
- These people won't stop until we're dead.
- We can't hide forever.
- How about that kid?
- The one killed his parents?
Oh, they got him. He's in custody.
I know what you look like, you son of a bitch.
Philly Falzone.
Word is someone knows where Fibonacci is
and you're not doing anything about it.
Help me.
Please.
You'll have to forgive my boy.
He has the propensity to be a bit gregarious
when he shouldn't be.
Fraternising in the prison shower. Come on.
Maybe you oughta cut the kid a break.
You wouldn't be meddling in my affairs,
now, would you?
You can't be that stupid.
Not while I'm so fully invested in your affairs.
What's between you and him
is between you and him.
That's what I thought you said.
You've gotta help me.
- You gotta help me.
- This is a matter for the police.
This is my son we're talking about.
He's missing. Do something!
You have got to understand,
I am the warden of a prison.
When it comes to the law,
there is nothing I can do.
Whatever happens is out of my jurisdiction
until it comes through those gates.
- Itjust did. Let me out.
- What?
Let me find him. I know how he thinks.
I know where he'd run.
That ain't true. In case of a family emergency,
you can grant an inmate supervised leave.
Your son is a prime suspect
in a double homicide.
Hey.
What do you think this is, a siesta?
You see that? You see my face up there?
Any idea how it got there?
Work ethic. Those two words
mean anything in your country?
You're on PI, so quit slow-walking me.
I'm not gonna warn you again.
What are you looking at?
The bulls find this stuff,
they'll know we're digging.
That's why we gotta get rid of it.
One piece at a time.
- Attention in the yard.
- All prisoners remain 40ft away from gate A.
New prisoners arriving in five minutes.
I repeat, attention in the yard.
All prisoners remain 40ft away from gate A.
New prisoners arriving in five minutes.
Attention in the yard. All prisoners maintain
a 40ft perimeter around gate A.
Freshmen.
Best put on ourjail face, BG.
These crabs see you puckering,
they bitchify you in a heartbeat.
- I gotta find something else to call you now.
- Why's that?
Cos you ain't a fish no more.
You ain't the newest con in the tank.
I could've done something.
No.
T-Bag had his hooks in that kid.
There was nothing you could have done.
I could've told the Pope.
He could've transferred the kid to ADSEG.
Go easy, Michael. You didn't even know him.
And that makes it OK? I turned my back
on him because I didn't wanna make waves.
It was just... easier
to look the other way,
keep the plan safe.
And you did.
But at what price?
That's not how she raised us.
A man's down, you give him your hand.
She'd roll over in her grave if she knew.
She wouldn't.
You've given me your hand, Michael.
My son's out there
with a bull's eye on his back.
Do whatever you gotta do
to get us out of here. Please.
What are you doing?
I was just looking for some coffee.
There isn't any.
They belonged to my father,
if you were wondering.
- How long have they been in there?
- I don't know. Five years?
You know, Veronica, we've been through a lot
and I'm freaking out here as much as you are,
but you get this look in your eye sometimes
like... like I'm the bad guy.
I don't know who you are. You just magically
show up like some knight in shining armour.
You know, I think
you seem to be forgetting something here.
I'm in the cross hairs the same way you are,
all for your ex, who is a scumbag criminal
who just happens to be in prison
for the one crime he didn't commit.
You know something? I got enough of my
own crap to deal with. You wanna go, you go.
- Mind if I lamp with you, cuzzo?
- Roll, snowflake.
Hey, man, I'm just... I'm just new, you know?
I'm looking for some homies.
- I said roll.
- Brother, I'm just launching.
Yeah? Well, launch somewhere else,
white boy.
All right, y'all.
I'm fitting to bounce.
Peace.
Boy's a bit confused about his pigmentation,
but he sure does have spunk, doesn't he?
- Abruzzi!
- Yeah?
What are you doing?
What do you mean, what am I doing?
- First of the month's coming up, John.
- Yeah? So?
I haven't got my monthly.
- What?
- I checked my balance. It's looking deficient.
Uh...
It's gotta be some kind of a mistake,
like an accounting error.
Yeah. Tell Falzone
I don't stand for accounting errors.
I'm going back into my office at the end of
the day. Gonna check my balance again.
If it's not up to where it's supposed to be,
all these privileges you got,
like running PI,
they're gone.
Get it done, John.
- Falzone Enterprises.
- Get Philly.
- Mr Falzone's not available.
- You tell him it's John Abruzzi calling.
- I'm sorry. I didn't realise.
- Well, now you do.
Um...
- I'm sorry. He's gonna have to call you back.
- What? Hey...
I'm sorry. About before.
Pressure's getting to us, that's all.
Good news is nobody can reach us out here.
My old man made sure of that.
Never even hooked up the telephone.
Same with the well and the generator.
I used to think he was
some kind of conspiracy theory wacko.
- Turns out maybe he was right.
- I can't stay, Nick.
I gotta get back. He's got less than two weeks.
The old man called this his serious tie.
He only wore it
when he really, really meant business.
Be dangerous showing our faces again.
Not if they're not looking for us.
They think we're dead.
Yeah, but how long is that gonna last?
Gotta be quick, be smart about it.
We're just gonna be running in circles
if we think we can find exculpatory evidence
before the execution.
I've gone up against every prosecutor
in Cook County.
Man gets murdered, the first person they
talk to to see who his enemies were, the wife.
- You wanna go after the queen bee herself?
- Leslie Steadman.
Everyone in town knows the old bird
lunches at the Lexington every day
with the society set.
Hey, hey. Hey, hey!
Slow down. Slow down!
Man, your brother's gonna give us away.
- Bull's coming.
- Let's move.
Hurry up, guys. Move it.
- All right.
- Everybody out.
- What?
- I said everybody out.
Now.
Move it!
- Where are we going?
- Around the corner.
And don't move a damn muscle
till I come get you. Go!
What the hell's going on?
- We're so bad, aren't we?
- You're damn skippy. Let's go.
- You gotta give us more of a warning.
- I'm sorry. He just showed up.
Mm. Mm. Mm.
Oh, we're gonna get caught
by the warden. Oh!
Baby, right now,
in this room, at this moment,
- I am the warden.
- Oh!
- Then say it.
- No.
- Come on, baby, say it.
- Oh!
- Say it.
- You're the warden, Louis!
Yes, yes.
The sneaky son of a bitch.
You think he found the hole?
Another inch and he'd have found it. We need
to find something to cover this hole ASAP.
Broke. What do you mean, broke?
The C-Corp, the investment accounts,
even the offshore stuff, Caymans, Bermuda...
Philly Falzone liquidated everything.
Hey, I told you from the beginning
what would happen if you screwed me.
I heeded it. That's why I warned you from the
get-go not to give Philly power of attorney.
We had that conversation, remember?
Look, the only real funds you have left
are the 30,000 in your wife's pocket account.
- Now, I can...
- Don't. Don't touch that.
Nobody touches that but her.
What do I tell her? You know, about all this?
Don't tell her anything, OK?
The statements are going to come.
She's going to know.
Hey, I told you.
Don't tell her.
All right?
You got a problem with that?
OK, John. You know where to contact me
if you need anything else.
The same goes for you.
Hey.
Hey!
- Philly.
- You.
So good to see you.
For you, the answer's always yes, Philly.
Sit down.
- Sit down.
- Come on, John.
There's no record
of a Fox River medical practice
on our list of participating HMOs or PPOs.
That's because we're a state penitentiary,
and we're in kind of a unique situation here.
Mr Scofield's insurance policy
from his previous employer hasn't lapsed.
The state's demanding that you pay
for his treatment and not the taxpayers.
OK. Well, it says here
he already met his deductible.
OK.
Oh, no, wait. That's his psych deductible,
not his medical.
Sorry. Psych as in psychiatric?
Did I give you permission to call Philly?
Hey, I asked you a question, man.
Listen. There, uh...
there's been a restructuring.
This comes from Philly himself.
You couldn't deliver Fibonacci,
so I'm the man in here now.
Run to the commissary and get me a packet
of chips. We'll pretend this never happened.
No, I'm telling you, John. The sooner you face
these facts, the better off we will all be.
I can kill you in a heartbeat.
Somehow, I doubt that.
The sooner you face facts,
the better off we will all be.
You're yesterday's news, John.
- What's the word? Y'all cooking brownies?
- Act your race, milk chicken.
What's the deal, yo?
You got tough buckets or something?
You're a disgrace to your skin,
you know that?
The boy just slipped.
Ain't that right?
- Come on. Stand up.
- Cons, let's get back to your cells.
What's your name, boy?
- Who's that?
- Stolte.
Stolte. You've heard about my kid, right?
- Take the tray, Linc.
- I, uh...
I just need to call him.
Just take the tray, or I'm gonna shove it
in there and you can eat it off the ground.
You have a son. Josh.
Don't do anything stupid, Linc.
I'm not. I just wanna ask you a question,
then I'm gonna let go.
What if it were Josh?
What if it were your son?
Please.
- Dad?
- LJ. Thank God. Are you all right?
No. Nowhere near it.
- What do you mean? Where are you?
- What they're saying about me, it's not true.
- I know it's not true.
- They killed her. They killed her.
Right in front of me.
Right in front of my eyes.
- You gotta...
- Why are they doing this?
You gotta step up. You gotta be the man now.
- You understand me, LJ?
- Yeah.
- OK. I want you to call Veronica.
- Her number is disconnected. I already tried.
Nick Savrinn. You call Nick Savrinn.
Works for Project Justice.
You call him once we're done. You got it?
Nick Savrinn. OK.
- OK, I'll call. I'll call.
- All right, man.
Hang in there, man. It's gonna be all right.
Hey...
- They're here.
- Who's here?
LJ?
LJ!
You hear that?
Did you hear it?
You know what that means?
Why don't you ask your mom what it means?
Oh, I'm sorry. You might have trouble getting
an answer out of her right about now, huh?
LJ?
- I saw that.
- Just getting connected, that's all.
There she is.
Mrs Steadman? I'm Dick Sisler.
This is Francette Kelly
of the National Victims' Rights Association.
We assist victims of violent crimes, gather
support for tough-on-crime politicians.
If your organisation's looking for a hand-out,
you can go through my business manager.
Ma'am, that is not why we're here, actually.
May we sit down?
We hoped you could help us with one of our
more public cases. The Lincoln Burrows case.
He's making claims that he's innocent, that
others had motive to murder your husband.
- I don't have time for a long conversation.
- It doesn't have to be long.
If we talked about who had motive
to kill Terrence, we'd be here all day.
- I'm sorry?
- Look around.
Half the people here
were shareholders in his company.
Every one of them
sat at my husband's memorial
and every one of them was thinking
the same thing: "Thank God he's gone."
- Why would they think that?
- Money.
As soon as rumours of the indictment started,
they ran for the exits.
- I wasn't aware of any indictment.
- It never came down. He died first.
- Anything to do with Ecofield?
- Do the math. CEO gets indicted for fraud.
Investors start losing money. Lots of money.
If I didn't know Burrows pulled that trigger,
I'd say it was any one of these people in the
restaurant. We're talking half a billion dollars.
People have killed for a lot less.
Hey, what's up? 'Sup?
Not a good position
you find yourself in, is it?
Whites don't want you. Blacks don't want you.
You're just caught in the middle, aren't you?
A regular 'tweener.
We're different, you and me, lot of ways.
But, you know,
the funny thing is we're also a lot alike.
Couple of dogs with runny noses
that nobody loves.
How's that knee, by the way?
- What the hell are you doing?
- Don't get me wrong. I'm just a friend.
- A fruity friend. I don't need none of that.
- Easy.
No. No. You think you're getting up in this,
you got another thing coming, you homo.
- You got a foul mouth, you know that?
- Yeah. I do.
And you come near me again,
I'm gonna kill you.
Well, then,
you're just gonna have to, little man.
- You sleep with one eye open.
- Bring it on.
- Oh, I'm gonna bring it on in spades.
- You oughta leave that kid alone.
Maybe you are in no position
to be telling me my business. Hm?
That's what I thought.
I'm sure you can understand
my reluctance to discuss past patients.
My understanding is that under HIPAA
we're allowed to share information
as long as it furthers the care of the patient.
I'm not accustomed to making
enquiries like this, but I...
I feel like I can get through to him.
I can help him.
- I imagine he needs it in there.
- What did you treat him for?
Michael suffered from a couple of things.
One was a condition
called low latent inhibition.
Sorry. I'm not familiar with the term.
People who suffer from low latent inhibition
see everyday things like you or I do,
like this lamp.
But where we just process the image
of a lamp, they process everything.
The stem, the bulb, the bolts,
even the washers inside.
Their brains are more open to incoming
stimuli in the surrounding environment.
Other people's brains - yours and mine -
shut out the same information.
We have to do it in order to keep our sanity.
If someone with a low IQ
has low latent inhibition,
it almost always results in mental illness.
But if someone has a high IQ,
it almost always results in creative genius.
Do you think Michael's a genius?
Well, I think that word's been derogated
in the media these days.
But in the classic sense of the word, yes, I do.
You... you said there was something else
you treated him for?
He came to me
with absolutely no sense of self-worth.
The loss of both parents
very often does that to a child.
But with the low latent inhibition,
something interesting happened to Michael.
He became very attuned
to all the suffering around him.
He couldn't shut it out.
He became a rescuer,
one of those people who are more concerned
with other people's welfare than their own.
I didn't know all this about him.
Then maybe you don't know Michael Scofield.
Yeah.
♪ Oh, Tweener ♪
♪ I'm coming ♪
♪ I'm a-coming for you ♪
♪ Coming ♪
♪ Is you ready? Are you ready? ♪
♪ However you are, see, I'm here ♪
♪ I'm coming for you ♪
♪ Are you ready? Are you ready? ♪
♪ I'm coming, I'm coming ♪
♪ I'm a-coming, I'm a-coming, I'm coming ♪
♪ I am coming ♪
I checked my voicemail at work.
Lincoln's son LJ just left me a message.
He's in trouble.
- Hello?
- LJ, it's Veronica. Where are you?
Oh, Veronica, I don't know.
You gotta come get me.
We can't, OK? We're not in Chicago.
You have to come to us.
Oh. All right. Where's that?
Oh.
Oh. How the hell do they know where I am?
- What's going on?
- How do they know where I am?
- LJ, LJ, I want you to listen to me.
- Everywhere I go, they're there.
I want you to listen to me, OK? I need you
to come to us. We're in Lake Mercer.
- Where's that?
- On the Iowa border.
There's a bus station. We'll meet you there.
- They're still alive.
- The bird in the hand just became three.
- Keep your cellphone open.
- Let's go.
- But the kid's right...
- OK.
- OK, what?
OK, I'll keep it open.
They're leaving. They're leaving.
LJ, I need to know that you hear me, OK?
Lake Mercer.
Lake Mercer. OK.
All right, bye.
What the hell are you doing?
Delivering yesterday's news.
Your bus leaves from depot six
in just a few minutes.
Thanks.
- Yo, man, get off me, bitch.
- Let's pants him.
I... wanted you to know that if you're looking
for someone to talk to, you're not alone.
It's part of my job to counsel inmates
and help them with their problems.
I got things pretty well figured out.
I sort of backed into
some information about you.
I hope you don't mind,
but there's a reason I became a doctor.
It's in my nature to want to help.
From what I understand,
it's in your nature too.
You did a lot of good things before you were
in here. Community work, charity work.
What happened?
The man you're talking about died
the moment I stepped inside these walls.
All right.
Shuttle now arriving on platform one.
Shuttle departs in ten minutes.
Ladies and gentlemen,
United States Secret Service.
Please remain calm. Remain where you are.
Watch your step, son.
Hey.
Come here.
It's OK.
They're leaving.
You're safe now, all right?
You received communication
from your attorney.
Please sign this document
certifying that I inspected it for contraband
without at any time
breaching attorney-client privilege
by reading the materials enclosed herein.
- What are you grinning about?
- I'm gonna be out in the real world in a bit.
The fact that I'm gonna get me one fine piece
of tail certainly don't hurt either.
Nothing like tail, eh, Scofield?
- Son of a bitch!
- This ends right now.
Oh, you just screwed
some major league pooch, pretty.
I'm gonna sing like a whole tree
full of birds now. Badge!
You wanna sing, then sing.
But you know what I think?
You don't have the guts.
You want out of here
just as much as the rest of us.
We got a problem here?
No.
I, uh...
I thought we was missing some tools here.
My bad.
Get back to work.
Now.
You and I may be stuck together
in this little dance, but I call the shots.
First shot, that kid out there,
you don't touch him ever.
Do we understand each other?
We do.
Out of the way, Julio.
Abruzzi.
You and me,
we're gonna have a conversation.
How come he didn't fall through?
- What?
- I warned you.
I'll get it together.
You gotta give me more time.
You've had your time, John.
You tripping on something, Alice?
Yeah. That's what I thought.
Lamp it up in here again,
I'll be fixing to break some shop.
Uh-oh. We got a problem.
Bellick.
Boss. Boss. What's happening?
What are they doing?
- Fixing the break room.
- What are you talking about? That's PI.
I run it.
Not any more, you don't.