Previously on "Prison Break":
There's a whole lot of real estate
in between here and the outside walls.
The infirmary's the weakest link
in the security chain.
These were seriously hard to get.
What you need 'em for?
None of your business.
If I'd known how this was gonna turn out,
I'd have gotten some crap job with the feds.
Keep talking like that,
I'm gonna put a bullet in your head.
- We gotta go.
- You're in trouble, aren't you?
- Veronica Donovan?
- Who is this?
I have information that will lead
to the exoneration of Lincoln Burrows.
I gotta check the status in there.
- It's all good.
- Then you won't mind me checking it out.
Get off of him! Get off. Get off.
- We leave tonight.
- Michael, we got a big problem.
Argh! Argh!
- Back out.
- Of the escape?
Or die.
- Stay with me, John.
- I need you to stay with me. Breathe.
Keep breathing.
You're gonna be OK. Keep breathing.
Stay with me, John.
You stay with me, John. You stay with me.
Stay with me.
All right? Can you do that? Keep breathing.
You'll be OK. Stay with me.
Almost there. Almost there.
Be OK.
Large laceration to the throat.
- He's lost a lot of blood. He's hypovolemic.
- Got it.
- What's his blood type?
- A neg!
His blood pressure's too low.
He's definitely hypovolemic.
- We gotta get him to Chicago.
- Chicago's a 20-minute flight.
We gotta go, Doc.
And then there were six.
Far as I know, there's five.
Don't you ever step up to me like that again.
Who's the tough guy now, huh?
Warden, where's my brother?
He's in a lot of trouble, son.
You have to let me see him.
That's not a request
I can grant at the moment.
Please.
We're 36 hours away from his execution.
He panicked. He got violent.
For the rest of his time at Fox River,
we're gonna keep him in ad seg,
It's not your right to see him...
until tomorrow...
at his execution.
I'm sorry, son.
The name is John Abruzzi.
A-b-r-u-z-z...
I don't care what protocol is.
I just want to know if he's OK. Hello?
Hello?
Coño.
The hospital won't give out any information.
Wonder what happened to him. Maybe them
Mafia chickens came home to roost after all.
- We gotta put this on hold.
- We're not putting nothing on hold.
I don't think you heard me. Until
I get my brother out, no one's doing a thing.
God bless Sink, but the man is gone.
You go to the tombs, you don't get out,
not until they strap you up.
If you think I'll leave my brother behind,
you have massively underestimated me.
- Really?
- Really.
That ain't my fight.
I'm through that hole, pretty,
with or without you, next time I'm on PI.
We're not having this debate.
We oughta open the floor to everyone else,
see what they all say.
We got a clear shot. Every day we don't use
that hole is another day the screws can find it.
- The way is not finished.
- We're clear to the infirmary.
That's all we need.
Through that window,
over that wire, over that wall.
The two of you will never make it.
Oh, fish, it's notjust two.
If it's now or never, we gotta go.
Go with us.
You've done everything you could.
They're grown men, Michael.
They can all decide for themselves.
- You son of a...
- Wait a minute!
- Hey! Who are you separating there?
- Hey, it's good, boss. Just playing around.
It's all good.
There are two things
that everybody needs to get with.
First, hillbilly,
you have got to learn some respect.
The man here made everything possible.
And you, you're gonna have to get with
that we are doing this thing this afternoon
as soon as we get on PI.
So you're just gonna make a run for it
in the middle of the day.
Well, you gotta do
what you gotta do, huh, baby?
You are gonna screw
this whole thing up.
That's not for you to decide any more.
Now, this train is leaving the station,
and I suggest you get on it.
Get on the train, fish.
Get on the train.
Well, you know what, you sons of bitches?
I won't let you do it.
What you gonna do?
Blow the whistle on your own escape?
He'll be back.
Those guys, they go before us tonight,
they use that hole, it's over.
COs will turn this whole place upside down
till they find it.
Well, sounds like you're thinking about it.
I'd be lying if I said I wasn't.
I want to be out of here yesterday.
I got a kid coming, man.
Michael, you can't get him out of there.
Can I say something?
I know you won't want to hear it, but...
they're strapping him up either way now.
Once he's gone,
you'll be stuck here for another five years.
If they trace the hole back to you,
they'll toss another dime.
That's 15 years, papi.
Of course, if I were you,
I wouldn't leave my brother behind either.
Not to die like that, no.
Uh-uh.
Worst thing in the world they can do to a man
is strap him to a chair like that.
- We're in business.
- What?
I just spoke to a friend who's a clerk at the
superior court. I told him about the informant.
If he gives any evidence to warrant a stay,
my friend will hear us out.
- We might be able to stop this.
- I gotta tell Lincoln.
Go to that prison, they'll be all over you.
They've kept us on the run because if anyone
hears from us, we can do them damage.
Maybe it's time
we do the exact opposite - go big.
What do you mean, "big"?
You mean media big?
We got all the ammo we need.
There's a string of murders connected to this.
Are you ready to show your face again? Huh?
Are you ready for that?
It's the bottom of the ninth.
What else are we gonna do?
Hello?
- Hey. This is Daddy, baby girl.
- Daddy!
Daddy's on the phone.
- How are the camels?
- Oh, well, the camels... the camels are fine.
- When do I get to see you?
- Earlier than I thought.
Daddy said he's coming home soon.
Hey, put Mommy on the phone.
Thank you, sweetie.
First Sergeant Benjamin Miles Franklin,
how are you?
Oh, baby. Just driving trucks, eating dates,
trying to keep the sand out of my eyes.
I saw on the news the other day
it was 110 in Kuwait.
- You must be melting over there.
- You have no idea.
What's this about you coming home?
You're not getting your daughter's hopes up?
- You sitting down?
- Sure.
Your man is coming home this week.
This week? What are you talking about?
They said it'd be another year.
The orders just came down the pipe.
And the hell if I care
where they came down from.
- All that matters is we'll see each other.
- When? When is this happening?
Thursday, Friday. I'm not sure yet.
Do you need me
to pick you up from the airport?
Oh, no. No, no.
The army's got that all arranged.
You know, you just be waiting for me.
Well, you know I got that down.
Today, C-Note.
Would you back up?
Hey, you know, comm is only letting me
use this linkup for a few more minutes.
- Is Darius there? I need to speak to him.
- Yeah, yeah. I'll go get him.
I love you.
I love you more.
Yo.
Yeah, what's up, money?
Your sister out of the room?
She is now.
So, how is it out there, man?
Fox River all that they say it is?
Oh, man, it ain't all that.
Not for long, anyway.
- What you mean by that?
- I need you to do something for me.
Yeah, all right.
- You still drive that Escalade?
- Is Michael Jackson still white?
Ha-ha, you gotjokes, son.
How many does it hold?
OK.
OK what?
Let's do it.
What? You mean tonight?
What about Linc?
I need a razor blade.
- A razor blade ain't gonna get him out.
- Do you have one or not?
Careful, bro.
Ay, Cristo amado.
Thou shalt not kill!
Leadeth me beside the still waters,
restoreth my soul.
Leadeth me in the path
of righteousness for your sake.
Though I walk through the valley
of the shadow of death, I will fear no evil,
for thou art with me.
Thou preparest a table before me
in the presence of mine enemies.
Surely goodness and mercy shall follow me
all the days of my life,
and I will dwell
in the house of the Lord forever.
- Amen.
- He does hear our prayers, the Lord...
- Yes.
On behalf of Lincoln.
- All who seek forgiveness will be delivered.
- Yes.
If your brother accepts the Lord,
he'll be free of this cage forever.
Yes.
I'll be available
through this whole thing if you need me.
Reverend.
Reverend, would you give this to my brother?
It'd mean a lot to him,
knowing it came from me.
I will.
That was my mother's.
Tell her it's going
to save someone a lot of pain.
You sure you know what you're doing?
It's in God's hands now.
You've been the clean-up crew for me
the whole time I've been in here.
Toes, contusions, insulin shots.
Well, somebody's gotta do it.
Well, I'm grateful.
You ever think, in another life...
- I won't be that woman, Michael.
- I wasn't asking you to be.
But it is something to wonder about.
What if?
Anyway, just wanted to make sure it was said.
Why do I feel
like you're saying goodbye to me?
I don't know.
I guess in a place like this, you never know
which day is gonna be your last.
- Sara, we got a backup out here.
- OK.
You're set.
I...
I'm sorry about your brother.
Doctor...
Thank you.
This is it, bro.
Hey.
Good luck to both of us.
PI! Let's do it!
Came to your senses, did you?
You figure a magic way to get your brother
out of that hole and into the guards' room?
He's not gonna be there.
Could you put the light on?
You OK?
What do you think, Rev?
I spoke with your brother today.
He's been praying for you.
He must be desperate.
What about you? Are you feeling desperate?
No.
Just for everyone else.
The ones you leave behind.
The ones I never got to say goodbye to.
I can be with you
all day tomorrow, you know.
Right up to the time.
Thank you.
He wanted me to give this to you.
Michael.
Thou shalt not kill!
- She's back in play.
- Good. Who's there with you?
- Tangren.
- What about Hale?
Nope. MIA.
He should be there. What do you mean, MIA?
I think it's a fairly concise term.
Don't get it.
- What time's the flight?
- 11. I gotta head up to Wrigleyville.
I'll be back in a couple hours to collect you.
Pack everything.
Once we're out that door,
we won't come back.
- What are you gonna do?
- There's a letter I gotta deliver.
Thou shalt not kill!
You'll have to step away.
I'm Veronica Donovan.
I represent Lincoln Burrows.
- This isn't the time.
- You'll have to step aside.
I'm sorry, did you say
that you represent Lincoln Burrows?
- That's right.
- Angela West. I'm a producer with News Six.
So, Mr Pied Piper, what's the play?
We do what we always do -
pretend to be working, be model citizens,
till the time comes.
- And that'd be?
- Nine o'clock.
You seem to be forgetting
that PI shuts down at five o'clock.
Well, we have to make sure
it doesn't, don't we?
Hammer.
Whoa! What the hell are you doing, man?
- What the hell happened here?
- Messed up. Hit a pipe.
- Should've killed the water before we started.
- Should've?
It's not that big a deal.
We can fix it in the morning.
I don't think mould
should be a problem before then.
- Mould?
- Scofield, shut up, man.
You shut up. What are you talking about?
You get drywall and insulation soaked like
this, you run the risk of stachybotrys mould.
Boss, that's just, like,
one time in a thousand, for real.
Tell you what.
You and all your compañeros here
aren't stepping outside this door
until every damn molecule of water
is out of this place.
- It's gonna take all night.
- Well, then it's gonna take all night.
Don't catch a sniffle.
Man.
- Free Burrows!
- Free Burrows! Free Burrows!
- Great. A lot of it checks out.
- Put her on.
- If you don't mind, we'd like to put you on.
- That's why I'm here.
Great. Holly here will be asking the questions.
Just watch his hand, OK?
Peter, I'm with Veronica Donovan,
the lawyer for Lincoln Burrows.
- You're petitioning for a stay, is that right?
- Yes.
- On what grounds?
- On the grounds that my client was framed.
Get specifics.
- Do you have any proof?
- There's a whole string of proof.
Murders - Leticia Barris,
a potential exculpatory witness,
Lisa Rix, the mother of Lincoln's child,
Bishop McMorrow,
who could have petitioned for clemency.
Someone's killing these people off?
Somebody's trying to hide what happened,
the truth about Terrence Steadman.
Is this speculation, or is there
hard evidence to substantiate your claims?
- I have a source.
- Get a name.
- Could you elaborate?
- No.
Somebody on the inside
claims they can exonerate Lincoln,
that Terrence Steadman
wasn't in the car that night.
Someone's been talking.
- Is there a reason you're on direct current?
- Sorry?
You know, ACIDC.
Alternating current, direct current.
DC's kinda yesterday's news
for this sort of thing.
You can kill a man
with half the energy if you go AC.
OK. Let's see what we got.
You ready to run one?
I think you better turn these lights on.
Can't do it. Your client's being disciplined.
You're violating
his Eighth Amendment rights.
Either you turn those lights on, or you'll
be the first defendant named in a lawsuit.
You OK?
- LJ?
- He's good.
He's scared, but he's good.
- I found someone who's gonna talk.
- Who?
I don't know,
but I'll meet him in a few hours.
- A few hours is cutting it close, V.
- We don't have any other choice.
You have to have faith, OK?
Nick's already primed the court
to hear our case.
Whatever Michael's doing,
he doesn't need to do it now.
- We'll beat this the right way.
- What if you're wrong?
- I'm not.
- What if you are?
You gotta trust me, OK?
Don't give up on me.
Promise?
- Didn't mean to scare you.
- It's all right. Paul, how are you?
I'm good, I'm good.
- You?
- Oh.
- Where you going?
- Vacation.
Bahamas.
- Packing kinda heavily for the Bahamas.
- You know women.
Yeah.
So, where's Danny?
- Running errands, I think.
- Errands, huh?
Where... where might those errands be?
- Lewis, you there?
- Yeah. Yeah, I'm here, Linc.
What time you got?
A little after eight.
It's 8:15.
You OK?
No.
Oh, Michael,
what have you done to me?
Nine o'clock, fish.
Showtime.
Let's go, man.
Tancredi leave yet?
I don't think so.
You better call her.
See you on the other side.
Well, everything tells me it's food poisoning,
which means you should
feel better in a couple of hours,
but...
I wish I could say that this would be enough
to forestall the execution. It's not gonna be.
It's all right.
I can stay with you if you want.
No.
It's fine. Thank you.
OK.
We got a lot to talk about
and not a lot of time to do it.
Your boyfriend, he can still be saved.
Burrows was chosen a long time ago.
Hand-picked to be an assassin.
But he never pulled the trigger.
Who did? Come on.
Who killed Terrence Steadman?
- Nobody.
- What?
Terrence Steadman's still alive.
There's three sheets of paper inside.
You'll find all the names
you need are on them.
Everyone that started this whole thing,
from top to bottom.
You need to take two steps that way,
right now.
Behind the car. Get behind the car.
You want to stay alive, do as I say. Now.
Your boys better be there, rughead.
They'll be there, cleatis. Don't you worry.
This is crazy.
So, what are you doing here, Danny?
- Where's the lawyer?
- I don't know what you're talking about.
Allison told me.
I got it out of her.
- You didn't touch her?
- Why would I do that?
We're partners, right? We're on the same side.
No.
Allison's fine. She's just...
You're gonna have to ask yourself
who you want to give up.
Your wife, or this lawyer.
Just tell me where she is.
Is she here? Has she been?
What exactly have you told...
Don't do this.
- Give me your gun.
- I can't.
Yes, you can. I'm your superior.
I give you a command. You obey it.
Give me your gun.
- Paul, it's nothing. It's not...
- Don't. Back up.
It's...
It's amazing.
You got it all on only... three pages.
You know what would happen
if this fell into the wrong hands?
You named me?
- Right there along with the rest of them?
- I got scared.
- You named me?
- Please, man!
Allison's due in one month.
Paul, you and me,
we-we've been friends since the academy.
You named me.
OK. Let's go.
Hey, hey, hey. Put that away, man.
What you doing? Put that away, man.
Hey, yo-yos.
This is a state penitentiary.
You can't park here.
You think we meant to park here?
Put your hands where I can see 'em.
I said put your hands where I can see 'em.
All fixed.
What do you say you two hit the road?
You two hit the road right now,
or we're gonna have a problem.
- You all right?
- I'm good. Haven't been this good in years.
They replaced it.
Michael?
He's there.
Son of a bitch!
Here, Michael. Use this.
Come on! You ready?
Shh!
Ready?
What? Talk to me.
- It can't be done.
- What?
It's too thick.
I'm so sorry.
We're not getting out of here.
Unfortunately, pretty,
that ain't an option.