Open one of those for us.
You know you're the only one who can stand these things?
They're the only things left.
The pigs have all gone.
Used to be full of pigs, that.
Yeah, that and pig shit.
Dogs took care of them.
Don't think I could hack being a pig.
I don't think you could either.
What's so bad about being a pig?
It's undignified.
Undignified?
Walking about with your nose the same height as your asshole.
- Snout.
- What's that?
Pigs have snouts, not noses.
So it would be your snout the same height as your asshole.
Nose, snout.
You're still trotting about
gazing up everybody else's assholes all day long.
What kind of society is that?
An equal one?
So what do you reckon?
Yes or no?
I can give it a go. You're not gonna be long?
Five minutes, max.
Fucking hell.
This is mental, this is.
I mean, he's dying anyway.
Well, he is.
I mean, it's not like it's gonna save him.
He's got, what, days?
Well, if it's what's in there makes those days easier...
that'll do for me.
I promised my sister we'd help him.
We all promised her.
Plus there'll be other stuff in there. Batteries.
- All sorts.
- OK. OK.
Leave the keys in the ignition.
I'm ahead of you there.
If you hear anything, yeah, don't fuck about, yeah?
Just tear straight off.
- Five minutes?
- No more.
All right?
You sure it's gonna be in there?
Course I'm not sure.
Fuck it.
Fuck.
95dy42 95-dy42.
95dy... 95-dy...
Quick.
Fuck.
Go. Go.
Go! Go!
Tony!
Clarke! Go!
Oh, fuck.
Come on.
Yes.
No!
Fucking hell.
No, please!
Please, no! Fuck, no! No, please!
Please!
Fuck!
Fucker!
Fuck. Fuck you, you-- Fuck!
Ok.
Shit.
Anyone?
Come in?
If you can hear me, it's Bella.
Hello?
Pick up. Please, fucking pick up.
Fuck.
Hello? Who is that?
I can't hear you. You're not clear.
Listen, if you can hear me, just whistle.
Don't say anything.
Ok, ok.
I can't talk for long.
We found a dog at the warehouse.
We didn't see it.
We don't know how long it had been in there.
It got Tony and Clarke.
So they're gone. I'm-- I'm sorry.
And can you tell Ali that I'm sorry too?
She said that we were mad to bother and she was right.
We... We just wanted to help her with Jack.
I don't know...
Get him something that might help.
I know he's in pain.
I've lost the dog for now,
but my guess is it's still operational.
And I'm figuring it can lock onto this signal,
so I'm gonna have to go dark.
It's, um-- It stuck me with a tracker,
but I managed to get it out.
I'm gonna have to find somewhere overnight to hide out, I...
Get some medical stuff or something.
If I don't make it back...
will you pass a message to Graham?
Just I love him.
Please would you pass that on?
I'm gonna have to switch off now.
I'll try and make it back.
Bye, now.
Fuck.
Fuck!
Come on.
Stay still.
Shit, shit, shit.
You can't do it.
Your arm's fucked, so you can't climb the tree.
Yeah, take a good look, mate.
You'll be waiting a long time.
A very long time.
God.
Welcome back.
1,000...
999,
998,
997,
996...
...nine, eight, seven,
six, five, four,
three, two, one.
1,000...
999...
four...
three...
two...
one.
1,000...
999...
998...
...three, two, one.
993, 992...
Yes.
...four, three,
two, one.
Oh, fuck.
Ah, fuck!
Ah, come on.
Oh, come on.
Oh, shit.
Come on. Come on, come on.
Car keys, car keys, car keys. Car keys.
Car keys.
Oh, fuck.
Keys, keys, keys. Come on.
Oh, my God.
Oh, fuck.
Fuck.
Oh, God.
Come on, come on, come on, come on.
Fuck! Fuck! Fuck!
Come on. Come on.
Come on.
*Golden brown texture like sun*
*Lays me down...*
*Every time just like the last*
*On her ship tied to the mast*
*To distant lands*
*Takes both my hands*
*Never a frown with golden brown*
Fuck.
Is there anyone there?
Maybe you can hear me?
Maybe someone can hear me.
If there is anyone there...
This is just to say that I'm not coming back.
Say I'm sorry to Ali and
that she should give Jack a kiss from me.
I'm sorry I didn't get the replacement like I promised.
I know how dear it was to him.
And I did try.
We all tried.
I hope you can look after him.
And, Graham, I love you.
And all of you.
I've always loved you all.