(SINGING IN ENGLISH)
(ROCK MUSIC PLAYING)
(INAUDIBLE DIALOGUE)
- Dad.
- Hey.
- What are you doing here?
- Well, I got an office here.
- You come down with Finn?
- And some people.
Promise me, no drinking and driving.
Who's your designated driver?
I'm not the one with all
the dents in their car.
All right. Have fun, huh?
You need some money?
Have a good time, sweetheart.
Be careful.
- You see Meadow?
- Yeah. I wish I knew she was here.
- I wonder what the fuck she's thinking.
- I'm sorry, Ton.
Some kid had a seizure upstairs.
It's been a horrible night.
Hey, Ton, Vito and Gene just called.
They're five minutes away.
All right. We're leaving. Here.
All right, call them and tell them
to meet us at Bud's Butter Bun...
...on Broadway and 18th.
All right.
Did I just see your father?
He's got an office here.
Saturday night?
That's dedication.
The guy sure can put in the hours.
- Why not?
- Let's go someplace else.
Tony's spending so much time
at the club.
You think that might have
something to do with you?
If you think I'm gonna blow this guy for
your sick purposes, you are mistaken.
So go on about this phone call
the other night.
It was just some guy
with a Southern accent.
Christopher yelled at him
for calling the house.
- Said he'd see him down there.
- Down where?
Did you check the log on his cell?
Not since I almost got caught doing that,
and I am not doing it again.
Wait till he goes into the shower.
See if there's a 404 or 336.
And memorize any other numbers
you don't recognize.
(GRUNTING)
- What's the matter?
- I gotta go to the bathroom.
- I know, you said.
- No, I gotta go.
- Number two.
- I'll take you to your car.
No, I gotta go now. Oh, my God.
(HEAVY BREATHING)
You okay? We're almost there.
Try to relax.
(GRUNTING)
Don't you got a general anesthetic?
This lidocaine didn't do much.
And we are...
...done.
Jan, you wanna do your thing?
- Just keep a little pressure.
- All right.
I'm gonna get this down to the lab,
see what's what.
Okay. There we go.
- You okay?
- You think he got it all?
We hope so. Meantime,
there's a canteen on level L.
I'll let you know when
the results come back.
Does having a bowel movement
relieve the pain?
Yeah.
Would you describe the diarrhea
as loose or liquid?
Liquid. But this is getting so I'm afraid
to be away from the toilet.
I'm so scared
I'm gonna have an accident.
- Is this tender?
- No.
Sit up.
- How's your personal life?
- What do you mean?
Well, sometimes GI disturbances
are stress-related.
Is there anything unusual that
might be giving you the jim-jams?
I just want something for my stomach
so I can quit going to the bathroom.
That's what's giving me stress.
Why don't you get dressed.
We'll talk in my office.
(DOOR OPENING)
I hear you're spending time
with today's youth.
You lost me.
Meadow said she saw you
at Adriana's club.
I gotta explain my business to you now?
After so many years?
- No, it's your life, Tony.
- Got that right.
What'd you do to your head?
Did you fall again?
Banged it on the medicine chest.
Don't worry about it. It's nothing.
There's your allowance.
Well, that actually looks like fruit.
Yeah. It's so hard.
What do you do it for?
Irritable bowel syndrome?
He'll know more when
the tests come back.
- I still gotta bring him a stool sample.
- Jesus, please.
You yelled at me
to go to the doctor.
I gotta know every detail?
I could be really sick, Christopher.
Yeah, my Aunt Josephine
had colon cancer.
Her whole asshole rotted out.
I may have to go into therapy.
- Plus, they're gonna put me on Prozac.
- For diarrhea?
It's to help me cope and handle stress,
which is a lot of what causes it.
What do you got to be stressed about?
That bar?
War, Christopher. The Middle East.
You don't listen to the president?
We're gonna mop the floor
with the whole fucking world.
The world's gonna be under our control.
So, what are you worked up about?
(DOOR OPENING)
Give me the Orioles over the Tigers for 2,
and the Jays over the Rangers, 3 G's.
(ROCK MUSIC PLAYING IN
BACKGROUND)
- Just getting my day planner.
- No, I'm done.
My stupid car. Five thousand miles
and the alternator's going.
What about you?
Mimi said you went to the doctor.
I've been having trouble
with my stomach.
- That's why I'm drinking White Russians.
- What, you got ulcers already?
- It's called IBS.
- What's that?
(EXHALES)
Irritable bowel syndrome.
My mother had that all her life.
- You see this?
- Yeah, I noticed that. What happened?
- It's cancer.
- What?
- Yeah, squamous.
- Oh, my God, that's terrible.
Well, they think they got it all.
Knock wood.
Just, cancer, the things
that run through your head, you know?
Sure.
I got a top guy, though. Katz.
Hesh recommended him, naturally.
So this disease you got,
what causes it?
I did a Google on it,
and, like, the doctor too...
...they all say a lot
of it's psychological.
So on top of everything,
now I'm a headcase.
No. Come on. Stop blaming yourself.
Christopher don't wanna know.
Not that I blame him.
I gotta take off.
A.J. should be coming home
from his volleyball thing.
Listen, don't say anything
to anybody, okay?
People hear cancer,
they start to bury you already.
And you don't tell anybody
what I told you.
All right, take care of yourself.
- Say hi to Anthony.
- Yeah.
You're such a good father.
I wish my dad had been like that.
Night, dear.
It's a straight shot on I-95 to Raleigh.
You give this shit to the fence,
I'll meet you in Winston-Salem...
...we'll load up the cigs and come home.
If we're picking up so many cigarettes...
...why don't we, instead of two vans,
rent a deuce and a half?
And then share the driving?
Because the cops.
The van's under the radar.
- Erik Estrada over here.
- You forgot your folic acid.
What is all this stuff?
Beauty parlor chair?
If they even heard of electrolysis
down there.
- Where you going?
- Jesus Christ, go back to bed.
- What the fuck's your problem?
- My fucking tooth is killing me.
Well, you should go back
to the dentist.
Why do you have to go?
Can't they drop the stuff off?
Tony wants me to talk
to the guy down there.
The jerk you were yelling at
on the phone?
Is that the cigarette thing
you were talking about?
Six different kinds of dope
you get for a stomachache.
I got a fucking impaction, I can't take shit
besides oil of clove because I'm sober.
I know. It's hard. I'm sorry.
Have a nice trip. I love you.
Call me, okay?
She's got diarrhea.
(CAR DRIVING BY)
(SNORTING)
- You want?
- Yeah, twist my arm.
I'm expecting some guys
from New York, so...
No problem. I got plenty to do out there.
(SNORTING)
- Who's this on?
- Oh, please. It's called the Lost Boys.
Sil's been ragging on me all week
for me to play them here.
Their manager or somebody
owes him money.
- So I thought this was your day off.
- Chrissy's away.
I don't like staying home alone.
Though at least I can pour a glass of wine
without him giving me the expression.
Yeah. Yeah, I know that look.
The constipated-owl look.
(LAUGHING)
You know, when I first met you,
I was scared of you.
- Really?
- Yeah, but I'm scared of everybody.
It's always my first reaction.
Well, you're not scared of me now,
are you?
No.
Do we wanna shoot?
Make it interesting. Sawbuck a game.
No, it's the round thing
in the middle there.
How you feeling?
Everything all right in here now?
Don't... I know what you're doing.
Don't distract me.
Ohh
Ooohhh
I've been hustled.
(DARTS HITTING FLOOR)
- Did I get your toe?
- No. No, no, no.
I'm so sorry.
Come on, get up. Come on.
(BANGING ON DOOR)
Shit. All right.
Wait.
Yeah.
(DOOR OPENING)
- Tony here?
- Yeah, come on in.
Hey.
Let me know if you guys need anything.
You gonna tell me
about the traffic again?
Here, our friend sent this for you.
Thank you for taking the appointment.
And I know I'm on probation,
and I deeply regret...
...what I did.
My nephew's fiancée.
I know what you're thinking.
- So?
- Well, nothing happened.
But it could have, very easily.
I mean, she really got to me,
this young lady. She...
- What?
- This is a very big step.
Yeah, tell me about it.
I mean that you've come here
to talk about this impulse...
...instead of just acting on it
without thinking.
- No, I always think.
- Really?
- Yeah.
- Having sex with your mistress' cousin.
Like the mistress wasn't enough
to piss off your wife.
Tell me about the niece.
She's drop-dead gorgeous.
I mean, someone like her, I could...
Well, I could do it right this time.
I could start a whole new family.
I'm young enough.
Fuck them all.
And this is something
you're contemplating?
What? It'd be a disaster.
Of major proportions.
Carmela, I'd get hosed financially.
There'd be no reasoning with her
after that.
And my nephew, it would kill him.
After years of grooming him
to be my number two.
And it'd be very bad for the girl.
She doesn't deserve that.
I mean, I'm not stupid. I know part
of it's this father-figure thing, and...
You know, on account of hers ran off.
It would be like committing
an act of symbolic incest.
Whatever.
But what am I gonna do?
I got lucky the first time
because I was able to control myself.
- But you only get one of those.
- Rationalizing. "I can't control myself."
- You can.
- I don't know.
It's different for women.
It's all about up here with them.
She could make a play for you.
You might wanna think about how you're
going to establish limits and boundaries.
For example, you could tell her
she means a great deal to you...
...but you think of her as a daughter.
Even if I wanna fuck her brains out.
This is a milestone for you.
You're at a very important crossroads.
For once, you want to avoid
doing something you know is wrong...
...and would be destructive...
...both to yourself
and to the people you care about.
That's growth. That's progress.
- Just tell me what I'm supposed to do.
- You have to be honest with yourself.
I know this is a powerful urge.
But if you can't keep it in your pants,
you have to stay away from her.
You know...
...not long ago,
you stood in my outer office.
I recall you used the words
"drop-dead gorgeous" about me...
...and how you had to have me.
I said I wouldn't date you,
and look, you survived.
What a horrible fucking job you have.
How do you do it?
But what happens now is your choice.
Act, and create a bed of misery.
Or you can look at this as a chance
to do something good.
You say she respects you.
Be worthy of respect.
See if you can remain a friend
to this woman...
...a help to her.
(DUCKS QUACKING)
You know, Tony had ducks one time.
In his pool.
- You need to find out where Chris went.
- I'm getting this vibe from him.
Who? Tony?
He's really nice. And he listens.
He's kind of attractive.
Definitely an alpha male.
- But what if Christopher found out?
- What?
- I'm not gonna fuck him.
- Then what are you talking about?
I love Christopher,
and sooner or later...
...we'll get out from under all this shit
and leave this fucking state.
Jesus Christ.
She's a good-looking woman
and she wants to fuck Barney Rubble?
Well, we really don't know him.
He listens.
(CLUB MUSIC)
Excuse me, is this seat taken?
- Tony, hi.
- Hey. How you doing?
Well, why I'm here,
Patsy's bringing somebody by.
I'm gonna need to use the office.
No problem. I made a resolution.
I gotta start spending a lot more time
on the floor. Crack the whip.
I'm beat, tell you the truth.
I think I'm gonna grab 40 winks
till Patsy gets here.
Wait, you don't have Chrissy's cell,
do you?
He called, but he didn't leave
a new number.
He'll probably try you again.
He's due back tomorrow.
- Excuse me. I'll come back.
- No, I'm all right.
Mole back there looked
irregular around the margins.
Every time I see anything now,
I think I got melanoma.
I can imagine.
Hi, it's Adriana at the Crazy Horse.
Yeah, I need a car, please.
Just tell him to wait outside.
- What, your car still?
- Yeah. They're replacing the alternator.
You want a belt?
What I could really use is some...
(SNORT)
I wouldn't say no.
Get me motivated to clean the house
before Christopher gets back.
Except I'm all out.
It's 2:00. Cross-eyed Billy
probably left the Bing already.
I know a guy, Andre. He's always up.
Well, cancel the car. I'll give you a ride.
You know who thinks you're cute?
Is Marlene.
She's gotta be over 30, isn't she?
She's 31.
You know who you ought to
introduce me to is that friend of yours.
- Who?
- The one you brought over to the house.
Tall, kind of blondish-brownish hair.
Danielle from Whippany.
She's dead.
- What?
- Yeah.
She... She drowned on a picnic.
Well, I thought I picked up on
something between her and me.
I'm not trying to be conceited.
Tony!
(TIRES SQUEALING)
(CRASH NOISE)
(WINDOW BREAKING ON CONCRETE)
(WHEELS WHIRLING)
I've reviewed your chart
and ruled out internal injuries...
...so you're free to go.
I'll have the nurse process
your discharge orders.
Whoa
This was a very bad accident.
I mean, are you sure you did
all the tests?
I can afford it.
I did the appropriate tests.
I hold a medical degree
from Johns Hopkins.
My grandma was the first black woman
licensed to practice medicine in Delaware.
All right, take it easy.
The young lady that I was with,
they said she was okay...
...but could I see her?
Ade.
- Hey.
- Hi.
They say you're gonna be fine, they just
wanna keep you here for observation.
You know, be on the safe side.
I don't even remember what happened.
There was a raccoon in the road.
I swerved.
- How's your car?
- Escalade?
It's totaled.
Probably saved our life.
Are you okay?
Yeah. They're gonna let me go.
I wanna go too.
Chrissy's coming home today.
We should probably talk about that.
(EXHALES)
Yeah. Right.
(BRAKES SQUEAKING)
Dude, how you doing?
(DOORS OPENING)
I hit the fucking mother lode.
Twenty G's of product a week.
Little Paulie's behind me
with the other half.
Fuck me.
20 percent of this load, they can stamp
the packs for the vending machines.
The rest, the cartons
can go straight to the bodegas...
...let them worry about the stamps.
I'm beat. I'm gonna hit
the fucking rack...
...have Ade cook me up
a nice carbonara...
What's the matter?
Adriana's in the hospital.
She was in an accident.
What? When?
Last night around 2:00.
Jesus Christ, what happened?
Is she all right?
She got banged up,
but she's gonna be okay.
The drinking and driving, I told her.
Where is she?
- Mount Mercy in Dover.
- Dover?
Apparently they swerved
to avoid a deer in the road.
- They?
- Her and Tony.
Tony? Soprano?
Uh-huh
- Is he all right?
- Not a scratch.
The fucking luck on this guy.
Yeah.
Oh, yeah, yeah, yeah. Dover.
Right, she's got an aunt
she's close to out there who's been sick.
She's friends with Tony's aunt.
All right, somebody take me
to get my car. I better get over there.
Fabio, put it up.
Thought I'd die in there
without a cigarette.
What, so you're just not gonna talk?
- I almost got killed, Christopher.
- I'm just curious.
What the fuck were you doing
in the middle of the night...
...in the middle of nowhere,
in a car with my uncle?
He was driving me home.
- Fucking Dover?
- We were talking.
We were going to get something to eat.
I get off of work,
I don't wanna go right home.
- You weren't even there.
- No, I was in a fucking ride-a-rent...
...busting my ass with a bunch
of rednecks, making a living...
...to buy you alcohol and coke...
...and all the other shit
you shovel into your mouth.
Two o'clock in the fucking morning?
- Don't fucking lie to me! I can't stand it.
- Nothing was going on, Christopher.
I should have made you walk home.
- I swear to God.
- You know how this looks?
Don't talk to me. Shut your mouth.
(GRUNTING)
(DOOR OPENING AND CLOSING)
You wanted to see me?
- Adriana okay?
- She's fine.
People who don't clean up
after their pets.
Pop this in that basket for me, will you?
It was blind luck, that accident.
Cop told me he thought he was coming up
on a fatality when he saw the car.
I'd be thinking the same thing
if I were you.
But it's not true.
I don't know what you're talking about.
Her car was in the shop, I was driving
her home from work, that's all.
We were looking to get a burger.
- In Dover?
- What difference does it make?
You don't seem to give a shit
she almost died.
She could have been paralyzed
or scarred up.
And you got a puss on?
What were you doing out there
alone in a car with my fiancée?
We were talking about you,
you selfish prick.
How you were the best thing
that ever happened to her.
Oh, you don't think
this fucking devastates me?
Frankly, you scored so far over your head
when you got her, what do you expect?
- What the fuck are you talking about?
- She's a knockout.
A 10.
And look at you.
You're average, at best.
So you better reconcile yourself
with that...
...or you're gonna be paranoid
your whole life.
- Oh, so this is my fucking fault now?
- Nothing happened.
And I'm not gonna say it again.
You should've married that girl
two years ago.
Everybody knows you've been
the biggest fucking cooze hound around...
...the past four or five years.
Your midlife crisis.
You'd fuck a catcher's mitt.
On everything I hold sacred...
...on my children...
...there's nothing going on
between me and Adriana.
(DOOR SLAMMING)
Tony walked away without a scratch.
But Adriana suffered a severe blow
to the head.
Adriana got caught
giving the big guy a blow job.
And when the paramedics found them,
she had his cock still in her mouth.
Statistics show that most single-car
fatalities are the result of guys...
...popping their load behind the wheel.
Apparently he came all over the sun visor.
(CELL PHONE RINGING)
Sanseverino.
Guess who went down
on Tony Soprano?
That's the truth. It's fact.
If it was my old lady,
the next thing she'd suck is a tailpipe.
That pretty little trim can suck this pipe
anytime she wants.
- Like you'd ever have a shot.
- Hey, let me tell you something.
When Christopher was in rehab,
she was calling me all the time.
- I was this close.
- Then you got a problem...
...because your braciole
isn't even that long.
- What's so funny?
- Nothing.
Didn't sound like nothing.
I wanna hear the big joke.
Take it easy.
We're just shooting the shit.
- We were just talking about my braciole.
- Oh, yeah, what about it?
- So deal you in, huh?
- I asked him a fucking question.
- What are you breaking my balls for?
- I want a fucking answer.
What's so fucking hilarious,
you fucking parade float?
I'm a fucking captain now.
You don't talk to me like that.
- Oh, come on, guys.
- Don't put your hands on me!
- Chrissy, for chrissakes...
- Fuck all of you.
- Hey, hey!
- Motherfucker!
- Hey, hold it.
- Vito, easy.
Vina, Jimmy, please join me.
So talk to me, guys.
How are we feeling in these?
Hey, hon. I already ate.
- There's a casserole in the...
- You fucking lying bitch!
- Stop it! What are you doing?
- You were sucking his cock!
Georgie told me everything.
The surgeon on the operating table
said you were moaning Tony's name.
- What are you talking about?
- Fucking lie to me!
What were you doing in Dover then?
See? See?
You can't tell me
because I know what you were doing.
Your other dope dealer's there.
I remembered.
- Go ahead. Deny it.
- Okay.
I was going out to see Andre,
but I wasn't sucking anybody's cock.
How could you say that?
So you two were just gonna go
toot up a bunch of lines...
...go fucking birdwatching?
Oh, you son of a bitch.
I was gonna stay up all night
and clean this fucking shithole.
Everybody knows about it.
Everybody's talking about it.
(TABLE CRASHING)
- No, please.
- You want me to use, you bitch.
- You're fucking killing me.
- No, I don't. I love you.
(LOUD SMACK)
Stop it.
- You motherfucker!
- Fucking whore.
My neck!
Get the fuck out of here.
I never wanna see you again.
(DOOR SLAMMING)
- Thought you had an algebra test.
- Oh, chill out.
What did you say?
Look, I studied for 45 minutes straight.
Don't I get a break?
(KNOCKING ON DOOR)
Hey, what's up?
A.J., how's it going?
Hey, Uncle Tony.
Did I come at a bad time?
I need to talk to you.
A.J., go upstairs, study.
- Well, what about the pizza?
- Now.
Study.
All right, what's up?
I went to the Belleville Tavern
after work...
...and Larry down there said our little
cousin was in there all fucked up.
Somebody told him
what was going on in the car.
- There was nothing going on in the car.
- Of course not, but he thinks there was.
He started drinking again,
he beat up Adriana...
...and he threw her
out of the fucking house.
Where's his fucking self-control,
this guy?
Little Paulie's out there looking for him
to reign him in.
He was saying some crazy things
about you.
(PLAYING DRUMS)
Oh, this goddamn kid.
Christopher's not right
in the head, Ton.
I mean, who the fuck knows
what he's capable of.
Well, he knows where to find me.
You see him, you tell him that.
Gotta use your john.
Get you a day early, huh?
I'll go to the store in the morning.
Look, relax. Go whenever you want.
What the hell is wrong with him?
What do you want, Tony?
He couldn't bring this in himself?
What, I can't even come in
and say hello?
What you want is to know if I heard
the disgusting shit they're saying.
At least have the guts
to come out and ask me.
- It isn't true.
- You know what, fuck you.
Fuck me? Fuck you.
You gotta put your son in hiding
because of your fucking philandering?
Afraid he'll get caught in the crossfire?
Your own son?
Christopher's upset.
He could come over.
He could say some things
that a kid shouldn't hear.
Just please leave.
I don't even wanna look at you.
(TIRES SQUEALING)
Motherfucker!
(BOTTLE SMASHING)
(GUN SHOTS)
(TIRE POPPING)
Motherfucking gun!
(ROCK MUSIC)
Give me two.
This kid ain't gonna show up, T.
He's probably in some gutter.
Yeah, hopefully he's wore himself down.
- Where are you, you fuck?
- He's got a gun.
I know you're up there, you motherfucker!
Why don't you come out...?
- You know what to do.
- You're fucking lucky!
You're fucking lucky I ran out of load.
Shut up, you little cock,
or I'll split your fucking wishbone.
It's all over, everybody.
Enjoy the evening.
Unhappy customer.
(CAR DOOR SLAMMING)
Let me the fuck go!
I'll kill all of youse!
Fucking kill all of youse!
(LOUD THUD)
You draw down on the boss
of a fucking family?
You lied to me!
You were scoring coke with her.
- She admitted it.
- So what?
I can't relieve stress once in a while?
I don't got enough fucking problems?
You sent me to North Carolina
so you could fuck my girlfriend.
What kind of fucking animal
you think I am, huh?
- The thought never even entered my head!
- You're a man alone in a car with her.
You fucking pushed me to this.
You pushed me to this!
Way I see it, Tony, he must have
known the gun was empty.
Look what he pumped into your car.
What are you trying to say, Paulie?
The fuck you trying to say, Paulie?
Either you tell me right now...
...that you can take it into your heart
that I did not do this shit...
...or this is as far as we go.
- Motherfucker.
- Tony, come on.
- Listen to somebody else for a change.
- Fuck him.
Tony, try it my way.
Listen to me.
Mr. Soriano,
what seems to be the matter?
Soprano. I'm fine. It's my friend here
needs to talk to you.
Well, you know where ER admitting is.
Look, you got someplace
maybe we could talk?
It's 3 a.m., and I just finished
a 17-hour rotation.
Any gunshot wounds
or broken kneecaps?
Two minutes.
You're an excellent doctor.
That's why I brought him here.
Come on.
(CAR DOORS OPENING)
This gentleman here is the fiancé
of the young lady that I was with.
Now he's got it into his head...
...that there was oral sex going on
at the time of the wreck.
- Listen, I...
- Hey, hey, hey.
Just a second.
And naturally he's very upset.
So I need you to tell him there wasn't.
He's obviously feeling the pressure.
He's just gonna fucking lie.
I'm not in the custom of lying
about anything.
But whether somebody was getting
something in the car...
...how could I attest to that?
Well, as the attending, you could explain
how medically it's not possible.
- Excuse me?
- Well, for instance...
...if she was wearing a seat belt,
there would've been abrasions...
...to the lateral anterior aspect
of the clavicle.
Or the right mid-sternum?
Are you a physician?
No, I'm a pre-board-certified
massage therapist.
So did she have
any of those kind of things?
Actually, yes.
On the right clavicle and the sternum,
just above the xiphoid process...
...which would indicate an upright
position at the moment of impact.
Okay, so, what he's saying
is that she was sitting up.
All right. Thank you, doctor. Come on.
For the kids, Make-A-Wish Foundation,
whatever. Here.
Thank you.
What do you want from me?
I guess I believe you.
All right.
You threw food at Vito.
That's gotta be resolved.
He was fucking laughing,
which was wrong.
But at this point now,
it don't make no difference.
Even if it wasn't true,
it's what people think.
They know you were out there
scoring coke with her.
What do you care what people think?
You know the truth.
I gotta live in the world.
And now I look like Joe Jerkoff.
(CAR DOOR OPENING)
No, no, no, no.
You know what?
I might as well have fucked her.
Thanks.
Hello?
(DOOR CLOSING)
I rang the doorbell six times.
Nobody answered.
- What are you doing here?
- I wanna talk to you.
- If you came to get him, he's not going.
- You believe all that shit they're saying?
Am I that horrible? Really?
Where there's smoke, there's fire.
I don't know what you did.
What'll happen when your children
hear this? Meadow already suspects you.
- Suspects what?
- She saw you at the club.
She said she thought you were coked out.
What are you talking about?
I don't do drugs.
She knows about the accident.
What do you think she's gonna think?
- And with Anthony at that age?
- Oh, come on, the kids.
- The kids. It's about you.
- Fine. So it's all about me.
What, do I mean nothing to you?
That I gotta live with this
swirling around me?
All right, look, forget about
what they're saying. I'm asking you.
You think I'd have sexual relations
with her?
Adriana, who's gonna be
a member of this family?
Now, I want you to answer me truthfully.
Look, I know I haven't been
a fucking saint, all right...
...and you got plenty of issues
of your own on that subject...
...but you haven't exactly been
a fucking saint yourself.
No. No, no, no. Come here.
You think I would go near
that girl like that?
Thank you.
Look, I'm asking you to pull with me
to put a good face on this thing.
For the sake of the kids and this family.
I gotta bail you out?
It's never-ending, your bullshit.
(CAR HONKING)
Use a fucking crosswalk!
Jesus Christ.
Don't get all excited.
Most of it's from the accident.
You okay?
What do you fucking think?
I'm kicked out of my house, I may have
ulcerative colitis, and you call me up.
We'd like your permission to put
a listening device in your business.
This relationship with Tony
could net us a lot of chatter.
- Don't forget, it's him we're after.
- There is no relationship.
The faster we put Tony away,
the sooner you can get on with your life.
We can get a court order to install
a device, but this will make life simpler.
Fuck you. I do enough for you people.
- You're not bugging my club.
- Adriana...
...it's a syndrome, protecting abusers.
If it would've been Christopher
alone in a car with a woman...
...I would've killed him.
Thank you.
Arthur's sending something over,
with his compliments.
Thank you.
Enjoy.
(AUTHENTIC MUSIC PLAYING)
I'm gonna go over there.
- Nice to see you, Ton.
- Oh, thank you.
Gravy's good tonight.
Nice to see you.
Hope you have a pleasant evening.
Ladies.
(AUTHENTIC MUSIC PLAYING)