I'm not Ana anymore.
My name is Carrie.
Is anything about us true?
About you?
Is Carrie even your real name?
Your mother has told you
many lies, Deva.
- We have two children
- Max!
Whose lives have been
turned upside down.
- My baby!
- And nothing and no one else
is more important than that.
You got a visitor.
You coming?
Making friends?
You know me.
You getting any more time for it?
They just let me off
with a warning.
Take it seriously.
They'll just keep you
in here longer.
I just can't stand
being in here,
not knowing if my kids are okay.
I can't talk to them.
- And then if he comes back...
- Rabbit?
If he's alive,
you hurt him pretty badly.
He's alive.
I put my kids in harm's way.
I have to get them out of it.
We will.
Hey.
All that time you were inside,
I never came to see you.
Thank you.
Just keep your head down, okay?
- Quiet time.
My grandfather says
green eyes are a sign of the devil.
Maybe he's right.
I put that in the category
of crazy shit old Injuns believe.
What?
Was it the shit part
or the Injun part that got you?
Sometimes I wonder
what planet you come from.
And the Lord God said,
"It is not good that man
should be alone.
I will make him
a helpmate for him."
And out of the ground,
the Lord God
formed every beast of the field
and every fowl of the air.
Want a bite?
We have got to get out of here.
Right now?
No, not right now.
The first chance I get, I'm gone.
Is it really that bad
on the reservation?
Our parents tell us how we were
this great warrior tribe,
but now everyone's on drugs
or in jail or getting killed.
I'm not gonna die on the rez.
No way.
Where would you go?
I don't know.
It's a big world out there.
And whatsoever Adam called
every living creature,
that was the name thereon.
You miss Rebecca, don't you?
And the Lord God
caused a deep sleep
to fall upon Adam
and he slept.
And he took one of his ribs
and closed up the flesh
instead thereof.
Is that what you want to become?
Are you gonna drive a horse
and buggy, grow a long beard,
and throw your children
on the streets when they tell you to?
And the rib,
which the Lord God
had taken from man,
made He a woman
and brought her unto the man.
You know, we could go together.
If you want.
- I'm going to get the horse.
- I'll stay here.
Solomon?
Solomon.
Solomon!
Her name is Lana Cleary.
She's Kinaho.
- What's she doing here?
- No idea.
Don't we have
a medical examiner for that?
Three counties sharing one ME,
we tend not to be a priority.
After last night's rain,
there isn't much left,
but we take the pictures,
send it all up to Harrisburg
for forensic analysis.
I don't need Harrisburg to tell me
she got her skull caved in.
Hey, that's the girl's
family over there.
You might want to talk to them.
They're pretty broken up.
I couldn't get any information.
Mr. Bowman,
please stay back.
- Sheriff.
- Mr. Bowman.
My son Solomon,
he never came home last night.
Whoever did this might have done
the same thing to him.
All right, Mr. Bowman, I assure you
every effort will be made.
But you can help us by asking your
people who saw Solomon last.
- Okay?
- I don't know.
All right, thank you.
I understand.
Right now I need you
to please step back.
- There's no connection?
- No.
Tell him.
Just tell him what you told me.
Now, come on. Now.
Lana was hooking up
with an Amish kid.
What Amish kid?
What's his name?
Solomon Bowman.
What?
This is... this is a... this is a lie.
This is a damned lie.
My son had no dealings
with Indian girls.
- So where is the boy?
- He's not here.
He's missing.
The boy is missing.
They're hiding the boy.
You're hiding the boy!
Why do you say this?
I am not hiding him.
He's hiding the boy.
Bring the boy here.
I will not bring the boy here.
He has nothing to answer for.
- He killed her.
- Why does he say this?
Both of you just back off now!
- If you're hiding him...
- What? No. What?
- I do not know where he is.
- He killed my baby!
I tell you he did not
kill anyone.
He killed her!
He killed my baby!
Mr. Cleary.
Mr. Cleary. Mr. Cleary.
- Mr. Cleary.
- Please stay back, okay?
I have to find my son.
The state is sending more
troopers to comb the area.
Okay.
Thanks.
Hey, who's the big guy?
Oh, that's Chayton.
He's head of the Redbones,
a gang on the reservation.
Real bad news.
Did some time a while back.
Beat the living shit
out of a busload of tourists
because some of them
were dressed like Indians.
Came out bigger and meaner
than when he went in.
You guys bust him?
No, staties got him.
Me and Brock tried
to arrest him a while back.
- You tried?
- He's a large man.
Siobhan.
Keep your finger
along the trigger guard
until you're ready to shoot.
Good.
Wide stance.
Good. Now let's see
what you can do.
That's very good.
Excuse me.
Solomon?
Solomon! Solomon!
Solomon!
- Solomon!
- Solomon, can you hear me?
Solomon!
- Solomon!
Hold on a moment, okay?
- Yeah?
- Sheriff.
Have you heard anything
about my brother?
Uh, no. Not yet.
State troopers are helping with
the search, but there's nothing yet.
Do you have any idea
where he might be?
Solomon's not a killer.
There's a lot of people
who believe he is.
That's why we need to find him
before the Kinaho do.
If I can be of any help,
Sheriff, any help at all.
Yeah, I'll keep that in mind.
Good.
Let's go, Rebecca.
Let the sheriff do his job.
Come on.
Please.
Just bring him back to me.
Rebecca Bowman
have anything to add?
No.
I think I got something
from the sister.
Lana Cleary had an ex-boyfriend,
a guy named Tommy Littlestone.
Apparently, when he found out
she was dating an Amish kid,
he went off on her.
Started sending her threatening
e-mails.
Tommy Littlestone?
Any relation to Chayton Littlestone?
Yeah, it's his little brother.
What, Chayton, the big guy
from the crime scene?
Yeah. Chayton isn't some
meathead gangbanger.
He's old school.
He's all about the purity
of the Kinaho tribe.
In fact, none of the Redbones
date outside the tribe.
So my guess is if his little
brother's girl was involved
with some Amish boy,
that wouldn't have
gone over so well.
Yeah, and according
to Lana's sister,
Tommy's now a full-fledged member
of the Redbones.
I guess we need to have a little chat
with Tommy Littlestone.
We have no jurisdiction
on the reservation.
We cannot take one step onto
their land without a federal warrant.
Exactly.
- What?
- Nothing.
Just wondering which one of us
has the best relationship
with the FBI these days.
That's what I thought.
Let's go.
What?
Hood. Hood.
Hey!
We should rethink this.
I agree.
We expecting trouble?
We don't have jurisdiction
here, all right?
Some of these kids are minors.
We pull our guns,
we could all go down for it.
- Okay, so no guns.
- Yeah, but if Chayton is in there...
We should probably
have a talk with him.
Where's he going?
Where are you going?
I'm gonna go around back,
poke around a little.
Okay.
He's gonna poke around.
Bring your Tasers.
Shit.
Heads up, guys.
There's cops.
Good afternoon.
Banshee County
Sheriff's Department.
We can see who you are, man.
Look, we just want
to ask you a few questions.
Go fuck yourself, bitch.
One of our girls
was killed on Amish land
and you're landing on us?
Typical racist
white man bullshit.
Yeah, I get that a lot.
Look, nobody's accusing
you guys of anything.
We're just trying
to figure this thing out.
Figure it out somewhere else.
This is the rez, man.
You're trespassing.
Look, son, I don't want to argue
the finer points of the law with you,
but we are investigating
a potential capital murder case.
- So we have jurisdiction.
- We have jurisdiction?
- Just go with it, okay?
- Get the fuck out.
Fucking cops.
We're looking for
Tommy Littlestone.
We just want to talk to him.
Look, you guys
can talk to us here
or you can talk to us
from a holding cell. Your choice.
Why don't you go find the Amish
motherfucker who killed her?
Get the fuck out of here.
- Hi.
- How the fuck did you get in here?
Hey, take it easy.
Take it easy.
This is a friendly visit.
I just want to talk.
I'm not looking
for any trouble, okay?
No? Well, it looks like
trouble is what you got.
You're Chayton Littlestone.
Just Chayton.
Well, Chayton,
I was just telling
your colleagues here
I just want to talk.
You got no business
being on the rez, cop.
Well, that's something
we can talk about.
Far as I'm concerned,
you have no authority
on or off the reservation.
You see, all the land
around here
was Kinaho land before
the white man ever sailed.
And then your forefathers stole it,
parceled it up and sold it
as if they were entitled.
Just like you feel entitled
to walk into my house
because you wear that piece
of polished tin.
And now a red girl
has been killed on white man's land
that should have rightfully belonged
to her people to begin with
and you...
you don't see
the audacity it takes
for you to turn up here
pointing fingers?
I'm trying to find out
who killed that girl.
You won't find that here.
If you didn't kill her,
then you got nothing
to worry about.
Do I look worried?
- Oh, fuck!
- Fuck.
Shit, Hood's in there.
- Open up!
- Kick his ass!
Hit it, Emmett.
Hit it.
Knock him out!
- Fuck this.
- Watch out. Watch out.
Get off!
Hey, get off me, man!
No! Hold still!
Let me go, man.
Let me go!
- Put your hands up!
Put your hands up!
Turn around!
Don't move.
- On your knees!
- Stay down! Shut up!
You're gonna bleed with me, cop.
Just like your ancestors
bled with mine.
Hood!
Hey!
Well, that's something
you don't see every day.
Everything all right in here?
Okay, which one of you assholes
is Tommy Littlestone?
Hey, Tommy.
Guess your brother ate
all the vitamins, huh?
Ow!
Baby.
Thanks for saving
my ass back there.
Guy was about five seconds away
from tearing me apart.
Well, we can't have that.
Not when things are
just getting interesting.
- Can I help you?
- Uh, yes.
I'd like to see Sheriff Hood.
The sheriff is busy right now, but
who can I tell him is here?
Jason.
Do you got a last name
like most people?
Uh, Smith.
Have a seat, Smith.
I'll let the sheriff
know that you're here.
So...
I got you on resisting arrest,
assaulting a police officer,
carrying a concealed weapon,
trying to slice me open
with that concealed weapon.
I could put you away
for 10 years on those alone.
But I'll bet
I could also make you good
for the girl's murder.
I don't kill Indians.
No?
What about your brother?
You came onto the rez
without a federal warrant.
These arrests are illegal.
Yeah, see, you guys all say this to
me like I should give a shit.
If you give a shit
about the dead girl,
seems to me you should
be looking for the Amish kid.
So you got nothing
to tell me about Lana
and Tommy?
I'll see you again, cop,
outside this cage.
Ever the optimist.
So what? So I sent her
some e-mails.
It doesn't mean anything.
I didn't do anything!
Sheriff Hood.
Your deputy just gave
us the rundown.
Alison Medding.
Ah, the new ADA, right?
That's right. With Gordon filling
the mayor's slot,
I will be running point on this.
What does that mean exactly?
It means it's my job to tell you that
you had no authority
to go into Kinaho land
and start shaking people down.
You get straight
to the point, huh?
- We have a murdered girl.
- Yeah, I'm aware of that.
And if this investigation is
compromised
- by illegal arrests...
- Jesus Christ. Listen to you.
...you'll blow the whole thing
before it gets started.
While you're standing here
worrying about rules,
I'm out there trying to find
the guy who did this.
Hey. That's enough.
Now, do you have anything solid
tying these men
to the girl's murder?
Well, when I asked him
if he killed the girl,
the big one tried to kill me.
Well, that's not exactly
conclusive now, is it?
Tommy Littlestone
is 17 years old.
You're questioning a minor
without representation.
Not to mention your arrests
were illegal to begin with
because you were out
of your jurisdiction.
You two should meet.
Chayton Littlestone
has two warrants in Jefferson County.
Probably why he resisted today.
They have priority,
so I'm having him transferred back
to their jurisdiction.
Believe me,
they're welcome to him.
You can take
the little brother now.
Let's go.
Tommy. Tommy.
Don't say another word.
I'm shutting this down.
- Come with us.
- We're not holding him any longer.
- This your first murder case?
- It is.
- Big career boost, huh?
- Damn straight.
I plan to crush it.
My boss doesn't like you.
Don't be ridiculous.
Everyone likes me.
- Sheriff Hood.
- Yeah?
I've got something
you might want to hear.
- Uh...
- What?
Someplace private we can talk?
- You know?
- Yeah.
It's crazy out there today, huh?
- Is it always like that?
- You got something to tell me?
You're not my father.
No, that's very true.
Yeah, but see,
you have his name.
I don't think
I introduced myself.
I'm Jason Hood.
I don't know who you are,
but you're not Lucas Hood.
What do you want?
Well, for starters,
where's my father?
Your father is dead.
I figured.
- Did you kill him?
- No.
Why should I believe you?
I have no reason to lie to you.
You already got me nailed.
You don't seem
too worried about that.
too broken up for a guy
who just learned
his father's dead.
We weren't very close.
If it makes you feel any better,
he died doing the right thing.
Thanks.
It doesn't.
Yeah, I had a father
like that, too.
So what's stopping me from just...
walking out that door right now
and blowing your shit
out of the water?
If you really think I'm the guy who
killed your father,
a cop, in cold blood,
then had the balls
to steal his identity,
do you really think it's a smart idea
to sit there and threaten me?
Come on, I'll buy you lunch.
I'm fucking starving.
I'll talk to her.
Hello, Miriam.
You allowed the elders
to send your only daughter away
with nowhere to go.
She would have ended up
in the streets.
But I was there to put
a roof over her head and feed her.
As I think you knew I would be,
right?
And now
could it really be that you'd just
rather hang your laundry
and leave your son to die
than speak to me,
the only person who
might be able to help?
Patia.
- Walk to the house.
- To the house.
We want the boy.
Patia.
Patia, wait, please.
- I can't talk to you.
- Please.
Look, you can think
whatever you want about me,
but you and Solomon
grew up together
and I know you care for him.
- You've got to help me.
- No, I can't help you.
You can and you will.
Is it true about Solomon
and the Indian girl?
You know that little bridge
in the woods
- where the boys used to fish?
- Yes.
Go there and I'll meet you
there as soon as I can.
Thank you. Thank you.
Fucking cham!
Kai, no.
Get over here, you bun runner.
Blessed are the peacemakers
that they will be
called sons of God.
Come on, you fucking Dutchy!
- Don't.
- Kai, don't.
That's it, come on, you bitch.
You're all brave men
intimidating people
you know won't fight back.
I'll give you 30 seconds to get back
into your trucks and go.
No, what I'm thinking is
I'm gonna take this bat
and shove it up your bitch ass and
see how you like that.
- Show him.
- I see.
- Oh!
- Fuck!
Let's go.
Be strong, man.
Come on, right here.
- He's going nuts.
- Hold up, hold up.
- Whoa, whoa, whoa.
- Wait, wait.
Crazy. Crazy.
Do you know what's worse than getting
your testicles crushed
with a baseball bat?
Getting them crushed again.
Oh!
Go home.
We're coming back
for you, Dutchy.
Are you hiding the boy?
'Cause if you are...
You dare speak to me like this?
As if I would do such a thing.
Kai.
Leah.
To the Lord our God belong
mercies and forgiveness
though we have
sinned against him.
This is about the life
of your grandchild.
If Kai can help,
I will not be the one to stop him.
Mudder.
So these guys killed my father
and then you just killed them
and figured what the hell,
I always wanted to be a sheriff?
Let's just say
I needed to become someone else
and the opportunity presented itself.
Your turn.
Well, I was working for
these guys out in Portland.
- What kind of guys?
- Pretty much what you think.
You know, bad guys,
bad-tempered, bad drugs.
Things got uncool
and I decided it was time to split.
And they sent some asshole
after me back in Nevada.
They sent someone after you?
That means you either took
something that didn't belong to you
or you fucked someone
that didn't belong to you.
Yeah, one of those things.
You boys need anything more?
You got any pie?
Look around you, son.
Does this look like
the kind of place that serves pie?
Thanks, Sugar.
- We're good.
- How good?
Good enough.
Here's what I'm thinking.
You got everyone here believing
that you're Lucas Hood, right?
That takes some doing.
There's identification,
social security,
credit card numbers, the works.
Do you know how to do all that?
I know a guy.
I'm thinking of
just disappearing.
You know, like going
up to Canada
and maybe get work
with the fishing fleets.
I just... I don't...
I don't want to be looking over
my shoulder for the rest of my life.
Yeah, I can help you out.
But it's gonna take a few days.
So in the meantime, I'm gonna need
you to lay low for a while.
You understand?
That's one of the few
skill sets I do possess.
Shut up.
You're gonna check in to the Valley
Motel and you're gonna stay there.
I don't want to see
your face around town.
I'll come to you.
We do the thing,
then you say good-bye.
You go off, start your new life.
And you do not come back.
Hey, where you going?
In case you hadn't noticed,
I'm a little busy.
You mean you actually
do the job?
Now and then.
He just leave me with the check?
It's on the house.
Well, thanks for lunch.
- What the fuck?!
- Sit down.
Ah, I'm fucking bleeding.
Pay attention.
I saw your father die
right over there.
He didn't deserve it.
And the man who just
walked out this door,
he killed the men who did it.
Now, you may find this
hard to believe,
given his winning personality,
but the man actually
has friends here.
Good friends,
if you take my meaning.
I know because I'm one of them.
And if I get as much as an inkling
that you pose any threat to him,
I will personally
turn your father's grave
into a family plot.
Do you understand?
Yes, I understand.
Let me get you a Band-Aid.
No! Get off me!
Get off of me!
No!
No! No!
Hey.
You okay?
Hey, hey, hey.
It's okay.
Hey, hey, hey. You're okay.
What happened?
- Rebecca, what happened?
- A man.
- What man?
- In the woods. He attacked me.
Hey!
What happened?
- Let me see that.
- It's nothing. I'm fine.
You need to get that looked at.
I think I might have clipped him.
We got to go back in.
No, no, no, no.
No, no. Not you.
- Not like this.
- We're wasting time.
Brock has got the staties combing
the woods for Solomon.
Whoever is in there,
they're gonna find him.
I'm fine.
When was the last time
you actually slept?
You've got to give it a rest.
I'm gonna drive you home, okay?
Okay.
I don't live here.
I know.
You haven't eaten anything today.
I'm gonna make you something.
I said posse, idiot.
- You want some more?
- Yeah.
Cheers.
With everything that's happened in
the last couple of days,
you know what's
sticking with me?
Lana's mother told me
her girl was gonna
be a schoolteacher.
I wanted to do that once.
A long time ago.
How's your head?
Fine.
I should probably go.
You should go.
This is a bad idea.