Previously on The Better Sister...
[Nicky] Now I lay me down to sleep...
"As I Lay Me Down to Sleep" is not
a ghost story, it's a prayer.
"Now I lay me down to sleep...
[both] ...I pray the Lord
my soul to keep."
- Calm down.
- Get the fuck off me!
- Just--
- [Chloe] You touch me again,
I will fucking kill you!
We're still looking for
your husband's killer, so you know.
Which means we're starting
from square one.
There is a growing list of people
wanted him dead.
You're gonna be busy.
You deleted all of the Gentry Group files
on Adam's computer.
What were you looking for?
[Chloe] The truth about
what happened to Adam.
[Bill] We may never know.
- Jesus!
- [Olivero] We did have a deal.
- [Jake] I'm fucking out.
- [Olivero] You know, Adam was out, too.
[Catherine] Little advice, my love?
Don't run from Bill.
He likes the chase.
You have any interaction with that sister?
- What, Nicky?
- Yeah.
[Arty] Still takes care of the mother
who lives in Ohio.
Adam's.
Detective Dildo showed up
at my meeting today.
[Nicky] Is that his wife?
She's the one that put him here.
This doesn't make any sense.
[Chloe] "Father reporting finding son
face-down in the water,
but son showed no signs of water intake."
[Ethan] What does that mean?
[Nicky] It means that he lied.
[dramatic music playing]
Why didn't you say anything?
It's why I came.
♪ ♪
Nicky...
[breathing heavily]
Wh-What are you saying?
[tapping on steering wheel]
- [Nicky] Jesus Christ.
- [birds twittering]
One monstrosity after another.
[sighs heavily]
[dark, suspenseful music playing]
[Adam] Have a good day.
[doorbell rings]
[door unlocks]
Hi, Adam.
What are you doing here?
Is Chloe here? Chlo?
This isn't-- This isn't okay.
You have to go.
Chloe?
You're not allowed
to show up here without...
- Chloe?
- ...advance notice
and consent from us in writing.
- You know this.
- Yeah, well, I sent a carrier pigeon.
- Did it not arrive?
- Are you drunk?
Oh, you wish.
You smell like booze, though.
Where have you been?
I cannot fucking deal with this right now.
Oh.
Rough day, darling?
- Get up.
- I am not leaving
until I talk to Chloe.
- I'm calling the cops.
- Good. Call 'em.
I'll tell them everything
that you've been doing to my sister.
What's that?
My kid knows, too.
Okay, now I know you're fucking high.
We're gonna ask him.
We'll ask him when he gets home,
and then I'm taking them with me.
You're not getting anywhere near them.
And you're not keeping me
away from them ever again.
Call the cops, Adam!
Call 'em, let's do it!
Do you think they'll believe you,
with your history?
My history? That's history you made up.
Is that the story
you're telling yourself now?
- That's the truth.
- You're a fucking addict
and you always have been.
And you're a fucking monster!
Get off me!
[grunts] No!
[grunting]
[Nicky exclaims]
[both grunting]
[panting]
No. Fuck.
No! [screams]
- [grunting]
- [choking]
[Nicky groans]
[pained grunts]
[screaming]
[sputters weakly]
[grunting, exclaiming]
[Adam coughs]
[choking]
[trickling]
[intense, pulsing music playing]
[insects trilling]
[panting]
[chair clunks, rattles]
[Debbie] Chair is acting up again.
Only works in reverse.
[Nicky] Well, how'd all that happen?
I was at the Dollar Store,
looking for one of those shell signs,
"Beach This Way," for the bathroom.
- I thought that'd be cute.
- Yeah, that'd be cute.
They were having a special.
Ladder, smack in the middle of the aisle.
Ran right into it and toppled over.
- Would you believe it?
- Oh, those negligent assholes.
Yeah, I was on the phone with Disability
for five hours yesterday.
Who has that kind of time?
Well, they're slow-roll
that shit for sure.
First thing when the money comes in,
I'm getting ol' Susie Cruisie fixed.
My feet are swelling,
sciatica nerve's on fire.
You plug one leak, another one springs up.
Well, I don't know,
your paws look okay to me.
Nurse you are not. No offense.
Your mother, now she was a healer.
Tough, but knew her shit.
You'll get a cut, too,
when the check comes in, for the errands.
- Stop it.
- You stop it.
What did you get me?
- [chuckling mischievously]
- You know, you're gonna love it.
- Oh, she has risen.
- [phone buzzing]
- Use my office.
- Okay.
- [phone buzzing]
- [Debbie] Don't touch my shit.
Hey, there you are. Finally.
I thought you might be ghosting me.
What are you doing?
Me? Uh...
I'm just puttering around, you know?
What are you doing? What's, uh...
Hey, what'd you end up wearing
to that gala?
Something fancy? Feathers?
Leather?
Hey, are you okay?
Not really.
Something happened, I...
I-I've been wondering
whether I should tell you.
Well, of--
Yeah, of course, Ethan, tell me.
I saw something,
couple days ago, with Mom and Dad.
It... It was, um...
It was-- It was bad.
Bad how?
I was...
I was out on the terrace
taking a selfie to send you, and...
...they were arguing, and then he...
shoved Mom.
Like, hard. Really hard.
She hit her head on the wall.
Uh... W-What did you do?
Well, Mom left.
This wasn't the first time
that he's hurt her.
Is she okay now?
[voice breaking] I don't know,
it's hard to tell with her.
Yeah, she shuts down.
Yeah, she gets, like, scary calm, just...
I'm sorry,
maybe I shouldn't have said anything.
Baby, it's okay, I'm glad you told me.
Hey, and-- Are you okay?
- [knocking at door]
- Shit. Um, I have to go, um...
I'll call you later, okay?
Hey--
Okay.
- Call me later.
- [call beeps off]
[tense music playing]
[grunts]
[Debbie] You all right in there?
[Nicky] Yeah.
[chair whirring]
[Debbie] Girl, I saw Chloe
in one of these last week.
Next to the woman with the lips.
She's a do-gooder now.
[laughing] What a hypocrite.
She looked terrible. Thin, though.
Arms like a gymnast.
No Adam.
It's always just her, at these soirees.
As a mother, you wonder,
you know, is he happy?
Ah, they left us.
They're in their world over there.
We're here.
[Nicky sighs]
Did you bring the heavy cream?
I forgot.
It's for Atkin's. It works fast.
Only thing, my mouth tastes
like seaweed when I'm in ketosis.
- But I think it's worth it.
- I got to go.
I'll bring it by, okay? I'll bring it by.
[door opens]
[door closes]
[pensive music playing]
[doorbell rings]
Hi, Adam.
[panting]
[hyperventilating]
- [winces]
- [water running]
♪ ♪
[exhales]
[phone buzzing]
[Nicky] That's when they called me.
You came to protect me?
He wouldn't let me see you.
You're not keeping me
from my sister a minute longer.
Chloe, it was me or him.
He was gonna kill me.
What were you supposed to do?
You had to defend yourself.
- I don't--
- What else were you gonna do?
- It's gonna be all right.
- It might not be all right.
I mean, I don't think
that cop is gonna stop
- until she locks me up.
- No, stop it.
- Chloe...
- That is not happening.
- You don't know that.
- I won't let it happen.
Do you hear me?
I'm not gonna let it happen.
What about Ethan?
You're here with him.
You're gonna be here with him.
Okay?
Okay.
[sniffles] Okay.
- Okay.
- [sniffles]
Tomorrow...
tomorrow, you and Ethan...
...just go somewhere, go on a hike.
Just spend time with him.
'Cause I could really use
some time to think.
About what the fuck we're gonna do.
- I get it.
- Okay.
Do you still have the knife?
[tense music playing]
- Yeah.
- All right.
Let me hold on to that,
and I want the gun, too.
I know you have it.
It's in the car.
What the fuck were you gonna do with that?
I wasn't gonna let Ethan go to jail
for something I did.
[scoffs] Jesus, Nicky.
- [knock on door]
- [Ethan] You guys okay in there?
[Chloe sighs]
Yeah.
Okay.
[sniffles]
Gonna be all right.
[both sniffle]
[indistinct radio chatter]
Debbie Macintosh, Adam's mother,
misdemeanor rap sheet a mile long.
Mm. Something sexy about her.
Degenerate opportunist used
her only son's social security number
to set up several
fraudulent bank accounts.
Smart, too.
According to the rental office,
a blonde woman shows up a couple times
a week with groceries.
Nicky stayed loyal all these years?
It looks like it.
Flying out in a couple hours.
Yeah.
All Debbie's phones are disconnected.
- Lieu know?
- He will when he needs to.
- Mm...
- What?
Just seems like a long way to go.
Back to the beginning. It's the only way.
Who made the man everyone wanted dead?
We don't even know who he was, really.
Well, he's not the murderer.
I got Fran working on getting me
Nicky's DNA off her cigarette butt,
retrieved from the AA meeting.
We're checking local records in Ohio.
Pulling her phone records.
What've you got?
The FBI was all over Adam.
He was working with them.
Then he changed his mind.
But maybe Gentry still sends
a clear message
to everyone else at the firm,
"You cross us,
we're gonna show up to your home
and murder you in your living room."
I hate to admit this... I like it.
Yeah
I, um, I got a direct line now
to the feds.
The agent Adam was working with
thinks he's playing me.
Halfway crooked, this guy.
Does Lieu know?
He will when he needs to.
[chuckles]
So that's what you've been hiding.
Well...
...got a little nervous there
for a minute.
What my temper might do
to your reputation.
Well, I'm gonna try to make you proud.
[bag unzips]
[door opens]
- [Chloe] Hey.
- Hi.
[uneasy music playing]
Okay.
All right.
Thank you. Um...
Bug spray, sanitizer, sunscreen,
- water...
- Yeah, okay. Okay, I got it.
Right.
[sighs]
Have a good day, but, um,
keep your phone on you.
Sound and vibrate, both.
Keep it fucking on.
I got you.
- [Ethan] Ready.
- I'm gonna cook
something special for dinner tonight.
Great.
- Yeah.
- Okay. Stay nearby.
- When I say so, I need you to be there.
- I'll be there.
Okay.
- [Nicky] Bye!
- Love you guys!
[tense, suspenseful music playing]
[Nicky and Ethan chatting indistinctly]
[phone buzzing]
[sighs]
Hi.
Very favorable numbers being discussed
for the book deal, at our best imprint,
with a huge first run.
- Oh, that's great.
- Easily seven figures.
Uh-huh.
Even more if you do it together.
Have you had a chance
to talk it over with Nicky?
Uh... Yeah, no. Have not had a
opportunity to discuss
that particular subject, no.
Then find the time, please.
And for Bill, as well.
I already spoke to him.
You have to make this right with Bill.
Otherwise, all of this is for nothing.
Meaning you're on his side,
and you don't actually
want me to find out what happened to Adam,
but you're more than willing
to sell some story.
Meaning we invite others in
only on our terms.
Family matters stay in the family.
And my husband murdered
is not a family matter?
Well, that depends on how
you're defining family these days.
And that son of a bitch
was no one's family.
Talk it over with Nicole.
A whole new life for her.
- [knock on door]
- [gasps] Jesus fucking Christ.
[sighs]
[knocking on door]
- Hi.
What-What's going on?
Bill fired me.
- Oh, that son of a bitch.
- Yeah.
Fucked from the other side
by our mutual friend Agent Olivero.
Wait, wait. How do you know him?
He's been blackmailing me
ever since Adam died.
He... [sighs] ...he said he had dirt on me
via my exposure to Gentry Group.
He conscripts me into working with them,
me thinking that they're halfway decent,
only to find out, no, they're worse,
and I can't even get them what they want.
[tense, dramatic music playing]
[sighs]
Okay. Okay. How can I help you?
The FBI wants what... [sighs]
...what Adam had on Gentry.
- [scoffs] What did Adam have?
- Proof.
How they could build the projects
so quickly and cheaply.
I don't know what you're talking about.
Chloe... [sighs] You could build
a stadium in a couple months
if you've got unlimited labor
and no regulations.
A worker dies on the job one day,
ten more are there
to replace him the next.
Even if they're lied to
about what they're doing,
their passports are taken away
when they get there.
Oh, Jesus.
That's-that's human trafficking.
It's indentured servitude.
It's manslaughter.
Oh, my God.
- That is fucking horrifying.
- Braddock and Braddock
helped those scumbags build out
their holding structures.
Most of us didn't know the worst of it.
Those on the inside--
Bill, eventually Adam--
they did.
Look, the FBI's case is close,
but Gentry's smart.
They outsourced the worst of their
holdings to other stakeholders, like Bill.
And most of them,
just happy to be bought, like Bill.
And Adam is one of the only people
that was willing to work with the FBI?
I don't know.
I guess his conscience
outweighed his greed.
But Adam had access to material I don't.
Okay, but his-his files
on them were empty.
His computer had already been wiped.
No, but he was meticulous. He...
he would've kept a paper trail.
He kept records.
He had records about everything Gentry.
- Okay.
- That was his guarantee.
He would print them.
He'd put them in that old briefcase.
No, no, there was no files in there.
It was just a gun.
[dramatic music playing]
[sighs] The same gun he was carrying
the night he was murdered.
Look, Chloe...
Olivero, he's gonna... [sighs]
...he's gonna get me disbarred or,
I don't know, maybe worse.
He shows up at my house...
I'm freaking out here, Chlo.
I set up cameras at my place,
and I put them inside fake rocks.
But if Gentry got wind that Adam and I
were working with the FBI?
As much as I hate to help
this asshole's case,
as long as they're operating...
...neither one of us is safe.
[sighs]
Okay.
[seabirds calling]
[line rings]
[FBI operator over phone] FBI,
Queens County Field Office
Department of Civilian Complaints.
- All calls are strictly confidential.
- [sighs] Yes, um...
I'd like to file an anonymous complaint
about Special Agent Edward Olivero.
Is this the right place to call?
Yes. I'm listening.
Agent Olivero was physically aggressive
and sexually inappropriate with me.
We met to exchange information
about a case,
and he behaved erratically and abusively.
We take these accusations seriously.
Thank you for reaching out.
Thank you.
[exhales]
Call Michelle Sanders.
[phone buzzing]
- Hello, Chloe.
- [Chloe over phone] Michelle.
Jake stopped by my house today.
- Okay.
- He seemed...
very nervous--
scared, even--
about what could happen to him.
I want to help him find these documents,
something to get
these people off his back.
What people?
[dramatic, suspenseful music playing]
Jake was working with the same FBI agent
that Adam was.
Informing on Gentry Group.
Shit. Chloe.
Neither you nor Jake are my client,
so whatever you're saying to me,
you need to not be saying to me.
[scoffs] I thought
you considered him a friend.
I do.
So stay the fuck away from him.
[call beeps off]
[birds singing]
[Nicky] A friend told me about this place.
Apparently, when the water comes in,
the path disappears.
So, who was that tall drink of water
in court?
[Ethan laughs]
[laughs] I nailed it.
Yeah. We've been texting.
Uh, and she was maybe thinking
about coming up on the train today.
- Today, really?
- Yeah. Uh, her name's
- Helen.
Well, if only you had some wheels
to pick her up.
Honestly, I'm not sure if I'm up for it.
That was a lot to take in last night.
No one expects you
to pretend it wasn't, okay?
[Ethan] Yeah.
I've had a stomachache all day.
I'm just-- I'm pissed at Mom.
I didn't even really realize it until now.
She picked him over you.
That's bullshit.
Babe, I really think she thought
she was doing what was best for you.
For me or for her?
It's just... fucked.
- [Ethan sighs]
- [Nicky sighs]
Are you gonna stay here?
Seeing as you made a friend.
Not sure yet.
I know you had a whole life in-in Ohio.
That wasn't a life, you understand?
Wasn't a day went by
I didn't want to be here with you.
[sighs softly]
That still stands.
Okay.
Just...
It's just not always up to you.
Yeah.
[Nicky chuckles]
[Ethan chuckles]
Well, hello.
I'm glad you took my recommendation.
I didn't know you fished.
Yeah. I'm a sucker
for repetitive action with little reward.
- [Nicky laughs softly]
- Hi.
I'm Ken.
Ethan. Hi.
- This is my son.
- Yeah.
- Nice to meet you.
Do you want to stay here and try?
Are you asking for my keys?
[laughing] Yeah.
Sure.
Have fun.
Nice to meet you, Ken.
- Helen.
- Oh.
- Uh-huh.
- So, wait.
- How are you gonna get home?
- You know what?
Um, I think I'm going home with you.
I like that. Want to fish first?
- I... Oh.
- Come on.
[slow, mysterious music playing]
You have documents you want to hide.
You think...
the office.
Perhaps you had a secret room installed
without your wife's knowledge.
You hid the documents in the safe.
[beep, musical beeping]
[muttering quietly]
Perhaps you hid the documents
in the off-season comforters.
You hid them in your many collared shirts.
Hmm.
Okay.
You leave the files, you take the gun.
You were scared
what Olivero would do when you backed out,
and what Gentry could do to you
if you stayed in.
[Bill on recording] And squeeze Gentry
for all they're worth.
The bigger the ask,
the bigger the fucking price tag.
And I want you to put the money
- in my private account.
- [Adam on recording] Okay, I'm on it.
Fucking Bill.
Rodriguez is done.
He's not your problem anymore.
[indistinct voice over phone]
No, you keep your house clean,
'cause someone from your side confirmed
that Adam was meeting
with the fucking feds.
Well, he's not talking anymore, is he?
Ah, she's all worked up,
she's not thinking straight.
- I'll take care of it.
- You sure?
I said I'll take care of it.
[sighs]
Today is not the day.
Are you, uh, doing poorly, Mr. Braddock?
I'm here to discuss the case files
from Gentry Group.
Do you have a brain in there,
or is it hair follicles all the way down?
I told you,
you don't get anything without a subpoena.
Maybe we can, uh, talk up in your office.
Listen, your two-bit CSI impersonation is
not only cheaply-wrought,
but it's rancid, and it's stale,
and it's long past it's expiry date.
You're done.
You ought to go back to whatever deli
or market your parents own because--
Actually, restaurant.
If you're ready for a pivot,
a handsome guy like you could make
a lot of money in other markets.
Hmm. So, you gonna invite me up?
I'll be back with a subpoena.
[door opens]
- Uh--
- I'll be working from home today.
Yes, sir.
[slow footsteps]
Oh.
[inhales]
Oh, it smells so nice in here.
Oh, yeah?
Like what?
Like you.
- Suntan lotion and the ocean.
- Hmm.
Is this your mom?
The one who saved you in Tijuana?
Mm-hmm.
Beautiful.
[Nicky sighs softly]
You okay?
Just feel like
that detective's everywhere.
Mm-hmm.
I'd be surprised
if she made it all the way out here.
It's just me.
Just... us.
Show me the bedroom.
[wind chime sounds]
[seabirds squawking]
- [Ken] I've been wanting to ask.
- Mm-hmm.
What...
- is.. this?
- [laughs softly]
What do you think it is?
- Mm.
Is it bigger than a bread box?
Is a cry for help
- bigger than a bread box?
- [laughs]
My dad had the same one.
- Ah.
- Mm-hmm.
It's a... it's an Army dog tag.
Only his had writing in it.
Name and ID of a buddy of his,
died over in Vietnam.
At least that's what I knew as a kid
'cause he never talked about it.
And I felt I needed to sear that feeling
permanently into my body.
Now there's a nice space there
for whatever disappointment
or regret I'd like to fill in.
Hmm.
Someday.
So... bigger than a bread box?
[laughs softly] Yeah.
Listen...
I think I might have to go back home
for a while, back to Cleveland.
Hmm. I was wondering about that.
Mm.
You taking Ethan with you?
[Nicky sighs]
That's up to him.
Well, I'll be damned.
What?
I'm gonna miss you.
[phone buzzing]
- Oh.
- Oh. Oh, it's...
it's my sister, and she's very particular
about response time.
[sighs]
Hello?
Mm-hmm.
Yes.
Okay, great.
Yeah, I can go right now.
Okay.
Okay, bye.
[exhales]
[sighs]
Can you drive me somewhere, please?
My kid took my dead ex-husband's car
to fuck his girlfriend.
[chuckles]
[knocking]
Oh, my God, Chloe.
- Hi.
- Come in, come in.
- Thank you.
- [sighs]
- I've missed you.
[door closes]
I saw this.
And I just felt very strongly
that you needed it.
- [chuckles] Okay.
- [chuckles]
And this is...
part of my mea culpa.
He'll be very glad to see you.
You just... move forward.
And he will, too.
Thank you.
- He's in the office.
- Okay.
[Chuck] That's very nice.
I wasn't expecting you.
I wanted to apologize.
For my behavior the other day.
Well, there's all sorts of things
clouding your mind.
And this is a part of that apology.
All the files Adam had
from the Gentry Group.
Everything that the FBI is looking for.
I don't want anything to do with it.
Or the FBI.
Why are you doing this?
I don't want to live like this.
I'm afraid all the time,
wondering if I'm gonna be next.
Whatever Adam knew...
...he died for.
I don't want that near my family.
Well, there's no reason it should be.
I just need to...
get back to doing what I love.
But first I have to put my...
family back together again.
Including your sister?
Yes, making peace there, too.
I mean...
it's the only way.
Hmm.
And when that's done,
then I can put my other family
back together again, too.
You...
and Catherine.
Consider my allegiance pledged
- from here on out.
- Mm-hmm.
You know, you've always been my favorite.
Don't tell Catherine.
[laughs]
Let's have a drink to commemorate.
You have one without me, I've got to run.
Trying to figure out the particulars
of some financial freedom for my sister.
That's very decent of you.
But I'll be back in the city
in a few days.
Let's get dinner.
- Yeah.
- I'll third wheel for you and Chuck.
[laughs]
[mysterious music playing]
[Bill] Bye.
♪ ♪
[sighs]
She was just at my place.
Where are you?
[menacing music playing]
Detective Matt Bowen?
You ordered take out?
Thank you.
[up-tempo music playing]
Papa, I got to go.
[Cyrus] Always.
Have something big.
I'm sending you the address. Call me.
♪ ♪
[sighs]
You're McCabe?
- Jerry.
- Interesting.
That for me?
You know, your sister was correct.
There's not much information
about this case online.
Yeah, I told her that.
Nor anything connecting it
to Detective Guidry specifically.
[sighs] Well, fuck.
But in certain official agency databases,
the records exist.
Redacted.
But I worked some magic.
Detective Guidry was
on the scene that day,
searching for a man by the same name
and the same race.
She beat the shit
out of the wrong fucking Black guy?
And they covered it up?
It's not admissible in court, any of it.
[laughs]
And the police higher-ups would
shut it down
before it even got there.
They're very good at protecting their own.
- Cocksuckers.
- [scoffs] Well,
court of law's not the one that matters.
Thank you so much
for getting this from, uh--
I don't want to know
where you get things from.
Nothing ever actually disappears.
That's unfortunate for most of us.
Nice doing business with you, Jerry.
[exhales]
Hey, your man came through, so...
Y-- I'm headed to her now.
Where the fuck are you?
I'll tell you later.
- I'm headed home.
- What do you mean, "later"?
Chlo, I am freaking out.
I got used to having a Nancy Drew shadow.
I do not like not knowing
where the fuck she is.
[thrilling music playing]
[phone buzzing]
[faint TV chatter]
Debbie Macintosh?
I'm Detective Nan Guidry.
I'm working on your son Adam's case.
Oh, yeah.
I saw you on TV.
Outside the courthouse.
It must've been difficult,
watching all that stuff.
Folks just loved it.
They couldn't get enough.
Story like that, though,
what do you expect?
It's like a Danielle Steel novel.
The Sisters.
Do you mind if I come inside?
Talk to you for a minute?
You got to push me the rest of the way.
Uh, you in neutral?
He was very uptight,
my son,
about the way things ought to be.
We didn't see eye to eye in that respect.
He didn't appreciate some of my choices.
Even though I told him he wouldn't even
have a goddamn social security number
if it wasn't for me.
We hadn't spoken in a long while.
Must've been hard doing it alone.
Father in jail and all.
[wheezes]
They let that bastard out about two weeks
before the cancer got him.
Huh.
My source said he died in jail.
Yeah, wrong again.
He called Adam.
Didn't hear back from him.
Died in my arms.
You and the ex reunited?
[laughs] Fuck no.
[laughs]
We, no, we hated each other, but...
You know, I couldn't let him die alone,
smelling like prison, so... [sniffles]
I did what I could, I...
clipped his nails and combed
the three hairs he had left on his head.
He just wanted to meet his grandson
before he died.
And he never heard back from Adam.
Particular type person can cut family out.
The only time I ever held Ethan
is when he was a baby,
before all that trouble.
What happened at the pool.
With Nicky.
Yeah.
This whole town chewed her up.
It's a tough thing to come back from.
You show me a mother
who's perfect all the time.
- Nobody wants to hurt their kid.
- [phone buzzes]
We make mistakes.
I mean, sure you have your Caseys,
your Andreas, they go crazy, lose it
and drown their babies in the tub.
But that's not Nicky.
You still see Nicky?
She brings food by for me,
Mondays and Thursdays.
On account of my not being able
to get around too easily.
'Cause my license still in limbo.
Yeah.
But not since...
since what happened with Adam?
She came back.
Not when she said she would.
She didn't even bring my cream.
Your cream?
Heavy whipping.
For my Jell-O.
You do Atkins?
- Uh...
- She left her phone here, too.
When was this?
The day before it happened.
I'm not sure when she got it,
'cause by the time
she did come back,
she said they called her on it.
And that's when she told me.
[menacing music playing]
Wait, what did you say to me?
[Nicky] The police in New York
called and told me...
...Adam's been killed.
Killed? Killed? Killed how?
He was stabbed.
Murdered? My boy murdered?
No, no, no, no, no, that' s impossible.
I'm so sorry.
You're a fucking liar.
I don't believe one fucking word.
You get out of my house now.
You get the fuck out of my house!
Coming here with that bullshit!
Get out!
[screaming]
But by that afternoon,
it was all over the news.
I kept calling her, leaving messages,
but she wasn't picking up.
Not at first, at least.
People find all sorts of ways
to disappoint you.
[Guidry] So Nicky was here
the day Adam was murdered.
You expected her to come back,
but she didn't.
Even though she'd left her phone here.
And it was here all night.
When she did come back,
she told you Adam had been
stabbed.
Would you say this was mid-morning?
What are you doing?
I'm just putting together
a statement that you could sign.
Just confirming those details.
I haven't told you shit.
[Nicky sighs]
Huh.
Definitely thought
the dog'd be gone by now.
Well, Franzen grew on me,
so I bought him a friend.
Winter.
Oh.
That's how it works.
Hi, Winter.
Okay.
You're gonna want to push this out
far and wide,
in as damaging a light as possible.
You're gonna like it.
It's like a gift.
Yeah.
- [chuckles] I know.
- You're gonna
piss off a lot of police with this.
What else is new?
This isn't Ohio, Nicole.
Noted.
Maybe you can use
that reporter Sid, from the wake.
He seemed to have no trouble
publishing from questionable sources.
Indeed.
Today.
Now.
Please.
And thank you.
This is good for you too, isn't it?
For whatever comeback campaign
you got going for Chloe?
Please and thank you.
Have you given any thought to my proposal?
I'm sure Chloe's told you,
they're talking big numbers.
You could get rid of the Etsy store.
Because it will be both of you
writing the book together.
[sighs]
I'd be intrigued if I had any fucking
idea what you were talking about.
[sighs]
Expedited warrant
for Bill Braddock's home office.
And there's your backup.
12th precinct.
And all goes well, they said
you could use their station, too.
Side entrance.
They understand we'd all like this kept
as quiet as possible.
Thanks. Should all be in there.
How'd you get your hands on it?
Someone from the office reached out
after I made my presence known there.
Thought I might be interested in taking
a look at his home office, as well.
Since you made it clear
how much these files meant to you,
figured we could help each other out
in the, uh,
furtherance of our objectives.
Nearby in case you need anything.
I won't.
[suspenseful music playing]
♪ ♪
[knocking loudly]
Hello?
- Charles Braddock? Detective Bowen.
- Yeah.
I have a warrant to search
your husband's home office.
- Let's go, guys.
- Uh...
Um...
What the fuck is this?!
Expedited.
Must've been something persuasive.
Rather talk at the station.
12th precinct has a room we can use.
- How thoughtful.
- [officer] Detective Bowen?
[knife chopping]
[heavy thump]
Nicky?
[suspenseful music playing]
[exhales]
♪ ♪
[phone chimes]
[line ringing]
[Clark] Guidry, where the hell you been?
Call me a seat cushion Lieu,
'cause I just saved our asses.
Nicky Macintosh left her phone
in Cleveland the night of the murder.
Told Debbie Macintosh-- Adam's mother,
still alive, by the way--
that Adam had been stabbed.
But we never gave Nicky that information.
Made this statement over the phone?
No, I came to see her in person, Lieu.
Oh, Jesus, Nan.
Statement's in an unofficial capacity
as of now,
but the DNA in the Ohio database--
Nicky's been arrested before,
unsurprisingly--
matches the cigarette butt
I nicked from her.
How much you want to bet we find that DNA
on Adam's clothes
from the night of the murder?
Waiting on Fran to confirm it,
could be any minute.
But I'm on my way
over to the house right now,
- so I'll see you there.
- No, you're not.
- What?
- You ain't seen the internet?
My phone just got juice.
First thing I did was call you. What--
"Detective with a history of aggression."
Oh, no.
Fuck!
- No.
- All your shit from years ago, Nan,
it's-it's all over the place.
- Oh, fuck.
- You're off the case.
- Officially.
- But, Lieu, I got her!
No, you didn't.
Hearsay heard
from an unreliable, grieving mother
by an out-of-jurisdiction detective.
Having her on record's
not even gonna matter
when we get the DNA match.
I put a stop to the labs, Nan.
What? Please don't, please don't.
Personnel on leave
cannot make tech requests.
On leave, Lieu?
Come on, don't put me on leave, Lieu.
Please, I can't be on leave.
And besides...
we've already taken in
a person of interest.
Who?
[Ethan] So you are leaving.
[Nicky] Maybe.
I don't know. I don't want to go.
I really don't want to go.
Yeah.
But I might not have a choice.
Sometimes, I...
wondered if I was supposed to be in there.
You know, in jail?
What?
Wondered if that was maybe why I felt
halfway okay inside.
Like I thought maybe I deserved it.
Ethan?
Let that go.
Mm. You don't get it.
When I left Kev that night, I came home.
I wanted to change.
When I walked in,
I knew something was wrong.
And then I saw him.
Mom?
My first thought was I had to find Mom.
Was she okay? Did he hurt her? But...
Mom?
...when I called, she wasn't there.
Then I thought, "She did it.
She stabbed him to death."
And then I thought,
"I have to protect her."
So I went to the office,
I-I threw things around,
made it look like someone broke in.
Smashed the window, grabbed some shit.
And when I was walking out, I heard...
[wheezing]
I could've called someone.
An-an ambulance,
I could've helped him, but...
...I just left.
[exhales]
When I think about it now...
...I'm glad I didn't.
I would do it again, to protect her.
[somber music playing]
[Hank] Killers all the same.
I wanted you to come.
And if you're leaving,
I'm coming with you.
[exciting music playing]
♪ ♪
[dramatic music playing]
[sighs]
- [door opening]
- [Nicky] Hello? We're home.
- [door closes]
- [Chloe] Perfect timing.
Dinner's ready.
Good day?
[Nicky sighs] Yeah.
You?
- Stayed busy.
- Uh-huh.
Um, what's going on with him?
[sighs]
He wants to leave, Chlo.
Go with me back to Ohio.
Wait, you're not, you're not leaving.
Well, I don't know,
I think that might be best, actually.
Uh, w-where is this,
you know, coming from?
Catherine told me about the book deal.
[sighs]
I didn't tell you about that yet
because we were dealing
with all this other shit.
I don't give a fuck about
a tell-all payday,
I care about where your loyalty lies.
Who you're with, who you back.
'Cause if it's not me, you, us,
this, Ethan--
100%--
then we are fucking gone.
[exhales]
You and Ethan are all there is to me.
Our life here together
is all there is to me, okay?
You have no idea
how much I have missed you.
[newscaster over TV] Reports coming in
that powerhouse lawyer
and man-about-town
Bill Braddock was seen leaving
his West Village town house in handcuffs.
Braddock flanked
by a detective from East Hampton,
where one of the lawyers
at Braddock's firm, Adam Macintosh,
was brutally murdered this summer.
Macintosh's own son was recently acquitted
for the murder of his father,
leaving the case unsolved,
seemingly, until now.
More on this evolving story
after the break.
- You guys okay?
- You ready to eat?
We should sit. Yeah.
[dramatic music playing]
[TV continues indistinctly]
[sighs]
[newscaster] Again,
this was just moments ago.
Bill Braddock taken into custody
by East Hampton police.
You called the press.
Bold, but really stupid.
Mr. Braddock is a person of interest
in the Adam Macintosh case.
But he's involved
in multiple ongoing investigations.
[reporters clamoring]
[reporter]
Any comments, Mr. Braddock?
♪ ♪
[sighs]
[reporters clamoring]
[newscaster] According to reports,
police raided Braddock's home office...
Good for you getting it all wrong.
Idiot.
Bill Braddock, powerhouse attorney,
taken into custody
for the murder of Adam Macintosh.
Boy, oh, boy.
- This case has captivated residents...
- Boy, oh, boy.
[news report continues indistinctly]
You motherfucker.
♪ ♪
- [Nicky] Jake?
- [knocking on door]
[Chloe] You can see Ursa Major, right?
[Nicky] Yeah. You can see it.
That's what we did today.
We smoked on the beach.
Built a fire.
Looked at the Big Dipper.
That's the story.
[dramatic music playing]
I don't have any story without you.
Not one that's worth telling, anyway.
How should we start? Hmm?
♪ ♪
[Nicky] Now I lay me down to sleep.
[Chloe] I pray the Lord, my soul to keep.
[Chloe and Nicky] And if I die
before I wake...
...I pray the Lord my soul to take.
♪ ♪