I don't like it.
His businesses are legitimate.
Why would he need us?
He's been buying most of the old city
and the outlying areas
using holding companies.
The land is mainly worthless,
but I don't understand what he's doing.
Encantado.
Likewise. Have you seen it before?
When I was a kid.
Road trip with my parents.
- Hasn't changed a bit.
- Hm.
Let me show you around.
Mm-hm.
We've upgraded the turbines.
They're rated to last
100 years without maintenance.
All to power... this.
We're looking for resilience.
Our timeline
is more ambitious than most.
We offer a unique proposition.
Data has always been fungible.
Temporary.
If you invest yours with us,
it will be written in stone.
- Forever.
- Forever...
in my experience
is a little bit longer
than most people expect.
How much of our platform
are you looking to reserve?
- All of it.
- Come again?
What I want is already in there.
It was stolen from me.
From one of my facilities,
eight years ago.
And I know you were
paid handsomely to store it.
I would suggest you take it up
with the person who stole it.
I can't. She's dead.
Which means I can't decrypt it.
And no one else can.
I don't want it moved or disturbed.
So I'll take the whole shebang.
This is a unique asset,
and as such, it's not for sale.
This is America.
Everything here is for sale.
That's a pretty good return
on your investment.
We know what you've been doing.
You think anyone sells land
without our approval?
We've been happy to sell.
It's worthless scrubland.
But you can't have this place.
You ever hear the one
about the missionary
who tried to negotiate with the tiger?
He told the tiger
he could eat most of him,
but he had to stop
when he got to his head.
You and your friends in the cartel
or whatever the fuck you're
calling yourselves these days
sell me this lump of concrete, today.
Or?
Or you give it to me
for nothing. Tomorrow.
We, uh...
we weren't very welcome
when we came here.
We had to accept
whatever the old timers
offered, at first.
We buried most of them
at the bottom of this lake.
Our organisation has
a long, proud history
of defending itself
and its business aggressively.
Door number two, then.
Mañana.
He said that
yesterday he would have paid.
But today we would
give it to him for nothing.
Thank you.
Is my work done?
Yes. You can rest now.
You're up. I have a dilemma.
Which would you choose? White or black?
Christina?
- They both look great.
- Pick a side, Chrissie.
What are you wearing tonight?
Uh, this?
Right.
It looks great,
unlike these damn bags under my eyes.
I look like a zombie.
- Bad night's sleep?
- Nightmares.
Maybe I should've taken a tab.
But, uh, I just kept
tossing and turning.
Is it that weirdo again?
I blocked him,
but he keeps getting through.
It's just some creep
or a bot trying to sell you
a privacy subscription.
I guess.
Lately, I feel like
someone's watching me.
No offence, but how?
I mean, except for work,
you don't leave the apartment,
which is why you're coming out tonight.
I mean, he's supposed to be
a really nice guy.
And his profile's platinum rated.
Set-ups are just so awkward.
And so is dying alone.
You cannot hide from the world
forever, Christina.
Okay.
That was insane.
This is way better than I expected.
This place is fucking wild.
Can't believe this is your first time.
Come on.
I know a spot that's really
gonna blow your mind.
Can you see it?
It's looming over us. The tower!
Can you see it? Huh?
Can you see it? Can you see it?
Record pitch.
There's a young girl.
Not that young.
More like late teens.
She lives at home
with her father in the country.
Scratch that. The city.
He's a little infirm,
so she spends most of her time with him.
But she dreams of a bigger life
with excitement, adventure, romance.
Christina.
Pause record.
We need to talk
about your work performance.
I mean, don't you want
to advance in your career?
- Of course I do.
- Well, then you got to stop
pitching these saccharine stories.
You know, people want sex,
danger, violence,
transgressions, melodrama.
They want tragedy.
- Yada, yada, yada.
- I know.
I... I was thinking maybe I could write
in some different genres
to broaden it out.
Maybe a little romance, some humour.
Maybe just save that for your diary.
I know you've got it in you
to write the kind of copy we need.
Now, take that story you wrote
a couple months back.
Poor schmuck loses everything,
drowns his sorrows,
stalks some girl.
How'd it end again?
- Everyone dies.
- Yes. That's right.
It's a real tearjerker.
Just, uh, bring more of that.
Or else I'm gonna have to
find another writer who can.
- Understood?
- Yes. Of course.
All right.
Hello? You hear me?
I know you're out there.
I saw what you wrote.
Why are you doing this to us?
You have to help me.
Your game is ruining my life...
Always a classic
by the inimitable Hendrix.
And now, back to our coverage
of the festivities.
Preparations are underway
for this year's...
No!
Are you ready, darling?
- For what?
- This is the new world.
And in this world, you can be
whoever the fuck you want.
Oh, for fuck's sake...
Got any plans for the anniversary?
Nah. Just work.
Cashing in on that overtime, eh?
Man, seven years ago,
it would've just been robots
working the holiday, but...
lucky for us,
they're all scrap metal now.
Least the riots
ensured our job security.
That wasn't exactly the point
of the riots.
Yeah, 'cause the riots had no point.
They won us our freedom.
Sure, but from what? Ourselves?
Hey, man, the way I look at it,
that Incite machine that they blew up
didn't tell us who we could be,
it told us who we already were.
- You actually believe that?
- Don't you? Let me ask you this.
Has your life changed since they
destroyed those machines?
You haven't been practising enough.
Dad!
Good to see you, Cookie.
Here. All right.
- How'd you do that?
- Like I said, practice.
A lot of it.
On cans?
Yeah. On cans.
Here.
M'kay.
Remember. This.
Now stare at it.
Okay. Visualise.
Breathe out.
Hold steady.
And squeeze.
Frankie! Caleb!
I was visualising.
Well, come inside
and visualise meatloaf.
- Just a little longer?
- C'mon, listen to your mother.
Coming.
Go wash up.
Enough with the cowboy shit.
- She likes it.
- She's seven, Caleb.
Thanks to you, her hobbies
are sugar and violence.
Look, I'm sorry.
I know it's not an easy day for you,
but the war is over.
It's time you start living that way.
Okay?
Hm.
Go set the table.
What's the magic word?
Divorce.
- Love you too.
- Hm.
You lose power the other night?
Must've been spared.
You, uh, sure you don't want
some extra bottles for your guests?
Guests?
Your friends.
Stopped by asking for directions.
I tried to describe it,
but you live pretty far
off the beaten path.
You really should get
a sat phone or, um,
- some kind of connec...
- These friends of mine,
how long ago did they stop by?
Not 20 minutes since you been in.
On second thought,
why don't you go ahead
and add that to my tab?
Fire!
How did you find me?
Two days ago. We got a signal.
Your little power outage. It was enough.
How many more are after me?
I'm no... not at liberty to say.
Well, let me liberate you.
Seven years,
I've been off the grid alone,
not bothering anyone.
And yet here you are darkening my door.
Who sent you, Colonel Brigham?
Who the fuck is that?
I'm afraid I don't have
the patience to explain.
Now be a dear.
Close your eyes, won't you?
Go get her.
I've got no idea she's home or not.
Haven't seen her
in a couple of days.
Shit.
Welcome home.
- Hello?
- You on your way?
Shit. I forgot.
You didn't forget.
You repressed.
I'm not going to be
an accessory after the fact
to the murder
of your social life. Let's go.
But...
Look, I'm sure it was nothing.
Probably that kid from the fourth floor
that likes to smoke weed
on the fire escape.
- Yeah. Right.
- Mm. You want some?
- No, I'm okay.
- Hm.
Here. In case.
And remember, smile.
You have to at least try.
Do I?
I mean, even if by some miracle
we're right for each other,
shouldn't it be natural and easy?
Are you kidding?
Take a look at this world.
Nobody wants easy or natural.
Art is a lie
that tells the truth, honey.
And the truth is, you need to get laid.
Look at this.
All the people. You like people.
- You should try breathing.
- I should get a drink.
Uh-huh. Yes, you should.
It's going to be great.
Thank you.
Huh. Just give me the signal
if he's a dud.
Hm?
Oh, and don't forget to smile.
Most people think
it's just elite gambling,
but there's a system to investing.
Patterns that some minds
can decipher.
If there weren't,
I wouldn't be sitting
in this lovely restaurant
drinking superb wine
with such fine company.
So, enough about me.
What is it you do, again?
I'm a writer for Olympiad Entertainment.
Thank you.
Uh, wh...
what games do you write for?
Maybe I've played them.
I've been working on a new game.
It doesn't have a name yet.
It's still in beta.
But even after it's released,
you probably won't know my work.
I mostly write non player characters.
What's that?
Background characters that interact
with the players on their journeys.
Not as high-profile
as programming the leads.
But it's just as important.
For most players, the background
characters are just cannon fodder.
I'm not doing it for the players,
I'm doing it for myself.
How so?
Real life can be disappointing.
Not that it's so bad. Just...
there should be more to it.
Maybe you just haven't found
the right man yet.
You sound depressed.
There's tabs for that.
They'll fix you right up.
What if I'm not the one that's broken?
What if it's the world that needs fixing?
There's tabs for that feeling, too.
Of course.
Will you excuse me?
- Please stop calling me.
- Wait, wait!
Don't hang up. You need to help me.
The doctors think I'm crazy.
But I know you're real.
Just like the tower is real.
You need to stop what you're doing.
I told you, I'm not doing anything.
You're destroying my life.
I'm not. I don't even know you.
You can't hide from me.
I will find you.
Do you understand?
You have to end this, or I will.
You need help,
and I hope you get it.
But next time you call,
I'm going to the police.
No, no, don't hang...
Yeah, I'm surprised.
I just bumped into a work friend.
Oh, really?
I think I'm gonna be out for a while.
Don't be discouraged about tonight.
Are you sure you're okay?
Maya, it's fine, really. Have fun.
- Where are you?
- I'm almost home.
Okay, good. I gotta go. You're okay?
- Yeah.
- Take care.
Bye.
- Sorry about that.
- It's my fault.
I wasn't paying attention.
I, uh, I didn't see you there.
But now I do.
It's okay.
You scared me.
I guess we're even.
I'm Peter.
I... I just have to get home.
My room mate's waiting for me.
I've been wanting to meet you
for such a long time.
- Excuse me?
- I knew you existed.
I was worried you weren't real,
but here you are.
Why are you doing this to us?
It's you. You're the one
who's been calling.
I need to ask you
to leave us alone.
- No.
- No, stop!
Stop! No, no, no!
- No!
- This isn't who I am.
- Get away from me!
- Please, this is important.
I lost my job, my wife.
I thought it was the tower. But...
it was you. You made me do those things.
All these people do
what you want them to.
I don't know what
you're talking about...
- No!
- No, no, let me go!
You need to stop!
No! No! No!
How did you know so much about us?
The game. You wrote us into it. How?
Listen to me.
Listen to me. Pe... Peter...
I'm so sorry for everything
that's happened to you.
But I have nothing do with that.
I can't help you.
You need to help me.
I need for the story to change.
I need the ending to be different.
- I'm sorry.
- No!
Get off me, man!
"They heard a voice scream,
'We need our dragon!'
But my father and the dragon knew
that nothing in the world
would ever make them go back
to Wild Island.
The end."
All right. Time to tuck in.
All right.
You and Bear Bear sleep good, all right?
Can we leave the lights on tonight?
- Why would we do that?
- Bear Bear's scared.
I told him I'd keep watch over him.
Well, you know the best way
to keep watch at night
is to turn the lights down
around you and light up...
Light up the perimeter.
That way, no one can see you,
but you can see.
See everyone.
Look, um, Bear Bear doesn't need
to think about this stuff.
Okay? Everyone is safe and sound.
Promise?
I promise.
Okay, goodnight.
- Did you hear that?
- It's probably nothing.
Goodnight, Mum.
Come on, let's get you in bed.
- Hey.
- Fuck!
What the hell is this, Caleb?
There is something out there.
Yeah. A raccoon or a neighbour
or a delivery man.
We've been through this.
You just need to take
deep breaths. Calm yourself.
The past is in the past.
Nothing is going to hurt you
except your own mind.
I'm sorry.
Are you gonna help me or not?
Peter, I know that you're upset,
but whatever you think is happening,
you're just confused.
So you're not gonna help.
I wish I could,
but the stories that I write,
they're not real.
Do you remember how mine ends?
What?
- Peter, where are you?
- Look up.
Is this up to me,
or did you write this, too?
I found it under her pillow.
You're rubbing off on her, Caleb.
Isn't that a good thing?
Not when she's pretending
to have PTSD.
I see the messages you and your
war buddies send to each other.
Chemtrails, government cover-ups.
You see threats everywhere,
and now so does Frankie.
Look, I am not paranoid.
Maybe you're right.
I'm beginning to think
it's not that you fear war,
- it's that you miss it.
- Oh, my...
This life is too ordinary for you.
What?
You have a job,
a home,
a beautiful child,
and a very patient wife.
But it's never enough, is it?
Hey.
False alarm, Bear Bear.
See? It's just a raccoon.
Crap.
Hey there.
Is your daddy home?
Daddy, this man wants to talk to you.
Frankie!
I believe this is yours.
- Who are you?
- An old friend.
Caleb!
Frankie!
Are you okay?
- Go inside.
- Okay. Are you okay?
Hello, darling.
It's really you.
You know, I thought...
I was sure I was never gonna
see you again.
And yet here I am,
disposing and dismembering
just like the good old days.
If something happened to my daughter,
you have no idea...
I have every idea...
which is why it won't come to that.
I know who sent those men after us.
William.
He's back at it.
I, uh... Frankie's asleep. Thank God.
I called Carver.
The guys are downstairs.
All these years,
I thought you were paranoid.
But the war isn't over, is it?
No, it is me they wanted.
Look, I am the one
who brought this upon us.
And I am the one
who has to end it.
So you're leaving.
Only for a little while.
You promised you'd be a father.
I am one.
Everything I do is for you...
and for Frankie.
You're going to get yourself killed.
Hey, I will come back to you.
I promise.
All right.
- You know the drill.
- You got it.
I always knew this day was coming.
As soon as you stop running,
everyone else starts to catch up.
- Any idea why now?
- I don't know.
But I had a little tête-à-tête
with the one that they sent after me.
We're not the only ones
William was after.
He was very interested in talking
to a Senator in California.
Then we should get to him first.
We?
I'm coming.
It's the only way
I can protect my family.
I'll be fine on my own.
You can stay here.
- You probably should.
- Would you?
No.
But I'd regret it.
Record pitch.
I want to write a new story.
About a girl...
a girl who's searching.
The girl doesn't know
what she's searching for.
She just knows there
is an emptiness in her life.
Or maybe it's inside her.
And when she finds the thing
she's searching for,
everything will make sense.
I want a story with a happy ending.
Stupid.
Stupid stories nobody wants to hear.