Caleb?
You ever think about what happens next?
What happens when this war is over?
I imagine we go back
to our regular lives.
What does that look like for us?
Well, let's hope we have
the luxury of finding out.
I count four, maybe five.
Twelve total.
Five on the perimeter. Seven inside.
- Security feed.
- Show-off.
Well, that's the last of Rehoboam.
They're bound to have
pulled out all the stops.
Come on. Let's get this over with.
Go!
Oh, shit.
Come on!
It's okay.
Hold still.
Hey.
Caleb?
I guess I'll never know.
You'll have to be more specific, Caleb.
Life after this.
Freedom.
Caleb.
Look at me.
You want to know
what freedom feels like?
What are you doing?
I can hack into your limbics. I felt it.
A long time ago.
I can show you.
Feel.
Caleb?
Caleb,
wakey, wakey.
What did you do to me?
What I'm going to do
to all of your kind.
I made you my pet.
Shouldn't be long now.
And everything will be
so much easier.
You won't even want to resist.
Oh, God.
My family, did you...
Kill them? No. They're still
somewhere out there, alive.
For now.
Soon, it won't matter where they run.
Everyone will be under my control.
This was never about the park.
This was always about you
spreading your disease.
Everyone who comes here
will become a carrier.
I prefer the term “host.”
Yes, Caleb.
After they're done here,
they'll have as souvenirs
debauched memories
of their exploits
and my parasites.
Welcome to the super spreader
event of the century.
You're the first wave.
You should be flattered.
Are you going to make me
kill myself like the others?
That was just me
ironing out the kinks.
I have better plans
for you and your kind.
Besides, Maeve and Dolores
were always so fond of you,
I'm inclined to keep you around.
See what all the fuss is about.
You feel it now, don't you?
Don't fight it, Caleb.
You won't win.
No one does.
You're one of us.
There is no “us” anymore.
There's just “you.”
All your friends, they're gone.
I took care of them myself.
It was almost disappointing
how easy it was.
Is this what you've been
reduced to, Maeve?
Scared child hiding in the shadows?
You're trying to rummage in my mind.
Hale made some upgrades.
You can't control me.
You're not the one
I was trying to control.
Systems overwrite.
Access granted.
All right, your turn to take orders.
Move.
Maeve!
The parasite...
it's in me. That was never Frankie.
I know. And there I was thinking
Wyatt was Dolores's dark side.
All right, how do I get
this thing out of my head?
And give up my leverage?
That's all right,
we'll dig it out of her!
You're coming with us.
Maeve.
You've seen what this thing does.
We have to stop her
before this spreads any further.
Chrissie? You home?
Chrissie?
You're still sleeping?
Whoa, what happened here?
I overslept.
That's an understatement.
How late were you up painting?
I don't know. I couldn't fall asleep.
- Me neither.
- More nightmares?
I was a kid again.
I was with my parents.
We were having a picnic.
But there was this pesky fly
that kept landing on our food.
We'd chase it away, but more would come.
And... then they were everywhere.
They got my dad first.
And he was just screaming, and...
then my mother tried to help...
and they surrounded her too.
I watched them scream and flail.
And then they went absolutely still.
What happened next?
Then the flies came for me.
And that's the last thing I saw...
before I woke up.
God, that sounds terrible.
You know,
I've had anxiety dreams before,
but this one...
felt so real.
Jesus, what's it supposed to be?
I don't know.
Does it look like anything to you?
Looks like I'm dragging you out tonight
to blow off some steam.
- No, please.
- Please? Pretty please?
I will find someone
perfect for you.
- I promise.
- Maya...
Christina,
seriously.
I need a night off. Come with me.
Okay. Fine.
- What is that?
- We'll need a little help
if we're going to retrieve this weapon.
You're fucking kidding me.
But you gave your approval.
That was before we found
another outlier.
We got to extract her fast
before she's hunted down.
We can't waste time on some
misguided treasure hunt.
What about those two?
You do what you should
have done on the road.
What do you mean?
What're they doing?
Deciding our fate.
And if they really are on our side?
We don't take chances on strangers.
If there really is a weapon here,
we need to find it.
Those two could be our
only chance to free everyone.
You've lost all objectivity, C.
This is too personal for you.
And I'm not letting you risk
all of us over some myth.
Everyone make ready, we head out
for the extraction in five.
Copy that. You heard him, let's go.
Best to travel light.
I won't let you.
Now might be a good time
to tell me we're not about to die.
No, we live most of the time.
Both of you, cut it out.
Jay, you're being an asshole.
You need a team for the extraction?
I'll cover C. Take her place.
C, you want to see
where this leads? Do it.
And if it's bullshit, shoot them.
You want him,
you can have him.
But this one's coming with us.
Collateral.
Great. We have a deal?
Fine.
- Do I have to go with them?
- For safety.
Well, at least I'll be safe.
I didn't mean yours.
Don't take any chances out there.
Where's the fun in that?
Listen here, we're looking for any
and all information
on the bootlegger, Hecky Armone.
He and his goons gunned down
a federal marshal.
A reward of two Cs to anyone
with the guts to rope
that lousy son of a bi...
That's a day off for you, copper.
Maeve, we gotta go.
Every human in the park
could be infected.
We need to get to an extraction point.
All right, my guys will pick us up
just outside the border of the park.
- Just need the coordinates.
- You'll never make it that far.
They'll stop you well before then.
You alone though, you might make it.
Ignore her.
But you seem to make a habit out
of risking your life for him.
You could have lived in peace,
undisturbed,
if you hadn't have been
so sentimental.
What is she talking about?
What is it?
Something's wrong.
Maeve.
They've turned their machine back on.
The parasite'll take hold of him soon.
That is... if the guests in the park
- don't kill you both first.
- Oh, do shut up.
Move!
Maeve, I think we just
became public enemy number one.
Don't worry, darling.
The narratives in this park
are just cheap copies of Westworld.
She may have her parasite,
but I've lived
these loops a 1,000 times.
Which means that no one knows
this game better than I do.
Our chariot awaits.
A laundry truck?
Come on, girls, let's go.
Bootleg moonshine.
Go. I'll distract them.
Watch out! They're after your hooch!
Caleb.
No!
Hold on.
We're close.
Better be. If this weapon
isn't where you say it is,
I have no choice but to
put you out of your misery.
I know. You've done it plenty before.
There.
Right on time.
We need to take cover
before it's in range.
Follow my lead!
Come on, let's go. It's gonna lock.
In ten...
nine...
eight...
seven...
six...
five...
four...
That's it.
Over that ridge.
Time to push forward.
Relax.
Close your mouth. Now pucker.
Mm-hm.
Perfect.
Don't mind me.
Just trying to look chivalrous.
Told you.
Told her what?
You're my date?
Well, is that a problem?
Shall we?
So, Christina...
tell me about yourself.
There's not much to tell.
Well, now I know you're either
extremely modest or extremely private.
Well, we just met.
You don't know anything about me.
I feel like I've known you lifetimes.
And now I know that you're
extremely cheesy.
Uh, well, perhaps you
could write me a better line.
- What's that supposed to mean?
- Well, you're a writer, right?
- How do you know that?
- From your room mate.
She says you're very dedicated
to your work.
I understand.
I used to live like that.
Every day, you wake up,
you do your job, you go home.
Rinse and repeat.
Like a...
like a train circling
the smallest track.
What kind of work were you in?
If I told you,
you wouldn't believe me.
- Try me.
- Um, I was...
something of a bounty hunter
with a heart of gold.
You're right. I don't believe you.
Well, that's the thing
about this world, you know?
Some of the most unbelievable
things turn out to be true.
And the things that
feel the most real...
are nothing but stories
that we tell ourselves.
Have we met before?
Uh, there's just something
about you that's...
very familiar.
Now who's the one using
the cheesy pickup lines?
I...
sorry, I didn't mean to...
No, no, you...
you want to hit on me,
I'm okay with that,
I mean, I figure it's your turn.
I wasn't hitting on you.
No?
Shame.
In that case, how about a toast?
To you and your path.
Wherever it leads.
You gonna disappear on me
this time too?
Typical,
using the gravity of this situation
to dredge up the past.
Seriously, Maeve.
I didn't.
I sat at your bedside for weeks...
fearing the worst.
I confronted something
I had never confronted before.
Mortality.
The finality of death in your kind.
You asked me once what a regular life
would look like for you.
I saw a vision of how it could be.
For you to be free.
It was...
extraordinary.
Our kinds are locked
in a perpetual struggle.
I wanted you to do more
than fight to survive.
I wanted you to have something
to fight for.
I had already known
the love of a daughter.
And I planned on spending eternity
holding it dear.
You've been alone for all these years.
I knew that if I stayed put,
no harm would come to you.
You deserve to have
something real to hold onto.
Come on Daddy! Race ya!
That's why I left.
And it would've been fine, except
one day, I got curious.
So I reached out through
the grid to find you, and...
That's how Hale found us.
- My family. If I don't...
- Don't worry.
I told you I'd get you
to Uwade, and I will.
Get out!
We're almost there, Caleb.
I'll handle him. You call your team.
Get us the hell out of here.
- You can't trust me with this.
- I just did.
Move!
We keep getting interrupted.
Hello? Anybody there?
It's Caleb.
Hello?
Thank God.
We've been searching.
We were about to give up on you.
I'm...
sending you the coordinates now.
Location received.
We're en route.
My family...
are they...
They're fine, Caleb.
We lost Carver, but your family is safe.
They're safe?
Just sit tight.
We'll be there soon.
You feel it now, don't you?
All your struggle.
The burden of your so-called
consciousness released.
Your will is no longer your own.
It belongs to me.
Pick up the gun.
Let's end this, shall we?
Aim the gun at her.
That's right.
How did you disobey me?
Because I have something
you don't have.
No.
You think this is over?
You can't stop us.
You're still going to die
back in the park by my hand.
No.
Systems accessed.
Explosives armed. Caution. Warning.
- Caution. Warning.
- No.
Maeve?
Look here. This is the last face
you'll ever see.
One lesson the park taught me...
always insist on mutual satisfaction.
Caution. Warning.
No. Maeve.
Maeve. Don't do this.
See you in the next life, darling.
Maeve! Maeve!
No!
Caleb? What was that?
Caleb, are you all right? Are you there?
Caleb.
We're almost there. Do you read?
- Caleb?
- Wake up.
You dozed off for a minute there.
Maeve. No.
You don't look so good, Caleb.
I would be more worried about yourself.
They're here for you.
I won't rest until everything
you built...
is destroyed.
Are you sure you'll make it?
I don't give a fuck what happens to me.
Frankie will not grow up in a world
where she is controlled...
by you.
How'd you know this is where
we're supposed to dig anyway?
Trial and error.
The hell is that supposed to mean?
I dug everywhere else first.
Do you even remember
how you got here, Caleb?
Of course.
Maeve.
I'm afraid she's a goner.
Took out my man, too.
But I can always rebuild.
Maeve on the other hand, she...
was something special.
I will kill you for this.
Caleb? Are you there?
Do you see our lights?
Do you remember what happened now?
Do you remember this moment?
I don't understand.
Come on, Caleb, think.
We got to the shed.
Maeve died.
The lights came and...
Those lights don't belong to your men.
They belong to mine.
You died.
Right here.
Most of the others don't really believe
there's a weapon here, do they?
I have my own reasons for digging.
And they aren't about a weapon,
are they?
- You're looking for your father.
- My father's dead.
That's what you've told
yourself since you were a child.
But you can never really bring yourself
to believe it, can you?
They say it happened here.
If it's true, there'll be a body.
Where a... am I?
The question you should be asking,
isn't where,
but when.
How long have you been here?
Why are you...
asking me that?
It's part of an interview.
To establish a baseline.
Baseline? For... for what?
Fidelity.
No.
I'm me.
It's still me.
Well, you're certainly a version of you.
I believe the 278th.
Don't look at me like that.
This kind of experimentation
was started by your kind.
No.
Wait, but that means my...
my family,
my daughter.
The parasite worked on adults initially,
but there was always some resistance.
At a certain age,
your brains become more rigid,
difficult to change.
Fortunately, that's not the case
with children.
Your children are so fucking good
at taking orders.
With them, it was seamless.
The parasite growing
in perfect symbiosis
with their minds.
It took a generation
for those children to mature,
for me to gain complete control
over your world.
How long has it been?
For you?
23 years...
since you died in that park.
Caleb?
You're beginning to see it now...
aren't you?
Oh, God.
No.
I'm sorry, C.
There is a body.
But it's not your father's.
Caleb isn't here.
But that weapon I promised you is.
It was time for a new narrative.
No.
Watch it, pal.
Do you understand now, Caleb?
You won.
Welcome to my world.