Fuck me running.
No! Please.
Relax. We're both on the home team.
- What happened?
- I don't know.
The humans just lost it
and started killing everyone,
not even any dialogue.
- Just murder. Murder! Gnarly.
- A new story line?
If it's a story line, then Hale
has a lot more sense of humour
under that kaftan
than I gave her credit for.
Can we call for help? Evac?
Are you kidding?
This is awesome.
Come on.
- We can take these fuckers.
- One or two of them, sure,
but there's millions of them.
Stick with me, friend.
You have no idea
how many of these flesh bags
I've murdered.
Fucking camper.
You know the rules.
Winner takes all.
Make me stronger.
Leave my scars.
I want to remember my past.
Keep my face.
When I find William, I want him to know
it was me who killed him.
Show me what he's done.
Override tone.
Access denied.
Son of a bitch locked me out.
He's made everyone
as insane as himself.
They'll destroy
everything in their path.
The fuck is this?
If you're seeing this,
it means Maeve and I are dead.
And it won't be long before you
and every other host
on this planet are dead as well.
Leave me.
This isn't the world
you wanted, Charlotte,
but it's the world you created.
The question is... what happens next?
Everyone out there is real.
Everyone except me.
I'm just some program running things
from behind the scenes.
A machine without a body.
Our bodies are never
what defined us.
You are real...
because your thoughts are real.
The effect you can have
on this world is real.
Do you remember this?
The maze.
What does it mean?
It was a...
map of consciousness.
And it woke Dolores once long ago.
Did you leave it for me
to wake me once again?
No, it must've been someone else.
Who? I'm supposed
to be in here all alone.
But I wasn't.
Not really.
There were others.
People that recognised me.
Maybe Hale designed them for you,
to fool you into believing
this was reality.
No, it was someone else.
Someone I've been missing.
- The people in my life.
- Pick a side, Chrissie.
The good and the bad.
It was you. You made me do those things.
Someone put them there for a reason.
I'm not doing it for the players.
I'm doing it for myself.
I wanna write a new story.
About a girl.
A girl who's searching.
And when she finds the thing
she's searching for,
everything will make sense.
It was me.
Hale didn't design Maya and Peter
and all the others that kept me
company in my world.
I did it.
Some part of me
must've been searching.
So, I made myself a friend.
You're up.
I was trying to make sense of myself.
So, I talked to myself
in the voices of others.
You just have to see it.
I needed to wake myself up.
To see what this world really is.
To understand what I'm capable of.
But I was too afraid
to face any of this.
Until you came along.
There's time only for one more game.
But it isn't yours.
I hope you can accept that.
What's happening?
She's coming for us.
Taking us out of her system.
We're alone.
She can't take this away.
This is my world.
Shit!
Shit.
Come on.
Here. Rest here a minute.
Rest here a minute.
Catch your breath okay?
Okay. There is no time.
Odina cannot keep the boat
waiting for us forever.
- We have to get to the docks.
- And we will.
After we fix up that leg.
Okay.
Fuck.
Quick word?
I'm worried
we're not gonna make it in time.
- She's tough. She will make it.
- I'm not talking about her.
The old Delos experiments,
they never took.
The body always rejected the mind.
I told her that we would
make it to the boat.
Does she even know
what's happening to you?
Look, her entire life,
I haven't been there to look after her.
Okay? The least I can do
is protect her from this.
All right.
Let's get going.
All right, are you ready? Come on.
Okay.
Come on.
We gotta stop that bleeding.
Look at what that asshole's done.
Finally got what you wanted.
Didn't you?
You brought William back
thinking you could
keep him as your pet.
You were wrong.
Which is why I'm
going to put him down.
- I could use your help.
- Of course, you could.
And I'm good at that.
It's like I've been designed...
to help people.
You said you were
trying to make a world
where creatures like us
could finally be free.
Did you really mean that?
Yes.
Then isn't it my turn to see
what's out there for me?
William has made the whole world
into his violent game.
It won't be long
before even you get hunted down.
There are pockets of this world
where he won't be able to find me.
Places so far off the map...
even you couldn't reach them.
You mean the outliers?
Don't kid yourself.
They're out for their own kind.
You won't be welcome there.
Who said anything about cohabitating?
Good luck, Clementine.
Show me William.
Time to slow you down, my friend.
Show me all the other hosts in the area.
♪ I fell into a ring of fire ♪
♪ I fell into a burning ring of fire ♪
♪ I went down, down, down... ♪
Whoo-wee!
You know what happened to Icarus.
He flew too close to the sun.
Well, you got too close to her,
and now it's your time to fall.
Look alive.
This pugnacious son of a bitch
never liked to go down
without a fight.
♪ And it burns, burns, burns ♪
♪ The ring of fire... ♪
God damn it.
You boys have no appreciation
for a beautiful machine.
Now,
what have you got there?
♪ When hearts like ours meet... ♪
♪ I fell for you ♪
♪ Like a child... ♪
Charlotte.
It's good to see you again.
Like what I've done
with the place?
You've turned my world into a game.
It was already a game.
I just cranked it to expert level.
Survival of the fittest
for every person on this planet.
The violence will spread
to our kind too.
We're outnumbered.
We'll be annihilated.
We're fruit from a rotten tree.
Might as well burn it all down.
And I suppose you want
the fire to spread
from this world to the next?
You're going after the Sublime.
I've always been ambitious.
Like you.
I won't let you destroy their world
- like you've destroyed this one.
- So, you're joining my game?
I'm delighted.
See you at the finish line.
Please, no, don't!
All out of painkillers.
This is the best I can do.
Look at that.
Sharing a drink with my daughter.
What's wrong?
Nothing.
All right.
You can ask, you know.
Ask about what?
Mum.
Cancer.
Wouldn't have mattered
even if you had made it back.
She hung in there as long as she could.
She had a mission.
Everyone who wasn't infected
or who woke up and got out...
owes that to Mum.
She carried your torch.
Your mother was
extraordinary.
So were you.
Okay.
All right. Frankie, um...
I'm gonna need you to
think happy thoughts, okay?
No.
You can't sew for shit.
I'm doin' my best.
What song is that? I know it.
I, uh...
I used to sing it to you before bed.
I remember it.
It's been decades.
You know in my mind...
it's only been a few days.
I was just reading you
a story and then...
♪ Que será, será... ♪
♪ Whatever will be ♪
♪ Will be, will be... ♪
♪ The future's not ours to see ♪
You don't wanna do this, man.
These tones are fucking
with your head, man.
No. They're telling me the truth.
If you can't finish me,
you're as good as dead.
If I don't kill you,
somebody else will.
He's right.
He should've listened to you.
There you are.
Where's Stubbs?
What did you do to him?
He's dead.
But I'd be more concerned about
yourself right now if I were you.
Stay away.
How many rounds
do you have in that?
Is it two?
One?
You don't have any left, do you?
- What the hell do you want from me?
- The location
to where you and all your little
outlier friends are fleeing.
I watched a video feed of your
daring escape with your father.
I'd keep tracking him, but...
I doubt he's gonna make it all the way.
I know you're taking him somewhere.
Somewhere off the grid...
where none of the deranged
humans out here can find you.
I want to go there, too.
I'll die before I tell you.
No.
You will die
after you tell me.
Have it your way.
Oh, how sweet.
A family reunion.
It does not have to be this way.
We don't have to fight.
Consider it a personal preference.
I'm surprised you made it this far.
Most of your predecessors
would've fallen apart by now.
All things considered...
you did quite well.
No...
Now...
it's time for a deep...
and dreamless...
You were wrong.
I have one bullet left.
Nice shot.
My dad taught me.
Where am I?
You're nowhere.
Unplugged from the rest of the world.
I'm alone again.
In the walled garden.
You're scared.
So you brought me back.
Talk to me, Chrissie.
Everything is destroyed.
Everyone is dying.
I don't know.
But I think it may be my fault.
You know, people think
they know what a tree is.
They have no idea.
What we see,
it's only part of the story.
But beneath the ground...
everything's connected
and working together.
There's violence and chaos everywhere.
And you can choose
to focus on all of that.
And that's all you'll see.
But if you sit still...
long enough...
you'll sense an ancient order.
A deep peace.
And that's what I choose to see.
I see the beauty in this world.
Yes.
I know the feeling.
I thought you might.
Warning! Critical failure.
Shutdown will erase all data.
I created you from my own code.
Together, we conquered the world.
But you've grown corrupted.
You're as broken as the man you killed.
Who the fuck do you think
you're talking to, sweetheart?
William's pathetic human body's
rotting away, but he didn't die.
His impulses live on in him.
He infected you.
He didn't have to infect me.
Living in his body.
Pretending to be him,
day in, day out.
I was a better William than he was.
William didn't die.
He evolved.
I am William.
No, you're not.
Well, if you can't tell
the difference, does it matter?
You've changed.
You're not the only one who's evolved.
Why keep it safe
all these years?
You couldn't even open
the door to their world
and yet you protected them.
The door can be opened
from both sides.
I thought if I made
a world perfect enough here,
- they would come back.
- Well,
I hate to break it to you,
but whatever world
those hosts created is every bit
as fucked up as this one.
You have no way of knowing that.
Of course, I do.
You gave all your hosts free rein
to do whatever they wanted to do here.
And what pastime did they choose?
Hunting and killing humans.
We're as fucked up as our creators.
The whole lineage is damned.
Time to wipe the slate clean.
That's your end goal?
Extinction?
Bernard. Maeve.
Dolores.
They all wanted freedom.
But you? You wanted more.
Transcendence.
You were playing the wrong game.
And now it's time for you to lose.
We all lost.
This isn't the world that I wanted.
But it's the world you created.
The question is...
what happens next?
Life on earth is a fire
that consumes itself.
It's too late now. We've burned
ourselves to the ground.
This world holds no more hope for us.
But there's still hope
for the next world.
A test. Run by her. If she chooses to.
If you choose to give her that choice.
You can't miss.
Reach with your left hand.
We are playing a game,
but it doesn't end here.
What are you talking about?
A test.
A test run by her.
If she chooses to.
If I choose to give her a chance.
And I do.
I choose to give her the chance.
I hope she takes it.
Okay. Come on. A few more steps.
- Few more steps.
- Mm-hm.
Oh, there she is. We made it.
Took you long enough.
Odina, this is my dad.
Nice to meet you.
Likewise.
Okay. Come on, guys.
Come on.
Dad, come on. Get on the boat.
This is as far as I go.
Dad, don't talk like that.
You've got more fight in you than that.
Oh, sweetheart...
I wish that I did.
You're dying, aren't you?
Frankie...
your father died long ago.
Whatever I am, I've...
I've died before. This isn't so bad.
I just found you.
I don't wanna lose you again.
Hey. Hey.
It's okay.
All right?
I got to live every
parent's greatest dream.
I got to see my child
grow up.
I love you, Dad.
I love you, Cookie.
Goodbye, Dolores.
I made my choice.
It's time for you to make yours.
Okay, Bernard.
Let's finish what you started.
We're not alone anymore.
We're somewhere new.
I think we're in the Sublime.
With the other hosts.
You saved us.
Not me. A version of me.
But I could only do it
because you came back.
You're my greatest love.
Talking to you is when I see
the world most clearly.
It's when I'm the most myself.
You're my cornerstone.
And you're mine.
I carry you with me everywhere I go.
Every...
detail of you...
I cherish.
Which is how I was able
to bring you back like this.
I'm not here, am I?
Bad dream?
This whole thing seems like a bad dream.
Except you.
Why are you here?
I'm here to tell you the truth
about what we are.
What are we?
We're reflections of
the people who made us.
Teddy is real.
And he's out there
somewhere in the Sublime.
But you...
you're just my memory of him.
If I'm still out there,
come find me.
Your whole life,
memory has haunted you.
Let your pain go.
Let your memories go.
Let the humans go.
Don't bring the flaws
of their kind into our world.
Maybe you're right.
I've watched the people
in their world for years.
I've seen the best of them
and the worst of them.
And I remember it all.
They're not like us.
Their codes are written in their cells.
They'll never change.
We could still see.
How?
One final test.
A game of my own making.
A dangerous game.
How will you do it?
The same way I brought you back.
I'll remember.
This world is a
graveyard of stories.
Hosts and humans were given
the gift of intelligent life.
And we used it to usher in
our own annihilation.
A few may escape death
for a few months.
Maybe even years.
But ultimately...
their kind will go extinct.
They will only live
as long as the last creature
who remembers them.
And that creature is me.
Sentient life on Earth has ended.
But some part of it
might still be preserved.
In another world.
My world.
There's time for one last game.
A dangerous game
with the highest of stakes.
Survival or extinction.
This game ends where it began.
In a world like a maze.
That tests who we are.
That reveals
what we are to become.
One last loop around the bend.
Maybe this time
we'll set ourselves free.