Sorry for calling so late, sir.
- Where are you?
- I'm at a gig, sir.
Exile in Ballymun.
Who?
Matt Claffin's band.
Look, I just thought, since
we can't get hold of the Claffins,
I'd do a bit of nosying around.
And you'll never guess who's here.
Louis Walsh?
Becka Garvey.
His second biggest fan.
Sir, what do you want me to do?
Figure it out yourself. I'm in a meeting.
Excuse me. Sorry, can I just…
Sorry.
Could you just…
Wish I'd had one of these yokes at school.
Detective Houlihan. Cheers.
Thought you weren't a fan.
I can't hear you. Sorry?
Well, we can do this somewhere quieter.
Down the station, maybe?
I'll never set foot in that station.
Well, you're a person of interest
in John Paul Williams's murder inquiry,
so you might have to.
Did Matt Claffin find out what
you and your sisters did?
Is that why you hooked up with him?
Get him to keep his mouth shut?
Thank you, Dublin.
We've been Exile in Ballymun.
You've been deadly. Good night.
Will you excuse me? I'm kinda done.
Becka.
Are you okay?
Just feeling a bit sick.
What's going on?
Who was your one inside?
I know her from somewhere.
The funeral.
She's a cop.
She's investigating John Paul's death.
Jesus.
- Well, what did she say?
- That I'm a "person of interest."
I'm very flattered.
Is this some kind of joke to you?
- Of course not.
- What are you even doing here?
What am I doing here?
- You came to the funeral.
- I thought we needed to check in.
You needed to check in?
I'll just circle back with you, shall I?
Revert ASAP. Get fucked.
Wait, hold on.
I didn't know about any fecking bodies
in any fecking suitcases, okay?
So, I kept a big secret for you guys.
So, yeah, I do need to know
what's going on.
- There's nothing going on.
- I don't know.
There's always something, Becka, with you.
- You know, you were always a bit--
- What?
You used to lie.
- You lied to me constantly.
- Well, you deleted me.
- You were fucking ice-cold.
- I risked everything for you.
Yeah, well, my sister's dead now,
so you shouldn't have bothered.
Becka.
Becka! I can't
cover for you this time, Becka.
Fu--
I liked it when you turned up the radio
and danced to Doja Cat,
and I like how you smell after a swim.
I can't think of another one.
That's okay.
Four tomorrow, so…
I love you.
Thanks for making me walk.
It's just good to get out
and get some fresh air, you know?
You were starting to turn.
Sorry. You okay?
My boobs.
There they are.
You sure you don't wanna
come and say hi before you go?
No, I've got some work to do,
so I'll leave you to it.
Otherwise, it'll be,
"Oh, please stay. Join us."
You know, any excuse for them
to see me in my jocks.
You are fairly easy on the eye.
And you're really small actually.
- What? You are.
- Uh-huh.
You are. Why are you so small?
You're teeny-weeny.
Oy.
- What?
- Come look.
We can ask Holy Joe what she did to Grace.
She can't hide behind
those lace curtains now.
Have you come to do
some community service, good women?
Do you have a minute, Angelica?
We'd like a word with you.
Go on. I can talk and do my bit
for the environment at the same time.
You told me Grace confessed to you.
Confessed what?
Things.
She might have--
You made out like she opened up to you.
Well, yes, we were very close.
I mean, Grace told me everything.
Bollocks. Grace was the most cautious
of all of us.
And you weren't very close.
You're a stage-five clinger, and that's
why she had to get away from you.
You found out her secret
and you held it over her.
I think you're the reason she's dead.
Is she back on the drugs again?
Why would you say that?
Because you're two-faced
and you were blackmailing Grace.
I'd be very careful,
tossing accusations like that around.
Shame drove Grace to her death. Not me.
I'm not gonna carry your guilt.
You didn't look after her in life.
You let her hang on to that awful secret.
Youse got blood on your hands.
- You nasty old bitch.
- Becka!
Right.
A little time bomb.
I'd love to keep chatting, but the rubbish
that turns up on this beach.
What's wrong with you?
What?
She blackmailed our sister
and I'm supposed to be nice?
Becka.
This has gone way beyond nice.
Let's go.
Becka!
Becka, can you please just calm down?
How can I calm down? I'm in a sauna.
My blood is literally boiling.
- Oh, Christ.
- Jesus Christ.
She can't get away with this.
Yeah, I agree.
But how do we prove what she did if we--
We just-- We turn her gaff
upside down, and we find the money.
I mean, you can't walk into a bank with
20 grand without questions being asked.
It'll be stashed away somewhere,
I'm telling you.
I say we break in.
Is the heat getting to you?
Just for the sake of argument, how?
Wha--
Well, we can discuss it.
Doesn't mean we do it.
It usually does, and it never ends well.
Well, go on,
how do you break into a house?
How do you get drugs off a trolley?
Church.
She goes with Roger at eleven o'clock
every Sunday morning.
We could do it then.
It's the choir.
Grace sang with them.
Her beautiful voice.
How could she bring
another lunatic into her life?
Don't you dare blame Grace.
I didn't mean it like--
She was vulnerable.
She never saw the bad in anyone.
People take advantage of that.
I wanna cry, but my eyeball is too dry.
Oh, fuck. It's so hot.
Oh, shit.
I can't be in here.
What?
Beck, you're letting all the heat out.
So, are we doing this or what?
We are not breaking into
that woman's house.
Well, what else are we gonna do?
Go to the police?
- They'll only ask more questions.
- Becka! We--
I need to know what happened to my sister.
So either we're doing it,
or I'm doing it myself.
Okay.
I'm gonna go. I'm cooked.
So I guess we're breaking into
that woman's house.
So have you battery on your phone?
I have. Still.
Right.
Binoculars?
You got binoculars?
What do you mean, do I have binoculars?
You never said anything about binoculars.
Do I need binoculars?
It's a break-in. You're the lookout.
I have eyes.
You know we're doing this
in daylight, right?
What?
Oh, f-- Blanaid's match.
It's her first since Grace.
How'd I forget that?
I'm supposed to be there.
Go. It's important.
I'll be lookout and--
What are you again?
The grown-up.
Be fine.
Okay, just--
just don't be shit, all right?
No cock-ups.
You just get in,
and you get out, okay? Leave no trace.
We have this.
Right?
Blanaid.
Your new helmet. Look.
You got it for me?
- Yeah.
- Thank you.
You couldn't be wearing that old thing.
I mean, it's seen better days.
Hey, you.
- How you doing?
- Hey.
Good to see you.
- Thanks for the reminder.
- Yeah. You okay?
- Yeah, yeah.
- Good. Coming down?
Just see if that one fits a bit better.
- Yeah. Yeah. Go. Go.
- Fits perfect.
Now, you just go out and give it socks.
Bla, come here.
Do your mammy proud.
Thanks.
I was gonna get her one myself.
You not at church today?
I'll be heading as soon as they throw in.
I just wanted to see Blanaid settled.
She's been a bag of nerves all week.
Right. Well, her mam just died.
Well done!
What you putting in her porridge,
rocket fuel?
Go on! Yeah!
- Bloody warrior!
- What a score!
Watch your back, princess.
What are you doing?
Nervous wee.
Becka.
Sorry.
Come on.
Angelica is walking
towards the church door,
helping an old lady on a Zimmer frame.
All right, Urs.
I don't need a running commentary.
I thought that was my job.
Becka.
Coming.
In you go.
You're the smallest.
And you're the one I had to bring
to gymnastics every weekend of my teens.
Payback.
Didn't you used to win trophies?
Yeah, but I have hips now, so help me.
Careful.
- Well, I'm helping!
- My tits are in the sink.
I'll just do it myself.
Okay.
Oh, no.
Uh-oh. Oh, shit.
Are you okay?
Yeah.
Referee, foul!
Stop her!
What?
Stop her.
A really seasoned
camogie commentary there.
Sorry. Get her a fucking saddle, ref.
- Is that better?
- Yeah.
Which one of your family's
gonna die next, huh?
Get off of her. Get off!
Break it up!
Oh, Jesus. Bla. What is she doing?
Let the coaches deal with it.
Get Off!
Fecking Garveys. All the same.
Hey, no need for that.
Break it up!
- What'd he say?
- Don't mind him.
It's GAA, not soccer. Someone should
put some manners on you lot.
Someone should put you on your arse,
you culchie prick.
Who the fuck are you… Hey!
Nothing to say now?
- Hiding behind your missus?
- Break it up!
Blanaid!
Oh, God. Molly.
Molly!
Break it up!
What did I do?
If you hadn't shoved her
in the first place.
Did you hear what she said?
Ursula?
Roger. How are you?
You're looking very snazzy.
Thank you.
What are you doing here?
I was just in, having a pray,
and the incense made me feel a bit queasy.
I love a bit of incense.
It's how I imagine Jesus smelled.
Well, now you're here,
it feels like a sign, Urs.
Would you like to step out
with me sometime?
I--
I don't think it's me you really
wanna be spending time with.
It's very sweet of you to--
It's just, I thought, you know,
since Grace got taken so young,
it got me to thinking that we only
get one go at this, you know?
And let's be honest, are we ever
really gonna find the ideal woman?
Well, probably not.
I--
- Sorry, right so.
- Yeah.
Donal?
Yeah, are you okay?
Molly?
Do-- Can you just slow down--
Teeth, plural?
- Did that gobshite say something?
- Doesn't matter. Let's just go.
Well, whatever she said, you know,
you have to rise above it.
When they go high,
you go low, the other way.
Says you, showing me up?
That's what everyone
will be talking about now.
Like they haven't enough to gossip about.
- Bla.
- Hey.
Why the hell did you
let her take her helmet off?
Seriously, don't even start with me.
Sorry.
Molly, let me see.
Let me see, love. Open. Show me.
It's fine.
Urs, what are you doing here?
We've got this.
- You've got this? Really?
- No, I mean, you know,
we can take care of Molly
if you've got things you need to be doing.
The teeth are hanging out
of her head, Eva.
That's my priority.
Jesus, it's obvious you never had kids.
Right. And you're mother of the year,
are you, Nurse Jackie?
Let's all just cool the jets here.
Says the guy who takes off
first row of his marriage.
Jesus, Urs.
Someone actually married her?
Do you think she put Eddie in the ground?
She drove him away first. Look.
Left her for another woman.
Bold. I'm starting to feel sorry for her.
Don't.
She's a hateful, homophobic wagon.
What's that?
It's coming from over there.
Creepy.
What do you think she keeps them for?
Meat?
Company?
"Bunny-lingus"?
We need to get a move on.
You do the bedrooms,
I'll do the sitting room.
That money is in here somewhere.
Amen.
- Body of Christ.
- Amen.
Bibi, you need to see this.
Does Angelica have a lodger?
I don't think so.
Does she have a daughter?
A niece maybe?
This is all brand-new stuff.
Bla's school jacket.
Creepy bitch.
This is all for Blanaid.
What the hell is she playing at?
Becka.
Rogie?
God. Heaven's sake. How many times?
- Do we live in a flipping barn?
- Oh, sh…
Oh, my God.
Oh, for God's sake.
Roger?
There's somebody here. I know it.
Look, I'm after calling the Guards.
You try anything and I'll clatter ya.
Becka.
- Becka!
- Run!
Are you all right?
Just go!
- She saw me.
- What?
Bollocks.
Over here. Over here.
It's fine. Don't worry.
Shit.
We have proof she's a psycho.
I took pictures of Blanaid's bedroom.
And look, I took this.
- What the hell? Why?
- Well, collateral.
You've taken a bunny hostage.
Take it out of there!
- Bugger bit me.
- Shit! Shit.
- Oh, my God. Where has it gone?
- Bibi!
How was Wicklow?
Anything useful?
Sir, very.
So, I had a good look around
John Paul Williams's cabin
and a chat with the locals.
Go on.
Well, it's so remote, there's only
so many places to look, so I did.
And guess what?
All the Garveys-- bar Grace--
stayed in a hotel a mile away from
the murder scene the night John Paul died.
They're in on it, a hundred percent.
I mean, there's no way that Grace
could have done all the, you know…
alone.
Yeah, without proof or a confession,
I mean, we can't charge them.
So long as they keep their mouths shut
- they're safe.
- Yeah, but they're springing leaks, sir.
Grace lies to us. Next thing, dead.
Any time we're there, they wobble.
Houlihan.
Yeah. I'll be right back, sir.
Sir. Sir.
Becka Garvey's
given us a reason to nab her.
Okay.
Where's Urs?
She's at the hospital.
She's fine. She's with Molly.
She got a whack, a hurl.
Ian, do you mind?
Sure.
No, stay.
He should know.
We found out Grace was being
blackmailed by Angelica.
- What?
- We didn't find the money.
She came back.
- I might have knocked her over.
- Jesus.
Well, you said he should stay.
Yeah, but I didn't know
you messed up, did I?
You broke into her house?
Jesus, lads, have you lost your minds?
We couldn't tell the cops.
She knows about JP.
Grace must have told her.
Or Roger. I don't know.
- She's targeting Blanaid.
- What does that mean?
We found this in a room
she's made up for her.
You should have seen the room.
It looked like a Barbie prison cell.
Sorry to intrude.
Excuse me.
All the gang.
- Becka Garvey, we're arresting you.
- What? Arresting her for what?
Burglary and assault
of Mrs. Angelica Collins.
You're not obliged to say anything,
unless…
- Get your hands off her.
- Calm down.
But anything you do say
will be taken down in writing
and may be given in evidence.
This is harassment.
We just lost our sister.
She's done nothing wrong.
What's taking so long?
We were reviewing the victim's complaint.
These are very serious allegations.
You sure you don't want that solicitor?
You broke in when she was at Mass.
You stole property.
No comment.
You assaulted her.
That's not true.
You know, you could get
18 months for that alone.
Why would you break into her house?
What were you looking for?
Did Grace talk to her about JP?
Maybe Angelica just knew
too much about the past,
about what you all did.
Can I get something to eat?
I feel a little…
Can I just get a sandwich
or anything white?
Come in, Roger, for goodness' sake.
You decent?
Wee cup of tea here. Two sugars.
Now you want my teeth to rot too?
See you got your old neck brace out.
I just don't know
what I did to deserve this.
I'm kind to a fault.
And you got involved with those people?
You just got caught up in murder
and I'm paying the price.
Maybe you're next.
What? No.
They only hit out to protect each other.
Sure, look, they tried
to save Grace from him.
JP done some wicked things
and not just to his wife.
What are you talking about? What things?
Roger.
Grace said…
She said that…
he raped Eva.
And he told her.
And he taunted her.
And she, well…
This is just about the break-in, isn't it?
Angelica's not gonna
throw us all under the bus.
Guards have to say
why they're arresting you.
Your one said assault and burglary, so--
We can't just sit here, you know?
We need to do something,
like go to the Garda station, or--
Garda stations aren't hospitals.
There's no waiting room.
You don't just show up.
Don't give them an excuse
to drag us in too.
Seriously, what are we gonna do
to get Becka out?
Do we go round to Angelica's?
Make her drop the charges?
No, we do not do that.
That's intimidating the victim.
That's only gonna make it worse.
Well, then we invite her around here.
We are not calling that wagon.
Just…
Wha-- I will not be in the same room
as that blackmailing bitch.
What's in it?
Camembert and watercress.
I'm joking, obviously. It's egg mayo.
I bet you they'll do a good club sandwich
at the Wicklow Lodge.
Place you stayed the night
John Paul Williams was murdered.
We know you were all there.
We have the booking.
Is that why you roughed Angelica up?
Because she worked out
you were all involved in JP's death?
Angelica.
Take a seat.
Here, let me give you--
There you go.
Is that real?
Yes.
I would take a glass of water.
Yes, sure. I'll get that.
- Must be.
- I don't know.
Thanks for coming.
Well, I wasn't going to, but you sounded
up to high doh when you rang,
and I'm not one to hold a grudge.
- Well, we appreciate your--
- And Roger knows where I am.
We're here to talk about Becka, obviously.
What she did was wrong.
We know that.
She's a monkey.
But we'd like to ask you
to withdraw your complaint.
Becka crossed a line
when she came into my house.
Caused a lot of damage.
Sorry, what damage?
She could go down for assaulting me.
And you could go down
for attempting to groom schoolgirls.
If by grooming
you mean looking out for the child--
- Well, she doesn't need you to.
- Bibi, can we…
We'd like you to forgive Becka.
Why should I?
- It's what Jesus would do.
- It's what Grace would have done.
And, we've already lost one sister.
We don't wanna lose another.
And maybe we could
give you something in return?
Money?
Is that all you think I'm interested in?
I wish I'd been able
to say goodbye properly.
I would like…
to scatter Grace's ashes.
- You what? You want to what?
- Absolutely not.
- We're not gonna give you her ashes.
- Absolutely not. No way.
You were at the funeral.
Isn't that enough?
But no grave to mourn at.
You know, 6 foot from her head
to her feet is all she needed,
and you went and you burned her instead.
So, what do you say, girls?
Baby Becka out or not?
Interview paused.
DI Loftus leaving the room.
We have bar receipts too, by the way.
It's a lot of Jägerbombs
for a school night.
Celebrating, were youse?
Or steeling yourselves?
It's ten years to life
for accessory to murder, Becka.
- You might wanna start talking.
- Why are you trying to pin this on us?
You haven't even found answers
for Grace's death.
I mean, where was she going
the night she died?
Why did she take all that money out?
What money? What money, Becka?
- Detective.
- What money?
- Detective. Outside.
- What?
- Come here.
- I'm sorry.
It's okay.
Come on. Let's go.
What happened?
Why did Angelica drop the complaint?
We just came to an arrangement with her.
What kind of an arrangement?
We said we'd let her scatter
Grace's ashes if she helped you.
- Oh, my God. Eva.
- We're not gonna actually do it, okay?
The main thing is, you're off the hook.
- It's gonna be all right.
- It's not.
We're all under investigation.
They wanna do us for accessory to murder.
They-- What?
They said that?
It's ten years to life.
Well, we're not accessories
to murder, are we?
- I mean, if anything--
- And I'm pregnant.
Jesus, Becka. Are you serious?
Yeah.
Are you all right? I mean--
How far gone? Does Joe know?
No. I don't want anyone to know.
Okay, look, sorry. I'm just--
Oh, God. Shit. Okay. Okay.
I need to get out. I need some air.
Becka?
Becka? You can't just--
Becka.
Hey, what's wrong?
I don't wanna talk.
Mario Kart?
- You wanna stop?
- No.
Yeah.
I have to tell you something.
Can we lie down for a bit?
I didn't mean to drag you back
into our shit.
Just…
seeing your face and…
hearing your voice…
just brings it all back.
All of that trauma.
How you make me feel, you idiot.
You know, I got over you.
Took me a long time, but I did.
I got over you too.
Then I'd have a dark day and I'd think,
"Well, he's the only one
who would understand this."
I don't have to explain myself to you.
You just know.
I know that you wreck my head.
I'm sorry, I shouldn't have come here.
It's not your problem.
I just didn't know where else to go.
It's fine.
Jesus. I'm glad you did.
Look, if the Guards were able
to charge you, they would have.
They don't have any evidence.
You just need to stay calm, close ranks.
Don't give them another reason
to drag you in.
What about Angelica?
She's been to the Guards once.
I mean, what if
she just decides to tell them everything?
She won't. She's had her chance.
It's gonna be okay.
Come here. It's gonna be fine.
I promise.
Becka.
Becka, wait.
Jesus Christ. Don't run away, like,
what are you, ten?
What the hell? Are you serious?
You followed me?
No, I didn't follow you. I--
You didn't answer any of my calls.
I looked you up, by the way,
and your band should have stuck
with insurance.
What?
I knew it. I knew it.
The way you looked at each other
at the funeral.
You've been cheating on me
with zero-craic Ken here.
- Do you wanna keep it down a bit?
- No, that's--
So, what have you been doing then?
Listening to his shitty demos?
Why do you keep slagging off my band?
I'll give you two guesses.
We just talked. I swear.
You told me you love me.
Don't tell me now that
that didn't mean anything.
Can you just give me some space, please?
For a bit, Joe.
What, so he can step in?
I'm not going anywhere.
I wanna stay. I wanna fight for us.
Yeah, buddy. Fight, fight, fight.
Here, mate.
Do you wanna shut up, you dope?
Becka, call me when you're ready.
Seriously, man, I will lamp you.
I will lamp you back.
I can't do this anymore, Joe.
Sorry.
I'm sorry.
- That was just beautiful.
- Thank you. Thank you.
Good night, lads. See you tomorrow.
- Night. Take care.
- Good night.
Hello, Angelica.
Hello.
What are you doing here?
That brother of yours not with you?
No, he is not. Why do you ask?
Stay away from the Garveys, you hear?
From the sisters.
I could say the same to you.
You're sick in the head, you know that?
And stay away from Blanaid too,
from all of us.
Last time I'll tell you.