What happened?
This is really bad. I mean, terrible.
- I'm gonna be sick.
- This is bad.
- It's the Irish Sea!
- How could you...
- I just don't understand.
- Really bad!
I mean, this is terrible.
- It's terrible. Jesus Christ. It's bad.
- It's an absolute nightmare.
- Bad, bad. Bad.
- This is bad.
- Oh, my God.
- This is bad, bad, bad.
Becka, I cannot think with you doing that.
Could you not just have--
- Just have what, Eva?
- Have just fucking saved her!
- The radio wasn't working.
- We tried everything.
- We didn't know what to do.
- Can we please drop it down a decibel?
Blanaid's upstairs.
I'll call the coast guard, okay?
We're gonna call a coast guard.
What... Is it 999?
Eva, don't.
There'll be police.
It was an accident.
We'd no reason to want her dead.
Yeah.
Oh, shit.
What?
I told Loftus
that Angelica was blackmailing Grace.
- What?
- You told Loftus?
- Why were you even talking to the cops?
- Oh, my God! Eva!
Because Blanaid was missing.
You have just given us a motive
for murdering the woman!
I didn't know you were gonna
take her out and bloody drown her, did I?
Don't you put this on me, okay?
Jesus Christ, you had one job.
- Eva. Calm down. It's okay.
- You--
Well, what does it mean?
We go to the cops now, what does it mean?
Like we...
We tell them it was an accident. We--
Manslaughter,
you're looking at seven to ten.
But...
I mean, you had a motive, so...
Oh, come on.
I need a drink.
- What, years?
- You can't drink. You're pregnant.
She's pregnant.
Well, I'm definitely not having the baby
if I'm going to jail.
Are you talking years?
Well, he's not talking about weeks, is he?
I mean, a woman is dead.
Who knows you took her on the boat?
Does Roger?
No, she knew he'd want to come.
Right.
Look, I'll go down to the marina,
have a look around,
see if there are any cameras, you know?
Anything to connect you to the boat.
I'll call you
when I've sussed things out. Okay?
We didn't kill her.
Well, you didn't not kill her.
Oh, fuck.
What?
Why isn't he calling?
- What are you doing?
- I'm reading about tides.
How do they work?
It's gravitational.
It's... You have the moon and it's...
- I don't know!
- Do you think I should call him?
Are you okay?
She's pregnant. She was in freezing water.
I was worried about her.
Oh, shit. It's Ian.
Hey, what's happening?
There's blood on the boat.
- Oh, my God. Well, that's just great.
- God, no.
- Put it on speaker.
- Hang on.
We'll go down there now.
We'll clean it up.
No, because we have another problem.
There's a security camera
on a house overlooking the harbor
looking directly at the boat.
Oh, Christ.
I'll have to think of
a way of getting at it.
I'll call you when I've figured that out.
Wait.
I think we need to talk to the police.
That would be a bad idea.
That will not go well.
Look, I think
you'll have to trust me on that, love.
Eva.
Okay.
This is bad.
Bad, bad, bad, bad, bad, bad, bad, bad.
Is Angelica Collins there?
I'm sorry. No, she's not in.
Well, do you have any idea
when she'll be back?
She didn't come home last night.
Oh, right. Okay. Is that usual for her?
She might have taken a notion
to go up north for a few days, you know.
As the Holy Spirit guides her,
she likes to say.
Well, would she usually just
take off like that without telling you?
Holy Spirit allowing.
No, she'd probably ask me
to feed the rabbits.
Oh, rabbits. Nice.
I always wanted a rabbit,
but my mummy said that
they live too long and shit too much.
So, sorry, what's this about?
Why would you need to talk to her?
Well, I'd prefer to
speak with your sister.
Is this about this run-in
she had with Ian Reilly?
Threatening her the other night.
- You're not Jehovah, are you?
- F--
No, I'm not.
My bicycle was stolen.
It was chained up just over there.
I was wondering, does that camera work?
Of course it works.
But I'm not letting you in.
- Okay.
- You could be one of them serial killers.
- Do I look like a serial killer?
- Well then, you never know.
I mean, a lot of those fellas
are very good-looking.
Not a serial killer.
Would you know anything about radiators?
Okay, it's safe to go.
We're just cleaning a boat,
people do it every day.
Let's just get it over with.
There you go.
You shouldn't have
any more trouble with that.
That's great.
Yeah. Can I maybe see the camera now?
- Of course you can. You're very good.
- All right, thank you.
My son had it installed.
He worries about me living here
on my own since Elsie died.
Elsie was my sister.
The one I told you had
the devotion to Padre Pio.
Uh-huh.
I showed you the picture of
the two of us in Rome, didn't I?
Yeah.
Lovely shot.
You know,
when we were leaving the basilica,
didn't she fall down the steps?
I can tell you, from that day onwards
she wouldn't get into a car if there was
a medal of Padre Pio on the dashboard.
Any sign of them there
that took your bike, is there?
No, unfortunately.
I guess we'll never know what happened.
You know, in olden times, when they wanted
to find out if a woman was a witch,
they tied her up and threw her in the sea.
Jesus, Bibi, do you have to be so bloody--
- Macabre?
- Macabre. That's exactly the word.
We're scrubbing away
the remains of a woman.
What's not macabre about that?
I think there's something going on
between Eva and Ian.
What? Why would you say that?
Did you not see them before?
The way he spoke to her, the way
he touched her arm.
I noticed it at her birthday too.
Bullshit.
I know what I saw.
- Whose phone is that?
- Can you hear that?
Where...
Where is it?
Oh, my God. It's Angelica's.
It's Roger.
I don't know if it's the nerves
or the pregnancy,
but my tonsils are floating.
Becka, wipe the bowl after you.
We don't want your DNA down there.
Poor Roger.
He must be going out of his mind.
Should I answer?
What did you do that for?
I panicked.
Urs!
I'm bleeding.
Go.
Go. I've got this.
- Come on.
- It's all right.
We'll go to the hospital
and get it checked out.
Okay.
Sir, Angelica Collins didn't
come home last night.
I'm going to the crash site to check
something, all right? Call me back.
DI Loftus, leave a message.
Grace was driving away from
Angelica Collins's when she crashed.
I think Eva Garvey was telling the truth.
Angelica was blackmailing her
because she found out about JP.
And I just found out that
Ian Reilly was threatening her.
Sir, it's all connected.
It's all...
Will you just call me back?
Where's the ultrasound scan... The...
Down there.
Oh, shit.
Calm down. This is probably nothing.
- Are you okay?
- Yeah.
What's he doing? What are you doing?
I'm just trying to locate the...
Locate it?
Have I lost it?
It's okay.
It's not always easy to see this early on.
I'm just gonna get the...
She should be in the...
Oh, my God. He's terrible at his job.
- Have I had a miscarriage?
- No. It's...
It's probably just hormonal, you know,
with all the stress from everything.
I should never have let you on that boat.
I don't know what I was thinking.
I didn't want the baby anyway,
so it's no wonder my body's--
Becka! Stop that.
Hello. Becka, is it?
Yeah.
All right. Let's see what we've got here.
Is it gone? Just tell me.
Let's have a little look, shall we?
There you are.
Hiding on us, were you?
It all looks fine.
Yeah.
- Should we take some pictures?
- Yeah.
Mr. Reilly.
Sorry, I can't resist a tortoise.
Each to their own.
Well, they always remind me of
my bio dad, as it goes.
Bald, angry, sex mad.
What can I do for you, Detective?
Sorry. Yeah, I was gonna call, but I don't
have a number for you, it seems.
Just wanted to have a quick word
about Angelica Collins.
What about her?
You did a bit of a job on her,
apparently, according to her brother.
I don't know about that.
She was bothering
the Garvey sisters, they're my family.
I asked her to stop. That was all.
Problem is, all I see is
a man threatening a woman.
And that friend, Cathal Leary,
that you claimed you were staying with
- the night Grace died--
- What do you mean claimed?
Well, I mean, we haven't
been able to contact him.
Maybe he's away.
I did mention that
he services nautical cranes.
Look, he has a work mobile.
I'm sure I've got
a business card somewhere.
I can drop it into the station, okay?
Yeah, why don't you do that?
Drop it into me.
Or I could just grab your number now.
In case I need to get a hold of you
sooner rather than later.
Gotcha.
- You go in and lie down.
- Yeah.
I'll bring you a cup of tea.
- Do you want something to eat?
- No.
Just a biscuit maybe, or a piece of bread.
Yeah.
A sandwich? Or pasta? Whatever's easy.
Eva.
Hey.
No need to look so delighted to see me.
Sorry.
I got you some dinner.
Yeah, that's very sweet, but--
The cops paid me a visit.
I'm sorry. I don't even...
Jesus. This is not good.
- Yeah.
- This is not good.
I'm so fucking scared for everyone.
And, Blanaid,
I'm supposed to be protecting her,
the poor little thing, and now--
Eva, this is not all on you.
I'm not going anywhere.
Now, I want to help protect her too.
I spent the morning listening to the news
every hour on the hour, I think.
And the longer it goes
without us hearing anything,
the less likely it is
for Angelica to wash up.
What a disgusting human.
Well, I spent the morning
bleeding an old woman's radiators
to get to her CCTV footage.
Well, that just all sounds like
a euphemism for something else.
What's wrong with you?
I mean, why are you sticking around?
Most men would have
run a mile from this mess.
'Cause I care about you. About all of you.
Now, in fairness, mainly you.
Sorry.
- Well, can we talk about what happened?
- Oh, God.
It's almost laughable.
I get off with my brother-in-law
and it's not even the most fucked up thing
that's happened in the past 24 hours.
I'm not really
your brother-in-law if that helps.
It's not just the...
Even if she...
Look, it's just very bad timing.
Because the thing about feelings is
they have to be timed right.
I think what I'm trying to say is,
you've been in a relationship with
your couch and your remote control
for a while now,
and I think it's time to move on.
What?
- Roger. Hi.
- Sorry to bother you, Eva.
You haven't seen Angelica, have you?
No. I haven't.
It's just, she's not responding to
her texts and that's not like her.
She loves a text.
No.
And I've had a detective at my door
looking for her as well.
What's going on?
My sister disappeared.
I was hoping maybe that
Blanaid might know something.
Bla, she's not here. She's with Molly.
I think Blanaid has
been through enough trauma
without stories of people going missing.
It's not a story.
You threatened her.
- I told the Guards about it.
- No, he didn't threaten her.
It was a misunderstanding.
Yeah, I told her
to stop harassing my family.
And you could do with
heeding the same advice.
Roger.
Did you have to be so hard on him?
I know what it's like to lose a sister
and not get to say goodbye.
Sorry, I didn't think. I...
I should go.
Yeah.
I'll see ya.
See ya.
Oh, sir.
I've been ringing you all day.
Did you get my voice messages?
Yep.
Okay, so, like I said, I think
that Ian Reilly went after Angelica
to get that money back for the sisters,
and I think that he could've done
something to her, either out of anger--
Those true crime podcasts
are rotting your brain.
No. There is something about him.
He's all smiles and charm
and soft, cuddly jumpers, but then--
Just shut up, all right?
Grace Reilly was on the run.
It's as simple as that.
No. What happened to all the money?
Where is it? Where is Angelica Collins?
Angelica Collins has been gone
for a few hours
and you already have her
in a shallow grave.
Have you even put out a general alert
for her vehicle?
- Well, no. But I was--
- Well...
No, maybe you should try that.
A bit of good, old-fashioned police work.
If that's not too much to ask.
Any room in there?
Yeah, if you like your sheets moist.
Gross.
- You'll be 50 one day. I can't wait.
- Yeah.
You'll be knocking on 70.
Yeah. I can't wait for that either.
You know you're gonna
have to tell Joe now.
I suppose it's only fair.
He'll be raising the child
while I'm in jail.
You're not gonna be in jail.
The sound of the boom hitting her.
I can't stop hearing it.
She didn't deserve to die like that.
I know she didn't.
Oh, shit the bed, no.
Hang on.
It's bloody...
ten past 7:00 in the bloody...
Hang on!
Jesus.
- Jesus Christ.
- We've got a problem.
What?
They were in Angelica's handbag.
So what?
Is he ever not here?
Hey.
Blanaid left her kit behind.
What's happened?
Bibi found Angelica's car keys.
Has she a car?
I only ever saw her on her bike
and her broom.
Well, if she drove to the marina
and parked there,
the cops are gonna know she got on a boat.
Then they're gonna start asking around.
Well, how do we find her car
if we don't know what she drives?
Go to the marina
and walk around pressing the key fob.
I'll do it.
Yeah, well, if you're gonna go,
you need to go now.
Sorry, it's...
Look, it's just, they're gonna
move fast on this
if Roger's reported her missing,
all right?
Don't leave any fingerprints.
Yeah, thanks for that, CSI Portmarnock.
DI Loftus, leave a message.
Houlihan.
That vehicle you were looking for,
it's been spotted.
What? Where?
It's in the marina car park.
Well, she's not gonna be driving that,
you dope.
What the hell are you doing in my car?
Oh, shit. Sorry. I thought it was mine.
- Fuck's sake.
- They're very similar.
Oh, God.
Shit. This is bad.
Well, at least she didn't see you, right?
- I don't know.
- Hey. Sorry I'm late.
Hey.
Are you okay? It seemed kinda hairy.
I don't know. I don't think she saw me,
but I legged it, so who knows?
Why the hell did we meet here?
Well, I thought it'd be better
to carry on as normal.
You know, be visible.
Well, look, we're here now,
shall we go for a swim?
Shock the nerves out of us.
I don't know. It doesn't feel right.
This was your idea.
Yeah, but I can't stop
thinking about, you know,
- floating around out there.
- Look, can we just not talk about it?
- Please, just for one hour.
- Fine.
So what do you wanna talk about, Eva?
What?
Have you any news?
Anything you wanna share with the group?
Why are you being weird?
Fine, I'll just ask you then.
What's the story with you and Ian?
- There's no stor... What?
- I know something happened.
Nothing's happened.
Okay, look, weirdly,
and I know it's fucking weird...
I have feelings for hi...
- We have for each other--
- What did I tell you?
- What?
- Are you joking?
Bloody Angelica called it on the boat,
and I stuck up for you.
Yeah, I should hope so.
Look, Bibi, there is nothing, okay?
- I'm only saying it because--
- Because nothing actually happened, Eva?
No, I'm...
Look, it's confusing, okay?
Because I like him, and--
You like him? What are you, 12?
I know you haven't had the ride
in two years, but--
- For God's sake, Bibi.
- No. Are you kidding me?
Grace is barely cold in the ground and
she's already trying to jump his bones!
How can you talk to me like that?
Easily.
Whatever feelings you two are having,
you better bury them
just like you did your sister.
Angelica Collins's van's abandoned, sir.
She's nowhere to be seen.
This is it. We can finally get Howlett
those heads on sticks.
The wrong bloody heads.
Sir, I understand
why you're hiding in a pub.
You're thinking,
"I'm not going out on a high,
Howlett thinks I'm a waste of space,
I failed."
But I think there is something bigger
going on here.
And all this points towards a cover-up
in John Paul Williams's death.
Jesus. God.
A woman died!
And now a woman is missing.
Wherever Ian Reilly is,
those Garvey sisters aren't far behind.
I think we should arrest him
before he runs.
No, we are absolutely not doing that.
And you know we can't do that.
Well, then, at the very least,
we go to his house,
- and we search for the money.
- So this time he took the money?
Last time he was still looking
for the bloody money.
- I'm just saying that if we find it--
- The money has been found, okay?
What?
What do you mean? Where?
In the car, okay?
And maybe if you hadn't been chasing your
tail so much, you would have found it.
- Well, why didn't you--
- Why didn't I what?
What, say something?
You've barely drawn breath.
It's like I've said from the start,
the money has got nothing to do with it.
Grace Reilly killed her husband
and then crashed her car
in the course of doing a runner.
The end.
Fuck.
Oh, Jesus!
- Oh, Christ.
- Let me in.
- Could you not ring the doorbell...
- Sorry.
- ...like normal people?
- Sorry. I'm sorry, I just...
I need to know
what's going on with Becka.
Well, that's not
for me to tell you, is it?
To tell me? So there is something.
Well, no,
she's all over the place at the moment.
It's probably hormones with the...
The what?
With...
Wait, were you gonna say baby?
It's not for me to tell you, Joe.
Is it mine or is it his?
Who are you talking about?
You know who.
His music's a crime, by the way.
I've listened to it.
Tell her I say congratulations, yeah?
You okay, Joe?
What did he say to you?
Nothing. It's...
Well, then why are you so...
Bibi said some horrible things
to me, even by her standards.
She thinks
we're having an affair or something.
Christ. Sorry.
What did you say to her?
I said...
- I said I had feelings for you, but if...
- You have feelings for me?
Do you?
Hey.
It's really good there.
Do you want anything?
- No, I'm all right. Thanks.
- No?
He's not even on LinkedIn.
What?
Ian. He's...
It... Doesn't that strike you as weird?
I'm not on LinkedIn.
You're not on LinkedIn.
- Can I watch some TV?
- Yeah, of course.
What's going on?
Are you having second thoughts again?
Why would you think that?
Because of the way you've been acting.
Last night
you were whimpering in your sleep.
The night before that,
you didn't even come home.
I only agreed to go back to the clinic
because you said you were sure this time.
It has nothing to do with the baby.
Yeah, well, whatever it is,
it's giving you nightmares.
Have a think about whether
you want to keep the appointment tomorrow.
Eva?
Yeah, sorry. I'm just... I'm in here.
Yeah, I know.
You okay? I loved that.
I'm sorry I fell asleep.
Yeah. That's... It's fine.
You know, you're clearly tired
and I'm emotional.
So let's just...
let's just leave it at that.
I'll see you around.
Fuck.
Eva. Can you open the door, please?
This is the worst thing I've ever done.
And I've done some very bad things.
Bullshit.
You've spent your life
putting everyone else first.
Grace said it all the time.
When is it your turn to be happy?
Yeah, but I'm just not prepared
to hurt people for my happiness.
Blanaid and my sisters,
especially Blanaid. I'd rather die
an old maid. I swear to God.
This isn't some grief thing for me, Eva.
You know, I'm in this
for you and for Blanaid.
Where's the harm in that?
And if the worse comes to worse,
then what?
What if I go to prison?
I'm the one the cops are chasing after.
A woman is dead because of us.
So if it does come to that, I need to know
that I've done everything I can for Bla.
There's things we can do. We...
We'll sort it out.
Okay. When?
We'll go to the bank tomorrow.
We'll make it work.
We will?
Whatever you need.
Speaking of which,
I'd better get back to her.
Will you tell her I love her?
- Yeah.
- Okay.
Hi, Becka.
- I'll talk to you later.
- Yeah, okay.
- Please don't--
- You do you, Eva.
Why don't you sort your own shit out?
Joe was here earlier.
He knows you're pregnant, by the way.
Yep.
What are you doing? Get out.
Sorry, sir.
Sorry.
Sir.
Sir. I checked that car, every inch of it.
- What are you on about?
- You tampered with evidence.
Detective, drop it.
I'm gonna report this.
I wouldn't if I was you.
Are you threatening me?
I'm offering you some advice, Detective.
And speak to me like that again,
and you'll find yourself
back on the South Circular
handing out speeding tickets
for your troubles.
Yeah, I like her.
You wanna tell Ruben?
Yeah.
Or maybe we should wait
until after the next appointment.
Bibi, come on.
She spits a lot when she talks.
Seriously? One hit me right in the cheek.
I mean, they need to get glass screens.
It's good to see you laugh like that, Eva.
What the hell?
Who are you?
Bibi. What's wrong?
What's wrong?
I did think it was weird
that you didn't have anyone there
belonging to you at the wedding.
No family, no friends.
Your best man was some random-er
you met a year ago
at some bereavement group.
Look, I know you're upset
about what Eva told you.
What, about you cracking on
to your dead wife's sister?
You've been under a lot of strain.
We all have.
Why did you tell me to go
and look for the car?
Did you know
that detective would be there?
- What?
- Angelica said something
before she went into the water.
She said you weren't to be trusted.
She was right, wasn't she?