Come here. Okay.
Hey, Eva.
Eva, it's me.
I'm-- I really need your help.
I'm so sorry.
Please call me back.
Play it again.
Hey, Eva.
Eva, it's me.
I'm-- I really need your help.
I'm so sorry.
Please call me back.
Why was she asking for help?
Hey, Eva.
Eva, it's me.
I'm-- I really need your help.
I'm so sorry.
Please call me back.
What's this?
I noticed
you hadn't brought breakfast.
Excuse me for not packing
hash browns to a crash scene.
We spooked her.
Yeah, well,
she was looking pretty guilty, sir.
She knew we were onto her, so she bolted.
What a bleeding mess.
What happens when the person
you're questioning just dies?
Well, it depends on who and how.
- Grace Reilly and in a car crash--
- Yeah, I know.
Rake of unanswered questions
and a heap of paperwork, that's what.
And a young girl left with no parents.
Poor wee thing.
My ma went missing when I was 12.
Said she was gonna go to Nottingham
to see her brother for his birthday,
but when we called,
he said that he wasn't having
a birthday party
and he hadn't seen my ma in months.
I'd feel a lot more sorry for you
if I couldn't hear your food
working its way around your mouth.
Sorry.
It's fine now though.
When I made detective
she booked us a spa weekend.
Have you got kids, sir?
Daughter. Twelve.
Twelve daughters?
No. Who do you think I am?
Boris bloody Johnson?
I've got one daughter.
She's 12.
Best kid you could meet.
Top of her class.
So she's first year?
Where is she going to secondary school?
Australia.
Oh, sorry.
Who goes on the run with nothing,
daughter in bed?
What in the hell was she thinking?
What are you doing?
I was trying to get ahold of Ian.
- Well, I don't want to say it, but I--
- That was group hysteria.
That was insane.
I don't know what we were thinking.
He has to come back.
He has to, hasn't he? She's--
I just can't see
how she crashed on a quiet road.
Eva. Will you stop doing that?
I just-- I can't take a breath.
Something's caught.
Okay. The last time someone died
there was 18 years ago, drink driving.
What difference does it make
who else died there?
Was she a bit out of it?
She'd never drink and drive.
She got a passive high off a joint once
at Tommy Doyle's house
and refused to cycle home.
She'd barely take a paracetamol.
Could she have? She was pretty riled up.
I have to get some air.
Come on.
Shit.
I can't look at any documents now. Sorry.
Right. Yeah. Well, I'll try and keep
any sudden family tragedies
to a more convenient quarter.
Sorry, Martin. I got cut off there.
Yeah. Stick your job up your hole.
I just handed in my notice.
Hey, honey. Do you want some cereal?
You didn't have any dinner last night.
Is Ian on his way?
Have any of you spoken to him?
I'm sure he'll be back soon, love.
Mam drove him away. I bet you anything.
Probably drunk. Psycho.
- What the hell, Blanaid?
- Watch your mouth.
She's devastated.
She's just saying things.
Stop telling me how I'm feeling.
You don't even know.
Oh, Jesus Christ. Hello?
Yeah, Mr. Reilly isn't here. He's--
Right, well, we can identify--
One of us can do it. Okay, thanks.
They want us to identify the body.
Please don't say "the body."
You all right, Urs?
You're very vacant.
Sorry.
Yeah. Snap out of it, Urs.
It's not like your sister just died.
- Jesus Christ, Bibi.
- What's the matter with you?
She hasn't spilled a tear,
just bloody quips all day. It's mental.
Maybe if you stopped crying
for a millisecond,
there'd be space
for somebody else to be sad.
You're such a horrible bitch.
I can do it.
I can identify the body.
Well, we need to discuss--
Well, look, somebody has to identify her.
Ian's not here. I'm a nurse.
I can do it.
- I could go in with you, you know, but--
- Eva, please just let me do this.
I've never felt more worthless
in my life to all of you.
Completely useless.
- I can handle this. Let me handle it.
- Okay.
Whenever you're ready.
What the fuck is he doing here?
What will I do if they ask about Ian?
You just say we're grieving.
We're grieving.
Okay.
I'm sorry for your troubles.
It's standard practice
for a spouse to identify the deceased
as the nearest next of kin.
Actually, Fergal,
any news on toxicology yet?
Why? Do you think she was intoxicated?
No. I don't.
Just maybe you could give me the heads-up
when the results come through?
Well, you know, we met. We got on so well,
so I thought maybe--
We chatted for 15 minutes.
And you gave me a drunk snog,
and you said "Donald" 17 times,
and you never returned my text.
It's "Donal."
We can go through now.
Miss Garvey,
has Ian Reilly still not reappeared?
Look, we don't know where he is.
We're grieving.
What should we dress her in?
Should it be a jacket and skirt or…
Either of these?
- Yeah. Nice.
- Good. Yeah.
Lovely.
No. Stop. Okay?
We can't just all go inside of ourselves
and become fucking polite to each other.
No matter what.
So, come on.
What do you think?
Okay. I hope she gets the assistant
manager's job at the petrol station.
Do you remember when she--
Do you remember when she made herself
a pair of leather trousers
out of a pattern?
That girl loved a bit of leather.
Little matching bolero.
You should add that to the eulogy.
Oh, God. The eulogy.
Do we have to make a speech?
No, can't write a bloody best man speech.
Try and sum her up
in four paragraphs for everyone.
No. We'll just mourn her in our own way.
Yeah, we'll sit around the fire,
drink a bottle of whiskey
and remember her properly.
When everyone pisses off
and leaves us alone.
Yeah. Sounds okay.
What about this one?
It's a bit booby, Becka.
Why would she wear that
as her final outfit?
Because she was a ride.
She was only just starting to notice.
Why were you laughing so much?
We were just
picking an outfit for your mum.
You don't need an outfit to be burned in.
She wore this on my 13th birthday
in The Gresham.
She said she felt like
Cate Blanchett in it, so…
I just want to scoop her up.
I wish we'd never started this.
What?
Never went after the prick.
That we left well enough alone.
Well, it wasn't well enough, was it?
None of this would have happened
if we'd just stayed the hell out of it.
That organ is awful.
Why did we let them choose it?
Bloody set menu funeral.
Can we just survive this?
Oh, God.
Can you believe that this is happening?
I just can't believe this is happening.
Thank you.
Can you believe it's happening?
- Just--
- How you doing, Roger?
He is a husk of a man.
And our hearts are broken.
Well, let us know if you need
a shoulder to cry on, Angelica, won't you?
I will.
I'm sorry.
Grief thief.
Come sit down the back there.
- No, I'm grand here, thanks.
- Angelica.
Sorry, Angelica. This is for Blanaid
and close family if you wouldn't mind.
Plenty of seats back there.
Can you move?
Yep. Of course.
Well, everyone's turned up.
Except for Grace's own husband.
Are you okay?
Do you want to come sit here? Come sit.
No, thanks.
Who's that?
Matt Claffin.
He's Grace's insurer.
Wow.
Geez, that was nice of him to show up.
Gone above and beyond.
You see, I'd do that photo.
Thank you for being with us today.
For the final… of Grace Reilly née Garvey.
May she rest in peace.
As we bid farewell to our dear sister…
Blanaid and her sisters.
What the hell is going on
with that priest?
He had a stroke last year.
He had a--
Oh, great. Well, that's just great.
Through Christ, our Lord. Amen.
And now we'll hear from Grace's family.
- What?
- Absolutely not.
- I am not saying something.
- Someone needs to go up.
- We need to--
- I don't--
No, I don't want to.
No, we said we weren't doing that.
Yeah, we didn't know bloody Mumbles
would be leading prayers, did we?
Oh, Grace
Just hold me in your arms
And let this moment linger
They'll take me out at dawn
And I will die
With all my love
I place this wedding ring
Upon your finger
There won't be time to share our love
So we must say goodbye
So sorry for your loss.
Thank you.
Hi. Thank you for coming.
Thank you so much.
This is very kind of you.
- Sorry for your loss.
- Thank you.
Thanks for coming.
Have a lovely day.
- Sorry for your loss.
- Thank you.
Thanks for coming. Yeah.
- Thank you, Mary.
- I'm really sorry.
Oh, thank God.
Where the hell have you been?
Where were you?
Why didn't you phone us, you fucking dick?
We had a fight. Grace told me something.
It made me very nervous.
I panicked and left.
No, the handshaking is closed, okay?
No more handshaking.
Thanks a million. Sorry.
What did Grace tell you?
She told me that she killed John Paul.
She told me everything.
Oh, God.
Just wanted to offer you all
our condolences.
And to you, Mr. Reilly.
Thank you.
Glad you made it back from the golf.
We'd love to speak to you
as soon as possible.
With respect for the situation, of course.
Well, can we just speak now, get it done?
Here? Yeah, if that's okay with you. Yeah.
Yeah.
- This is bad.
- Is he gonna tell them?
Oh, Jesus. Jesus Christ. Jesus.
He wouldn't do that.
Look, Grace and I had an argument.
Nothing major, but, yeah,
I went to stay with a pal.
Who?
Cathal Leary. He lives in Kildare.
I can give you his number.
Excuse me for prying on a day like this,
but, well, it would be
really handy for us to know.
What did you and your wife fight about?
A bicker about nothing that escalated.
You weren't married that long, right?
Can I ask how you met?
Through the sisters?
No. Online, the old fashioned way.
So were you aware that
her father-in-law was murdered
and was dead for nearly ten years
while they spent his pension?
I don't know why all this
is on my shoulders.
I didn't know her previous husband
or her father-in-law,
and I only met the sisters last year.
And I don't think
this is appropriate right now.
Are we done?
Absolutely.
He's dodgy, right?
Yeah.
We should go in.
There's people here already.
What did the Guards ask you?
Can I ask a question instead?
Did you help her?
We covered it up.
Am I expected
to just keep quiet about all this?
Oh, Ian. Jesus.
I'm sorry for your loss, man.
Thanks, Joe.
God.
- Joe, you're fine. We'll do that.
- No, it's grand.
- I'll bring these out for you.
- Joe.
Oh, God! Sorry. Jesus.
Can you just leave it there?
We're talking.
Sorry, lads. I hope I haven't--
Can you just leave it?
- Sorry. No.
- Sorry, Joe.
Just go make a drink,
and we'll be in in a minute.
I just need a pause.
Then I'll figure out what to do, okay?
I'm sorry. I'm gonna go see Bla.
Ian.
- I'm so sorry.
- Can we trust him?
Well, we have to
for now.
No, thanks.
Shock yourself back to life
with a little bit of sugar.
Beautiful family.
You know, I lost my husband very young.
Eddie.
He used to pick daisies for me
and dry them out in a big book about cars.
He loved cars. Cars and women.
You can never get grief right.
I never shed a tear
for my father when he died.
I mean, whatever you feel is normal.
I feel guilt.
Why?
You know, Grace loved you very much.
She often mentioned you, Ursula.
Did you talk much?
She was my pal.
Mine too.
See, I know what Grace went through.
Sorry, what do you mean?
I know what JP did to her.
And what she did to him.
I just can't understand
what had her so upset.
Having gone through all that.
Just a beautiful life
gone.
I've never seen her like that.
Never. Not even with him.
That's why I--
You…
No, just…
I was so worried.
I'm sure you were the best person
to help her in that state.
I offered her something.
Pills.
Just to calm her down.
Well, you're a nurse.
The most natural thing in the world.
I think this is my fault.
That which is done in love cannot be bad.
Jesus Christ.
Get your feet off the desk.
Sorry, sir.
I think I've found something.
So, I was doing a bit of digging
into all the Garvey sisters.
Eva left a huge firm
where John Paul Williams worked.
Bibi has been a semipro poker player
for the last two years.
Can you believe that?
Actually, I can.
And Ursula, well,
I'm sure you know all about her, sir.
But look what I found on Becka.
What am I looking at?
Matt Claffin.
Ever since we saw him at the funeral,
I haven't been able
to stop thinking about him.
Not like that. Well, a bit like that.
But I went through all his socials.
Becka's been liking
and commenting on his posts,
and then all of a sudden
it stopped, right?
So, look at this,
Becka's is the same story,
but now it's Matt who's stopped liking.
Stopped liking what?
What? No, he stopped liking.
Hang on.
See? There's a heart
from Matt in the comments.
I think they were an item, sir.
We know the Claffins were convinced
that Grace killed John Paul.
But what if Becka was using Matt,
like, through womanly wiles,
to get Thomas Claffin to back off?
What if the sisters
were all in on it, sir?
What if they all helped with the murder?
Is that a good noise, sir?
It's a neutral noise.
Yeah, it's not nothing.
I keep thinking of Ian Reilly at the
funeral trotting off after those sisters.
Womanly wiles, sir.
Stop saying womanly wiles.
Yep. Well, should we go and maybe see--
No, we won't.
Let's wait for the tox report
that Ursula Garvey is so desperate for.
You just keep your powder dry
if that's possible.
Yes.
Hi, Angelica. It's Ursula again.
Sorry for all the calls.
Just wanted to say--
It just got a bit intense
last week at the funeral,
so I just wanted to make sure
that we're okay after our chat.
Hey, honey, you on your way over?
I've got your room nearly--
Bla, you have to let me try.
Fine.
Well, I'll pick you up for the swim later.
All the girls are gonna be there.
Right, well,
I'll kidnap you if I have to then.
Love you. Bye.
Are we still going to the Forty Foot?
Jesus Christ.
Ursula, what's the matter with you?
Yes.
Please put your chairs away.
Thought Ian might have come.
Do you think he'll be back to group?
How would I know that, Caroline?
Just excuse me a moment.
Someone needs my help.
Hi…
I obviously told you
something quite intense,
and then I couldn't get ahold of you.
I've been calling you for over a week.
I felt like your stalker.
I'm so sorry.
I have just been so busy.
You know, since Grace's passing,
it's just renewed my vigor.
God. Look at this.
Oh, God.
Yeah, okay-- So I just wanted to check,
that you hadn't, you know, told anyone…
about the pills.
Do you see this place?
I mean, it's very precious to me
as it was for your sister.
You know, we cooked
an unholy amount of lasagna in there.
It's home for people
who just don't feel comfortable
anywhere else.
You know, it's a stable, safe, good place.
I mean, there are not many places
like that around nowadays.
Yeah. No, absolutely. Well done.
Do you see that window?
Just broken.
And the noise from the matches
just seeps right through into my group,
into every group, you know?
Yeah, I think that window is gonna
stay broken like that all winter.
It would cost 200 euros to solve,
but we just don't have it.
I mean, it's a paltry amount of money.
Yeah, that's not that much money.
No, I mean, not for the quiet.
Surely that's worth it.
Yeah, well, it's meals-on-wheels tonight,
and those carrots
won't julienne themselves
no matter how nicely I ask.
I mean, they told me not to come in
because of what I'm going through,
but the hungry must be fed.
God bless.
Good puck.
Good.
Right.
Hey.
Jesus.
Why didn't you bring her over?
She's been here all week.
You know, I just got her room finished.
We were supposed to
be taking her swimming.
She just really wanted to stay put.
It's hard enough trying to look after her
without you just bloody hogging her.
The kid wouldn't piss on me if I was
on fire right now let alone listen to me.
So next time she comes over,
can you just-- please just send her home?
This is her home.
Yeah, I am her stepdad, Eva.
Now, I know
I've not been around that long,
but we had a good thing,
me and Grace and Bla.
It's not safe for her to rely on you.
I don't know what your plans are.
You know, you could be planning
to hotfoot it onto Tinder
and just abandon the whole mess.
Tinder?
Jesus wept.
Eva, I'd rather put my dick in a door.
What? In the keyhole or--
What? No, like, slam it in a door.
Right. Well, that makes more sense.
We'll get there, you know, day by day.
But for now, just let her be here
until the open wound of it all eases.
Look, I'm sorry.
- I don't want to be controlling it all.
- No, it's grand. It's--
I'm not a mother, but,
you know, Grace wanted me
to step in if the worst happened.
Course she did.
And I know that.
Thanks for not telling
the Guards what we did.
Jesus, that's a weird sentence
to have to say.
But thank you.
You saved our lives.
Wish I could have saved Grace.
Yeah, me too.
- What's up?
- I just-- I can't breathe.
I mean, I can obviously breathe.
I just-- I feel like some--
I feel like something's stuck.
It's the shock.
Muscles are all tensed up.
When my sister died, it happened to me.
Oh, Jesus, sorry.
You can release it a bit
if you just-- Here.
Try it.
Right, just-- If you--
Now, breathe into your belly.
There.
Thank you.
I'm gonna find better ways to thank you
than just saying thank you all the time.
Chips? Do you have time?
For chips? Yeah.
Blanaid, I'm gonna head out for chips.
- You say it. She won't come down for me.
- She will.
If not for you, for chips.
Okay.
Bla!
Yeah?
Anything with the chips?
No, I'm all right.
Are you sure? You want scampi?
No.
Okay then.
Can't believe Bla's not coming.
I thought it was just you
she hated right now.
Why ain't any ye answering your phones?
- Do you look at my messages?
- What's wrong?
I think Grace was in trouble, look.
Are these Gracie's?
- Yeah, look.
- Let me see.
All taken out hours before she died.
Look.
That's a shit ton of cash.
Well, where is that cash now?
So she took out 20,000 euro
and left Blanaid?
What the hell
was going on with Gracie, lads?
God knows. Who was that money for?
Sorry.
- Ursula, what are you at?
- Ursula.
- Ursula, you have my towel.
- Ursula!
Shit.
- Hey.
- Hey, sorry about the change of plan.
I just needed to come home to you.
Urs…
No, I don't--
I mean come home to all of you.
You know, to make an omelet with Michael.
We always used to make omelets
on Wednesdays when you were off.
Yeah, of course. Come on.
Would it be okay if we didn't ask--
Well, I mean, is Ally coming over?
Like, if she wants to, then of course.
But I wanted to talk to you
about something.
Yeah.
She's working anyway,
so I wasn't seeing her tonight.
Why is she working nights?
She doesn't normally work nights.
Don't know. They called her in.
Some drama about the requisition book,
some missing pills.
Doing an audit now, I think.
Don't know if the cops
have been called in yet.
Ursula?
Sorry.
It's not what it looks like.
- It's just a misunderstanding.
- Sorry to interrupt you there,
I just don't want you to make this
any worse for yourself.
Look, I've been working here for decades--
years longer than you, with respect--
and I've never put a foot wrong.
Then why would you do
something so reckless, Nurse?
We'll go through the due process,
and you'll have plenty of right to reply.
Are you doing this out of spite?
Because you don't like me?
Why would I not like you?
It was for Michael, originally.
He was having nightmares,
and our GP was away all summer.
And one night I took one,
and I slept better than I had
since I was a child.
And I couldn't stop.
If I get struck off…
I won't cope. Not now. Not since Grace.
Did Donal know?
We were barely speaking at the time.
Ally, please.
This is illegal.
It's serious, Ursula.
You should go home now.
Ally, I swear, I will--
Go home, Nurse.
Did somebody tip you off about this?
Was it Angelica Collins?
Please, Ally.
Fergal!
Can you give us a sec?
No problem. I'll get a Ribena
from the vending machine,
- or an Appletis--
- Yeah, I don't care.
What's happened? Is Jessie okay?
- She's fine. She's at boxing.
- When did she take up boxing?
I'm not here to explain
your daughter's hobbies to you, Fergal.
Nice of you to take
Miss Daisy out for a little spin.
Kept your daddy issues quiet, by the way.
You're my only issue, Fergal.
Why haven't you signed the papers?
I can't believe I'm still hounding you
for basic communication.
Yeah. Well, I can't believe
- I'm standing here--
- Oh, shut up.
Do you think I've nothing better
to be doing than hunting you down
and begging you to do the right thing?
Sign the papers.
Are you hearing me? Let us go.
And that's my fecking car, by the way.
Are you okay?
What do you need?
We just got the toxicology results.
Should I call the Garveys?
No, we'll go see them.
They've had their grace period.
Literally.
Sorry for barging in on you.
We have the toxicology results
for Mrs. Reilly.
- Detective.
- Oh, yes.
So she was tested for alcohol,
narcotics, anti-inflammatories,
antihistamines, everything, basically.
And it's clean.
Not even half a shandy.
- Nothing?
- Clear as water.
Nothing at all?
Urs?
Urs, come here, honey.
It's an emotional business.
Can I just ask Becka, isn't it?
Yeah.
Is it true that you were involved
with Matt Claffin?
What?
Well, we were just trying to work out
why Grace would have retracted her claim
with Claffin Insurance, citing suicide
when clearly there was no suicide.
I was not involved
with Matt Claffin.
Apparently you were doing
a lot of likes on his "YouTubes."
Huh?
Were you a fan of his music, then?
Hardly.
Must have got that wrong.
Well, so many unanswered questions:
Where was Grace going?
Was she running from something?
Was it because we were
looking into JP's death as murder?
Well, don't you worry.
We will get to the bottom of it all.
See you soon.
Wait.
Thanks for letting us know.
Did Matt fucking talk to them?
Why would he do that to us?
They saw him at the funeral, Becka.
They were bound to start digging.
Stop shouting at me.
Literally not shouting.
Urs, love. What?
I thought it was all my fault.
Oh, God.
I was taking pills…
and I gave some to Grace,
and I couldn't remember
if I told her not to drink on them.
You've been carrying
this around the whole time?
Poor thing, Urs.
Why would you think giving her drugs
was a good idea?
Sorry, you know how vulnerable she was.
Oh, come off the cross.
The amount of triple-- quadruple whiskeys
you've poured down me
when I've had so much as an inconvenience.
Yeah, fair point. Sorry.
There's more.
I told Angelica about the pills.
You told that Christian weirdo and not us.
Why would you do that?
She jumped on what I told her.
She used it against me.
She got fecking money out of me.
What?
I think she did the same to Grace.
I mean, blackmailing her
with what she knew about JP.
- I mean, why else would--
- Angelica knows about JP?
I think Grace must have told her.
Just go steady, okay.
We don't know anything yet.
We need to get the cops
looking at the right person.
We are the right person.
In case you didn't notice,
they were here looking at us.
That bloody wagon.
She's a parasite.
She'll be searching
for the next person she can leech onto.
So, let's get one step ahead of her.
There she is.