Feel that torque?
It's like riding a hard-on.
Come on! Floor it!
My little girl's got a heavier foot.
I'm going back.
Knock it off, Mikey.
Go on the shoulder.
I want to shoot this sign.
Put the gun away,Jack!
Jesus, what the hell are you doing?
Arnie, you should eat something.
How about some leftover veal
and some cold pasta?
Want a beer, honey?
Chicken salad or tuna?
Here come the judge.
What's the difference? Eat it.
Who says we can't hire more people?
Why don't you take a nap?
Your face looks like a bag of walnuts.
Everyone should take a rest.
It's an easy thing to say, isn't it?
You're not thinking. You're not writing.
Ted, calm down. You need a nap too.
- Can you believe this crap?
- Yes, I can.
- Sorry I'm late.
- You're sorry you're late?
You couldn't call?
He called. I told you. There's no news.
You did not make that clear.
You really didn't.
You just said "no news."
You didn't say Kenny called in.
- Pow.
- Damn it.
No one cares that I almost got killed?
- What did they say?
- It's just like last time, no.
- What does that mean?
- It means they didn't like it.
Then they got drunk.
They took me for a joyride in the Impala.
Why can't we have the Impala?
What did they say?
They said they didn't like 'em.
It's your job to make them like them.
- Are you not up to the task?
- Don.
What? We've given
them seven ways to go in six weeks.
We don't even get to talk to them?
We have to depend on this cripple?
- You don't know what he's up against.
- I've got to sit down...
but I'm not gonna if you're just gonna
continue to insult me.
Just sit down.
They gave me this,
and I can't even show it to you.
What is it?
They typed up their rejection?
It's worse.
They finally gave me a calendar.
Three years of monthly deadlines.
That's the rest of'68, '69 and '70.
Best case scenario,
six months of strategy statements...
every one of them
backed up with copy tests.
And then, if and when
they land on something...
it's got to kick its way up the ladder
through all of GM until it gets to God.
And then he's got to run it past his wife.
So what happens now?
You take a swing at it,
and they take a swing at me.
They want another packet Tuesday morning.
- But they want me back on Sunday.
- For what?
I guarantee you
they're not going to church.
We cannot go on like this.
This is what Chevy is paying us for.
It's not our clock. It's theirs.
So what's another weekend?
Because they're really paying us.
Mr. Chaough, you have a phone call.
- Take a message.
- It's Nan. It's about that matter.
Excuse me. Mr. Draper?
Get all the Chevy materials
back in my office.
- We're working the weekend.
- Yes, of course.
But I wanted to tell you
Dr. Rosen is on the phone.
- Do you want me to take a message?
- Yes.
- I'll find out what it's regarding.
- No.
I'll take it.
You know what, Don?
That's a great idea.
I'm gonna call my doctor.
I'm gonna get Kenny here fixed up.
I'm gonna get everybody fixed up.
- Arnold, how are you?
- It's me.
I'm glad to hear that.
Oh, I bet you are...
because I wanted to let you know
that's what that would feel like.
I thought I misunderstood.
Oh, bullshit.
You have got to stop
loitering in my hallway.
Sylvia, I'm glad you called.
He saw all the cigarette butts out there,
and he thinks I'm smoking again.
I want to see you.
I was in the kitchen biting my nails
thinking, "I just cleaned it up."
How many nights are you out there?
I know you want to see me too.
All I kept thinking
is he's gonna come in...
and ask me why there's
no lipstick on them...
and I'm gonna burst into tears
and tell him everything.
Then he's gonna murder me and murder you.
- Are you afraid of him?
- No.
I'm afraid of you.
I don't think you understand.
Look, I'm too old
to say this was a mistake...
but I want you to try and be happy.
About what?
That you got away with it.
When you start something like this,
it takes a lot of convincing.
It's all about whether
or not the other person...
has as much to lose as you do...
because you want to be able
to trust them when it's over.
And right now I'm wondering
how I ever trusted you.
I don't really have a choice, do I?
Because you've got me.
So if you ever really cared
about me at all, knock it off.
Don't cry.Just listen to me.
I'm feeling a lot of emotions too.
- I'm hanging up.
- Please, just listen.
I just want to talk to you
about a few things.
You loved Megan once.
- Stop it.
- Nothing else gets through to you.
I'm going.
Don't make me hang up on you.
I'm hanging up.
Mr. Draper?
Mr. Draper.
I'm gonna go in there.
- Yes?
- Is everything okay?
Yes, I'm fine.
I'm gonna-
I'm tired. I'm just gonna take a nap.
You do that.
You girls should back away.
Does he have a fever?
You get your bedroll.
You stay in here,
you'll get everybody sick.
- You sleep in the cellar.
- Yes, ma'am.
If the fever doesn't break,
we'll call a doctor.
Better for you than for everyone.
Aimée, did you leave
that plate in the lounge?
Mr. Draper?
Yes, what is it?
Do you need some water?
No, I'm fine.
Bobby, go get your suitcase.
- That's mine.
- What about Gene's?
I'm not going to pack his suitcase.
- I already did it. You just have to get it.
- Go get it, Geenie.
Go up there and get Pinocchio
and bring it down.
I have to do everything.
- Where's Daddy? We're ready to go.
- I'm taking you.
Were you sitting under the hair dryer
and just remembered that?
- Where did you get that skirt?
- I bought it.
You mean Megan bought it for you.
- I earned it.
- On what street corner?
She pays me to babysit.
You're not a hired hand.
You're their sister.
Boys, let's go.
I'm sorry to bother you,
but Mr. Cutler wants to see you.
It's been two and a half hours.
Do you want to rest some more?
No.
May I clean that up?
Please.
Put the Chevy materials
on the coffee table.
The funeral will be tomorrow.
Frank's family has asked
that in lieu of flowers...
a donation be made to
the American Cancer Society.
Frank Gleason was a great artist
and a great friend.
And he made our company whole.
I'm not gonna be able to work with you
through the weekend.
I apologize, but I'm afraid
this takes precedence.
I'll attend the funeral
if that's all right.
But I can still make myself
available for Chevy.
That's helpful.
I'm sorry for your loss.
He's a piece that cannot be replaced.
The doctor's here,
and I want you to see him.
- I don't know.
- No, he's gonna fix you up.
That's an order.
Can I see him too? I did it last time.
We're a team. If he does it, I do it.
Age before beauty.
How old was he?
Older than you, younger than me.
You either get used to it
or stop thinking about it.
Sorry about your friend.
Yeah, it's tragic.
I hope we don't lose Ted for too long.
He doesn't know
how to deal with these things.
- Do you feel anything? 'Cause I don't.
- He said it takes a minute.
- Well, maybe I need another.
- I'm next.
Actually, Roger,
I think Don should go next.
Pleasure to meet you. Dr. Hecht.
Don Draper. Where do you want me?
Anything in your medical history you
want to alert me to?
No. I'm just-
Hell, I don't even know
what I'm doing here.
You're exhausted.
Turn around and drop your pants.
This goes in the gluteus.
- What is it?
- It's an energy serum.
Oh? What's in it?
It's proprietary.
But all you need to know...
is it's a complex vitamin superdose.
It's basically my own combination
of"B" vitamins and a mild stimulant.
You have a heart condition?
No. I thought you said it was mild.
What does it do?
Well, a lot of things. But I think it'll
give you what Jim Cutler says you need-
24 to 72 hours of uninterrupted
creative focus, energy and confidence.
- Really?
- Really.
No one told you about this?
I've visited some agencies lately.
- You've got a great outfit here.
- Thank you.
All anybody wants to know
is what are you gonna call this place.
Can you tug your drawers
down a little?
"SCDPCGC"?
That's a mouthful.
Stan again.
What do you say, Don?
You think you can beat me?
I want another chance. You changed course.
- Who's next?
- That'd be me.
- And I have a heart condition.
- Don't worry about it.
Come on. Let's go. Best two out of three.
You can beat me any day.
Let me see the doctor first.
Hell, we'll do before and after.
Hey, kid. Where you going?
Come in here.
Sit down.
Breathe deep.
Is that you?
No.
It's a chest cold.
I've seen plenty of consumption.
You don't have it.
Lay down here.
Your mama don't know
how to take care of nobody.
She ain't my mother.
Can I help you?
- Do we know each other?
- I'd like to think so.
Can I help you?
I meant from somewhere
other than from this moment.
I don't think so.
- Where's Ed?
- He said his heart stopped.
- Roger took him to the hospital.
- But they were both laughing.
The strategy is about some kind
of love transaction...
between a parent and a child...
involving the greatest
gift of all, a Chevy.
I was a child, and she was a child
in this kingdom by the sea.
Four score and seven years ago...
this country had some
memorable happenings.
What I don't understand is...
is it "Dad, I want this car,"
or "Son, I bought you this car"?
Great, that's two.
We need 15 more and we can try another.
In what family is it
"Son, I bought you this car"?
- Good night, all.
- That guy's family.
Did you hear about Frank Gleason?
Yeah, I guess dreams do come true.
I think that's in poor taste.
Tell him, Peggy.
Tell him what a son of a bitch he was.
I liked him.
Before he was sick?
I hate how dying
makes saints out of people.
Well, he's obviously in a better place.
Have a good weekend.
"Dad, I need the car. I've got a date."
"Dad, everybody at school
has a car but me."
"Dad, I can only go to college
if I have a car."
- "Dad, I-"
- "Dad, I could be dying in Vietnam.
Don't you want me to have a car?"
Damn it, Ginsberg.
I had another 80 of them.
I got nothing interesting to say
'cause I'm not on drugs?
No, you just flushed a toilet in my head.
"Son, I got a car
when I was your age."
"Son, they didn't have cars
"Son, you can fly till you're high
as an elephant's eye."
That's great.
What are you, class secretary?
I want to write stuff down
so it looks like I'm working.
Fine.
The child is the father of the man.
Spectacular.
Mr. Draper.
Mr. Cosgrove is here to see you.
Hello, Kenny. How you feeling?
My foot's like new.
You think you'll have new work
on Monday?
I'll have 15 campaigns for you by then...
but you have to get me in a room
so I can look them in the eye.
The timbre of my voice
is as important as the content.
I don't know whether
I'll be forceful or submissive...
but I must be there in the flesh.
You understand that I have
no power whatsoever?
That's not true. Not if they like you.
Oh, they like me all right.
- I'm their favorite toy.
- That's your job.
It's my job to take them to dinner
at 80 miles an hour.
It's my job to stop a mile
from the restaurant...
so they can have
five pounds of crab legs...
and three bottles of beer apiece
and then go get prime rib.
It's my job to go hunting
so they can fire off their guns...
an inch from my ear and laugh
when I get startled because it's my job.
Where'd you learn that?
My mother. No, my first girlfriend.
One doesn't like changing
so often, you know?
- I don't know.
- I'm not myself, you see?
I don't see.
And she comes to the fork in the road...
then she says to the Cheshire Cat,
"Which road do I take?"
I know this. Where do you want to go?
- I don't know.
- Then it doesn't matter, does it?
- How's it going?
- What's going on?
I know you're all feeling
the darkness here today.
But there's no reason to give in.
No matter what you've heard,
this process will not take years.
In my heart I know
we cannot be defeated...
because there is an answer
that will open the door.
There is a way around this system.
This is a test of our patience
and commitment.
One great idea can win someone over.
Dear Lord,
you're as good as they say.
That was very inspiring.
Do you have any idea what the idea is?
No. But I'm not gonna stop looking.
I think we should order dinner.
I don't think I'll ever eat again.
Do what you have to.
You're burning up.
You have to eat something.
Sit up.
I can't, Ms. Swenson.
Call me Aimée, and yes, you can.
I've got it.
How many times do you do it?
I need six throws for a reading.
- What are you doing?
- The I Ching.
Have you slept?
Crap. I missed the funeral, didn't I?
- How was it?
- It was rough.
- It was beautiful.
- Who are you?
Her name is Wendy. Wendy, this is Don.
Don. Ask a question.
- I'm supposed to be next.
- Are you done with mine?
You can just think of it.
You don't have to say it out loud.
Perfect.
Peggy, do you remember when we had soup?
Maybe.
Could you be more specific?
Carnegie Deli has great soup.
No, he's talking about some account.
He asked me yesterday.
I don't think it exists.
- No, I didn't.
- I don't understand what you're asking.
We had an account at Sterling Cooper.
A soup account.
That must have been before my time.
Can you go to the archives
and look for it?
I already looked.
Why are you asking her?
- 'Cause you think I'm incompetent?
- I did it!
I've got 666 ideas.
I'm wasting my Saturday with lunatics.
- It's Saturday?
- Yes, it is.
Why don't you lie down for a little while?
Because I've got it.
I want you to go to the archives.
Look in 1958 or '59 for soup.
You'll know it when you see it...
and it's gonna crack this thing wide open.
You see the mess you made?
That was fast.
What are you doing in here?
You said you were going to get some ice...
and we were going to have a drink
and watch the sun set.
I have some things to do.
Stop doing that.
You are really uptight, aren't you?
No, I'm just on a deadline.
- Where'd you get that?
- It was upstairs in one of the offices.
You want to get it on?
Wendy, what are you doing here?
I'm here to make you feel better.
I feel great, but I'm on a deadline.
"Does someone love me?"
What?
That's what your question was.
- Why would you say that?
- That's everyone's question.
I want to hear your heart.
I think it's broken.
You can hear that?
I can't hear anything.
I think it's broken.
You should go.
I'm in the middle of something.
Good morning. Good morning.
Any complaints?
Can you get that?
If it's Jeff Hunter, I'll be right there.
- Draper's.
- Sally?
- When are you coming home?
- Is Megan there?
- I want to talk to him.
- It's my dad.
Where are you?
I'm still at work.
I have to leave. I'm leaving right now.
I'm really sorry. I'm not finished yet.
It- I'm really close.
It's just the research hasn't come in.
Don, I don't care.
What am I supposed to do?
I watched them last night
so you could work and now-
I'll be home in a little bit.
Well, I don't like you working so hard.
You must be exhausted.
Actually, I've got a second wind.
When's he coming home?
Sally, how would you like to earn
some boots to go with that skirt?
You're going to leave us with her again?
I'm really sorry, sweetie,
but you know you'll have fun.
Don't make her feel bad.
- Where are you going?
- I'm going to see a play.
And Jeff, my agent, is going to
introduce me to some producers...
so that maybe I can be in their play.
Why do you want to do a play?
You're on TV every day.
Don't they know that?
Shit, you must be hungry.
Sally, would you put
a pot of water on the stove?
I'm gonna make spaghetti in a minute.
- I'm gonna wait for Dad.
- We're not hungry.
Okay, but go make Gene
a peanut butter and jelly.
Come on, that thing's twice
the size of a real apple. Step right up.
How about everybody takes one?
Do a real firing squad.
He's gonna look just like Saint Sebastian.
Hold on a second.
One at a time. Everybody'll get a chance.
You're pretentious,
you know that? I love that.
- I want to do it.
- Fine, but I'm gonna go first...
because you're drunk.
In fact, I believe I'm the only person...
in the Time-Life Building
who's not out of his mind.
But you hate him.
I hate apples more.
- Don't hit his eye.
- Don't hit anything.
- Crap.
- Who's next?
It's fine. It's fine.
I've done that before.
- Doesn't hurt at all.
- Let me see. Let me see.
- Keep pressure on it.
- Honestly, Peggy, I don't even feel it.
Come on. You've got to wash this.
Hold still.
You got a great bedside manner.
What are you doing?
You're lucky I don't like beards.
Women say that,
but they don't act like it.
You're like my brother.
You don't have a brother.
I want you to stop.
No, you don't.
I have a boyfriend.
No.
Come on.
I need this.
I know, I know. You're in pain.
My cousin Robbie was killed in action.
Twenty years old.
Had to join the fucking navy.
That's awful.
What happened?
They don't tell you.
They just tell you when it happened.
March 4. Three months ago.
That means my aunt sent 16 letters
that he never saw.
You know they get mail
right up to the front lines?
That'd be a bad job, right?
Delivering mail into combat?
I'm so, so sorry to hear that.
I've had loss in my life.
You have to let yourself feel it.
You can't dampen it with drugs and sex.
It won't get you through.
Maybe we're different.
Why don't you go home?
'Cause I can't stand up right now.
That's from the shot.
You've got a great ass.
Thank you.
Hello?
You startled me.
I didn't know anybody was home.
- What are you doing?
- Go back to sleep.
What are you doing here?
I'm visiting. Didn't nobody tell you?
No. Who are you?
I'm your grandma.
That's impossible.
Now, why is that impossible?
Okay, I know.
But I raised your daddy.
What are you doing here?
I was just looking for a serving plate.
I was gonna make your daddy's favorite.
You know, he loves fried chicken.
I bet you do too.
Ooh, you sure look like him.
No one said you were coming.
Well, I think I was supposed to be
a surprise for you.
And your daddy said I could visit,
and he gave me a key.
I thought nobody was home.
Come over here and give a hug
to your Grandma Ida.
Now, don't you be rude to me.
Is that how you was raised
to speak to your betters?
No.
I'm gonna fix you some eggs.
And you're gonna sit down
and you're gonna eat 'em.
But first, you're gonna tell me
who else in the house.
How come you don't know?
I haven't talked
to your daddy in a long time.
And he want to surprise me too.
I've never heard of you.
Your daddy
Mr. Donald Draper or not?
You come over here
and give me some sugar.
Now, I know you ain't
here all by yourself.
My little brothers are here.
Well, there's no need to wake them.
Just be us.
Okay, let's go and make you some eggs.
I bet you like them scrambled.
I can make them.
And burn yourself on the stove?
- When you think they're gonna be home?
- I don't know.
When's the last time you saw my dad?
Years ago.
I doubt he's changed.
He still handsome?
Yes.
Your mama still a piece of work?
Now, what do they call you?
Sally.
Your fever broke.
- Yes, Ms. Swenson.
- Call me Amy.
It's not really Aimée.
I just liked the way it was spelled.
It's got two E's and an accent.
It's a nice name.
You are better.
- Do you like this?
- I do.
Do you like girls?
You don't even know what to do
right now, do you?
- But you like it.
- Stop it.
You like my bosom.
I don't know.
Don't you want to know
what all the fuss is about?
No.
It's okay. I'll do everything.
- What are you looking for?
- Now you stop asking questions...
or I'm not gonna let you eat
in your nice living room.
Maybe I know where it is.
I'm just looking for some place
to hide my presents I bought y'all.
My, that TV's in here good!
Who's she?
Is that little Bobby?
My, you have grown up big!
- Who are you?
- That's Grandma Ida.
We don't have a grandma.
You do now.
And you gonna get
all the candy and toys...
and good stuff your grandma bought you...
when you wake up in the morning.
But right now, you go back to sleep.
I'm not tired.
Now, Sally don't remember...
but I gave your daddy a watch...
gold watch.
And I got a new band for it...
and I wanna fix it up before he come back.
You seen it?
He has four watches.
I'll know it when I see it.
They're in the drawer by his bed.
Are we allowed to watch TV?
I think she's lying.
Are we Negroes?
Hello. Will you put me
through to the police? It's an emergency.
I'm at 783 Park Avenue,
and there's a stranger in our apartment.
What?
No, I'm 14.
My name is Sally Draper.
Hello?
Yes, sir.
These children ought to be in bed...
and they ain't too well behaved.
Yes, sir.
They played a joke on both of us.
Uh-huh.
Good night.
Now, why'd you do something like that?
You hurt my feelings.
I'm gonna go out and get some air.
When I come back, you best be sleeping.
"This may be hard to believe,
but the history can't be ignored.
The history should not be ignored.
Look, I don't want to waste
your time, with-"
Peggy!
"I don't want you to shut this door.
Just let me say a few things.
You and I both know-"
- Did you want us?
- Yes. Get everyone.
No, wait.
Just listen. I've got it.
Great.
Remember this work?
I've never seen it before.
Well, it says it all. It really does.
Okay, I've got this great message...
and it has to do with
what holds people together.
What is that thing that draws them?
It's a history.
And it may not even be
with that person, but it's-
it's like a-
well, it's bigger than that.
And that makes them buy a car?
If this strategy is successful,
it's way bigger than a car.
It's everything.
I keep thinking about
the basic principle of advertising.
There's entertainment
and you stick the ad...
in the middle of the entertainment
like a little respite.
It's a bargain.
They're getting
the entertainment for free.
All they have to do
is listen to the message.
But what if they don't
take the bargain at all?
What if they're suddenly
bored of the entertainment?
What if they don't-
What if they turn off the TV?
- You gotta get your foot in the door.
- Exactly!
So, how do I do that?
Let's say I get her face-to-face.
How do I capture her imagination?
I have a sentence, maybe two.
Who's "her"?
Promise them everything.
You know, you're gonna change their life.
- You're gonna take away their pain.
- That's good.
Then you hit 'em with the one-two punch.
What's the answer
to all of life's problems? A Chevy.
- No, it's not.
- Then it's oatmeal?
No.
What have you been doing
the last three days?
Have you been working on Chevy at all?
I gotta go.
You wanna get someone in here
who can draw?
No, I don't have time for art.
He's happy. Now we can relax.
You think he'll care if I nap in here?
Don? Wait.
I'm going home!
Okay, I'm gonna change my shirt...
tell Megan I'm going out for cigarettes...
then I'm gonna knock on her door.
Sylvia, don't close the door on me.
"When in the course of human events-" No.
"You haven't heard
everything I have to say."
Don't shut the door on me.
All right, all right, he's home.
Oh, thank God you're here.
What's going on?
I'll tell you what's going on.
Some elderly Negro woman held your
children hostage and robbed you blind.
- What?
- Betty.
She robbed a bunch of places
in the building, and she came in here.
Our back door was open.
She said she was your mother.
We think we caught her boarding the I.R.T.
You'll need to come down
in the next 24 hours and I.D. your things.
Because no one was here.
Because she's off
on the casting couch and you're-
What does he tell everybody?
That he's at work?
This is not the time or the place
for this conversation.
Ma'am, this could have happened to anyone.
Anyone who lives
in this disgusting city...
and leaves their three children alone.
Do you know Henry's running for office?
Sally, I'm really sorry.
I should have been home earlier.
I want to go home.
You get your hands off me!
I don't need to be manhandled!
- I know you've been holding out on me.
- You don't know anything.
- I defy your accusations.
- You peddle that ass on the street.
You don't deserve a home.
You don't deserve me.
Yeah? I do fine without you.
And you owe me money,
not the other way around.
- Get out.
- 'Cause I took that boy's cherry.
$5.00, we'll call it even.
- Is that true?
- No.
You filthy, shameful,
disgusting, shameful, horrible-
You're trash!
You are filth! You know that you are!
After I gave you a home...
you go and do something this disgraceful!
I know you're exhausted,
but I could feel the floor swimming too...
when I came home to that.
I'm surprised we didn't all faint.
I'm really sorry.
Sally seems so grown up,
but she's really still a kid.
- How are you?
- Busy.
You should talk to him.
Hello?
I just wanted to call
and tell you I'm okay.
I didn't have a heart attack.
I've just been working too much.
I'm- I'm so embarrassed.
I acted like a stupid little kid.
No, you didn't.
And I'm sure she's fooled
plenty of adults too.
She said she knew you.
I asked her everything I know...
and she had an answer for everything.
Then I realized I don't know
anything about you.
Mr. Chaough wants to see you.
You did everything right.
Try and forget about it.
Okay.
- Bye.
- Sally.
I left the door open.
It was my fault.
Okay. Bye.
I need to talk to you.
Morning, fellas.
I'm fine. Thank you for asking.
How could you bring
Frank's little girl here?
I let her tag along.
I kept an eye on her, didn't I, Don?
- Who?
- Wendy.
Believe me, it's a lot better than
what could have happened...
if I had let her loose
in the Village like she wanted.
Well, that's not what her mother thinks.
What the hell went on here this weekend?
Half of this work is gibberish.
"Chevy" is spelled wrong.
Look, I am going to continue on Chevy
in my function as creative director.
That is, evaluating other people's work.
That's all I can do right now.
Call me around 1970
when they're ready to make an ad.
What are you talking about?
I can't do this by myself.
I'm sorry, Ted.
But every time we get a car
this place turns into a whorehouse.