- Morning.
- Don.
Can I have a moment?
I know you're deciding who's gonna be
on Sunkist, so I wanted to volunteer.
You want to go?
You know that's a demotion.
You'll be in one room
with one account.
Thought about that, but rather than
just being a satellite office...
I was thinking I could
turn it into a little agency.
Los Angeles is not what
you see in the movies.
It's like Detroit with palm trees.
So it's the frontier.
I don't even need running water.
Just let me set up the homestead.
You think you're asking for a promotion...
but if you fail there,
you'll be out of advertising...
because no one takes it seriously.
All I'm saying is that
I think it'd be exciting...
to build one desk into a real business.
That's not the way I saw it.
That's not the way you saw me.
And you're gonna change that.
I've always felt you learn more from
disappointment than you do from success.
Well, I suppose I'm becoming
a very wise man.
- Hello, Daddy.
- How are you doing, sweetie?
Oh? Well.
He did get my good side.
He made it for his generous Pop Pop.
Why don't we take you to lunch?
Come on, honey,
I've taken up enough of Dad's time.
I wanted to say thank you...
but obviously that would be premature.
It's time to take a breather.
It's prudent investing, it's not personal.
No, it is personal. I'm your daughter.
What do I have to do to get on the list
of girls you give money to?
- Honey.
- Don't be a brat.
Brooks won't say it,
but you're taking food out of our mouths.
Don't even bother to come to Thanksgiving.
The table will be empty.
Stop it. I'll buy a turkey.
Sir, she doesn't mean it.
Mr. Cosgrove is here.
Send him in.
- Name a chocolate.
- What? Like Hershey's?
Kenny, there's a reason I'm standing here.
Hershey's Chocolate sent an RFP out
to the top 30 agencies...
and all anyone seems to care about
is that we're in the top 30.
Because Hershey's isn't serious.
They don't advertise. They never have.
Mars bills at 10 million.
We think Hershey's is asking for someone
to talk them into that.
What did Ted say?
He said his plate is full
and yours isn't.
But if you want to take the lead on this,
I think he'll follow.
I love Hershey's. Get me in a room.
I'll get you what they sent me.
How's the Motor City?
I found a deli,
but the airport's like Calcutta.
Should be easier once I get an apartment
and stop commuting.
- It's a hell of an account.
- Don't I know it.
You're back in one piece.
Oh, one bigger piece.
I'm putting on weight.
- No one can see it.
- What's that?
- It's a racehorse.
- It's for Kevin.
Don't do that.
He's just gonna want a real one.
We'll see. They just gave Bob one.
Well, you know what
they say about Detroit.
It's all fun and games
till they shoot you in the face.
Aren't we going to have dinner?
Eventually.
I'm worried. Now they sent a letter.
Sally has to call them.
I'll talk to her at Thanksgiving.
I told you. We just have the boys.
Miss Porter's doesn't have
Thanksgiving vacation.
I read the letter.
The next step's a subpoena.
Okay.
Hello.
You can have one.
Then we're having dinner.
Sounds like a plan.
Could you get Bob Benson for me?
Bob Benson's here to see you.
Really? Send him in.
Were you circling my office?
- I don't understand.
- Sit down.
It occurred to me that you haven't had
a performance review.
Yes, I did.
Didn't Mr. Cutler tell you-
I don't give a shit.
You have a hand on every rung, don't you?
I don't think I know
what you're talking about.
What are you doing
buying presents for that kid?
Leading that woman on?
That's another man's kid. You know that?
I assure you, I'm not involved with Joan.
We're just buddies.
Joan's known for having a lot of buddies.
They go fishing together.
What does this have to do
with my performance?
I'm asking the questions here.
I see what you're up to.
Look, I know that you're concerned
with your career...
and Chevy's counting on you
being a family man...
but playing with Mrs. Harris's feelings
is not the right way to go about it.
You're right.
Damn it, Bob, I better not be.
I'm keeping an eye on you.
I appreciate your candor.
I'm looking forward to having you
out in Detroit, Bob.
Yes, sir. Thank you.
This is Sally Draper speaking.
It's Daddy.
What do you want?
I wanted to wish you a happy Thanksgiving.
Okay. I have to go.
Also, I'm calling because...
well, I know it's unpleasant...
but you have to give a statement
regarding the burglar.
You need to make arrangements
to be out of classes December 1.
My calendar's full.
Honey, you have to. It's the law.
Well, I wouldn't want
to do anything immoral.
You know what?
Why don't you just tell them what I saw?
Hello?
I've got it, Moira.
I have a personal plea.
Is this about Hershey again?
No, the folks from
Sheraton are in the lobby.
Royal Hawaiian. We can't find Draper.
Again?
You don't have to listen,
but I have to say it.
We're all brothers in Christ.
That's His gift to us.
We're talking about a fellowship
far more powerful than drink.
Can you keep it down? I'm trying to drink.
What's your occupation, young man?
Staying out of people's business.
You're not doing a very good job of it.
I didn't mean to engage you.
But you did.
'Cause something's on your mind.
You need to talk.
I don't.
What if I told you that Jesus
could offer you not only eternal life...
but freedom from pain in this life?
I'm doing just fine.
Nixon's the president.
Everything's back where Jesus wants it.
He doesn't work that way.
'Cause He's mysterious.
He offer the same deal to Kennedy?
Martin Luther King?
Vietnam, for Christ's sake?
Studies show Jesus had a... bad year.
Well, I'm afraid there's not one true
believer in that list.
What the hell did you just say?
I told you before to get out
and not come back.
- Be on your way.
- This is a house of sin.
You can't keep these girls
from the righteous path.
- They belong to the Lord.
- You're wrong on that.
You love the Bible
'cause you can't get your dick hard.
Repentance is your salvation.
I'd tell you to go to hell, but I never
want to see you again.
The only unpardonable sin
is to believe God cannot forgive you.
Excuse me. Hey.
- I shouldn't be in here.
- You're right.
You punched a minister.
You should be in Rikers.
Sleep it off.
Absolutely not!
You'll have candy at the theater.
- Oh, hello, Peggy.
- Hello.
Good night.
Come on, boys. Let's go.
Clara, I'm going to give my keys
to the subletter.
Did you get me a room
at the Roosevelt?
Yes, and you just got this telegram.
Open it.
Let's see.
"Need to inform you, mother lost at-"
Oh, my goodness. She fell off a ship!
What?
Get Bud on the phone.
I assume this has something
to do with last night.
Yes.
Megan, I-
Come over here.
Where were you?
I spent the night in jail.
Why are you laughing?
Because I realized...
it's gotten out of control.
I've gotten out of control.
Sorry you had to find out that way.
But I realized something else too.
I don't want to be here anymore.
- It'll get easier.
- No.
I want to move to California.
What?
I don't want you to give up your career.
I don't want you to think that.
I just can't be in New York anymore.
I want to move to LA.
I don't-
I don't know what to say.
There have been all these
opportunities in Hollywood...
but I never even considered it...
because I thought it
would make you go crazy.
But- I mean, wouldn't it?
What would you do out there?
Sunkist wants us to have someone local.
It would be like having my own shop.
A small team, a desk...
windows, some sunlight, the ocean.
You'd throw everything away here.
No.
It's an opportunity to build one desk...
into an agency.
We'd be homesteaders.
Really, Don?
What about the kids?
I'm sure they'd trade weekends
for a whole summer in LA.
We were happy there.
We could be happy again.
Is that a yes?
This was to be a junior position.
Look, I'm the search party,
and I decided we were thinking too small.
Well, I think we can spare you.
I apologize for Sheraton, Ted.
That won't happen again.
That's my recommendation.
Of course I welcome a vote on the matter.
How is it every decision
made in this place...
is subject to 10 opinions unless it's him?
What if we need him here?
It's California, not the moon.
There are telephones and airplanes.
You're already doing the heavy lifting.
This is good for you, Ted.
Honestly, I have
bigger problems than this.
Dawn, could you bring me
a carton of cigarettes?
You didn't think ahead.
You let her go, and yet
you still need something.
- She's not going anywhere.
- But you are.
California, here you come.
You probably dictated the memo right to her
and had no idea she'd be affected.
Hold on a second.
I was gonna talk to you.
Really? Why? You don't owe me anything.
I can probably get you
out there eventually.
To work for you?
Nah, I'd rather stay here.
Where are you going?
I'm gonna have that sandwich on my desk.
I need to get to it before you do.
Are you kidding me? They got married?
What the hell was he even doing there?
You should really get going.
You tell those Panamanian criminals they
should put Manolo under house arrest!
Or ship's arrest or whatever it's called.
Fine, the brig. Do whatever it takes.
- What's wrong?
- Get me Bob Benson this minute.
He was waiting for you.
You're late for your flight to Detroit.
Hold that.
- How are you?
- Not great, Bob.
- What's wrong?
Don't play dumb.
You don't know that your boyfriend Manolo
kidnapped my mother...
married her at gunpoint,
then threw her off a ship?
Slow down. I know you're exaggerating,
and you're being hostile.
If you want to run, I'd do it now.
Because you're an accessory to murder!
I will never, ever let this go.
Manny wouldn't hurt a fly.
Even if he thought it was rich?
I swear I knew nothing about this.
Ignorance will not be
a very good defense.
Get your own cab.
I'm leaving a little early
because I have plans.
I hope that's okay.
Yes, of course, dear.
Chanel No. 5?
It's all I wear.
Vixen by night.
I'm very excited to see the scale model.
And I'm even more excited
to go to the London Chop House.
Bob loves it.
Well, unfortunately
Bob's not feeling well.
Pete, have you seen this beauty?
No, not in the flesh.
- That's a Camaro Z28. Am I wrong?
- No, you are not.
I like a man with gasoline in his veins.
You've got to try it.
We can't do that in here.
I did. Last week.
Shit, it's our floor.
We can do whatever the hell we want.
Keys are under the visor.
Go to town.
Bobby, you like to get
into trouble, don't you?
It's standard.
So is the solid-lifter 302 V-8.
Listen to that music.
That's good enough for me.
Ah, take it out. Come on, boys, back up.
You looking for first?
It's written right on there.
I got it, Bob.
Jesus, you can't drive a stick?
We'll pay for that.
What are you doing here?
Waiting for you.
I told your neighbors I was a cop.
You should go home before they kill you.
I need to talk to you.
How was your date?
Is that why you're here?
I just want to know.
You didn't bring him home.
It was terrible, okay?
He works in finance
and ate with his hands.
Not that it's any of your business.
I don't know what we're doing.
You don't know?
Why don't you have your wife
drop by again? I'd love that.
She came in with the kids.
Why did she give me that look
on the way out?
Did you tell her something?
Do you two talk about me?
I don't know why women do anything.
Why did you parade your ass
in front of my door...
on your way out to see another man?
I'm following your lead, Ted.
You let Don terrify you into ignoring me,
and now you're here.
Because I don't want
anyone else to have you.
You should go.
Peggy, I'm going to leave my wife.
Don't say that.
I'm not that girl.
I love you.
Hello?
I just got off the phone
with Miss Porter's.
Sally's been suspended.
What did she do?
She bought beer using
the name "Beth Francis"...
with a false ID she'd made.
Kids do things, Betty.
At least they didn't kick her out.
Henry's already in Albany.
I'm supposed to join him tomorrow.
I know you're picking
the boys up Thanksgiving Day...
but could you go get her tomorrow?
They're holding her in the infirmary.
I don't want to have this conversation
with my mother-in-law.
I can't, Betty. I have a big meeting.
She was drunk.
And she got other girls drunk.
I've done everything I can think to do,
everything my own mother did...
and it doesn't matter.
The good is not beating the bad.
She obviously needs
more than I can give her.
Birdie, this isn't your fault.
Don, she's from a broken home.
Pauline doesn't need to know.
I'll come get them Thanksgiving morning,
and then I'll come get her.
Okay.
I'm sorry.
Is everything okay?
No.
Is there anything I can do?
Let's go to Hawaii.
For work?
For Christmas.
We'll come back with tans.
You should probably go home.
I don't want to.
I can say I worked late on Hershey.
Don't you always go home, though?
I don't want to sneak around.
I promise we won't have to.
I don't want a scandal.
I can wait.
Go.
No, you should go.
Oh, good, you're home.
Yeah, I didn't want to wake you.
- Oh, come to bed.
- Okay.
Oh, sweetheart, you're working too hard.
What are you doing back?
- You haven't heard?
- Heard what?
I need a place to live.
I spoke with the GM
personnel department.
No, here in New York.
I'm done in Detroit,
and the tenant's already moved in.
Oh.
Your brother's been trying
desperately to reach you.
Did they find her?
Well, let him know I'm back.
I'm gonna be gone for a couple of hours.
Roger needs me to go to the bank
before the holiday.
You want someone on his desk?
I'm not sure he's coming in.
I'm worried about him.
What's wrong?
For one thing, Margaret and the son-in-law
are bleeding him dry.
Trust me. He loves it.
Well, he's forlorn. I'd invite him
to my place for Thanksgiving...
but Ralph stopped drinking
and you know little Ralphie's spastic.
I think both are too much for him.
Mr. Draper.
Mr. Chaough's here to see you.
Send him in.
- I need to talk to you.
- I was thinking the same thing.
You should come to Hershey's
since I'm going to California.
That's not why I'm here.
Do you want something?
No, thank you.
I don't know how to say this,
but I want to go to California.
Really? We can't both go.
I know.
I want you to stay here.
You put all that energy and optimism
back into the business...
and let me go out there.
I'm the one who needs to start over.
With Peggy?
No, with my family.
I don't understand.
Yes, you do.
It's my only chance, Don.
I've got kids.
I can't throw this away. I can't-
I can't go on like this.
I'm sorry, Ted. I wish I could help you.
I don't know what I brought out in you...
but I know
there's a good man in there.
I need you to help me
put 3,000 miles between me and her...
or my life is over.
I didn't make my decision lightly.
I need it too.
And, frankly,
they're writing my wife off her show.
It's too late, Ted.
It will go away.
Will you have a drink before the meeting?
My father was-
You can't stop cold like that.
Every agency you're going to meet with
feels qualified to advertise the Hershey bar...
because the product itself is one of
the most successful billboards of all time.
And its relationship with America
is so overwhelmingly positive...
that everyone in this room
has their own story to tell.
It could be rations in the heat of battle
or in the movie theater on a first date.
But most of them are from childhood.
Mine was my father...
taking me to the drugstore
after I'd mowed the lawn...
and telling me I could
have anything I wanted.
Anything at all. And there was a lot.
But I picked a Hershey bar.
The wrapper looked like what was inside.
And as I ripped it open,
my father tousled my hair and forever...
his love and the chocolate
were tied together.
That's the story we're going to tell.
Hershey's is the currency of affection.
It's the childhood symbol of love.
Well, weren't you a lucky little boy?
Our company excels in television...
and we'll tell you exactly when and where
to tell those stories.
Sweet tales of childhood.
I suppose we'd start with yours.
You can't just have that.
You got to pay us first.
And that's what's so exciting.
I'm sorry. I have to say this...
'cause I don't know
if I'll ever see you again.
What?
I was an orphan.
I grew up in Pennsylvania...
in a whorehouse.
I read about Milton Hershey
and his school...
in Coronet magazine or some other crap
the girls left by the toilet.
And I read that some orphans...
had a different life there.
I could picture it. I dreamt of it-
Of being wanted.
Because the woman
who was forced to raise me...
would look at me every day
like she hoped I would disappear.
Closest I got to feeling wanted
was from a girl...
who made me go through
her johns's pockets while they screwed.
If I collected more than a dollar,
she'd buy me a Hershey bar.
And I would eat it... alone,
in my room...
with great ceremony...
feeling like a normal kid.
It said "sweet" on the package.
It was the only sweet thing in my life.
Do you want to advertise that?
If I had my way,
you would never advertise.
You shouldn't have someone like me
telling that boy what a Hershey bar is.
He already knows.
Don's being modest.
But it's just this kind of theater that
makes our work so different.
Well, that's quite a story.
It was a pleasure meeting you.
We'd love to have a meal...
stop you from going to
some of these other meetings.
Ted?
- It was a pleasure.
- Yes.
You're going to California.
Are you sure?
I want you to.
Thank you.
Dawn, get my things.
You know, you shit the bed in there.
- I don't care.
- Was any of that true?
Yes. I have to go home.
Happy Thanksgiving, sweetheart.
You, too, Mr. Draper.
It occurred during
the roaring '20s dinner dance...
so your mother likely went
missing over the promenade.
It's the only way
she wouldn't have hit a deck below.
No, where was the boat?
Oh, somewhere off the coast of Martinique.
Did they check the beaches?
- First of all, there are a lot of sharks.
- Dear Lord.
As I said, there's no impetus for either
government to investigate...
and the SS Sunset Princess in
contacting you has fulfilled its obligation.
It's 1968.
Surely you're not telling me...
there's still some international oceanic
limbo where murder is smiled upon.
I have a private investigator
prepared to board the ship...
and locate your mother's husband-
well, nurse-
Manolo Colón, alias Marcus Constantine.
We also have wheels
we can grease in Panama.
No stone unturned, no expense spared.
Let's say we want
the very best of everything.
- What are the expenses?
- To bring your mother's killer to justice?
Ballpark.
It may take time.
Now that Manolo's aware of her limited
financial resources, he may bolt.
Alvin, I have another call coming in.
Can we continue this later?
When you think about it...
it won't bring her back.
She's in the water with Father.
She loved the sea.
I didn't want to disturb you.
What happened?
I don't even know how to say this.
Did you tell Nan?
Did you confess? I told you to wait.
No, that's-
I'm going to California.
You can stay here and have your life
and your career and let this be the past.
I can't believe Don did this.
I knew he wasn't going.
He knows it's Siberia. I can undo this.
No, Peggy.
He gave up his spot for me.
Don?
I wanted this so much,
but I have a family.
The world out there-
I have to hold onto them
or I'll get lost in the chaos.
Oh.
You have to listen to me.
I love you that deeply.
I can't be around you.
And I can't ruin all those lives.
Get out. Just get out!
Someday you'll be glad
I made this decision.
Well, aren't you lucky...
to have decisions?
Dawn just called.
She said there's a partners' meeting
tomorrow about California.
Attendance is mandatory. 9:00.
You have a meeting on Thanksgiving.
They must really want us out of here fast.
Honey.
- You have to sit down.
- Why?
Because something came up.
And it's not just Sally, it's-
It's what?
I'm sorry, but we can't
go to California right now.
No. Don, that's-
That's not possible
because I already told Mel...
and Jeff Hunter's got me a bunch of
meetings out there...
- and the train is leaving the station.
- The agency decided that-
Fuck the agency! I quit my job!
Megan.
You know what?
I don't even know
why we're fighting for this anymore.
I don't know what it is.
We don't have any kids.
You want to be alone with your liquor
and your ex-wife and your screwed-up kids.
Don't say that.
I love them to death.
I used to feel pity for them...
but now I realize
we're all in the same boat.
I know you're upset.
But I'm gonna be
out there all the time with you.
We'll be bicoastal.
Megan, I love you.
I can't do this.
I can't be here right now.
They'll deliver the lowboy
and the china closet next Friday.
I couldn't take any more and I already
look like the Beverly Hillbillies...
with the chair tied to the roof.
I don't want your mother's things, Peter.
Well, Bud's not getting everything.
And I'm not moving
everything to California with me.
It's fine. I'll manage.
When are you leaving for your parents'?
When Tammy finishes her nap.
When are you leaving for Los Angeles?
Soon as I can.
I'd invite you, but I think it's best
you're alone right now.
Don't be cruel.
No.
It's going to take you
a moment to realize where you are.
You're free.
Free of her. You're free of them.
You're free of everything.
It's not the way I wanted it.
Now you know that.
Can I go in and say good-bye?
I won't wake her.
I was told 9:00.
Right on time. Impressive.
Don, we need to have a serious conversation.
Where would you like to do it?
Is this about the Hershey meeting
yesterday? Because I can explain.
Well, unfortunately, that meeting...
and most of your questionable behavior
is beyond explanation.
Should I sit down?
Yes.
I'm not going to defend myself.
I've tolerated plenty
from every one of you.
Don, there's no need for defense.
This isn't a trial.
The verdict has been reached.
So what time did this meeting start?
We think it's best for you and the firm
if you take some time off and regroup.
- How much time?
- A few months.
But the holidays are coming.
That will take up most of it.
Did you tell Ted?
'Cause he can't go to California if
there's no one here to run New York.
Ted feels confident
he can oversee Peggy from LA.
He knows it's temporary.
I want a return date.
We can't give you that.
You all agree with this?
Try and see it from our side.
- Good morning.
- Hello, Don.
You're early.
Sorry about that, old chum.
This is Lou Avery from Dancer Fitzgerald.
We've met.
Going down?
What's that?
We couldn't send it back.
- Hey.
- What?
Happy holidays.
What's he doing here?
I'm inviting you into Kevin's life,
not mine.
Okay.
Hi, Bob.
Mom, Roger's here.
Gail got her hair done for you.
Hello, little man.
- You ready for some turkey?
- Yes.
Here, let me get it for you.
I thought you left.
No, I've got too much to do.
And you thought you'd do it in here?
It's where everything is.
See you Monday.
Did they name it "Hershey's"
because of the chocolate...
or is the chocolate named after the city?
There was a man named Hershey.
He made enough chocolate to build a town.
Why are we stopping?
This is a bad neighborhood.
Come on.
This is where I grew up.