It tastes better
because it's more expensive.
It's the premium brand
and it's priced accordingly.
Price is irrelevant because the question is,
does it taste better than butter?
Butter is actually fresh.
Margarine is indestructible.
He's right because he's only comparing
different margarines...
and margarine
has a 70% market share over butter.
But it's hard to say
any brand is luxury...
when although Fleischmann's
is the most expensive...
and Blue Bonnet, owned by the same
company, is the least expensive...
the difference is only pennies.
Forty-five cents a pound is the highest.
Twenty-nine is the lowest.
That's 50% more expensive.
Fleischmann's is Chivas Regal.
Still half the price of butter.
It's Budweiser.
But what's the market share?
I just said it's much higher than butter.
Seeing as I have the ear of the client...
it's my recommendation
we go on taste alone.
Peggy!
Don, I agree with you.
You're in the market buying margarine.
Okay.
What goes through your mind?
Mouthwatering, savory, delicious taste?
Or mouthwatering, savory,
delicious taste and price?
I'd buy the cheaper one.
There's one for 45 cents a pound
and one for 29.
Which one do you think
is gonna taste better?
It's a terrible gamble to tell a client
that their product is expensive.
Shh. Let her answer.
I don't know.
They both sound good.
Really?
Does everyone agree with yours?
It's not his and mine.
Everyone has an opinion.
We haven't heard it, but I'm sure they do.
I like Don's.
What did Harry say?
I feel strongly both ways.
They're both so good.
I'd probably ask someone to run them
by the client on the sly.
The meeting's tomorrow.
You know what, Don? Let's go with yours.
Nah, I'm not even gonna be there.
You should go with
whatever you're most comfortable with.
Could you get me another
copy of that research?
I want to make it big on a board.
Did you see that?
He didn't even turn around.
- Yep.
- Oh, it speaks.
I wasn't gonna get in the middle of that.
You suddenly dumber than Peggy?
So you're content in silence?
I'm content with reality.
You know what this place looks like
to the outside world?
A mess.
We don't even have a name.
- We're the '27 Yankees.
- Says who?
Pete, you want to get your balls tickled?
Go see a headhunter.
Are you leaving?
Look, when things settle down,
I'm gonna be a partner.
For the time being, it's nice to know that
the water's warm out there.
Did you lose something?
Yes.
I was looking for-
How do you say? A pen
to write something down.
Oh. Well, the desk is littered with them.
Would you like a drink?
Certainly, Colette.
Although this is my husband's office.
I should be offering you one.
- It is no trouble at all.
- We're a lot alike.
We're both interested
in things that belong to me.
I don't know what you're talking about.
I don't know what your relationship
is with my husband, but it's over.
Cut. Let's clean up in there and back up.
Megan, sweetheart,
what are you doing on the floor?
The script said to spill the drink.
It doesn't say to clean it up.
I just thought-
Your sister Corinne is the maid.
You're Colette right now.
She's blonde, classy.
We need you to make
these women different, honey.
Let's take it from the top, ladies.
Don't worry about it.
I think Phyllis left for the day, but I
never saw the boards for tomorrow.
Stan has them.
- What are you working on?
- Royal Hawaiian.
- How's that going?
- I'm sure you will tell me.
I will.
I'll look at it very carefully...
and then I'll formulate
an educated opinion.
You should try it sometime.
It's what professionals do.
Don.
Been debating that for weeks.
You both have a point.
I'm not paying you to be a diplomat.
Well, you're both
more experienced than me.
I don't know that my opinion matters.
Your opinion matters. Now, what do you
think is the best way to go?
- It's somewhere in the middle.
- No, Peggy.
There's a right and there's a wrong.
How could that be?
What you're really saying is
there's you and there's him.
And I don't know how I became in charge of
turning this into a collaboration.
Isn't that your job?
You're both demanding
and you're both pigheaded.
You're the same person sometimes.
The difference is that
he's interested in the idea...
and you're interested in your idea.
He's interested in his idea.
Don't let him fool you.
Well, he never makes me feel this way.
He doesn't know you.
Henry said you were leaving.
He just had to make one phone call,
which turned out to be two.
- Full house, I see.
- He should be off in a minute.
Well, he's a lucky man,
but not as lucky as me...
because I wanted to be
alone with you all night.
He'll be out in a minute.
I don't think you heard.
I want to be alone with you all night.
Mr. Dell, I have three children.
I don't care.
No, look at me.
Can you believe I've had three children?
How was your evening, Stew?
Raised a lot of money.
Darling, shall we?
- What's going on?
- There was an incident.
Oh, my God!
- They hurt you.
- I'm fine, honey.
He was getting off the subway
and two guys stabbed him.
- What?
- Hey, I don't want to worry her, man.
I'm sorry, but I'm trying
to get it straight.
And, frankly, she should know
so she can keep up her defense.
- Jesus! What happened?
- Are we done here?
For a reporter, this is missing detail.
And if you'd waited at the hospital,
as you were instructed, we'd be done.
But for some reason you didn't.
I filled out the form.
Come on. Were they colored
or Puerto Rican?
Or white?
I'm from Brooklyn
and I always keep my eyes down.
Could you describe the shoes?
Look, both of us have done our civic duty.
So, respectfully, I think you should go.
I'd get one of these.
Good evening, ma'am.
Can you believe those questions?
Fascist pig!
Shut up, Abe!
You don't know what they look like?
You have a photographic memory.
Peg, I'm not gonna give him an excuse...
to shake down every kid
that walks through this neighborhood.
What about the one that stabbed you?
This is a fucking police state,
and we're gonna have to fight, okay?
They did it in Prague.
They did it in Paris.
And, believe it or not,
we're gonna have to do it here too.
That doesn't mean protecting criminals.
Listen, baby, it's my right to tell
whomever whatever I want.
But you can keep talking because
everything you say is going in my story.
What are you talking about?
It's just fascinating,
the attitudes I'm encountering.
But why would you side with the cops?
I don't know.
I read about this.
You obviously had a traumatic experience,
not unlike combat.
So I'm going to let you do
whatever you're doing.
Don't patronize me.
Those kids have no other
recourse in this system.
- They're animals.
- They were brought here by slave ships.
Well, I was brought here by you.
I don't care if I take a loss.
I'm gonna sell this shithole.
You're worried about me
and I love you for it.
I don't think I can type with this thing.
Get my Olympia.
Help me get some of this down.
I'm going to bed.
This is nice.
It's Thursday.
Told you I was making dinner.
Sit down.
How was your day?
How was yours?
It was-
Ugh, it was terrible.
I don't even know
if I want to talk about it.
What's for dinner?
- I think they hate me.
- They just gave you a second part.
I feel like an idiot because they keep
telling me they can't tell the twins apart.
I think I'm playing them very differently.
It's not like it's never been done before.
Exactly.
I told Mel I didn't want to be a cliché.
Then he starts rapping about how they're
two halves of the same person...
and they want the same thing, but they're
trying to get it in different ways.
Listen, would you mind
if we just go in and turn on the set?
I'm really not hungry.
Did you have a bad day?
I'm just tired.
Go lie down. I'll clean up.
I already packed your bag
for Bobby's camp.
Tomorrow's another day.
John, could you give us some privacy?
- Was the evening a success?
- You tell me.
Well, I, um-
I found it fascinating, as usual,
watching you work your magic.
And while you were watching me...
everyone was watching you,
weren't they?
Stewart did everything but grab your ass.
I didn't notice.
What did he say to you?
I don't want to get anyone in trouble.
Word for word.
He said he wanted to be alone with me.
What else?
All night.
Daddy, I don't want him
running on the steps.
Why not? Kids are supposed to run.
Ellery, come down.
We don't have any steps in the apartment.
He's not good at them.
So what do you think, girls?
See any resemblance?
He's very handsome.
So, Ellery, take a good look.
Who's your type?
Hello, Margaret.
I'll tell you mine later.
It's nice to see you.
Oh, he's precious. How old is he?
He's four.
He's having a special day with Pop-pop.
We're going to the zoo
and maybe the movies.
So it's just a regular workday.
Don't fill him full of junk.
Can't promise that.
Wave good-bye, swabby.
We're shoving off.
How many times have you met with Harry?
Too many.
Don't waste my time like Crane.
I'm a headhunter, not a fan club.
Fine. Let's talk about me.
Let's talk about Burt Peterson.
I got him a vice presidency
at McCann.
If he keeps his head down,
he's set for life.
But the merger was fresh.
I don't know your situation.
You weren't very straight on the phone.
You think they're gonna cut you loose?
How come you didn't get yourself a job?
That's a Yankee wrinkle.
You interested in my business?
No.
Well, if we sat down
a couple of months ago...
this would have been
a different conversation.
Nothing's changed.
I'll show you my Rolodex.
It's not that. It's your lack of a role
in the management structure.
Sterling Cooper Draper Pryce
Cutler Gleason and Chaough?
Who the hell's in charge?
Two of those men are as dead as doornails.
There's still a lot of chiefs
and only a couple of Indians.
And a lot of questions.
What the hell happened with Vicks?
So... paint me a new portrait.
I'm glad you said that.
How about seeing things
from the client's side?
There's a head of marketing job
in Wichita that you'd be perfect for.
Anything back here on Earth?
You know,
I've always liked you, Campbell...
so forgive me for saying this...
but if you do a little better,
I can do a lot better.
I don't know what else I can do.
I've been you.
And I went on interviews and I realized
I was filling the room with desperation.
Five cents worth of free advice.
You've got to spend
less time in this place and more at home.
This is a reluctant necessity.
My mother's run amok.
Pete, one day I looked in the mirror
and I realized I had regrets...
because I didn't understand
the wellspring of my confidence.
Gin?
My family.
My family is a constant distraction.
You better manage that
or you're not gonna manage anything.
Hey, buddy.
Can you help me?
Uh, I'm occupied at the moment, sir.
Hello there.
Oh. Are you lost too?
Not yet. I'm trying to get some gas.
Lady asked for directions.
Fill 'er up with regular.
Where's Henry?
He's coming tomorrow.
I'm surprised you were able to get away.
Where are you staying?
Somewhere over here.
Just go down here.
Stay on here a mile and a half till you
get to the big mill. Make a left.
Go back through town
till the railroad tracks.
Hang a right over the bridge
and then you come to the little mill.
Do any of the roads have names?
Follow me.
Fleischmann's just called.
See? You were worried for nothing.
Well, they just requested
some more recent figures on market share.
I'll handle it.
Peggy, may I speak with you?
Go ahead.
What the hell were you doing back there?
You didn't want me to talk.
I didn't talk. That was the plan.
Did you want me to talk?
- No. You touched my hand.
- What?
When you handed me the board.
What? No, I didn't.
Yes, you did.
And you can't do that in a presentation.
I doubt anyone saw that
because I didn't even know I did it.
It jarred me. And when I finally
caught up, then you smiled.
You can't smile at me like that.
I never should have kissed you.
I assumed we were forgetting about that.
I forgot it.
Well, I haven't.
Oh.
What an old tune.
The boss in love with his protégé.
Is this all me? Because that'll help.
I think about it.
Well, we can't.
I have someone, you have someone.
And believe me, I've considered it
a lot further than that.
I didn't know you felt this way.
I don't want to. That's the point.
Now I realize I never should
have brought it up.
Do you want me to work someplace else?
No. Of course not.
Come on. You have to do it.
And the left.
Father Abraham
had seven sons
Seven sons
And seven sons
had Father Abraham
Daddy, you came!
You didn't tell him I was here?
I wanted it to be a surprise.
You catch any fish?
Damn it. I made you a wallet,
but it's back in my cabin.
Bobby, language.
We'll get it later.
Mommy said we can have anything we want.
Hi!
This is my mom and dad.
That's Bobby Two. He's shy.
Are you Bobby or Bobby One?
I'm Bobby Five.
It's sad. There's no Bobby One anymore.
Because of Bobby Kennedy?
No. He went home.
Do you want me to get the waitress
so you can get a drink?
- Is that possible?
- No.
Mommy's having a chef salad
and I'm having a cheeseburger.
What do you want so I can order?
- What's good here?
- I'm afraid nothing.
Daddy, I want to teach you this song.
Just do what I do.
Father Abraham had
seven sons, seven sons
And seven sons
had Father Abraham
And they never
laughed, ha ha
And they never cried,
boo-hoo
All they did was go like this
With the right
Father Abraham
had seven sons
Seven sons
had Father Abraham
And they never
laughed, ha ha
And they never cried,
boo-hoo
All they did was go like this,
with the right
Can I walk you out?
Certainly, if you don't mind waiting.
I need your advice.
And, well, it's of a personal nature,
and thus above Clara's security clearance.
How can I help you?
Do you feel my attention to business
has been dilute?
How personal is this conversation?
I'm being pulled in a million directions.
My wife, my child, my mother.
I can't solve those problems, Pete.
I have those problems.
I live with my mother.
Has your mother exhausted
every nursing agency?
No, but she's exhausted me.
Well, the options are my home and a home...
neither of which will make me feel better.
I am sorry to hear that.
- Do you want to get supper?
- I can't. I have plans.
Thank you, Joan.
For what?
I don't know.
Welcome.
Oh, I'm a little damp.
- Did it finally rain?
- No, but I walked.
This was cold when I left.
You walked from the West Side?
What an incredible space.
Did you do this yourself?
Oh, I had a little help.
Arlene, you read about
the shootings in the park, didn't you?
I'm not gonna let a few lunatics
ruin a gorgeous night like this.
Should I go get my script?
Megan, darling...
you're a good actress,
on your way to becoming, well...
at least a successful one.
There's nothing I can tell you
about that script.
I came over here because
I'm worried about you.
Am I gonna get fired?
I remember my first job.
Believe it or not, in radio.
Against the Storm.
Very classy,
a lot of big words, high morals.
And my agent, who I later learned
was angling to sign Roger DeKoven...
told me my voice was childish.
And every day I would vacillate between...
"Arlene, you're wonderful"
and "Arlene, you're caca."
Which was it?
Honestly?
I was wonderful.
You should go inside.
You'll get eaten alive out here.
You know mosquitoes ignore me.
In those shorts?
Did you find a bottle?
Maybe.
Cheers.
I loved camp.
I never went.
Yes, you did.
Remember when we went
to Lake Champlain with my parents?
I remember.
And you got in a horrible fight with my father
about who would carry the luggage.
And then we went in the woods
and made Sally.
I don't understand her.
Henry says she's a lot like you.
How would he know?
He says she reminds him of you.
I think she's a lot like you.
Bobby reminds me of my father.
So bossy.
All the teenagers
of the world are in revolt.
What were we like?
You and me?
When I saw you earlier today,
I thought for a second...
"Who is that man?"
And I forgot how mad I was at you.
I don't know what's happened,
but I'm all bit up.
Close the door. You'll let the bugs in.
What are you doing?
Waiting for you to tell me to stop.
What did you think when you saw me?
That you are as beautiful
as the day I met you.
So finally I said to Mel...
"I'm either his mother or his girlfriend.
I can't be both."
That's bad writing.
You're so lucky he's at work.
Please, dear.
That's a complex relationship.
But he understands what you do...
and he wants you to be great.
And he's always proud of you.
I've seen it.
Don's very proud of you.
You can tell by how protective he is.
It's been so different.
You know, we worked together
and I left to pursue this.
And he was so encouraging.
And then you started succeeding.
He's old-fashioned.
He'll get used to it.
I think he did.
And I think he got used
to me not being around...
and having a bunch of problems
that he couldn't solve.
And I don't know...
if it's him or me, but...
I feel so lonely.
Arlene.
What? I want to make you feel better.
This isn't the way.
Oh, forget it.
I can't believe you.
I'm trusting you and you're taking
advantage of every private moment.
Well, what was I supposed to think?
You invited me over.
Your husband's not here.
Two bottles of wine to go over a scene
a child could understand.
"I'm so lonely."
I work with you
and your husband is my boss.
And now what am I supposed to do?
Am I gonna be punished
for not doing something...
that you won't stop trying to do?
Megan, it's okay to say no,
but you don't have to embarrass me.
I'm sorry.
I didn't mean to.
No, stop it.
You're a tease.
Fine.
No, I'm fine with being a tease.
Well, honey, just learn the lines.
Two characters is tough,
but you know what Olivier says.
"Let the wig do the work."
I'm gonna go before I-
Well, it's too late for that, isn't it?
Thank you for that.
No hard feelings.
Everything as it was.
I missed you.
Do you feel guilty?
No.
This happened a long time ago.
Ugh, menthols.
I don't miss that.
Is this what it would have been like
if we'd stayed together?
I don't think about that anymore.
I'm happy in my life.
Let's just enjoy this.
But you used to?
What are you thinking right now?
I'm thinking about how different you are,
before and after.
I love the way you look at me
when you're like this.
But then I watch it decay.
I can only hold your attention so long.
Why is sex the definition
of being close to someone?
I don't know, but it is for me.
It is for most people.
Just because you climb a mountain
doesn't mean you love it.
Climbing a mountain.
Is that what making love is to you?
If we'd lied here together
with you in my arms...
I would have felt just as close.
But the rest of it- I don't know.
I don't know.
It doesn't mean that much to me.
Is it the same with Megan?
Why do you want to talk about that?
That poor girl.
She doesn't know that loving you
is the worst way to get to you.
Are you sure you don't
want to just hold me?
Oh, Jesus.
Oh, thank God. What are you doing in here?
I was just fixing the window.
What the hell happened here?
I'll replace it tomorrow
when I get back from work.
Because you're leaving me here after
someone threw a rock through our window?
That's not what happened.
Well, I came in here and there's glass
all over the floor...
and you're holding a rock.
I'm tired of being interrogated
in my own home.
Do you think they saw you
talking to the police?
If you're gonna let your imagination run
wild, come to the paper with me tonight.
Abe, I have to go to work tomorrow.
And this is our bedroom.
Someone was in our yard.
I'm really scared here.
And you're going to protect me?
You only have one hand.
You're right.
We'll start looking. Put it on the market.
You'd really do that for me?
Maybe we're not cut out to be pioneers.
Sleep in the parlor if you're worried.
I won't wake you.
Hello?
You took a four-year-old
to see Planet of the Apes?
He's been having nightmares all night.
Hold on. Hold on.
He wanted to see that.
He doesn't decide that.
Well, Don took his kid.
Don Draper, Father of the Year.
Margaret, honey, he loved it.
Put him on. I'll do Dr. Zaius again.
He laughs like an idiot.
The Forbidden Zone was once a paradise.
You're not funny, Daddy.
We'll probably have to get rid of the dog-
he's that afraid of fur.
Listen, I saw The Golem
when I was his age.
You don't even know what scary is.
I was fine. It's not my fault.
Yeah, you're right. It's my fault.
For letting you talk me into having a
four-year-old watch another four-year-old.
Listen to me, young lady.
You calm down this minute.
No, Daddy, you listen to me.
You can keep up your fantasy
of acting like a father...
but your grandfather days are done.
I'm sorry you're upset. I'm coming over.
- I'll calm him down.
- No.
And call Mother next time you want to see
him, 'cause she has to be there.
- Morning.
- Good morning.
Good to see you.
It's such a project going to the beach.
Can I go get Kevin?
Let him sleep a little more.
I'd love to get one
of those summer rentals.
Doesn't Pete Campbell have a beach house?
I wouldn't ask him for anything.
Don't you like him?
It's not that.
Actually, he's the only person there
who's never broken a promise to me.
He's a very generous person.
And frankly, I think
he's having a rough time.
So he told you about his mother?
No, I wish he would have. What's wrong?
He needs a nurse.
He's not gonna ask you. He's too ashamed.
She back from the track already?
Ugh. She must have forgotten her keys.
Oh. Hello, Roger.
- Who are you?
- It's me, Bob Benson.
From the office.
What are you doing here?
Oh, I was, uh, out shopping...
and I realized I had misplaced
some paperwork.
And I, uh-
What are you two doing?
We're leaving for the beach.
- I should go get the car.
- Good idea.
No, Mr. Sterling is just leaving.
Roger, I'm sure this can wait till Monday.
Sure, absolutely. Sorry about that, Bob.
I guess we're all a little bit
out of context right now.
I take no offense.
Didn't know you were friends.
Some people never stop working.
I'm going to freshen up
and we'll get out of here.
It's our block! Get outta here!
Get out!
What's going on?
Oh, my God! Oh, my God!
Jesus!
Why didn't you say something?
- What do I do?
- Don't pull it out.
- If I don't make it-
- Stop it.
You're going to make it.
He's going to make it.
Look, I don't want you to think
this is about what you did.
It was an accident. I feel horrible.
No, you're scared.
You're a scared person
who hides behind complacenc-
cy.
Save your strength.
You're not making any sense.
I don't know why
I thought you'd be braver.
You're... in advertising.
Don't do this right now.
I said I was sorry.
Your activities are offensive
to my every waking moment.
I'm sorry.
But you'll always be the enemy.
Are you breaking up with me?
Gotta hand it to you.
You gave me a great ending to my article.
Oh, you're back.
Did you have fun?
I missed you.
Well, I miss you all the time.
I don't know when I started pretending
like everything was sunny.
I don't know where you've gone,
but I'm here.
I keep trying to make things the way
they used to be, but I don't know how.
And maybe that's stupid
or young to think like that, but...
something has to change.
Megan.
You're right.
I haven't been here.
Roger, please.
Come on. Just take it.
They're Lincoln Logs.
I thought maybe
he'd build his mother a house.
You can't drop in on me like that.
But I want to.
Oh, Roger, I'm so sorry,
but you can't do this.
Why not?
Because it's too confusing.
For Kevin. You know.
But I'm his father.
No, his father is Greg.
But I'm here.
For now.
But every day Greg is some hero out there...
and I'd rather him think
that is the man in his life.
Who's gonna watch TV with him?
Bob "Bunson"?
I just want to be around.
I know you want to.
But I can't count on that.
Thank you for the gift.
Something delicate
has come to my attention.
Have a seat.
I, uh- I've really debated
whether to bring this up with you...
because I don't want to put you
in a strange position...
and in the end it's probably just gossip.
It's come to my attention...
that you may be in need
of a nurse for your mother.
Joan had no right to tell you that.
His name is Manolo Colón.
He's an army-trained registered nurse,
and he's available now only because...
he's brought my father
back to full health.
Is he Spanish from Spain?
Because otherwise Mother will refuse.
He's very well-bred.
And don't blame Joan.
She was concerned about you
and had exhausted her resources...
and is well aware that your well-being
is also an interest of mine.
Good morning.
- Is he in?
- Yes, just a minute.
It's okay.
Hi. Good morning.
Good morning.
I just wanted to-
I needed to talk to you.
Peggy, what's wrong?
I, uh-
Abe got stabbed.
My goodness.
Is he okay? What happened?
He's going to be fine.
But it's over.
We're done.
I'm sorry to hear that.
You are?
You'll find someone else.
And whoever he is, he's lucky to have you.
Thank you.
You ready to get to work?
Excuse me?
It's Monday morning, Peggy.
Brand-new week.
Morning. How was your weekend?
How'd it go with Fleischmann's?
They just called. Full speed ahead.
Good work.
Round up the team.