Here we go.
The one with the fur.
You know, I might just take you up
on those theater tickets.
- You must see Hair.
- Oh, you like that?
- Who doesn't?
- What is it?
Oh, it's just filled with profanity...
marijuana smoking,
and simulated sexual acts.
Simulated?
And a few songs.
The two holiday chairmanships that remain
are the Fourth of July block party...
which really consists of
calling the fire department...
or the Labor Day Soap Box Derby,
which consists of calling the hospital.
Which one do you do?
Our family has claimed
the Easter egg hunt.
Do you dress as a bunny?
Maybe a little cottontail?
It's very wholesome.
Mmm.
I'd like to surprise Doug
for his birthday.
Maybe you could get me
the tickets in secret.
Arrangements could be made.
Just pick a date and ring me up.
I have to warn you,
I'm from a small town...
and all of my forays into Manhattan
have been a disaster.
We'll make a deal.
Brave your way to Grand Central...
and I'll hand off the tickets
and throw in a hot dog.
You have another one of those?
But you've already seen Hair.
Maybe I want to see it again.
Oh, there you are.
Gentlemen, it's been a pleasure.
Thank you both for your hospitality.
- Thank you again.
- It was lovely.
Consider what I said about the pool.
That is the end of the welcome wagon.
We'll basically have to move to get
someone to make dinner for us.
What was that about the pool?
He's insistent we all go skinny-dipping.
Ha! Let him get his own pool.
- Turn it off.
- ... under almost constant enemy shelling...
since ground attacks
commenced on January 2 1.
Turning now to North Korea,
the Pueblo situation-
I need to put it in the mail today
and the tailor.
Sylvia, sweetheart-
Good morning.
- Morning.
- Honey.
- Oh, I'm sorry.
I'll swing by the bank at lunch.
I give her cash every month...
but I think she's secretly
sending it all to our kid.
You don't have to explain anything.
You're lucky your wife works.
- She doesn't earn much.
- Not yet.
I forgot my cigarettes.
You got to stop that nonsense.
Listen, don't worry about dinner Wednesday.
We'll have money by then.
Looking forward to it.
I knew it'd be you.
It wasn't all bad. I got me some memories.
And the boy.
Don't know what it is yet.
I mean Dick here.
Well, hello there.
This is Mack.
He's with me, so he's your uncle.
We thank the Lord
for opening your rooms to us.
All I said was,
"My sister's coming with her boy."
Mack's the one that brung ya.
I'd do the same for mine.
And, of course, Ernestine told you we could
always use a little help around here.
Let's get you off your feet.
Dick, you help Mack with the bags.
You keep your eyes down
and mind your own business here.
Good-looking kid. He yours?
Not that I know.
Little boy, find your own sins.
Stay away from Mack's.
Afternoon, Charlotte.
Hey, kid, you were raised
on a farm. Am I right?
Yes, sir.
Well, I'm the rooster around here,
understand?
You help all the hens?
And I'll bring on the day.
I feel bad.
You should. I have to go to work.
You get to sleep.
No, about dinner.
I thought there was no smoking.
I just found out the maid smokes.
She doesn't sleep in here, does she?
You don't mind sitting across the table
from your wife and my husband?
I don't think about it.
They're both good company.
They are.
I suppose that has nothing
to do with this.
This didn't happen.
Just in here.
You're right.
Every hour on the hour,
WQXR brings you the latest news-
I only said yes
because Arnold wants to impress you.
because Megan keeps asking.
- She likes you.
- And I like her.
Vietcong raiders drove into the center of
seven major Vietnamese cities early today...
burning government buildings,
freeing prisoners from provincial jails...
and blasting military installations
and airfields.
It's 9:00. I have to go.
You love to go.
Well, it's nice to know
that no matter what...
we got something done today.
You found it in the cookie jar.
I have money. I just never have money.
The earliest attack took place at Da Nang,
the second-largest city in the country...
and the base area of military operations-
Mr. Mathis and Mr. Gifford
are waiting outside.
Why didn't you tell me?
Because they don't want to come in.
Look, Phyllis, I've had their job.
I know.
And you've had my job too.
So you know it wouldn't hurt
if you were to act like-
if you were as encouraging
to them as you are to me.
Just get me whatever book you read
and save me these little lectures.
More coffee?
She's ready for you.
Have a seat.
- No, don't.
- What's wrong with them?
The strategy is, Clearasil stops blemishes
that keep you from having fun.
That means no one should be having fun.
Okay. So we'll just start over.
Just a minute.
I don't want you to think
that just because I have high standards...
that means I'm not happy with you.
Especially, you know, the way you are.
The way you are has nothing to do
with the fact that the work needs work.
Thank you, Coach. We'll try our best.
There you go.
Please, dear. Don't linger in the hallway.
Your coat?
Can I get you something to eat?
I think I have some peanuts
and some cheese crackers.
No, thank you.
Perhaps something to drink?
I have bourbon, vodka, gin.
Champagne?
I shouldn't. I started on the train.
- What kind of music do you like?
- None for me.
Is the temperature okay?
Yes.
Hmm.
It's been known to get hot.
I'm fine.
That's a pretty shade of lipstick.
Thank you.
I'm glad you came.
Come with me.
DDB managed to get me on the 50-yard line
for the Giants game last November.
If we'd done it,
the Steelers would have won.
We'd do anything to make you happy.
I'm not unhappy with DDB.
No notes.
When I presented the numbers
for my division...
Timmy came up to me and said,
"How the hell did you do that?"
So I figured he's in town,
why not take him to the horse's mouth?
The past few years,
I've overseen ketchup to great success.
But how long before we're old news?
And, hell, when I saw baked beans
have a sales spike like that-
Raymond has demanded our best work.
So then the question is,
what can we do for you?
What can we do for ketchup?
Let me know.
A pleasure to meet you, Timmy.
This isn't an official visit.
I'm just dropping by.
Ken, Don and I have a little
beans housekeeping, if you don't mind.
I'd love to walk you out.
Raymond, we're grateful
for this opportunity...
and consider it
quite a vote of confidence.
It is, but I don't want you
to waste your time.
Well, then if nothing else,
we appreciate the introduction.
I'm not winking here.
There is to be no further communication
with Timmy or his division.
I'm sorry, Raymond.
Did we do something to upset you?
You guys are doing a bang-up job.
And now that polished Polack
wants the same.
I'll take that drink.
No one's paid attention to me
in nine years at the company.
They gave me a suicide mission.
Vinegar, sauces and baked beans.
And then in my moment of triumph,
he comes up to me...
and he didn't say, "How did you do that?"
He said, "How did you do that?"
Smug bastard.
I taught him everything he knows.
- We understand, Raymond.
- No, forget it.
I know ketchup's the gold standard.
But after all we've been through,
I'm sure I don't need to tell you...
that if you so much as send him
a ham at Christmas, well-
I'd rather retire than watch that guy
screw my girlfriend.
- Let me walk you out.
- No.
If he lingered at all...
I'm gonna pretend
I'm on my way to the men's room.
I'm sorry. What a waste of time.
I don't know. We met Timmy.
- He's certainly going places.
- Raymond's so weak.
But he brought his business here
when we were barely standing.
It's Heinz Ketchup, Don.
It's the Coca-Cola of condiments.
I know.
But sometimes you've gotta dance
with the one that brung ya.
I'm afraid that's the end
of your toilet paper.
This place could really use
a woman's touch.
You think so?
I might come to town Friday.
There's always a sale at Macy's.
We'll see.
Okay. I'll call you.
If I let the phone ring once and hang up,
then you'll know it's me.
Don't do that.
Well, I'm going to park my car...
in front of the driveway
instead of in the driveway.
Then you'll know I'm thinking of you.
That's sweet.
I really have to get back.
Can you move it along a little?
You told me you were
washing these by hand.
- No wonder the elastic's shot.
- I forgot.
And you forgot
you left the vacuum on the terrace.
I was changing the bag.
And you forgot not to use
SOS on the Teflon.
I mean, I leave for work every day...
and I wonder what you're
going to ruin in my house.
I'm so sorry, Mrs. Draper.
I don't know how to do this,
but you're fired.
I'll get my things.
- I'm sorry.
- No.
I walked in on it,
and then I didn't want to pretend.
Are you okay, honey?
No.
Come on. Let's go upstairs.
I don't want to go up until she's gone.
Along with your silverware.
So after weeks, I finally show him
the picture of my mother...
but that's not enough because her name
has been changed in the will.
That is quite a story line.
Well, you asked.
- It's meaty, isn't it?
- It is.
I just wish watching TV during the day
didn't make me feel so guilty.
I had a miscarriage.
All right. I will watch.
No, um, in real life.
Two days ago.
I'm so sorry to hear that.
I'm sorry.
I shouldn't burden you with this.
No, you obviously need to talk.
I was sloppy in Hawaii-
the time difference, vacation.
Now I feel so guilty.
May I?
What do you have to feel guilty about?
What did Don say?
I didn't tell him.
It's been a hard couple of weeks.
Oh.
I don't know why.
I mean, I do.
You were raised the same way I was.
I keep hearing Sister Eugenie in my head.
I'm such a horrible person.
You're not a horrible person.
No, I am.
I mean...
to be pregnant now...
at this moment?
I didn't know what I wanted to do...
and I was so relieved
that I didn't have to do anything.
I see.
Has this ever happened to you?
About a year after I had Mitchell.
So I certainly understand
some of what you're feeling.
But the rest of it...
no.
I'm sorry.
Really?
Because I was raised the same way, so...
I would never even
consider that my decision.
- You really believe that?
- I do.
And I think you do, too,
or you wouldn't feel this way.
I just feel so shitty.
I'm sorry I brought it up.
Hello.
- Sylvia's here.
- I see that.
Hello.
I should be going.
You don't have to rush off.
- Have a drink.
- No, I'll leave you two alone.
- I fired the maid today.
- Good riddance.
Good night, both of you.
See you tomorrow.
- Excuse me?
- For dinner.
Oh, of course. Yes.
So send her in.
Sorry to bother you,
but this was on my desk.
Is it new?
There's usually a memo
for everything around here.
- What is it?
- It's Quest.
Feminine... hygiene powder.
- Did I miss a meeting?
- "Proof points-
has baking soda,
makes you nicer if you're stinky...
kills overly critical bacteria."
"Target-
professional women and other Olsons."
Just give it to me.
Calm down. I think
this is somebody's idea of a joke.
Of course, when you want them
to be funny, they're useless.
Hello, gorgeous.
Hello, Herb.
Did you get all gussied up for me?
No.
I had no idea you'd be
darkening my doorway.
When are you gonna come out to the lot?
I told you, I'll let you have a Jaguar
for as long as you like.
I take the bus.
I know there's a part of you
that's glad to see me.
And I know there's a part of you
you haven't seen in years.
Herb! There you are.
How are you today?
Toodle-oo.
- Mrs. Harris is here to see you.
- He's here.
Thank you.
- Who are you?
- I'm Bob Benson.
We've met before. I'm part of the team.
Doesn't the elevator go up to this floor?
Herb. What brings you by?
I had some thoughts, the complexity of which
could not be expressed over a telephone.
What is it you want?
Well, you guys are gonna make some
fancy-schmancy Michelangelo TV spot...
and the dealers are gonna
foot most of the bill for running it.
That's how it works.
Well, I'm the only guy
actually out there selling hamburgers...
and I want people to know
there's a hamburger store in Englewood...
not England or in your mind.
I don't want another thing with some
schmuck sitting on his lawn mower...
fantasizing that he's gonna win
the Grand Prix driving a Jaguar.
I need foot traffic.
Get 'em in the door so I can move metal.
Well, you, along with the factory guys...
have already signed off on the work
as well as the buy.
I just think there should
be retail radio as well.
You know?
"Does your car sound like this?"
Voom voom!
"Does your wife sound like this?"
"Ooh, I love your car."
And then you say the phone number twice.
Wonderful. We'd love to increase
the exposure of the campaign.
How much more would you like to buy?
There's no increase.
Just adjust the proportions.
I think we should spend
60% of the money...
on local dealership ads
instead of national.
Herb, that would really take a bite
out of the national campaign.
Well, if you say so.
Unfortunately, it's not up to me...
so I am suggesting that you
recommend this plan to all of us.
Why don't you recommend it?
It's your idea.
Because it's an idea you had yourself.
And Lord knows you're so damn persuasive.
We understand, Herb.
See how easy that was, Bob?
Bob, why don't you show me the sights?
You must be like a kid
in a candy store out here.
Vavoom, vavoom.
- You can't shake his hand?
- He didn't seem interested.
In fact, the only thing he seemed interested in
was gutting our national campaign.
You do realize that defeats
the purpose of having Jaguar?
So he's demanding and unreasonable.
How does that make him different from
the other people who walk through that door?
I wish you would handle the clients
as well as you're handling me.
Jimmy's Condom Warehouse,
where the rubber meets the road.
- Jimmy speaking.
- You want a drink?
No, thank you. I'm quite comfortable.
How was your day, honey?
- Okay.
- Okay?
What happened to Shangri-La?
Chaough quit crapping out snow cones?
Everyone hates me here.
Well, that was bound to happen.
You worked for me, and you like me.
- I worked with you.
- I was tough but fair.
Oh, speaking of people who hate you...
Raymond J. Beans came in today
and pulled a real boner.
Go on.
- He brought in the head of ketchup.
- He's obsessed with that man.
Yeah, he should be. I met him.
So Raymond makes the introduction...
and then, according to Ken,
ketchup leaves, but Raymond lingers...
and he says he's gonna
kill the account and himself...
if they even talk to ketchup again.
- Why'd he bring him in?
- Because he's Raymond.
He's a fraidycat.
And- here's the part
that's gonna make you happy-
Kenny spent two weeks telling everybody
how he was getting ketchup.
Okay, Tuesday morning is perfect.
What? Oh, yep.
We'll have your wig ready then, ma'am.
You're allowed to make
personal calls after 5:00...
especially if they make you laugh.
My friend Stan was telling me a funny story
about one of our old clients.
- What happened?
- Oh, it's complicated.
But basically the guy from Heinz Baked Beans
hates the guy at Heinz Ketchup.
Of course he does.
Well, surprisingly, beans brought ketchup
in for a meeting at the agency...
and everyone got excited...
and then, unsurprisingly,
he sent ketchup out of the room...
and told everyone it was just for show.
So he's unhappy?
He's not going anywhere.
Probably misses you.
No. I assure you, he doesn't.
There's nothing like things going badly
when you leave, is there?
Sorry I'm late.
Third Avenue was a parking lot.
I'm not feeling well.
That's not where it hurts.
Oh. Did you cancel?
No, I thought I'd feel better
by the time you got home.
We're supposed to be there in 15 minutes.
They're probably already there.
I know, but I don't want to pretend
like I'm having a good time...
and it's too late to cancel.
- They'll survive.
- I want you to go.
I want you to have fun.
Okay.
But you go right to bed.
Yes, sir.
Willis Reed replaces Nate Bowman.
Go away!
Somebody help me!
What on earth is that?
Somebody, please!
Somebody help!
- Oh, my goodness!
- What happened to you?
Hey, Campbell! She's your problem now!
I'm sorry. I didn't know where else to go.
He was chasing me.
Close the door.
- Hold this to your nose.
- What the hell happened?
I'm so embarrassed.
We had a terrible fight.
- I'm going to call the authorities.
- No, please.
- Well, then I'm taking you to the hospital.
- I'll be fine.
What do you think you're doing?
You're not going back there.
Peter, go to Tammy's bathroom.
There's some cotton wool.
I'll be right back.
I hope you haven't been waiting long.
Oh, don't worry about it. I was late too.
They already gave us a hard time.
Where's your wife?
She sends her regrets.
She wasn't feeling well.
That's too bad.
- You look lovely.
- Let's get you a drink.
We'll get the waiter
to do the whole show again.
I'm afraid there's only
going to be three of us.
- Don?
- Old-fashioned, please.
Subito.
Well, the North Koreans
really took that ship.
And the Vietcong-
did you see them storming the embassy?
I haven't followed it today.
- We got it back.
- Still.
These two little pissant countries
handing our head to us.
Well, I don't know about the ship...
but from what I've read,
the embassy was an ambush.
They broke the cease-fire.
We gave them peace
for their sacred holiday.
Next thing we know,
they cut us to ribbons.
Reminds me of Cuba.
No one took Fidel Castro seriously.
We thought he was Señor Wences.
Turns out he was George Washington.
- And they say surgeons are arrogant.
- Who says that?
You know we're losing the war?
You wouldn't know it
from looking around here.
Yeah, it's something. Right?
- You are Dr. Rosen?
- You see this service?
Yes. We'd like to hear the spiel again.
Uh, scusi. There is a telephone call.
Really?
I'll be right back.
I'm gonna take this as an opportunity
to powder my nose.
There's no answer.
Is there anyone else? Family?
My sister's back in Oneonta.
My mother's in Boca Raton.
Well, you can't go home.
We should find a hotel.
Let's try some ice.
What did you say to him?
Hello? Yes. Do you have
any vacancies this evening?
Take me to the city.
I want to be with you.
Absolutely not.
Very good. Thank you.
The Old Greenwich Inn has rooms.
- Can you take me there?
- We'll get you a taxi.
Nonsense. I'll drive you.
I don't know what I was thinking.
I'll run you over.
Brenda, dear, let's go.
It's best this way.
Emergency averted?
Unfortunately, no.
Sylvia and you are having dinner.
- This is silly.
- We can do this another time.
I'm not taking my foot out of the door
of this restaurant.
Order for four, or they'll punish me.
Good luck.
What are you having?
I don't know that I'm that hungry.
You want another glass of wine?
Should we get a bottle?
You're drinking something else.
I don't want you to have wine
if you don't drink wine.
I'm not gonna drink a whole bottle,
obviously.
I don't know how obvious that is.
Another glass is fine.
So what looks good here?
Depends what you want.
Well, I'm hungry, I'm in a good mood...
and I'd like some guidance on the Italian menu
from my favorite Italian.
I didn't cook it,
so I can't speak to its quality.
You think I'd like eggplant rollatinis?
For the lovely signora?
- We're not ready yet.
- Yes, we are.
Can she have another glass of wine,
and could you give us a minute?
Certo.
What's wrong?
How could I possibly know
what you like to eat?
I thought you were
looking forward to this.
I don't know what we're doing.
We're having dinner together.
And I'm sorry, but I guess
it was a stupid idea...
to think we could spend time together
outside of your maid's room.
Just because they cleared their
place settings doesn't mean we're alone.
Is that what's bothering you-
that everything worked out perfectly?
And you enjoy how foolish they both look.
Now I understand.
You want to feel shitty...
right up until the point
where I take your dress off.
Because I'm going to do that.
You want to skip dinner?
Fine. But don't pretend.
And what if she had come?
The evening would be just the same,
only it would be someone else's dress?
What are you talking about?
Weren't you the one who told me
you were drifting apart?
Isn't that what this was about?
I want you.
I want you all the time.
But if you've suddenly decided
you want something more than that...
well, then, that's news, isn't it?
So, have you decided?
I don't know. Have you?
He'll have the steak diavolo,
and I'll have the branzino.
Anything to start?
No. We're in a bit of a hurry.
I'm sorry.
I'm so sorry.
I have no right to be jealous.
This is just us here tonight.
We have to be careful.
We can't fall in love.
It won't be so French anymore.
Hi, this is Johnny Carson. As you know...
this is the usual starting time
for The Tonight Show.
And tonight my guest is the New Orleans
district attorney, Mr. Jim Garrison...
who is with us to discuss, as he puts it...
some new and vital information concerning
the Kennedy assassination.
But because of the critical
war situation in Vietnam...
especially around Saigon,
NBC for the next 15 minutes...
is going to bring you
a special news program via satellite.
So stay with us. We'll return in 15 minutes
with our guest, Mr. Garrison.
Did you have fun?
Arnold had an emergency,
so Sylvia and I had to eat enough...
to keep him in good graces there.
Are you feeling better?
I need to talk to you.
What's wrong?
Um-
Well, I had a miscarriage
a few days ago.
Are you okay?
Did you go to the doctor?
Yes.
How far along were you?
Six weeks.
I wish you would have told me.
I guess I didn't know how you'd feel.
I didn't know what you'd want.
Megan, you have to know
I'd want what you want.
Is that what you want?
Of course it is.
But I don't know that it's even the right time
to have a conversation about it.
And I guess that's why I didn't tell you.
But I should have.
Yes, you should have.
Do you want to have that conversation?
Whenever you want.
Now I can go to sleep.
Good morning.
- Where's Tammy?
- Leticia took her to the park.
Oh.
Well, I'm off.
Couldn't you just pretend?
I let you have that apartment.
Somehow I thought
that there was some dignity...
in granting permission.
All I wanted was for you to be discreet.
She lives on our block!
Trudy, don't jump to conclusions.
There's no way for me to escape,
to not be an object of pity...
while you get to do
whatever you feel like.
I have never said no to you.
That is not true.
What are we doing out here?
We're done, Peter. This is over.
You want a divorce?
I refuse to be a failure.
I don't care what you want anymore.
This is how it's going to work.
You will be here
only when I tell you to be here.
I'm drawing a 50-mile radius
around this house...
and if you so much as open your fly
to urinate, I will destroy you.
Do you understand?
You know what?
You're going to go to bed alone tonight...
and you're going to realize you don't
know anything for sure.
I'll live with that.
- Good morning.
So far this is all we have...
but I want you to find out
everything you can on Heinz Ketchup.
What?
And this is not a joke.
- No. I can't do that.
- Why not?
It's a little bit of a secret,
but it turns out they're taking meetings.
I told you that secret,
and I shouldn't have.
Look, everybody's gonna know.
We just know a little sooner.
My friend told me that in confidence.
- He's not your friend. He's the enemy.
- Well, he doesn't know that.
Maybe you need a friend
more than you need a job.
I didn't know that. I'm in advertising.
It's not that. It's just that
it was a private conversation.
What are you, his priest?
This is how wars are won.
Your friend's mistake
was underestimating you.
I hope ketchup makes the same mistake
so you can blow their mind.
So, correct me if I'm wrong, Pete.
I certainly will.
You're suggesting that we forgo
this sparkling national ad campaign...
in favor of hard-driving sales ads
at the local dealer level?
Not exactly.
We will still have a national presence...
with the sophisticated work
that Don presented and you loved...
but we will increase sales...
with a surgical and financial focus
on local media.
Well, that sounds good to me.
Of course, I'm a little bit biased.
Why would we do that?
We feel it's best to have a plan
that creates customers...
not just aficionados.
Don, are you really in favor
of throwing our emphasis into radio?
Well, it's hard to argue
with a more direct appeal to customers.
I mean, we can artsy up
the image of Jaguar...
make it look romantic and stylish...
but isn't it better to tell people who are
actually in the market for a car...
that a Jaguar is available?
I think it's an exciting new angle
to use direct sales on a luxury vehicle.
I mean, forget about radio.
How about a mailer
or a circular in the Sunday paper?
I don't know if that's
what we had in mind.
So this is your recommendation?
I think it's better to think about
someone in New Jersey...
driving in their current car and hearing
that right around the corner...
there's a Jaguar to buy
at a low, low price.
I bet the numbers would support that.
Don't they, Harry?
That, uh, is really a statistics game.
You know what?
I will have to double-check.
Look, why are you limiting yourself?
Wouldn't you rather cast a wide net so you
can sell Jaguar to the average guy?
You know, truck drivers, housewives.
I was under the impression,
from the work you showed us...
that this would be
a more elegant approach...
that made the Jaguar seem rare
because, let's face it...
the gentleman who buys our car
needs to be of some means.
I am 100% positive
that this approach moves cars.
And not just Jaguars.
This is proven to move all kinds of cars.
Hell, even used cars. Am I wrong, Herb?
No, he's right. It moves cars.
Gentlemen, we appreciate
the recommendation...
but we believe we should stay
with the proposal as first discussed.
And as persuasive as these arguments were...
that is how we will continue to proceed.
Let's not be too hasty.
Maybe we should listen to them.
At least give it some thought.
Herb's right.
We still believe
this is our best chance for success.
Fellas, this is gonna work.
I'm sorry, but this is our final decision.
Thank you very much.
What the hell was that?
Herb, we couldn't have pushed any harder.
You pushed. Then you let Don talk.
You should know better.
The guy's not a salesman.
That was the deftest
self-immolation I've ever seen.
I don't know what you're talking about.
I didn't know you were
capable of being that bad.
- What was that in there?
- I wasn't feeling well.
Something about that guy makes me sick.
Don't be cute.
I still have his spit in my hair.
Why can't you just follow the rules?
I did. I did exactly what he asked for.
Not in spirit. You know damn well
that is not what he wanted.
Why do we care what that guy wants?
- Because he's a client.
- Our client.
And so we just keep saying yes,
no matter what...
because we didn't say no to begin with?
You know what this is? It's Munich.
You guys are always talking about Munich.
What the hell does that mean anyway?
It means we gave the Germans whatever
they wanted to make them happy...
but it just made them want more.
Well, who the hell won the war?
As my mother used to say,
"Your options were dishonor or war.
You chose dishonor.
You might still get war."
That was Churchill.
First one in, last one out.
I don't know how you do it.
Me either.
Well, it can't be that bad when you're
doing something that you love.
I'm glad it looks like that to you.
I spent a year in finance...
watching identical men
in identical suits...
sneak drinks out of a desk drawer
while counting other people's money.
What house?
My family's been at Brown Brothers Harriman
for three generations.
You make this look a lot better.
It's all about what it looks like, isn't it?
I'm going down to the deli.
Can I get you something?
No, thank you.
Bob.
My wife asked me,
and I seem to have forgotten.
Could you pick me up some toilet paper?
I got it, chief.
Good evening.
He's home.
You can't knock on the door like that.
I was taking the trash out,
and you left it open.
Tomorrow morning?
You're a dirty little spy.
I dropped a penny.
You got your own room.
That's how things work around here.