(Lecter)
'Previously on "Hannibal"...'
(Crawford) 'You make jumps
you can't explain.'
- The evidence explains.
- Then help me find some evidence.
I wouldn't put him out there!
Should he get too close, I need you
to make sure he's not out there alone.
(Graham) 'I don't think the Shrike
killed that girl in the field.
'This girl's killer thought
she was a pig.'
Think this was a copycat?
I think I can help good Will
see his face.
- Hello?
- They know.
You said he wouldn't get too close.
See?
(Muffled gunshots)
We're here.
It could be a permanent installation
in your Evil Minds Museum.
Well, what we learn
about Garrett Jacob Hobbs
will help us catch
the next one like him.
There's still seven bodies
unaccounted for.
Yeah, well, he was eating them.
Had to be some parts
he wasn't eating.
Not necessarily.
All right, what if Hobbs wasn't
eating alone? It's a lot of work.
Disappearing these girls,
butchering them
and not leaving a shred of anything
other than what's in this room.
- Someone he hunted with.
- Someone who was in a coma.
Who also happened to be
someone he hunted with.
Abigail Hobbs is a suspect?
We've been conducting
house-to-house interviews
at the Hobbs residence
and at this property also.
Hobbs spent a lot of time here.
Spent a lot of time
with his daughter here.
She would make the ideal bait,
wouldn't she?
Hobbs killed alone.
Ah. Someone else was here.
(Applause)
Thank you.
Please stop that.
This is how I caught
Garrett Jacob Hobbs.
It's his resignation letter.
Does anybody see the clue?
There isn't one.
He wrote a letter, left a phone number,
no address. That's it.
Bad bookkeeping and dumb luck.
(Gas-ping)
Garrett Jacob Hobbs is dead.
The question now is
how to stop those
his story is going to inspire.
He's already got one admirer.
A copycat.
Hi.
How are you, Will?
Uh, I have no idea.
- I didn't want you to be ambushed.
- This is an ambush?
Ambush is later.
Immediately later, soon to now.
When Jack arrives,
consider yourself ambushed.
Here's Jack.
How was class?
They applauded.
It was inappropriate.
The review board would beg to differ.
You're up for a commendation.
And they've okayed
active return to the field.
The question is, do you want
to go back to the field?
I want him back in the field.
And I've told the board
I'm recommending a psych eval.
- Are we starting now?
- The session wouldn't be with me.
Hannibal Lecter's a better fit.
Your relationship's not personal.
But if you are more comfortable
with Dr Bloom...
No, I'm not going to be comfortable
with anybody inside my head.
You've never killed anyone before.
It's a deadly force encounter.
- It's a lotto digest.
- I used to work Homicide.
The reason you currently
used to work Homicide
is because you didn't have
the stomach for pulling the trigger.
You just pulled the trigger
ten times.
Wait, so a psych eval
isn't a formality?
No, it's so I can get
some sleep at night.
I asked you to get close
to the Hobbs thing.
I need to know
you didn't get too close.
How many nights did you spend
in Abigail Hobbs' hospital room, Will?
- Therapy doesn't work on me.
- Hmm...
Therapy doesn't work on you
because you won't let it.
Because I know all the tricks.
Perhaps you need
to unlearn some tricks.
Why not have a conversation
with Hannibal?
He was there.
He knows what you went through.
Come on, Will.
I need my beauty sleep!
- What's that?
- Your psychological evaluation.
You are totally functional
and more or less sane. Well done.
- Did you just rubber stamp me?
- Yes.
Jack Crawford may lay his weary head
to rest knowing he didn't break you
and our conversation can proceed
unobstructed by paperwork.
Jack thinks I need therapy.
You need a way out of dark places
when Jack sends you there.
Last time he sent me into a dark place,
I brought something back.
A surrogate daughter?
You saved Abigail Hobbs's life.
You also orphaned her.
That comes with certain
emotional obligations,
regardless of empathy disorders.
You were there. You saved her life too.
Do you feel obligated?
Yes.
I feel a staggering amount
of obligation.
I feel responsibility.
I've fantasised about scenarios
where my actions
may have allowed
a different fate for Abigail Hobbs.
Jack thinks Abigail Hobbs
helped her dad kill those girls.
How does that make you feel?
How does it make you feel?
- I find it vulgar.
- Me too.
- And entirely possible.
- It's not what happened.
Jack will ask her when she wakes up,
or he'll have one of us ask her.
Is this therapy,
or a support group?
It's whatever you need it to be.
And, Will,
the mirrors in your mind
can reflect the best of yourself,
not the worst of someone else.
What is that?
- I bet it's marijuana.
- Mushrooms.
Look, they got tubes
to water 'em or something.
No, it's a marijuana plant.
That's not marijuana.
(Gunshots)
I'm pretty sure firearm accuracy
isn't a prerequisite for teaching.
Well, I've been in the field before.
- Now you're back in the saddle. Ish.
- Ish, indeed.
Took me ten shots to drop Hobbs.
Zeller wanted to give you the bullets
he pulled out of Hobbs in an acrylic case,
but I told him
you wouldn't think it was funny.
Probably not.
I suggested one of those
clackin' swingin' ball things.
That would've been funny.
You're a Weaver.
I took you for an isosceles guy.
I have a rotator cuff issue,
so I have to use the Weaver stance.
- You are tight.
- I got stabbed when I was a cop.
Yeah, I got stabbed in the third grade
with a number two pencil.
Thought I was gonna get
lead poisoning.
Uh, no lead in pencils,
it's graphite.
See if that helps with the recoil.
That was better.
You come all the way down here
to teach me how to shoot?
No. Jack sent me down here to find out
what you know about gardening.
So, Lecter gave you the all-clear.
Therapy might work on you after all.
Therapy is an acquired taste
which I have yet to acquire.
But it served your purpose.
I'm back in the field.
Local police found some tyre tracks
on a hidden service road
and some small animal traps
in the surrounding area.
He wanted to keep his crop
undisturbed.
The only thing missing
is the scarecrow.
OK, we've got nine bodies,
various stages of decay,
and as you can see,
all very well fertilised.
He buried them
in a high-nutrient compost.
He was enthusiastically
encouraging decomposition.
They were buried alive with the intention
of keeping them that way...
I mean, for a little while.
Long enough for the fungus to eat away
any distinguishing characteristics.
Line and rebar were used to administer
intravenous fluids after they were buried.
He was feeding them something.
No restraints?
Just dirt.
The other end of the air-supply system
comes up over there.
It isn't a very considerate
clean air solution,
which clearly wasn't a priority,
cos he isn't lazy.
No, he's not.
- You find any shiitakes?
- No.
Welcome back.
Tell Sam to give me a call, will you?
Thank you.
Excuse me.
I'm one of the parents
of the explorers who found the bodies.
I wanted to thank you
for being so good with all the boys.
- Those boys were very brave.
- They are good boys.
- You're a local police detective?
- Yes, ma'am.
Would it be an imposition
to ask a few things?
The boys are gonna have questions,
and I just wanna be honest with them...
Of course. Yeah, yeah.
Can you tell me what that man
is doing over there by himself?
He's some kind of special consultant.
Works for the FBI.
Huh...
(Electricity buzzing)
(Sound distorts)
(Soft ambient pulse)
(Sound returns to normal)
I do not bind his arms or legs
as I bury him in a shallow grave.
He's alive. But he will never
be conscious again.
He won't know that he's dying.
I don't need him to.
This is my design.
- I think your family's leaving.
- We drove separately.
(Muffled gasp)
(Gas-ping)
Don't touch him!
(Man) Oh, my god!
(Graham) This may have
been premature.
What did you see, out in the field?
Hobbs.
- An association?
- No, a hallucination.
I saw him lying there
in someone else's grave.
- Did you tell Jack what you saw?
- No.
It's stress. Not worth reporting.
You displaced the victim
of another killer's crime
with what could arguably
be considered your victim.
I don't consider Hobbs my victim.
What do you consider him?
Dead.
Is it harder imagining the thrill
somebody else feels killing,
now that you've done it yourself?
The arms.
Why did he leave them exposed?
To hold their hands?
To feel the life leaving their bodies?
No, that's too esoteric for someone
who took the time to bury his victims
in a straight line.
- He's more practical.
- He was cultivating them.
He was keeping them alive.
He was feeding them intravenously.
But your farmer let his crops die.
Save for the one that didn't.
And the one that didn't
died on the way to the hospital.
No, they weren't crops,
they were the fertiliser.
The bodies were covered in fungus.
The structure of a fungus
mirrors that of the human brain,
an intricate web of connections.
So maybe he admires
their ability to connect
the way human minds can't.
- Yours can.
- (Laughs) Yep.
Um... Yeah, not physically.
Is that what your farmer is looking for?
Some sort of connection?
Have a good evening, Will.
- Miss Kimball?
- Yes.
Good evening. Please come in.
I've... never seen
a psychiatrist before.
And I am unfortunately
thorough,
so you're one of three doctors
I'm interviewing.
It's more or less a bake-off.
I'm very supportive of bake-offs.
It's important you find someone
you're comfortable with.
I can imagine you as my therapist,
which is good.
If I can't visualise opening up emotionally,
I know it would be a problem.
May I ask why now?
Do you mind if I ask you
a few questions first?
Of course not.
I love that you've written
so much on social exclusion.
Since that's why I'm here,
I was wondering...
Are you Freddie Lounds?
This is unethical,
even for a tabloid journalist.
I am, uh...
I am so embarrassed.
I'm afraid I must ask for your bag.
- What?
- Your bag.
Please hand it over.
I'd rather not take it from you.
Thank you.
I was recording our conversation.
Our conversation?
Yours and mine?
Yes.
- No other conversation?
- No.
You were very persistent
about your appointment time.
How did you know
when Will Graham would be here?
I may have also recorded
your session with Will Graham.
You didn't answer the question.
How did you know?
I can't answer that question.
Come. Sit by me.
Delete the conversations
you recorded.
Doctor/patient confidentiality
works both ways.
Delete it, please.
You've been terribly rude,
Miss Lounds.
What's to be done about that?
(♪ Johann Sebastian Bach:
"Cello Suite No 4 Prelude")
(Lecter) Loin, served with
a Cumberland sauce of red fruits.
Er... loin? What kind?
- Pork.
- Wonderful.
I don't get many opportunities
to eat home-cooked meals.
My wife and I both work,
and as hard as I tried not to,
I did wind up marrying my mother.
- Your mother didn't cook?
- She did, she did.
I only wish she didn't.
There was this meal she used to prepare.
She liked to call it "oriental noodles".
Spaghetti, soy sauce,
bouillon cubes and spam.
I was very thin as a youngster.
Well, next time, bring your wife.
- I'd love to have you both for dinner.
- Thank you.
Mmm.
Lovely. So, why do you think
Will Graham came back to see you?
I'm sure he recognises the necessity
of his own support structure
if he is to support you in the field.
I believe that Will Graham knows exactly
what's going on inside of his head,
which is why he doesn't want
anyone else up there.
Are you not accustomed
to broken ponies in your stable?
You think Will Graham's
a broken pony?
I think you think
Will is a broken pony.
Have you ever lost a pony, Jack?
If you're asking me whether or not
I've ever lost someone in the field,
the answer is yes. Why?
I want to understand
why you're so delicate with Will.
Because you don't trust him or because
you're afraid of losing another pony?
I've already had my psych eval.
Not by me.
You've already told me about
your mother. Why stop there?
Oh, great. All right.
Mm.
What were they soaked in?
A concentrated mixture of hardwoods,
shredded newspaper and pig poop,
perfect for growing mushrooms
and other fungi.
It was not the mushrooms, though.
They all died of kidney failure.
Dextrose in all the catheters.
He probably used some kind
of dialysis or peristaltic
to pump fluids after their
circulatory systems broke down.
Force-feeding them sugar water?
(Zeller) Know who loves sugar water?
Mushrooms. They crave it.
Recovering alcoholics.
They crave sugar.
- Don't take that personally, buddy.
- Oh, I'm not recovering.
Feed sugar to the fungus in your body,
the fungus creates alcohol,
so it's like friends
helping friends, really.
It's not just alcoholics who have
compromised endocrine systems.
They all died of kidney failure?
Death by diabetic ketoacidosis.
- Did you know they were diabetics?
- We don't know they were diabetics.
No, they're all diabetics. He induces
a coma and puts them in the ground.
How's he inducing diabetic comas?
Changes their medication.
So he's a doctor or a pharmacist.
Or he works somewhere
in medical services.
He buries them, feeds them sugar
to keep them alive long enough
for the circulatory systems
to soak it up.
- So he can feed the mushrooms!
- We dug up his mushroom garden.
Yeah, he's gonna want
to grow a new one.
I'm picking up a prescription
for Gretchen Speck.
Gretchen Speck... (Typing)
- Horowitz.
- Oh, it's just Speck.
We're divorced.
I lost the hyphen, kept the ring.
- Insulin.
- Yes.
Oh...
Oh, it's the wrong one. Just...
- Uh-oh.
- No, no, it's OK.
Just gonna be one second.
There. There you go.
Oh, could you sign here please?
- And that's your correct address?
- Yeah.
- Thank you.
Mrs James.
If you could sign here, please?
Thank you.
She's the chain's tenth
diabetic customer to disappear
after filling a prescription
for insulin,
second to disappear
from this exact location.
- And the other eight?
- All over the county.
One pharmacist
all over the county as well.
- Floater, huh?
- Floater's floating right here.
Still logged in at his work station.
Everyone please stop
what you are doing!
Put your hands in the air!
Special Agent Jack Crawford.
Which one of you is Eldon Stammets?
Eldon was just here.
Just now.
Is his car still in the parking lot?
His car!
Give me your baton.
(Coughs)
She's alive!
(Coughing)
EMTs! Now!
All right.
We know his name,
we have his address, we have his car.
Jack. We just checked the browser
history at Stammets' work station.
- Am I gonna wanna hear this?
- No.
And yes, but mostly no.
- Freddie Lounds.
- Tattlecrime.com.
"The FBI isn't just hunting
psychopaths,
"they're headhunting them too,
offering competitive pay and benefits
"in the hopes
of using one demented mind..."
Keep going.
(Katz) It's about Will.
(Crawford) Go on.
"One demented mind to catch..."
- She goes into a lot of detail.
- Son of a bitch!
You are naughty, Miss Lounds.
(Knocking)
Who is it?
(Zeller) All clear.
I appreciate the pageantry,
Agent Crawford,
but you can't arrest me
for writing an article.
You entered a federal crime scene
without permission.
- Escorted by a detective.
- Under false pretence!
It is as good as permission.
You lied to a police officer.
You can't arrest me for lying.
You got all that information
from a local detective?
Lots of talk about your man Graham.
Not to mention the rivalry
of who gets the collar.
A local police detective looking
for a pissing contest with the FBI
might have some insight.
- (Crawford) And evidently did.
- Sure did.
You know, the unfortunate
timing of your article
allowed a murderer to escape.
(Yelps)
You were in Minnesota.
You were in the Shrike's nest.
You know how I know?
Cos you left one of these hairs behind.
You contaminated the crime scene.
Just like everywhere you go,
you contaminate crime scenes.
That's obstructing justice.
I can indict you for obstructing justice.
I'd appreciate it if you didn't.
You don't write another word
about Will Graham and I won't have to.
(Zeller) You used me.
(Monitor beeps, ventilator pumps)
(Echoing footsteps)
(Bloom) "...he and the Grandmother
discussed better times.
"The old lady said that,
in her opinion,
"Europe was entirely to blame
for the way things were now.
- "She said..."
- What are you reading?
Flannery O'Connor.
When I was Abigail's age,
I was obsessed.
I even tried to raise peacocks
because she raised peacocks, but...
They were really stupid birds.
- You could be reading to a killer.
- Innocent until guilty and all that.
I'm about to broach the subject
of that "Takes One to Know One" article.
Oh, that.
- Did Jack send you?
- No, I sent me.
I don't think we've ever been alone
in a room together, have we?
I haven't noticed. Have we?
Not that we're necessarily
alone now.
Yeah, right. Back to...
- "Jack Crawford's crime gimp".
- It certainly creates an image.
I don't need to talk about it
if you don't.
No, no, we can talk about
or not talk about whatever you want.
Actually, I was... I was just
enjoying listening to you read.
Abigail Hobbs is a success for you.
She doesn't look like a success.
Don't feel sorry for yourself
because you saved this girl's life.
I don't.
I don't feel sorry for myself at all.
I feel, um...
I-I...
...good.
Don't know where you got
half that information. It wasn't from me.
- I may have made some inferences.
- They think I told you all of it.
They saw you talking to me.
They also think it's my fault
Stammets escaped.
- I'm sorry I got you fired.
- I wasn't fired. I was suspended.
They're gonna fire you.
Jack Crawford will make sure of that.
You...
You stir the hornet's nest,
and I'm the one who gets stung?
I can help you get work
outside the force, if you want me to.
I know people in private security.
Not the first cop you got fired.
Guarantee you it pays better.
Right now, future you
is thanking me.
I read your article.
Tell me about Will Graham.
(Lounds) Jack?
Miss Lounds?
Go ahead and stand down, officer.
Miss Lounds, are you all right?
Where's Will Graham?
We have an eyewitness to the murder.
We don't need Will Graham.
No, that's not why I'm asking.
Someone find me Will Graham!
This is about Will?
He was talking about people
- having the same properties of a fungus.
- Stammets?
Thoughts leaping from brain to brain.
They mutate, they evolve.
- What does he want with Will Graham?
- Someone who understands him.
Graham was right.
Stammets is looking for connections.
What did you tell him?
I need to know what you told
Eldon Stammets about Will Graham.
- I told him about the Hobbs girl.
- What did you tell him?
Everything-
He wants to help Will Graham
connect with Abigail Hobbs.
He's gonna bury her.
Sorry.
(Phone rings)
- Hello?
- 'It's Jack. Are you at the hospital?'
- Yes, I am.
- 'Stammets knows about Abigail.'
Where is she? Abigail Hobbs,
the girl in 408. Where is she?
- They took her for tests.
- Who took her?
- I... I don't know.
Hey!
(Grunts in pain)
What were you gonna do to her?
We all evolved from mycelium.
I'm simply reintroducing her
to the concept.
By burying her alive?
The journalist said
you understood me.
I don't.
Well, you would have.
You would have.
If you walk through a field of mycelium,
they know you are there.
'The spores reach for you
as you walk by.'
I know who you're reaching for.
I know.
Abigail Hobbs.
And you should have let me
plant her.
You would have found her
in a field,
where she was finally
able to reach back!
(Lecter) 'When you shot
Eldon Stammets,
'who was it that you saw?'
I didn't see Hobbs.
Then it's not Hobbs's ghost
that's haunting you, is it?
It's the inevitability of there being
a man so bad that killing him felt good.
Killing Hobbs felt just.
Which is why you're here,
to prove that sprig of zest you feel
is from saving Abigail,
not from killing her dad.
I didn't feel a sprig of zest
when I shot Eldon Stammets.
You didn't kill Eldon Stammets.
I thought about it.
I'm still not entirely sure that wasn't
my intention, pulling the trigger.
If your intention was to kill him,
it's because you understand
why he did the things he did.
It's beautiful in its own way...
...giving voice to the unmentionable.
I should've stuck to fixing
boat motors in Louisiana.
A boat engine is a machine,
a predictable problem, easy to solve.
You fail, there's a paddle.
Where was your paddle with Hobbs?
- You're supposed to be my paddle.
- I am.
It wasn't the act of killing Hobbs
that got you down, was it?
Did you really feel so bad
because killing him felt so good?
I liked killing Hobbs.
Killing must feel good to God too,
he does it all the time.
And are we not created in his image?
That depends who you ask.
God's terrific.
He dropped a church roof
on 34 of his worshippers
last Wednesday night in Texas,
while they sang a hymn.
Did God feel good about that?
He felt powerful.