(Lecter)
'Previously on "Hannibal"...'
- What's that man doing over there?
- He's a special consultant for the FBI.
I asked you to get close
to the Hobbs thing.
'I need to know
you didn't get too close.'
What you need is a way out of dark
places when Jack sends you there.
Last time he sent me
into a dark place,
- I brought something back.
- 'A surrogate daughter?'
Abigail Hobbs is a suspect?
She would make the ideal bait.
Wouldn't she?
Just a second. Dad? It's for you.
- Hello?
- They know.
Easy, Abigail.
Be patient. Wait for your shot.
(Gunshot)
(Soft thud)
Ready?
And three, two, one. Go.
(Abigail) She was so pretty.
(Hobbs) She is so pretty.
Aren't deer supposed to be
complex emotional creatures?
Yeah.
I read they're like the equivalent
of a four-year-old human being.
They're smarter than a four-year-old.
And they care about each other.
They care about their environment.
They tread lightly
through the underbrush
because they don't want to hurt
the plants.
They're a lot like us.
And we're gonna honour
every part of her.
Her hide is gonna make
a beautiful rug.
Her leg bones
we can carve into knives.
None of her is gonna go to waste.
Just like we talked about.
Start at the sternum.
Keep the blade pointed up.
Damage the organs...
you ruin the meat.
I don't know how I'm gonna feel
about eating her after all this.
Eating her is honouring her.
Otherwise, it's... it's just...
...murder.
OK.
Nice and easy. Big breath.
Good.
(Gasps)
(Monitors beeping)
(Muffled whimpering and coughing)
Morning.
- Didn't hear you drive up.
- Hybrid. Great car for stalking.
- I'm compelled to go cover myself.
- I have brothers.
I'll put a robe on just the same.
Want a cup of coffee?
- More immediately, why are you here?
- Yes, and Abigail Hobbs woke up.
You know how to bury the lead.
You want me to get you
a cup of coffee?
- No. I want to get my coat.
- Let's have a cup of coffee.
(Ringing)
(Phone vibrating)
- Is he gonna keep calling?
- Jack wants you to go see her.
- And you don't.
- Eventually.
Jack thinks Abigail was an accomplice
to her father's crimes.
I don't want to get in the middle
of you and Jack,
but if I can be helpful to you
as a buffer...
I... I like you as a buffer.
I also like the fact
that you rattle Jack.
He respects you far too much
to yell at you,
no matter how much he wants to.
And I take advantage of that.
Abigail Hobbs doesn't have anyone.
You can't be her everyone.
When I said what I was going
to say in my head,
it sounded really insulting,
so I'll find another way to say it.
Say it the insulting way.
Dogs keep a promise a person can't.
I'm not collecting another stray.
The first person Abigail
talks to about what happened
can't be anyone who was there
when it happened.
So that means no Dr Lecter either.
Yeah, much less the guy
who killed dad.
Jack's wrong about Abigail.
Let me reach out to her
in my own way.
Hi.
I'm Alana Bloom.
Are you a doctor?
Not medicine.
I'm a psychiatrist.
What do you specialise in?
Among other things,
family trauma.
I asked the nurses
if my parents were dead,
and they wouldn't tell me.
Said I had to wait for you.
I'm sorry you had to wait.
I know they're dead.
Who buried them?
They haven't been buried.
Don't you think they should be?
Your mother was cremated per
the instructions in her living will.
(Clears throat) My dad?
Your father is more complicated.
Because he was crazy?
The nurses said you didn't remember.
I remember. I just didn't want
to talk to them about it.
I want to sell the house.
I guess it's mine now.
I can use the money for college,
get an apartment.
What are all those?
I brought you some clothes.
Thought a change might feel good.
I guessed your size,
so anything you don't want,
leave the tags on,
I'll bring it back.
- And I brought you some music too.
- Your music?
If there isn't anything you like,
I've got a stack of iTunes gift cards.
I... I've got a stack of gift cards.
I don't do well redeeming gift cards.
- Probably says something about you.
- Probably does.
I got seven families waiting.
No, let me rephrase...
Demanding that we find
whatever's left of their daughters.
Abigail Hobbs may be the only
person who knows the truth.
You can't ask her right now, Jack.
We have to create a safe place for
her first or you won't get any answers.
I respect your sympathy for her,
Dr Bloom.
I hope one day you'll appreciate
my lack of it.
You really think Abigail Hobbs
helped her father kill those girls?
I think it's a possibility
that needs to be ruled out.
If Abigail didn't help her father,
maybe she knows who did.
- How was she when you saw her?
- Surprisingly practical.
Suspiciously practical?
I would suggest you can be practical
without being a murderer.
- I think she's hiding something.
- (Lecter) It may simply be a trauma.
Yeah, it could also be more.
She has a penchant for manipulation.
Withheld information
to gain information.
She demonstrated only enough emotions
to prove she had them.
You're beginning to appreciate
my lack of sympathy?
You said it may be more
than trauma yet you question
her involvement in the murders
the father committed.
What I'm questioning
is her state of mind.
I want Will Graham to talk to her.
Jack, not yet.
You are not Will Graham's psychiatrist,
Dr Bloom. Dr Lecter is.
Garrett Jacob Hobbs,
the, uh, Minnesota Shrike,
abducted and murdered eight girls
over an eight-month period.
Each of them had the same hair colour,
same eye colour,
same age, same height,
same weight
as his daughter Abigail.
There was a ninth victim
who also fit Abigail Hobbs's profile,
but Garrett Jacob Hobbs
didn't murder her.
The killer who did wanted us to know
he wasn't the Minnesota Shrike.
He's better than that.
He is an intelligent psychopath.
He is a sadist.
He will never kill like this again.
So how do we catch him?
Giving a lecture on Hobbs's copycat?
Well, we need every good mind
we can get on this.
This copycat is an avid reader
of Freddie Lounds
and tattlecrime.com.
He had intimate knowledge
of Garrett Jacob Hobbs's murders,
motives, patterns,
enough to recreate them
and, arguably, elevate them to art.
How intimately did he know
Garrett Jacob Hobbs?
Did he appreciate him from afar
or did he engage him?
Did he ingratiate himself
into Hobbs's life?
Did Hobbs know his copycat
as he was known?
Before Garrett Jacob Hobbs
murdered his wife
and attempted to do the same
to his daughter,
he received an untraceable call.
I believe the as-yet unidentified caller
was our copycat killer.
So you're not a doctor, a nurse
or a psychiatrist?
I'm a journalist.
I want to tell the truth.
Your truth.
Sometimes that involves
some deception,
but know this,
I will never lie to you.
Sounds like something
a liar would say.
If you tell me what you know,
I can help you fill in the blanks.
How about you tell me
what you know?
Your dad was the Minnesota Shrike.
Your mother wasn't the first person
your father killed.
He killed eight girls.
- Eight girls that looked...
- Just like me.
Yes.
Why do they call him the Shrike?
It's a bird that impales its prey,
harvests the organs to eat later.
He was very sick.
Does that mean I'm sick too?
You'll be fighting that perception.
Perception is the most important thing
in your life right now.
- I don't care what anybody thinks.
- You'd better start caring, Abigail.
What you remember,
what you tell everyone
is going to define the rest
of your life. Let me help you.
How did they catch him?
A man named Will Graham.
Works for the FBI but isn't FBI.
He captures insane men
because he can think like them.
Because he is insane.
Would you excuse us, please?
I'm Special Agent Will Graham...
By Special Agent
he means not really an agent.
He didn't get past the screening
process. Too unstable.
I really must insist
you leave the room.
If you wanna talk...
Abigail, this is Dr Lecter.
Do you remember us?
I remember you.
You killed my dad.
You've been in bed for days, Abigail.
Why don't we have a walk?
I'm sorry we couldn't save
your mother.
We did everything we could
but she was already gone.
I know.
I saw him kill her.
He was loving right up
until the second he wasn't.
Kept telling me he was sorry,
to just hold still.
He was gonna make it all go away.
There was plenty wrong
with your father, Abigail,
but there's nothing wrong with you.
You say he was loving.
I believe it.
That's what you brought out in him.
It's not all I brought out in him.
I'm gonna be messed up.
Aren't I?
I'm worried about nightmares.
We'll help you with the nightmares.
There's no such thing as getting used
to what you experienced.
It bothers me a lot.
I worry about nightmares too.
So killing somebody,
even if you have to do it...
it feels that bad?
It's the ugliest thing in the world.
I wanna go home.
Special Agent Graham.
I never formally introduced myself.
I'm Freddie Lounds.
Are you trying to salvage this joke
from the mouth of madness?
Please. Let me apologise
for my behaviour in there.
It was sloppy and misguided
and hurtful.
Miss Lounds, now is not the time.
Look, you and I may have
our own reasons for being here,
but I also think
we both genuinely care
about what happens
to Abigail Hobbs.
- You told her I was insane.
- I can undo that.
You help Abigail see me
as more than her father's killer
and I help you
with online ad sales?
I can undo what I said.
I can also make it a lot worse.
Miss Lounds... it's not very smart
to piss off a guy
who thinks about killing people
for a living.
(Crawford) "It isn't very smart
to piss off a guy
"who thinks about killing
people for a living."
You know what else isn't very smart?
You were there with him.
And you let those words
come out of his mouth.
I trust Will to speak for himself.
Evidently you shouldn't.
I'm just happy the story
wasn't about Abigail Hobbs.
Well, then it's a victory.
So Abigail Hobbs wants to go home.
Let's take her home.
What Abigail wants and what
she needs are different things.
Taking her out of a controlled
environment would be reckless.
(Crawford) You said she was practical.
(Graham) That could mean
she has a dissociative disorder.
You take her home, she may
experience intense emotions,
respond aggressively,
or re-enact some aspect
of the traumatic event
without even realising it.
Where do you weigh in on this,
Doctor?
Dr Bloom is right.
But there is a scenario where revisiting
the trauma event could help Abigail heal
and actually prevent denial.
Then we have a difference of opinion,
therefore I am going to choose
the opinion that best serves
my agenda.
I need to know if you're right
about the copycat, Will.
We have no way of knowing what's
waiting for her when she goes home.
(Lounds) Thanks again
for meeting with me.
- I know this hasn't been easy for you.
- Oh yeah? How would you know?
I've been writing about
Garrett Jacob Hobbs.
I've spoken to the relatives
of some of his other victims.
Hobbs is dead.
He deserved a lot worse.
Him and his whole family.
There must be some small comfort
knowing that justice was sewed.
Comfort?
My sister was impaled on a severed
stag head, cut down the middle.
He pulled out her lungs
while she was still breathing.
- There's no comfort in that.
- I'm sorry. I am.
But you have to try not
to remember her that way.
What do you want from me?
I just thought you should know
Abigail Hobbs came out of her coma.
- Is this where my mum died?
- (Graham) Yes.
I was sort of expecting
a body outline in chalk or tape.
They only do that if you're still alive
and taken to the hospital
before they finish the crime scene.
Goodbye, Mum.
If you ever wanna go,
you just have to say so and we'll go.
Go where? The hospital?
For now.
They turned all the pictures around.
Crime scene cleaners will do that.
They did a really good job.
Is that where all my blood was?
Yes.
You do this a lot?
Go places and think about killing?
Too often.
- So you pretended to be my dad.
- And... people like your dad.
What did it feel like?
To be him?
It feels... like...
I'm talking to his shadow
suspended on dust.
No wonder you have nightmares.
The attacks on you
and your mother were different.
They were desperate.
Your dad knew he was out of time.
- Somebody told him we were coming.
- The man on the phone?
It was a blocked call.
Did you recognise his voice?
I'd never heard it before.
(Bloom) Was there anybody new
in your father's life?
Someone you met
or someone he talked about?
Abigail, he may have been contacted
by another killer.
A copycat.
Someone who's still out there?
Yeah.
- Can you catch somebody's crazy?
- "Folie à deux."
- What?
- It's a French psychiatric term.
Madness shared by two.
See?
One cannot be delusional if the belief
in question is accepted as ordinary
by others in that person's culture
or subculture. Or family.
My dad didn't seem delusional.
He was a perfectionist.
Your dad left hardly any evidence.
Is that why you let me come home?
To find evidence?
It was one of many considerations.
Are we gonna re-enact the crime?
You be my dad, you be my mum,
and you be the man on the phone.
Abigail, we wanted you to come home
to help you leave home behind.
You're not gonna find
any of those girls.
- (Graham) What makes you say that?
- He would honour every part of them.
He used to make plumbing putty
out of elk's bones.
Whatever bones are left of those girls
are probably holding pipes together.
- Where did he make this putty?
- At the cabin.
- I can show you tomorrow.
- (Door opens)
Abigail, there's someone here.
Hey, Abigail.
So, uh, does that hurt?
Sometimes.
Everybody on the block was
on the news.
And everyone at school.
Such whores.
- Did you talk to the news?
- No.
No!
My mum doesn't want me talking
to you, much less the news.
Since when do you listen to her?
Well, clearly I don't.
I'm talking to you right now.
Everybody thinks you did it,
you know?
Do you think I did it?
I don't think you're the type.
Then again, I didn't think your father
was the murder-suicide type.
Although I guess the hunting
could've been a clue.
Mine or his?
Both, now that you mention it.
I don't think you did it.
- I do.
- This is private property.
You were the bait, right?
That's how it worked?
You lure them back to daddy for
dinner? How'd you trap my sister?
- Did you chat her up?
- Hey! Piss off!
Did you help your old man
cut out my sister's lungs
while she was still using...?
(Abigail) He said he was
somebody's brother.
- Marissa! Come home.
- No.
- Come home!
- Can you stop being such a bitch?
- See you later.
- Bye.
He's gone.
You've never seen him before?
(Abigail) No.
(Graham) Let's get back to the hotel.
We'll go to the cabin tomorrow.
We should report this, yes?
Yes.
I'm sorry, OK? This must all stop.
I'm gonna make it all go away.
(Alarm beeping)
He cleaned everything.
He said he was afraid of germs,
but I guess he was just afraid
of getting caught.
No one else ever came
here with your dad,
except you.
He made everything by himself.
Glue, butter...
He sold the pelts on eBay
or in town.
He'd make pillows.
No parts went to waste.
Otherwise it was murder.
He was feeding them to us.
Wasn't he?
It's very likely.
Before he cut my throat,
he told me he killed those girls
so he wouldn't have to kill me.
You're not responsible for anything
your father did, Abigail.
If he would've just killed me,
none of those other
girls would be dead.
We don't know that.
Your father...
I need ERT at the Hobbs cabin.
- (Bloom) Abigail...
- (Screams)
Marissa!
Do you think she knew
the guy down by the stream?
Somebody's brother.
Not somebody.
Abigail said he asked
if she helped her dad
take his sister's lungs
while she was alive.
The young woman on the stag head.
Cassie Boyle.
Had a brother, Nicholas.
But Garrett Jacob Hobbs
didn't kill Cassie Boyle.
I know.
Garrett Jacob Hobbs would've
honoured every part of her.
You brought Abigail Hobbs
back to Minnesota to find out
if she was involved
in her father's murders
and another girl dies.
Yep, scraped his knuckle
on her teeth.
There's foreign tissue and
what could be trace amounts of blood.
You said that this copycat was
an intelligent psychopath, Will.
That there would be
no traceable motive, no pattern.
He wouldn't kill again this way.
You said it.
I may have been wrong about that.
Yes, because Garrett Jacob Hobbs
never struck his victims.
Why would the copycat do it?
I think he was provoked.
Nicholas Boyle murdered this girl
and his own sister.
- With or without Abigail Hobbs?
- Without.
Do you think that Abigail Hobbs
knew Nicholas or Cassie Boyle?
No...
You don't think she knew them?
Or don't wanna think
that she knew them?
She said she didn't know them.
Dr Bloom says that
Abigail has a penchant
for, uh... manipulation.
Is she manipulating you, Will?
Agent Crawford.
He said he was wrong
about the copycat killer.
I want to know what else
he's wrong about.
Whoever killed the girl on the field
killed this girl, I'm right about that.
He knew exactly
how to mount the body.
Wound patterns are almost
identical to Cassie Boyle.
Same design, the same...
...humiliation.
Abigail Hobbs is not a killer.
But she could be the target of one.
I think it's time that Abigail Hobbs
left home permanently.
Doctor, would you be good
enough to collect Abigail
and all of her belongings and
escort her out of Minnesota, please?
Not you, Will.
I want you here.
(Reporters) Abigail! Abigail!
You killed my daughter!
- Abigail...
- Why come back here?
Why did you come back here?
Why come back?
Stay here.
(Woman sobs)
Abigail!
Miss Lounds, you're on
the wrong side of the police line.
I've been covering the Minnesota Shrike
long before you got involved.
I wanna help you tell your story.
You need me now more than ever.
- I wanna talk to her.
- No, you don't. Go inside.
I'm not the only one lurking about
the Hobbs house peeking in windows.
You really should monitor
those police lines more carefully.
Have you seen a young man,
mid-20s, ginger hair, unwashed?
I'll tell you if I saw him
if you tell me why it's important.
(Sobbing softly)
(Hobbs) 'None of her
is gonna go to waste.'
I'm not gonna hurt you.
I just want you to listen to me.
I didn't kill that girl, OK?
I didn't kill her!
Wait!
Listen! I didn't...
Abigail?
(Lecter) She'll be all right.
Show me what happened.
- He was gonna kill me.
- Was he?
This isn't self-defence, Abigail.
You butchered him.
I didn't...
They will see what you did,
and they'll see you as an accessory
to the crimes of your father.
I wasn't.
I can help you, if you ask me to.
At great risk to my career
and my life.
You have a choice.
You can tell them you were defending
yourself when you gutted this man...
Or we can hide the body.
No, I don't remember anything.
Maybe a blur out of the corner
of my eye,
and then a big fat cut to black.
(Crawford) Well, Nicholas Boyle
attacked Abigail, you.
Struck Dr Lecter
in the back of the head.
- Well, where's Abigail?
- Lecter took her back to the hotel.
She scratched Nicholas Boyle
on his way out the back door.
The blood on her hands
matches the tissue that we pulled
from Marissa Schurr's mouth.
And then what,
he... he got away?
We'll catch him one way
or another.
Where are you going?
I wanna go home.
(Creaking)
Hello, Abigail.
- How did you know it was me?
- The hospital called.
You climbed over the wall.
Where else were you to go?
Home's no longer an option.
Come down from there.
I don't want to go to sleep.
You can't anticipate your dreams.
Can't block them, can't repress.
I didn't honour any part of him
so it's just murder, isn't it?
Most would argue self-defence.
Then why not tell the truth?
Most would argue.
There would still be those who would
say you were taking after your father.
You're glad I killed him.
What would be the alternative?
- That he kill you?
- I don't know if he was going to.
No, you don't.
You're the one who called the house.
You talked to my dad before...
What did you say to him?
A simple conversation,
ascertaining if he was home
for an interview.
Then why not tell the truth?
I think you called the house
as a serial killer.
Just like my dad.
I'm nothing like your dad.
I made a mistake.
Something easily misconstrued.
Not unlike yourself.
I'll keep your secret.
And I'll keep yours.
No more climbing walls, Abigail.