I need your help. You gonna
tell me what's going on?
It's Kacey.
- Kacey's gone missing before.
I know, but Kacey was picked up
by a john in a red pickup truck.
I saw a red pickup truck
outside of my house.
You think he's been following you?
- I don't know.
Kacey ever go down the airport?
- Never.
The girl that OD'd this week had a napkin...
...from 7 Brothers near the airport.
I'm gonna go and see if
anybody recognizes the victims.
Yeah,
I know that girl.
She was in here with this guy,
Jimmy Scanlon.
They were fighting really bad.
I need to speak to Jimmy Scanlon.
He hasn't been in in days.
I'm not convinced that Michaela's
not in some kind of trouble.
I worry about that little boy.
You heard of a guy
named Dock McClatchie?
No.
- He's tagged in a bunch of pictures...
...on Kacey's Facebook page.
You recognize him?
No.
What is it?
Nothing.
You're gonna go look for her, aren't you?
Hello, Mickey.
You know who I am?
Kacey told me about you.
I'm not... I'm not trying to make trouble.
I'm just trying to f... find my sister.
Yeah? I'm trying to find her too.
She took something of mine.
Whatever it is, I'm sure--
- Whatever it is,
it's between me and her.
Well, I know she was here 'cause
I saw her shoes in the other room.
So now you care all of a sudden, huh?
Look, I already told ya,
she ain't here.
Now go.
This ain't a place for you.
Take it.
Go on, take it.
I give one warning shot.
I'm fair.
Now, don't ever come back here again.
You know what I do for work, right?
I don't know what you want
to find her so bad for anyway.
Don't you got better things to worry about?
Like what?
Like your son.
Thomas, right?
Cute kid.
Stay away from my son.
Stay away from my house.
Okay, so you've given them
all their cards, then what?
Uh, then, we see if they raise.
Very good.
Uh, don't tell your mother
anything about the soda, okay?
It's our little secret.
Okay.
You in or you out?
Yeah, McGivney.
Kid doesn't have all night.
You're a natural.
What the hell?
What... What is he doing here?
Yeah, Gee.
What's the kid doing here?
McGivney, don't help.
Please.
Kid's having fun is what he's doing.
Oh, yeah? The kid's supposed to be
doing his math homework at your house.
He is.
We're working on probabilities.
All right.
Get your coat.
I asked you to do one thing for me.
Just one. One thing.
Why can't you do that?
Cool your jets.
The kid's gonna be all right.
I raised you,
and you're doing just fine.
Yeah, I'm just winning at life.
You're mad.
I'm not mad at you.
I'm mad at the infant you
have for a great-grandfather.
But I was having fun in there.
I know.
That's not the point, though.
Gee-Pop knows better.
Just... please don't push him away.
You getting your stuff
all packed for tomorrow?
Good job, buddy.
Luck is what happens when preparation...
Meets opportunity.
- Yep.
Well, just because
I get upset with Gee-Pop,
doesn't mean we're not going to see him.
You don't believe me?
We don't see any of our family.
For like, Thanksgiving
and Christmas and stuff.
David at school told me he
sees his cousins every week.
All the holidays too.
Do you not like them or something?
Of course I like them.
I just... I...
I usually have to work
during those holidays.
Do you have to work this year?
I... I don't know yet.
'Cause I need pictures of
them for my family tree.
And if we could go to
Thanksgiving, then I could--
I have pictures of...
I have pictures. Come on.
All right.
Okay.
There's cousin Hailey.
Caden.
You can take these.
You can take 'em out for your tree.
I've never seen this picture. That's--...
That's you?
- Mm. Yeah.
How old were you there?
I was about eight,
I think.
She's so beautiful, right?
You look just like her.
And that's your dad.
Yeah, long time ago.
- Before he died.
How come you never talk about him?
Well, he wasn't really
around much when I was a kid.
Like my dad.
Where's their father?
Gee didn't want him here.
I heard he's not doing too well these days.
They say it was a lot of things,
but you know what it was.
We all know what it was.
It was that damn drug
that got her in the end.
You poor souls.
She loved you two more than anything.
You never forget that.
Look, Mick,
it's Daddy.
Kacey,
get away from the window.
Gee will see.
Son of a bitch.
How dare you come here,
you fucking no-good junkie!
Mr. O 'Brien, please.
- You did this to her.
You killed her.
You killed my baby girl!
Mickey,
is Mama gone?
Yeah.
She's gone.
- To heaven?
Yeah.
And she's not coming back?
No.
Who's gonna be my mama now?
I'll be yours.
And you'll be mine.
What's his name?
And he knows Dock?
Name is Winton.
Owns a tire store near a
dope set at K and Westmorland.
Keeps it looking
closed up from the outside.
Why?
Because he runs a supervised
injection site on the inside.
Unofficially.
What'd you do last night after I left?
Hello, Mickey.
I had to help Thomas out
with his homework.
He wants to see his cousins
for Thanksgiving.
And that's a bad idea why?
'Cause they kinda suck.
He's not gonna see his dad?
- Mm-mm.
I'll come with you if you want.
To your cousin's.
You know, strength in numbers.
I wouldn't do that to you.
You might be doing it for me.
Sheila's taking the girls to visit her parents.
Mm.
And I still can't get used to not
seeing them during the holidays.
Since we separated.
You don't think that you
guys can work it out?
Sheila's thinks I'm still betting.
Are you?
Sheila didn't believe me. So.
I guess there's no reason to stop.
What about you and Thomas' father?
You think you'll work that out?
That was over
before Thomas was even born.
That's why I transferred to the 30th.
You know, all the time we were
partners, you never told me that.
Yeah,
there's nothing to tell
Hello.
I understand, yeah.
Sure, yeah.
I'll come after work.
Hey! Hey, you! Hey, I'm
over here! Great, thanks.
Yeah, he's a regular.
I got it.
Everything okay?
Simon stopped paying tuition.
Oh,
so everything's not okay.
No warning.
No nothing.
That why you sold the house?
Yeah.
- I wondered about that.
How can a father not want to see his kid?
He deserves better than that.
So do you, Mick.
Sure. I know, Dock.
He comes in here every now
and again, use the back.
He a dealer?
Yeah.
- Of what?
Drugs, girls.
Got a rough crowd he runs with.
You know where we can find him?
Mm-mm.
No, last time I knew,
he was, uh,
squatting at an abando off Braddock.
I don't know if he's still there.
You know this girl?
Her name is Kacey Fitzpatrick.
Yeah, I know Kacey.
Sweet kid.
She used to come in here with Dock.
Used to? Have you seen her recently?
Not for a couple months.
And the last time she was here,
she was all beat up.
Her eye was swollen shut.
I gave her some ice and some Advil.
You think that Dock might have
been the one to beat her up?
I don't know.
Could have been a john.
What's this about,
Truman?
Kacey's missing.
We're tryna find her.
Do you think Dock could
have done something to Kacey?
Like what?
- Like kill her.
Dock...
...talks a big game,
but he's no killer.
He-He's more bark than bite,
if you ask me.
Maybe you should have asked Kacey.
Mickey.
How are you so sure Dock's the guy?
You know something I don't?
No, I just... I have... just
a feeling about that guy.
Look, I know you want to find her. I do too.
We gotta explore every avenue, all right?
Not just the Dock leads.
- All right. Yeah.
Let's talk to this Jimmy Scanlon's family.
If he was seen arguing
with one of the victims,
maybe his wife knows something about it.
I got a friend at Delaware PD.
He'll set up a meeting.
All right.
I gotta go to work.
Ahearn's already pissed off
because of yesterday.
All right, I'll give you a ride.
- Thanks.
What's going on?
Danjarat found a video of the
perp in those girls' murders.
You can't see shit.
He's purposely keeping his face hidden.
Wearing gloves too.
So we know he's six feet or taller.
Couple hundred pounds.
Race, indiscernible.
A Wildwood sweatshirt's our
biggest get, in terms of ID.
Dude's got to be white.
- Excuse me?
Black people
don't go to Wildwood anymore.
They go to AC.
Is this footage taken near
the Taylor Yoon crime scene?
Yeah.
Well, this,
coupled with the witness account...
...from the second victim's crime scene,
tells us we may have our perp.
Show this around the neighborhood.
See if any of the girls recognize him.
Do you recognize this guy, Alonzo?
Mm-mm.
- His name is Dock McClatchie.
Okay.
- Kacey's got a thing with him.
Or used to.
I don't.
Most of the time Kacey was in here,
she was working, so...
Thanks.
- Yeah.
Nicole! Nicole! Nicole?
Hey, you got a sec?
Nicole.
Hey, you all right?
Will you look at something for me?
What's wrong?
You all right, Nicole?
And it was like she was mad at me.
Or scared.
- Of you?
I don't know.
And it wasn't just Nicole, either.
Every woman on the avenue
was the same way.
It's just, they've never
been like that with me.
You know, there's a killer on the loose.
Maybe they're just all on edge.
But why run from me?
Right?
Don't take this the wrong way, Mick, but...
...are you holding back on something?
No. Why?
Universe is speaking to me.
What is the universe saying?
It's saying,
'Truman,
'Mickey's holding back on something.'
You know you can talk to
me about anything, right?
Yeah.
Hey, remember.
We've got to be careful what
we ask Scanlon's wife in there.
Can't be raising too many flags
on a case that's not ours.
Yeah.
It just isn't like Jimmy to disappear like this.
Our son, he's sick, and all he keeps
asking is when Daddy's coming home.
He has to come home.
On the night that Jimmy disappeared,
was he acting differently?
Behaving weird?
He was anxious. Uh...
He got a call, told me he had
to meet someone from work.
I didn't ask who.
I should have asked who.
But the weird thing was that the cops...
...at the Wilmington Police Department...
...said that no call came in on his phone.
So he might have had a burner.
What's that?
A second phone.
Oh, God. Did he?
Do you recognize...
...these women?
No.
Why? Who are they?
Well, this is Elizabeth O'Connor,
and this is Taylor Yoon.
And they were...
They both went missing...
...around the same time
that your husband did.
And you think they...
...they may have had something
to do with him being missing?
We're just trying to see if any of
these disappearances are related.
So you handed over your phone
records to the Delaware Police?
They said they didn't
find anything unusual.
How about bank accounts?
Uh, I gave them everything.
But I mean,
there wasn't anything weird.
We shared our accounts,
so I would know.
Is there any chance
that he had a bank account...
...that you didn't know about?
Um...
Sorry, I... I...
I wouldn't know the first thing
about trying to find that.
Um... we... I... I...
I thought we shared everything.
Okay, um,
thank you for your time.
Thank you.
DPD are doing everything they
can to try and find your husband.
Yeah.
Uh...
Do you recognize this guy?
His name is Dock McClatchie.
Does that name ring a bell?
- Mickey.
No.
Sorry.
Okay.
- Come on.
Girls, I hear ya cackling up there any more.
I'm gonna give you
somethin' to cackle about.
How come he doesn't like us?
He does.
He's just sad
'cause we remind him of Mom.
Besides, we don't need Gee-Pop.
Right?
All we need is each other.
Come here.
I want to show you something.
Whoa, what is that?
It's for us.
You ever need to hide something,
you put it in here.
You ever need to tell me anything,
And if you ever need to tell me something...
I'll put it in here, too.
We can put notes and stuff.
And no one will ever see it.
Except me and you.
- Except me and you.
This is Danjarat.
Detective Danjarat,
it's Mickey Fitzpatrick.
I'm sorry I'm calling so late,
but do you have a second?
Sure. I'm still at the station
if you can believe that.
No rest for the weary.
Yeah, something like that.
Anyway, what's up?
Mickey?
Yeah. So...
I-I showed the video around today...
...and one of the women I spoke to...
...thought she recognized the guy
in the Wildwood sweatshirt.
Uh, she's scared to come forward officially,
but she did give me a name.
What was the name?
Dock McClatchie.
If you keep putting your head down,
they'll think you're sleeping.
Even if you're not.
Just look out the window.
if you get bored.
Okay, okay. It's just not easy
sitting still for a whole hour.
They should make classes shorter.
Hey.
Mickey,
what's in there?
Nothing.
No, seriously,
I want to know.
An oboe.
That's cool.
Can I hear you play?
I always wanted to play an
instrument. My dad won't let me.
Can I hear?
Don't.
Thank you.
It's really nice of you.
Give that back!
That was a mistake,
little girl.
Now I'm definitely not giving it back.
Kacey! Stop!
Come on.
Let's go home.
Were you waiting long? Okay.
- No, no.
Mickey, the problem... Oh...
- I wanted to... Sorry.
I wanted to apologize,
uh, for my outburst.
It... it...
I was upset with the situation, not with you.
I understand.
Thank you.
I apologize, too.
Thomas is a really special child,
and I'd do anything to keep him here.
Except actually keep him here?
I went to the school board on his behalf.
Their argument is that he's already
a recipient of a partial scholarship...
...and that your financial situation
hasn't demonstrably changed.
But they have agreed to keep Thomas
through to the end of this term, and...
Then he'll have to...
Have to leave.
You can say it.
Yeah, I'm afraid that's the case.
Unless you can get Thomas's father--
No. Not an option.
Look.
I looked up the public school
in your catchment.
It's actually quite good.
But it wouldn't be the public
school in our catchment.
Uh, it doesn't allow for early drop-off,
so he'll have to go to Ashbridge.
I see.
- Which is where I went when I was a kid.
And it wasn't good.
It was overcrowded.
Thirty-three kids to a
classroom, and Thomas is just...
He's not the kind of kid who...
Keep the money.
What?
- No one knows you gave it to me.
I wish there was something
more I could do for Thomas.
So do I. Thank you.
It's called Ashbridge Elementary.
It has an aftercare program as well.
Just like Valley Green.
So then I'll just pick you up at night.
It's, uh, it's where you went, right?
Mm-hmm.
Your new school?
Yeah, that's where I went.
Did you like it?
I loved it.
This is Ashkenazy's version, but
I think I like Sokolov's better.
You're lying.
What?
When you said you loved your old school.
I heard you talking about it before with Gee.
You told him it was terrible
and that you hated it.
You told him that's the reason you
were sending me to Valley Green Friends.
I don't remember saying that.
But if I did--
- I'm not a baby.
What does that mean?
You tell me the least important stuff.
Instruments and the planet
and trees and the government.
But Thomas,
those things are important.
I know too much about the
history of Philadelphia.
And about Faust and the devil and about...
I don't know,
about bird calls.
Do you not like learning
about those things?
I do, but...
I'm big now, and you can
tell me the other stuff, too.
Like, that I have to go to a crappy school...
...because we can't afford
a good one anymore.
You need to tell me where my dad's been...
...and why he isn't talking to me,
and why he isn't paying
for school anymore!
Calm down.
He's just...
You can tell me, Mom.
I know I can tell you.
There's just nothing to tell.
But I can tell you something that I think...
...might make you feel better.
I have Thanksgiving off this year.
You do?
All right, here we go.
Hey, guys.
- Hi.
Wow. You really came.
We really came.
Hey, sweetie.
How you been?
Good.
And you are?
Truman. Truman Dawes.
I'm Hailey.
Hailey O'Brien.
Well, come on inside. It's
fuckin' frigid out there.
Ry, you remember Thomas,
don't you?
Are you kidding me?
Like, seriously? Get up.
Get up!
Get the fuck up!
Let's go. Come on.
Why don't you take your cousin
down the basement? Go play.
Come on, let's go.
Truman,
can I get you a plate?
Uh, sure.
Hey, Mick, you, uh,
you want one?
Um...
Yeah.
I'm gonna be right back.
I'll be right back.
Sorry.
I'm gonna...
He's very vulnerable,
but a heck of a player.
Hey.
Look who it is.
What's goin' on?
- You all right?
Yeah. I've been trying to get a hold of ya.
You didn't get my texts?
Nah, something's wrong
with my phone I think.
Yeah, Kacey's missing.
Oh, man,
I'm sorry to hear that.
Do you have any idea where she might be?
Nah, I ain't seen her in a minute.
I ain't been down the Ave much.
Bobby, I don't care if you're dealing.
I just want to know when the
last time you saw Kacey was.
What you think, Jer?
Like two months ago?
Something like that.
Okay, do either of you
know a guy named Dock?
Oh, shit. Yeah. Why?
Because I think that Kacey and Dock
were together before she went missing.
That guy's bad news.
A buddy of his turned
up dead about a year ago.
Rumor has it, he was
skimming off Dock's supply.
When Dock found out about it...
What do you think?
Mm.
Good.
Just good?
I made it.
It's extra good.
- Mm.
You're Mickey's cousin, right?
Yeah.
Were you all close growing up?
Mm, kinda.
I was always closer to her sister, though.
What was Mickey like as a kid?
Mickey was...
I don't know.
Same as she is now.
Smart, quiet, uptight.
Not many friends.
Mostly she just kept to
herself and played her music.
You know, she used
to watch us sometimes.
You know, like, um,
like, babysit.
And guess what she made us do.
What?
Okay. So she would, like,
set up a little audience...
...and put us in chairs,
facing her.
And, like,
play a concert for us.
And, you know, like, I mean, me
and Kacey, we were just the same.
We couldn't sit still for nothin'.
And she'd make us sit there
while she played.
'Course, we always started laughing, and...
...and Mickey would get pissed,
tell my mom.
She always was a little fuckin' narc.
Made to be a cop from day one.
No offense.
None taken.
You know,
I do remember you.
Back when I was still talking
to Mickey. Long time ago.
I met her after work one day.
And you were there.
I remember thinking you were cute.
You're not talking to Mickey?
Why not?
You know, you'll have to
ask Mickey about that.
Gotta warn you though.
She lies.
Here you go, bub.
You okay?
- Yeah.
Is that Mickey?
- Yeah, it's fine.
And Thomas.
- Hi, Aunt Lynn.
Have youse been here the whole time?
Yeah.
He looks just like your mother, honey.
You got so big.
Last time I seen you, you were
- - - We're gonna head out.
Actually--
- Youse're leaving already?
Yeah.
Thanks for having us.
Well, you can't leave yet.
We haven't said grace.
We have to say grace, everyone.
Jesus Christ, Ma.
Everyone's eaten already.
You watch your fucking
mouth, Hailey O'Brien.
It's grace time.
Hold hands.
Everyone hold hands.
I wish you never started
going back to church.
What's that, Hailey?
- Nothing, Ma.
I'll start.
Dear Lord in heaven,
we thank you for the food you
have put on our table today.
We thank you for the roof over our head,
and we pray for the
forgiveness for all our sins,
known...
...and unknown.
And we pray that the Birds
win the Super Bowl.
Amen
- ALL: Amen.
Wait.
The rest of youse gotta go now.
What do you want to pray about?
Just talk to God.
He's listenin'.
Uh, I pray for Loogie and Joey B.
I pray that everything goes good
at Juju's doctor's appointment...
...on Monday.
Lord, please let the Cowboys lose...
...and the Lions game go over
so I can finally hit a parlay.
Hailey.
What do you want to pray for?
Come on. Just say something
you're praying for...
...or something you're grateful for.
I'm praying for Mickey.
Well, I'm grateful for Mickey.
The only problem was that
Ryan said that his sister...
...wouldn't let us use the PlayStation.
And, Mom,
can we get one of those?
'Cause Ryan said that I could
come over and play with it...
...whenever I want when she's not home.
And also he wants to have a sleepover.
And Mom, can we see my
cousins all the time now?
Um...
- Because I really want to.
Because guess what?
Ryan said he can eat whatever he wants...
...out of the fridge anytime he wants it.
So I think we need to see them all the time.
All the time, huh?
Yeah, all the time.
Or, like, every other day and...
Mom?
- Yeah.
Who's the girl with the pink hair?
What'd you say?
The girl with the pink hair.
I brought my family tree there
to fill in some stuff...
...and when I showed it to Ryan,
he said I was missing
the girl with the pink hair.
I don't know what he meant.
Uh...
I think he might have been mistaken.
Okay.
Go let yourself in.
I'll be right there.
Can you start getting ready for bed?
Yeah.
- Good night, Thomas.
Good night, Truman.
I never talked to him about her.
Just, I always felt like it was safer not to.
Thank you for coming.
Don't say a fucking word.
I know it was you.
Mom!
I can't find my toothbrush!
I'll...
I'll be right up, babe.
What? What was me?
What was me?
Got a visit today
from some of your cop buddies.
You telling me that's a coincidence?
If you fuck with my life,
I'll fuck with yours.
Maybe I should go up there,
talk to Thomas, huh?
Like you had your buddies
come talk to me today?
Please... please, don't.
I swear...
I didn't send...
I didn't send them.
I didn't.
- Mickey.
We both know you're lying. Okay?
Tell me the truth.
You sent them.
Say it. Say it.
Okay.
I sent them.
Get down on the ground. On the ground.
- No.
On the ground.
I told you I give one warning shot, right?
No... not in... Not in front of my kid.
- You had yours already.
Close your eyes.
- Please. No, don't let him...
...find me like this. Please, no!
- Close your eyes.
Okay? Okay.
- Count me down.
One, two, three. Say it!
- No.
One.
One... one.
Two.
Mickey!
Hey, Mickey.
Are you all right?
What happened?
Hey.
No, it's okay.
It's okay.
I think he's gone.
- Who?
Who's gone?
Dock.
McClatchie?
- Yeah.
How'd he even find you?
Why'd he find you?
I...
I found him first.
What?
- Yeah.
The other night, you showed me
that picture of Kacey and Dock...
...in front of this abandoned house.
- Yeah.
I know that house.
- How?
It's been used for shit like that for years.
Kacey OD'd there once,
when she was in high school.
I had to, like, go and save her.
But...
why didn't you call me?
Why would you go there alone, Mickey?
You know,
I don't fucking get it.
Why the fuck you hiding shit from me?
Of all people.
I'm just trying to help you.
Truman,
it's complicated.
What's so fucking complicated, Mick?
Aren't we friends?
Have I ever let you down my whole life?
Have I ever done anything
to make you not trust me?
No.
- No.
No. Then why?
I... I...
- I just don't get it.
You know what your cousin
Hailey said about you?
She said you lie, Mickey.
You got a problem.
You got a bad sense of who to let in.
The people who never let you down,
those are the people you let in.
But those who let you down
again and again and again,
those are the ones you push away, Mickey.
You hear what I'm saying?
Okay,
so let's start again.
Why would you go to Dock's without me?
You know what, Mickey?
When you're ready to talk,
I'm here.
I found it.
Mom,
I have to spit.
Hi.
- Mickey.
Yeah. I'm sorry to disturb you on holiday,
but I just wanted to let you know
we looked into Dock McClatchie.
We brought him in for questioning, but...
He's got an airtight alibi for at
least two of the three homicides.
What is it?
He was in custody at the time.
Mickey?
Mom?
You okay?
Mom,
can you talk to me?
How did you--
- I stole it back.
But how?
- It doesn't matter.
But Louis won't ever bother you again.
That's dangerous, Kacey. Louis
Driscoll's dad is really mean.
Anyway,
it's my job to take care of you.
Not the other way around.
I want to take care of you, too.
You can tell me stuff,
and maybe I can help you.
You're my mom.
And I'm yours, too.
You said so.
So when you're ready to talk.
I'm here.
What are you thinking about?
My birthday party.
- Oh.
I want to have everyone this year.
Can I?
- Mm-hmm.
I want to have it at,
uh, Land-O-Fun.
And I want to invite Carlotta and Lila.
Okay.
And Dad.
I wanna invite Dad.
Thomas, I want to discuss
something with you.
You've been asking about
where your father is and...
I've never told you the truth because...
I didn't want to hurt you.
And now I can tell that
not telling you the truth...
...is hurting you more.
As far as I know,
there's nothing going on...
...in your dad's life that's
preventing him from seeing you.
He's just...
not being a good dad.
Or a good person.
I, uh, I think that he's making...
...all the wrong choices right now.
And this is not your fault.
Okay?
Because you're perfect.
Hey.
You are perfect.
Do you hear me?
Do you understand me?
This is on him.
Okay, Thomas?
Okay?
But can we still ask him?
Just to see?
He loves Land-O-Fun.
I will ask him,
but I don't want you...
...to be disappointed if he can't make it.
Hey.
You like Truman, right?
- Yeah.
You think he's a smart guy?
Do you know what he
said to me the other day?
He said that there are
some people you let in,
and some people you keep out.
And I think that it's time for both of us...
...to recognize which one
of those your dad is.
So, does this mean Dad won't
take me to see the Sixers anymore?
Well, I'll take you to see the Sixers.
You don't know anything about basketball.
I do. I do, too.
Name one player on the team.
Allen Iverson.
Mom.
Okay, okay,
but I will learn.
I'm smart.
I'm good at learning things.
Kacey! Kacey!
Kacey!
You need something?
Sorry.
Three-alarm fire at 222 Braddock Street.
56201 responding.
Was anybody inside?
Not sure. It was pretty
well gone when we got here.
Keep some distance.
Get in line.
Where's that water?
Paula!
Was Kacey inside?
Was... was she inside?
Come on, Paula. Come on.
Please!
- No! I told you. She's gone.
Can you help me out
with something? Please?
What?
Did you know any of the girls
who were killed?
What about 'em?
- I got a video of the perp.
Can you look at it? Just see
if you recognize him, please?
He's still out there.
Paula, come on.
Look at the video.
Come on!
God, Mickey.
Are you serious?
Are you shittin' me?
Serious about what?
- Don't bullshit me.
Don't bullshit me.
You know him?
Yeah, I know him.
You know him too.
'Cause he's a cop.
Guy comes around here,
wavin' his badge for blowjobs.
It's only a matter of time
before he upped his game.
What? Wait, wait.
- You stay away from me!
You're gonna get me killed.
I'm ready to talk.