Oz.
That's the name on the street
for the Oswald Maximum
Security Penitentiary.
[BUZZER SOUNDS]
HILL: Oz is retro.
Oz is retribution.
You wanna punish a man?
Separate him from his family,
separate him from himself,
cage him up with his own kind.
[YELLING]
[BUZZER SOUNDING]
HILL: Oz is hard times doing hard time.
GLYNN: McManus, don't you ever knock?
Been through the files
of the inmates that arrived today.
-I want Tobias Beecher.
-Okay.
-Miguel Alvarez.
-That'll be tough. He's in the hospital,
-stab wound to the chest.
-He gonna live?
Apparently. MAN: Fuck you, Healy.
-All right.
HEALY: Shut the fuck up, asshole,
before I come in there-
-Hey, warden.
-Hello, Mike.
And I want, uh, Donald Groves.
-Groves?
-Yeah.
Let me ask you something,
don't take this the wrong way.
-What?
-Are you out of your fucking mind?
Groves is a demented sociopath
without a skoosh of remorse.
-Well, maybe.
-He ate his parents.
He killed them,
carved them up, and he ate them.
-What can you do with him?
-Teach him table manners.
The only thing a guy like that
understands is punishment,
hard and swift. McMANUS: Mm-hm.
MAN 1: Come here and lick me.
Leo, you said it yourself,
our first conversation,
all we do is recycle.
MAN 2: Warden, need to talk to you.
-Later, Johnson, later.
A new inmate comes in, we sit on him,
send him back out,
he's back with a vengeance.
If we don't do something different,
we don't do something radical,
we're never gonna break the chain.
Groves isn't going out. He's here
till God drop-kicks him to hell.
Do I have to call the commissioner?
I was given total autonomy
to run cell block 5 my way.
Fine, take Groves.
-Thank you.
-And Paul Markstrom.
Markstrom? He's a petty drug dealer,
and I got enough petty drug dealers.
You want Groves, you take Markstrom.
Why? JOHNSON: Warden, I need to talk.
Why? JOHNSON: Just give me five minutes.
He's my cousin.
HILL: Timmy McManus.
He created
an experimental unit inside Oz,
a new approach to the prison problem.
Some people call it Emerald City.
To me, it's a concentration camp.
In Emerald City we got rules,
got a lot more rules
than anywhere else in Oz.
Your cell is your home,
keep it clean, spotless.
You are to exercise regularly,
attend classes,
go to drug and alcohol counseling.
You are to work
in one of the prison factories.
You are to follow the routine.
We tell you when to sleep,
when to eat, when to piss.
There is no yelling,
no fighting, no fucking.
Follow the rules, learn self-discipline,
because if you'd had any self-discipline,
any control over yourself at all,
you wouldn't be sitting here now.
Questions? MAN: Yeah.
-Can I go to the bathroom?
WITTLESEY: Suck it in, tough guy.
Okay, these are your sponsors,
they will help you
get used to the routine.
I don't want any fucking sponsors.
I don't want any fucking routine.
WITTLESEY: Shut up, Groves.
-Hi, I'm Bob Rebadow.
Nice to meet you too.
Paul Markstrom, Jefferson Keane.
Yo.
Tobias Beecher, Dino Ortolani.
ORTOLANI: I really have to do this?
-Cut the shit. It's your turn.
BEECHER: Hello.
ORTOLANI: Beecher, huh?
I'm guessing you ain't Italian.
What are you in for?
Shaving strokes off your golf score?
HILL: Prisoner number 97B412,
Tobias Beecher.
[TIRES SCREECHING]
HILL: Convicted July 5th, '97.
Driving while intoxicated,
vehicular manslaughter.
Sentence: 15 years.
Up for parole in four.
HILL: In Oz, the guards lock
the cages and walk away
and the predators rise,
take control, and make the rules.
But in Em City, the guards
are with us 24 hours a day.
There's no privacy. Everybody sees
what everybody's doing.
Eyes are everywhere. McManus' eyes.
See, in Em City,
retribution gives way to redemption.
Timmy boy believes he can save
every one of us, from each other,
from ourselves, from the system
that dumped us in here.
Only thing he don't get is,
you gotta want to be saved.
Hey, Dino. How you doing?
Hey, look, pal, I know
I'm supposed to be some kind of bro,
but the headline reads:
"I don't give a shit about you."
That's fine, Dino. Okay.
Hey, let me give you a slice of advice.
-Mm-hm.
-Get yourself a weapon.
Anyone tries to fuck with you,
take them out.
-Anything else?
-Yeah.
Don't smile. Ever. MAN: Dino, telephone.
What are you looking at?
[CHUCKLING]
You got a code for the phone, man?
-MCI.
-What's the number?
Hey, Ginnie, how you doing, baby?
-Yeah, baby, I miss you too.
-Get out the line.
Are the kids around?
POET: I could have sworn
I seen the motherfucker in my cell
Going through my personal effects
He fingers, fingering my cigarettes
Came out like nothing was happening
Whistling his tune
So I mushed his ass, like,
"Move, motherfucker, make room!
Hey. Ain't that my cigarette
Hanging off the tip of your lip?"
I didn't even give him a chance
For his confession
Just leveled his ass
With all that aggression
Left, right, to the dolex
Ha-ha-ha, foots to the chest
Uppercuts to the grill, I'm like, "Kill!"
He's like, "Chill!"
Take that for me Even being in this pace
Take that for that fucking CO
Baton across my face
Feel that for that lawyer
Who ain't give two fucks about me
And feel this, feel this
For me being enslaved by poverty,
Motherfucker
Give me them damn cigarettes
Oh, these is Marlboros
I don't smoke these
[MEN LAUGHING]
I got some veal coming
you are gonna love.
[SPEAKS IN ITALIAN]
-Excuse me, may I sit here?
-No.
-Excuse me, is anybody sitting here?
-You.
-You're right, you know.
-Beg your pardon?
-You're right.
-About what?
REBADOW: Genevieve.
She's thinking about divorcing you.
In fact, she's having lunch
with your old law partner
to talk her through.
-How do you know my wife's name?
-God told me.
Attention! According to new state
health guidelines,
starting the end of the month
smoking will be prohibited
inside Oswald Penitentiary.
[MEN YELLING]
Settle down! Settle down!
Anyone caught with tobacco
will be charged
with possession of contraband
and sent to ADSEG!
That is all.
BEECHER: So this is where
they make the prison uniforms?
Well, actually, no.
The uniforms come from Taiwan.
These are prison clothes we make to sell.
Sell? To who?
They're hip or hop. I'm not sure which.
Grab a bolt and pull.
You know, I'm not really
used to doing this kind of work.
Not that I think there's anything wrong
with it or demeaning.
-What'd you do on the outside?
-I was a lawyer.
I fucking hate lawyers
almost as much as I hate cops.
[BUZZER SOUNDS]
Count!
BEECHER: What now?
-We go to our cells,
they count heads,
then lock us up for the night.
It's 5:00. What am I supposed to do?
-What time is lights out?
-100 p.m.
-What do I do for five hours?
-Try to keep breathing.
Hey, what are you doing with my stuff?
Come on, those are mine.
Anything you got belongs to me.
You understand?
Time to count, gentlemen. Come on out.
I was getting to know my new cell mate.
There's something in the air...
...and it ain't love.
I won't be fucking you, prag.
At least, not tonight.
Hey. Mind if I sit here?
Vern Schillinger.
I understand.
I saw last night, Adebisi giving you shit,
taking your stuff.
This morning he stole my watch.
That sucks.
He tried the same shit with me
when I first got here.
What did you do?
I went to McManus, asked him
to switch me to another pod.
-And he did?
-Yeah, sure.
Just don't say it has to do with Adebisi.
You get him in trouble
and he'll kill you.
-In the meantime, wear armor.
-Armor?
So...
-You ratted on me, eh?
-Back off.
-Who are you telling to back off?
-You, boy.
[LAUGHS]
Oh, yeah? Make me back off.
Play nice.
-I'm on top.
-Okay.
You're not a Jew, are you?
Me? Jewish?
I don't even like Barbra Streisand.
[CHUCKLES]
Like my tattoos?
I'm gonna have to get you one.
-Uh... No, thanks.
-Oh, yeah.
I'm gonna brand you myself.
Livestock gets branded.
Livestock. That's what you are.
My livestock.
Because now, Tobias...
...your ass belongs to me.
HILL: They call this the penal system,
but it's really the penis system.
It's about how big, it's about how long,
it's about how hard.
Life in Oz
is all about the size of your dick,
and anybody who tells you different
ain't got one.
[HUMMING]
[BUZZER SOUNDS]
-Bitch, come on. Breakfast.
-No.
Suit yourself. WITTLESEY: Shakedown.
[ALARM RINGING]
[CHATTERING]
[DOGS BARKING]
No, that ain't mine. That ain't mine!
[YELLING]
-You asshole.
-Hey, get this scum out of here,
do you believe this?
GLYNN: Shakedowns aren't enough.
We need more than a few sniffing dogs
-to stop the flow of drugs.
-We need to fight the addiction.
-No, no, we need to fight the traffic.
-How do we do that?
Week-long lock-down.
Let's see them trying to move their shit
sitting in their cells 24/7.
Yeah, so I get it.
Your big idea is punish everybody,
guilty or not, right?
I don't hear you coming up
with anything better.
I'm telling you, Leo, fucking McManus
is out of fucking control.
He tells me yesterday
he's thinking of starting a quiet time.
You ready for that? An hour every day
when the cons gotta sit in silence.
I mean, what's next?
Milk and cookies? Arts and crafts?
Maybe you should've listened
to what I was saying, Healy.
We gotta make them be quiet in here,
because when they get out and get a job,
they're gonna have to sit
and do their work and be quiet.
Come on, man. What kind
of fairy dust you been snorting?
These stupid fucks aren't gonna go
work for fucking Microsoft.
-It's bullshit.
-If an inmate survives Oz,
he's got balls on the street. I wanna
take some of the glamor away.
I wanna take some of the glory
away from that.
Maybe a high school education,
maybe to learn to fucking read.
If everybody's done making speeches,
I'm moving on.
-Next item, no-smoking rule.
-More bullshit.
You expect us to enforce this ban?
These are state guidelines,
recommended by the Board of Corrections,
passed by the legislature,
signed by the governor.
The governor is an asshole.
You mean politically
or are you speaking personally?
He campaigned on the "no perks
for prisoners" platform.
He's gonna reinstate the death penalty,
he's gonna slash our budget,
he's gonna incite a riot.
HEALY: A riot?
-Yeah.
I heard what happened in the cafeteria.
It's just gonna escalate.
This place is fueled by smoke.
I know that Marlboros
aren't gonna disappear.
They're just gonna go underground
like drugs.
I said we have to enforce the new
rules, I didn't say that I like them.
Next item, Kareem Said.
Now, he arrives today
and I don't have to tell you
what a potential powder keg this can be,
not just because he blew up
a white-owned warehouse
in his community.
Said claims that he is not a criminal,
that he is a political prisoner,
and until all the appeals
and shit are cleared,
he is to be treated with kid gloves.
After that, we can bury him in Gen Pop.
HILL: Prisoner number 97S444.
MAN: Open.
HILL: Kareem Said
AKA Goodson Truman.
Convicted June 6th, '97.
Arson in the second degree.
Sentence: 18 years.
Eligible for parole in five.
In Em City we treat each other the way
that we would like to be treated.
We treat each other with respect.
SAID: And what happens when
one of us does not respect the other?
There's violence.
SAID: Then prison life isn't
all that different to the outside world.
Your celebrity status doesn't buy you
any extra advantages here.
All my prisoners are equal.
[LAUGHING]
How ironic.
To finally be an equal in a place where
I do not have the freedom to enjoy it.
McMANUS: You do the work assigned
you, you stay out of trouble,
we're gonna get along just fine.
Otherwise, you go into the general
population and, Kareem,
in the rest of Oz, nobody's treated
the way they would like to be treated.
Then I consider myself warned.
[MEN CHANTING IN ARABIC]
McMANUS:
I've read a couple of your books.
I know the influence
that you can have over other men.
So I'm hoping we can work together,
make everybody's
stay here more productive.
SAID: I would like to help
my brothers live a full life.
Yes, so would we all.
Anything else we can tell you? SAID: No.
-I do have one thing I can tell you.
GLYNN: What's that?
Seventy-eight percent of the population
at Oswald State Penitentiary
are men of color.
The ratio is, at last count,
one officer for every nine prisoners.
We could take this prison
anytime we want to.
You could take it,
-but you wouldn't be able to keep it.
SAID: Hmm.
That remains to be seen.
You telling me
you intend to start a riot?
What I'm telling you is,
as of today...
...I run Oz.
Don't you fuck with me, my brother.
-Officers.
-As-salamu alaykum, brother.
[MEN CHANTING IN ARABIC]
[CHANTING STOPS]
HILL: There is always in Oz
an undercurrent of fear,
of violence,
of hate,
waiting to explode.
[EXHALES SHARPLY]
Prisoner number 96C382, Dino Ortolani.
Convicted December 12th, '96.
One count murder in the first degree,
assault with a deadly weapon.
Sentence: Life imprisonment
without the possibility of parole.
[GUNSHOTS]
[GRUNTING]
-McManus, we gotta talk.
-About what?
-About sex.
-Sister, you're insatiable.
And you are not that funny.
Now, look, Dino Ortolani
has requested a conjugal visit.
So?
Well, that would make it
the fourth since January.
-So?
-Well, so it's part of my job
to arrange for inmates and their wives-
Excuse me, am I in your way here?
To arrange for inmates
and their wives to make whoopee.
And it's part of your job to tell me
if said inmate has earned said whoopee.
Four times in a year. That's more sex
than I had when I was married.
Maybe that's why you're divorced.
Give him a six-hour conjugal.
-Wow, is that all?
-Yep.
Well, I just hope
he's not a premature ejaculator.
[McMANUS CHUCKLING]
[WHISTLING]
[CHATTERING]
ORTOLANI: Whoa, for a second there
I thought you'd escaped.
-Thanks, kid.
-He ate his mother.
SCHIBETTA: Get out of here.
D'ANGELO: So I heard.
He killed her, then he boiled
the head, smothered it in onions.
-What, no garlic?
-He had his father in the freezer.
Sick fuck. What the fuck's
wrong with this country?
In the old days, murder was murder.
You killed someone, it was business.
-You sure as Christ didn't eat them.
-Times have changed, Nino.
Fuck that. Times changed.
Nothing changes. Nothing ever changes.
Now, my brothers,
we must dedicate ourselves
to a whole different set of principles,
to a whole new set of priorities.
We must rekindle
our natural sense of purity.
The heart and the mind
must be cleansed and set free.
And that means no drugs...
...no alcohol,
and no cigarettes, brother.
[CHUCKLING]
Yes, my brother.
No foul language and no abnormal sex.
You see these temptations?
They must be replaced
by a strict discipline
and a channeled focus.
And not only will our lives here
in Satan's house be improved,
-but our spirits will be renewed.
MAN: Yes, brother.
We are not a gang of hoodlums.
We are a group of men
rooted in Africa and living in America.
We are strong and proud.
We are an entity, a presence.
We are a force,
and we must be dealt with.
We are voices, and we must be heard.
[CHUCKLING]
Now, this white man, he may have
enslaved us with his laws,
and he may have enslaved us in his jail,
but he has not...
...cannot...
...will not enslave the very essence
of our mortal soul.
[MAN SPEAKING INDISTINCTLY]
[SAID SPEAKING IN ARABIC]
You hearing this shit? ORTOLANI: Yeah.
Yabba-dabba-doo.
This fuck Said is a threat.
You tell Schibetta
we gotta stick together on this one.
-See me riding a bicycle?
-What?
I ain't a messenger.
You got something to tell Nino,
-tell him yourself.
SCHILLINGER: Yeah, yeah.
Hey, lookie here.
We might not have to worry.
Fuck you doing, Kareem?
You like being on your knees, yes?
Maybe you like to suck these?
What the fuck you doing, huh?
Get your ass out of here.
You talking to my boys
about dealing drugs?
-Stay the fuck out my business.
-Is this what you want?
-Huh?
-Is this really what you want?
To bust your ass, yeah.
We Muslims believe in non-violence.
We believe in respecting our neighbor.
Well, we don't.
-I will give my life for you.
-You gonna have to.
So be it.
Brother, hit me.
Now, I told you to hit me, now hit me.
Hit me. Hit me. Hit me!
[BOTH GRUNT]
Hit me in the face, brother.
SAID: Again.
Harder.
What the hell's going on over there?
Come on, break it up.
You a crazy motherfucker, you know that?
Asalaam aleikum, brother.
Peace be unto you.
What day is it? SCHIBETTA: Friday.
Friday? Feels more like Monday.
Ready for this? Guess who's
checking into Oz tomorrow?
-Your Uncle Vinnie.
-No, feds got Vinnie.
[SCHIBETTA LAUGHS]
Ryan O'Reily.
-Get the fuck out of here.
-I'm shitting you?
Why am I gonna shit you about that scum?
ORTOLANI: Gotta be crazy
to put the motherfucker near me.
Maybe they know exactly
what they're doing. Be careful, Dino.
He ain't gonna be in Em City.
He gonna be somewhere over the rainbow.
I'm gonna cap that motherfucker.
You ain't gonna do a fucking thing...
...unless I say so.
[SPEAKS IN ITALIAN]
Thanks.
Count.
HILL: Oz is where I live.
Oz is where I will die,
where most of us will die.
What we were don't matter.
What we are don't matter.
What we become...
...don't matter.
Does it?
[WATER RUNNING]
[CHATTERING]
ORTOLANI: Hey, what's up?
You fucking faggot.
[ORTOLANI SCOFFS]
[SCHIBETTA SPEAKS IN ITALIAN]
Come on, get up.
He's gotta disrespect me like that, man.
Are you stupid or what?
There are cops all around the place.
[MUTTERING]
O'REILY: Who's Keane?
-Me.
-So?
-I'm O'Reily.
Like I said, so?
I heard you can take care
of a little business for me.
-What kind of business?
-Dino Ortolani.
I want him air-holed,
and I am willing to pay.
We don't kill wise guys around here.
Yum-yum, plastic.
My brother says hello.
Says you can help.
-I'm here, ain't I?
-Mm-hm.
Open gate 57 Vegas.
Shut it.
-Who?
-Ortolani.
The niggers are afraid to touch him.
You don't have to worry
about wasting Ortolani.
He's on self-destruct.
[YELLING]
MAN: Yeah. Bet me on the board.
Give it up.
[SAID PRAYING IN ARABIC]
[GRUNTING]
[ALARM SOUNDING]
Fucking faggot!
[SCREAMING]
MAN: Back to your cells. Lock-down.
Back to your cells.
KEANE: What happened? What happened?
-Lock-down. Lock-down.
KEANE: Who did this to my brother?
Who did this to my brother?
NATHAN: Don't play with that.
You better hope they get Billie Keane
to City Hospital on time.
If he flames out, you're up for murder.
Doctor, I'm in here for life.
I don't think one more murder's
gonna matter.
By the way, you have an angel's touch.
When you were outside,
you ever get laid with a line like that?
-Outside I was faithful to my wife.
-Yeah.
I was faithful by choice.
In here I don't got no choice.
Or do I?
No choice, no chance.
How come you're not volunteering
over at the women's prison?
How come you're in here
shaking your tits in front of 1,400 guys?
I'm trying to meet men
and I'm bored with the bar scene.
-So you married?
-It's none of your business.
Because I gotta wonder about a guy
who'd let his slice
come into a pit like this.
I mean, don't he got any concern for you?
-He's got plenty of concern.
-Oh. So you are married. Aah.
You happy?
Happy, Doctor?
Oh, I'm delirious.
[KNOCKING ON DOOR]
McMANUS: Yep.
Yeah, have a seat, Dino.
-Take the cuffs off, please.
-You sure?
Am I sure? Yeah, I'm sure.
Take the cuffs off, please.
[HEALY SIGHS]
McMANUS: You can wait outside.
[ORTOLANI SIGHS]
How you doing, Dino?
You doing a lot better than Billie Keane
because he's in intensive care now.
-I don't start fights.
McMANUS: Yeah, you finish them.
I'm gonna tell you something.
I'm gonna say it once and I'm gonna
say it as simply as I can.
Every inmate, every officer
either hates your guts
or they're terrified of you, or both.
Being popular
has never been a big concern of mine.
Well, how about staying alive?
Is that a concern, hmm?
Keep it up, someone's gonna kill you.
So what?
I'll be sitting in that cell until they
carry my guinea ass out in a body bag,
so why don't you shut up
and put me in the hole?
Dino, do you know why in Em City
I put lifers in with all the rest?
So that people can learn
to live together.
And not just for when they get released.
Even if you're in here
for the rest of your life,
even if you're in here until you die,
your life can have some purpose.
[LAUGHING]
Hey, you hear that?
Are you on drugs, McManus?
If you're not, you should start.
You know, this is your third fight
related to a homosexual encounter.
You can't go swinging on a guy
every time he makes a pass at you, Dino.
What am I supposed to do?
The guy's being faggish,
stroking his dick,
trying to make it hard.
-Laugh it off.
-I don't have that sense of humor.
As punishment,
instead of putting you in lockup,
I'm assigning you to work
in the AIDS ward.
-What the fuck?
-Mr. Healy.
Are you fucking nuts? I work the kitchen.
-You work in the AIDS ward.
HEALY: Come on.
You fucking punk!
Get the fuck out of my office.
Nino, you gotta do something
about this, man.
You gotta get me off
this hospital duty shit.
Who the fuck are you talking to?
I don't gotta do a fucking thing.
I'm telling you right now, man,
I am not touching no diseased faggots.
-Most of them are junkies.
-Junkies, I don't care how they got it.
-I don't wanna get it.
-Then be careful.
-Are you saying you won't do nothing?
-That's right.
-I run the kitchen, Nino.
-You're raising your voice to me.
[SPEAKS IN ITALIAN]
This is what I'm talking about.
You gotta learn to behave.
Wise guys been running these joints
for generations.
How? With this:
And this:
We run the racket same as on the street,
but you, you're arrabbiato.
You're gonna kill O'Reily,
you're gonna kill the faggot.
You gotta learn to think before you act.
Life ain't an ice pick.
So go play nursemaid for a while.
-Go wipe some asses.
-Hmm.
-Wipe some asses.
-Yeah.
Fuck McManus. Fuck these motherfuckers.
[SCHIBETTA EXHALES SHARPLY]
[MACHINE BEEPING]
[MAN COUGHING]
Chow time, Sanchez.
-I'm not hungry.
-Dr. Nathan said you might say that.
Dr. Nathan said to feed you anyway.
Jeez, you're like one of my kids.
-Open your mouth.
-I wanna die, man.
Open your goddamn, motherfucking,
cocksucking mouth.
Well, thanks a lot.
It's so good to see you too, Gloria.
Thanks for shackling me
with Dino Ortolani.
Not only can't he keep
his hands off my fanny,
he's got the bedside manner
of Attila the Hun.
Well, he gets into a fight,
I stick him in the hole. Every time.
I'm trying to break the pattern here.
He's a violent criminal,
a thug born to kill. He'll never change.
So, what do you suggest then?
Caning? Castration?
Lorazepam.
Sedate Ortolani
with 4 milligrams of Lorazepam.
Put him in a passive state,
he gets a great buzz,
-and he doesn't harm anyone.
-Better prison through chemistry?
-Grow some balls, Tim.
-Free for dinner tonight?
-I'm married.
-You're separated.
Wanna have dinner?
Yes.
-I'll have balls by then.
-Hopefully.
My brother's lying in the fucking
hospital, half-dead,
tubes running up his nose
because of that fucking dago.
What do you want?
I heard you were having a meeting
about Ortolani.
-Brothers only.
-Yeah, whatever.
HEALY: What's going on?
What you all doing in here?
He's just consoling me about my brother.
Well, your brother's a fag, Keane.
They say it runs in families.
You a fag too?
Why don't you suck my dick and find out?
[HEALY CHUCKLES]
You got two minutes to finish
your work. Everybody else out.
That's cute.
You and me, we can get this job done.
Johnny, you're up. I want you to go
in the hole and whack that wop.
McManus didn't put Ortolani in the hole.
He's got him doing bedpan duty
in the AIDS ward.
-Yeah?
-Yeah. It'll take a couple of days,
but I'll get your man Post here
reassigned to the AIDS ward.
KEANE: Fine. When the moment's right,
you take that guinea out. For all of us.
Dino, my friend.
I've been looking for you.
Yeah, what do you want, Schillinger?
Heard you crippled Billie Keane.
-The Aryan Brotherhood is grateful.
-Swell.
Just trying to give you
a little jizz here.
I don't need your jizz.
-Fuck you then.
-Fuck you.
What happened in that shower
was between me and the fag boy,
had nothing to do with you,
you fucking redneck scumbag.
Why don't you take your pure white
ass and get the fuck away from me?
Stupid grease-ball.
Count!
HILL: Grease-ball, cracker, mick,
spic, kike, gook, nigger.
Words. Words are weapons.
I'd rather have a Mac-10 anytime though.
Some inmates say that violence
is the worst thing we gotta face.
For me, the worst thing
is the great yawn.
How do you fill day after dull-ass day?
We have these routines
that are supposed to give our lives
order and meaning.
But I'm here to testify I'm less afraid
of getting shanked in my back
than the routine.
Because the routine,
man, the routine'll kill you.
[WATER RUNNING]
I wanna see my daughter.
Hey, I wanna see my daughter.
You're more fucking trouble
than you're worth, Sanchez.
You have a daughter?
I thought you were queer.
Queers have daughters.
I guess so.
SANCHEZ: She's 3.
I have a son that age.
You want cigarettes?
ORTOLANI: Not allowed to smoke.
I wanna see my daughter, where you going?
I wanna see my daughter.
Right here, man.
So...
...why the fuck did you get AIDS?
I loved-
I loved heroin.
It took me to another body.
Made me feel golden.
You?
No, I never liked that shit.
I sold a lot of it though.
Maybe-
Maybe I got mine from you.
No, I was never on the street dealing.
SANCHEZ: Still...
Listen, you little fuck,
I was in the business.
Pure and simple.
I never told you to fucking share
your needles with anybody.
No smoking.
-Yo, Ortolani.
-What do you want, Post?
I'm gonna be working
in the AIDS ward with you.
Great news, huh?
Got a extra cig?
-No, no extra.
-Hey, Ortolani.
How you doing? ORTOLANI: Oh, Christ.
You know, Jesus Christ,
this is like fucking high school.
You think by shoving me in the AIDS ward
you gonna change me? Huh? Huh?
Let me tell you something, coach.
Even with all your good intentions,
all your reforms, and all your overhaul
policies, I ain't ever gonna change.
We ain't ever gonna change. None of us.
Hi, Timmy, what's up?
Dino Ortolani.
Cancel his conjugal visit.
Tell him, uh, instead
he can have family time.
Family? He's Italian.
That could mean upwards
of a hundred people.
No, no, just his wife and kids.
And I want them to meet behind the glass.
I want him to see them, but no touching.
Oh, Tim.
-You wanna be careful.
-About what?
Of playing God once too often.
If you're not careful,
the real one's gonna get very pissed off.
Hi. Thank you, baby.
Why don't you go play over there?
Let me talk to Daddy.
ORTOLANI: Hey.
-Hi.
What happened? Why you got sandbags?
I slipped in the shower.
[CHILDREN SPEAKING INDISTINCTLY]
-Shh. Be quiet.
-Let them play, they're kids.
Shouldn't feel cooped up.
How you doing, Ginnie?
GINNIE: The house is so empty.
-They treating you okay?
-Of course.
But, babe, the money,
it don't mean nothing to me.
As long as you can take care
of those two, that's what's important.
-I miss you.
-What'd I tell you about that?
-You have to go on with your life.
-I don't wanna hear about that.
You have to go on
with your fucking life, Ginnie.
You have to make
like I'm dead, like I got shot
-like Mario and Jake.
-What?
You want me to find a guy?
You want me to get married again?
You want some guy
watching your kids grow up?
Call him Daddy?
I don't want you ever bringing them
back here, ever again.
POST:
Pussy inmate took the state to court,
said smoking was bad for his health.
This whole fucking place
is bad for your health,
-you know what I'm saying?
-Mm-hm.
POST: The state, they pussies too.
Ban cigs in all the prisons. I'm 30 more
years without a fucking cigarette?
No fucking way. They won't even
let the brothers in solitary puff,
like they're worried about catching
fucking lung cancer.
You like to hear yourself talk,
don't you?
You ever wonder what it's like
to burn someone's eye out?
ORTOLANI: Oh, yeah.
-Put that out. You, get out of my chair.
Yes, ma'am.
-Go take care of Emilio Sanchez.
-What'd he do now?
He had an accident.
Change him and then sponge him.
No way.
I ain't touching that diseased turd.
-Oh, yes, you are.
-Oh, no, I ain't.
Look, Sanchez hasn't got long
and he knows it.
I can't do more for him
than dull the pain,
and the least that you can do
is not let him die lying in his own shit.
Okay.
Thank you. NATHAN: You're welcome.
ORTOLANI: Let's go, Sanchez.
I wanna die.
Hey, you're gonna get your wish.
Please.
ORTOLANI: Please, what?
Help me.
Help you?
Here.
Help me die.
Fancy meeting you here.
Hey, I want you to know, Dino,
I got no hard feelings.
Your goombah tells you to kill me,
you trying to make your bones,
I appreciate that.
It's not your fault I didn't die.
It's not your fault you'd have the balls
to come after me, right? You were
running to the DA, you rat bastard.
Now you're trying to provoke me into
a fight, which'll go down on my record,
which'll keep me
from getting a berth in Em City.
-You coming to Em City?
-Yeah, how about that?
You and me, lasagna boy, side by side
every single day
for the rest of our lives.
Unless, of course, I get paroled in 12.
-Come to Em City, you're dead.
-I guess that means
I can't use you as a reference, huh?
O'REILY: Fuck. Fuck you.
Dirty motherfucker! ORTOLANI: Eat shit.
[O'REILY GAGGING]
O'REILY: Shit.
You can take a punch, huh?
When I have to.
Got all the answers too.
No, not all.
But some.
Yeah, well...
...it's too bad you're the wrong color.
[HEART MONITOR BEEPING]
[EKG FLAT-LINING]
-What's going on?
-Killed one of my patients.
I came in, but it was too late already.
He's a monster.
You gotta do something.
You gotta stop him.
All right.
McMANUS: No! No! No!
MAN: We can handle this, McManus.
Fuck you. Fuck you.
HILL: People kill to stay alive.
That's as true in prison as out.
But I'm wondering why in here
we fight so hard to stay alive.
A man gets sentenced to 100 years,
he really thinks if he exercises,
gets all buff stays diesel,
he's gonna walk out?
A judge says life imprisonment
without the possibility of parole.
Without the possibility.
[LAUGHS]
Lifers.
At some point they realize
they ain't going nowhere.
I seen it happen.
A calm comes in their eyes.
It's like they figured out something
that the rest of us are never gonna see.
They're suddenly free in a whole
other kind of way, they're ready to die.
And maybe they do what they can
to help that shit along.