"The best laid schemes of mice
and men most often go astray."
That was written by Mr. Robert Burns
way the fuck back in 1785
and it still is news.
In Oz, we got all sorts of schemes
to change our lousy, lonely lives.
But no matter how much we plot and plan,
something outside our control always
comes along and fucks things up.
HILL: You take Tobias Beecher.
Six months ago, if you'd asked him
where he planned to be today,
he'd have said at his daughter's
4th birthday party.
Instead, he's howling at the moon
thanks to some bad angel dust.
[SCREAMING]
HILL: Old Vern Schillinger.
Before he got to Oz,
he wanted to get America
back on the right track.
The white track.
Now Beecher smashed a piece
of glass in his pure Aryan eye.
[YELLING]
HILL: Timmy McManus.
He's slowly watching as his dreams
for the perfect prison fart away.
And then there's
the Reverend Kareem Said.
He was working on a way
to bring the brothers together,
to fight the injustices we endure
in the name of justice.
He was working it and working it,
till a heart attack worked him over.
GUARD: Huseni Mershah,
this is Kareem Said.
SAID: Maybe Allah sent me to remind you.
Sit down.
-Help me.
-You must go ahead and die.
[YELLING]
MAN [ON TV]:
Black Muslim leader Kareem Said
remains in critical condition
at Oswald State Penitentiary
after a heart attack last Thursday.
Said, who is serving five to 18 years
for burning a White-owned warehouse,
is an outspoken critic
of the American judicial system.
Oh, man, it's almost as if he knew.
Man, like, right before the heart attack,
Said said to me, he said, "Huseni,
if anything should happen, I want you
to gather up the true believers.
Carry out my work, carry out my mission.
Start a holy war right here in Oz.
A war that will set fire on the sky."
He said, "Tell them, my brother,
and guide them."
Man.
Hey, hey, hey. Look who's alive.
You know, Said, I gotta tell you, odds
were 60-40 you were worm's meat.
Yo, Groves, go get Dr. Nathan.
Tell her Said finally woke up.
You're gonna pull something out.
-Said, you shouldn't be doing that.
-Stupid nigger.
Groves. Groves. Get a doctor.
You,
get my clothes.
Now.
I'm telling you, I'm perfectly well.
You had a heart attack. You nearly died.
But I didn't, did I?
-Excuse me.
-Yeah, this time you were lucky.
-What if it happens again?
-Well, believe me, doctor,
I now know what I must do to keep alive.
McManus, I'm ready to go back to Em City.
Okay, but you have to start taking
the medicine Dr. Nathan prescribed.
Agreed?
Agreed.
I know. This way.
HILL:
People do terrible things to people.
That's why we got so many prisons
in the world.
People rape other people.
They rob and beat and cheat other people.
But the worst crime of all is betrayal.
And there ain't no jail terms for that.
Huseni Mershah.
You saw that I was dying
and yet you walked away?
You wanted me to die.
No, Kareem, come on, bro.
I would never want-
No. This man is not
our brother. He is our enemy.
As of this moment, this man is cast out.
No Muslim will speak to him, look him
in the eye or acknowledge him.
You wanted the death of another?
Right now, you're dead to us all.
MAN: Kidnap the president's wife
Without a pan
Kidnap the president's wife without a pan
Yeah, I got a pan
It's etched with a knife
In the center of my hand
So I guess I'm gonna have to
Keep my fist clenched
Walk around D.C. in the rain
Till my wares is drenched
Wait for that motherfucker
To take out the garbage
Do a press conference about
What great shape this country in
And when them welfare cuts gonna begin
And when he pat his dog
And kiss his wife goodbye,
That's when I move in
I throw that silly ho in a headlock
I muffle her grill so her screams stop
I whisper to her, "Your man
Ain't here to protect you, baby"
He gone
I dial up my nigger, tell him, "Meet me
With the Caddy on the white lawn"
I toss her in the back seat
I cover her head with a black sheet
"Put the steel to her grill piece
Be like, "If you don't shut up,
I'm gonna lit two shots off
In your dome piece"
Watch her have fits
If she don't understand, I'm gonna
Give her a quick lesson in Ebonics
"I'm gonna shoot you, baby"
I take her to my hideout in the
Low-income houses down the street
I replace her Joan & Davids
With purple Reeboks on her feet
I give her four hungry kids,
No job, no ambition
No family support
And a last welfare check
I give her crappy-ass Medicaid
And an ill type of growth
Growing out the side of her neck
I tell her, "Fend for yourself, keep you
And them shorties in proper health"
Then after sufficient time on that hype,
I'll introduce her to the crack pipe
Yeah, I'll let her
Feel its soothing effects
As she tries to forget about
The absence of them checks
I'll make her sells her jewels for it
I'll make her-
I'll make her pay her dues for it
And then I'll come to her late at night
"And I'll be like," Yo, everything
Ain't gonna be all right
You ain't gonna be able
To go quietly into that good night
"Peace ain't gonna come
Till your death be done"
And then I'll lead her up to the roof
And I'll show her
All the shit she don't own
I'll lead her over to the edge
And leave her there all alone
[CHATTERING]
Yo.
Yo, y'all wanna play that two on two?
Huh?
Give that two on two?
[YELLING]
Can I get the ball?
I can't get the ball?
Could you throw me the ball, man?
Arif, Arif, you wanna
watch some ball, man?
Wanna play some hoop, huh?
No? Hoop, man. What?
In the name of Allah, most gracious.
Oh, man, why you gotta do me
like this, man? Come on.
-He is Allah, the one and only.
-Come on, you know I would never
-Allah, the eternal.
-Say that I wanted Said dead.
-The absolute.
-Please.
-He begets not.
-He's crazy, you know.
-Nor is he begotten.
-The medication gone to his head.
And there are none like unto him.
In the name of Allah,
most gracious and most merciful.
Yo, Said. Said.
Don't fall asleep, brother,
you might not wake up.
Adebisi. Adebisi. Adebisi.
Yo, my African brother. How you doing?
-Gotta talk to you.
-You and me?
-Yeah.
-Talk about what?
It's about Said, man. He's responsible
for the death of Jefferson Keane.
Jefferson Keane? Ancient history, baby.
Look, Said got to die.
I know what's going on, holy boy.
Yeah, I know they turned
their backs on you.
And you,
you think because we have
the same color skin,
we have some connection.
[LAUGHING]
Go, go, little man, go.
SIMON: Try the man next door.
I'm telling you,
Said wanna start a riot up in here.
He wanna take over Oz.
Do you have any evidence?
No, just what he told me.
Well, we need something more tangible.
Has there been
any stockpiling of weapons?
Just the usual jobs, homemade.
Mershah, why are you doing this?
Why are you giving up Said?
-I wanna stop the violence.
-That is bullshit.
-McManus.
-Leo, you know as well as I do
why he's here.
You're so fucking transparent,
it's laughable.
McMANUS: Officer,
-get him the fuck out of here.
-No, no, look, look. No, wait.
-I'm telling you, man...
-Out. Out. Go.
McMANUS: Get out!
His motive for betraying Said
isn't important.
His information is.
Leo, we're not gonna get anything
out of him.
He's clearly out of the loop. I wanna
move him to another cell block.
-Why?
-Because I don't want the bad blood
that's happening between him and
Said to erupt into something bigger.
He's out.
All right.
When's the last shakedown
you had in Em City?
Couple of weeks ago.
Well, I think it's time for another.
Shakedown.
[BUZZER SOUNDING]
[CHATTERING]
[YELLING]
Look what I have.
I can't put you all in the hole
because the hole is full right now,
and I can't transfer you
out of Emerald City
because all the cells in Oz
happen to be full too.
But what I can do
is take away your privileges.
No TV, no gym,
no phone calls for one month.
Gee, Dad, I hope I can still make it
to the prom.
Two months.
You happy, Alvarez?
That's all.
[CHATTERING]
You know, looks like
everybody but Said has a weapon.
He ain't stupid.
Yo, who was the rat?
I hear it's Mershah.
[MAN CHANTING IN ARABIC]
You know something?
Kareem, you're supposed to be an imam.
Teacher.
And all you taught me
was that your God is full of hate
and vengeance.
So you better watch out, okay?
Because he could turn on you
just like he turned on me.
HILL: You wanna kill a man?
Stick a shank in his chest.
[MEN SPITTING]
HILL: You wanna torture a man?
Feed his loneliness.
Fiending for friendship, for peace,
he will search everywhere.
And when he realizes
that he won't find it,
he will destroy himself.
SAID: I have asked you here
because I'm a worried man.
The death of Huseni Mershah
is yet another example
of the brutality that we suffer here.
But his death was a suicide.
That is what the authorities
have claimed.
But what I know is, six men have died
under bizarre circumstances.
Suffocation.
Fire. Mutilation.
And the list continues on.
And Warden Glynn
sits in his office, aloof.
Now, the FBI was brought in
to do an investigation
but where is their report?
Are you saying it's been repressed?
I don't know.
I ask the question in the hope that you,
the press,
can find out.
Because we prisoners of Oz, I believe,
will sit here waiting for answers
that never come.
[ON TV]
The FBI investigation into the deaths
at Oswald State Penitentiary is ongoing.
We're not about to rush it just
to satisfy the media or the inmates.
We intend to do our work thoroughly
and completely.
GLYNN: Your television show
got everybody's attention.
I'm afraid
that was your last performance.
I'm ordering a press blackout.
Warden, can't you see?
Now, why is blackout a big bad thing?
You can get whiteout in a little bottle.
Don't be smug. Don't you be smug
with me, you son of a bitch.
From the first day you got here,
you have tried to destroy
everything that I built
and everything that I stand for.
Oh, that is pride.
I know that well.
McManus, you've given yourself
far too much importance.
You see, because
this thing's larger than you.
It's larger than me.
So go ahead. Take the media away.
Give us a blackout.
Censor our letters. Tape our mouths shut.
There will always be a man
to tell the truth.
The truth will be heard.
May I go now?
Because it is time for me to pray.
[CHANTING IN ARABIC]
WITTLESEY: Listen up, here are
some new rules from the warden.
As of today, no inmate will be allowed
to use prayer beads, prayer mats,
or special oils for religious
or other purposes.
Inmates will no longer be allowed
to wear similar clothing or head apparel,
identifying them as a member
of any group, gang or cult.
-Whoa!
No. No.
Now, you do realize this is a violation of
our right to freely practice our religion?
You can practice all you want.
Pray till the cows come home.
The constitution does not guarantee
that you, as a prisoner,
have the right to any stuff.
-Easy.
-You're gonna have to hand it over.
Look, this can go one of two ways.
I vote for no blood.
This is a meaningless gesture, brothers.
Our faith is not in kufis, beads or mats.
It is in our hearts.
GLYNN: All right, everyone,
can I have your attention, please?
I've got some news for you all.
The FBI report will be released today
and it will state emphatically
that Sanchez, Ortolani, Post,
Martinez and Markstrom
were all killed by inmates.
[MEN YELLING]
Quiet down.
GLYNN: The death of Huseni Mershah
has been ruled a suicide.
Stop it.
It is likely that some correctional
officers may have been involved
in a secondary manner
with some of the murders.
Knock it off.
People, if you don't knock it off,
I'm not gonna be able to finish.
Fine.
[YELLING]
We will stand up, look in the mirror,
and say, like Solomon:
I am black, but I am comely,
O ye daughters of Jerusalem.
[GUARD WHISTLES]
GUARD: Come on, let's go. Let's go.
-Go. Go, go.
Mr. Said.
Hm?
I just wanted to tell you
that the whole thing with the spoons,
the whole Allah thing, it's awesome.
[SPEAKS IN ARABIC]
So, what's up?
-Turning Muslim on me?
-Mm.
He's a great speaker, that Said.
He says our lives are crap because
of Glynn and McManus and the rest.
Said says
that Glynn's guilty of worse crimes
than any of us have committed.
-You ever kill anybody?
-Mm-mm.
No, I ain't done nothing.
I got a bum rap, you know.
I'm innocent.
I thought it'd be hard
to murder my parents, but it wasn't.
Hey, how did you whack them?
Ball-peen hammer.
HILL: Prisoner number 97G414,
Donald Groves.
Convicted July 3, '97.
Two counts, murder in the first degree.
Sentence: Life imprisonment.
I think I should kill Warden Glynn.
-What?
-I think I ought to kill Glynn.
All right, look.
This is what you should do, all right?
You know that chick, Dr. Nathan?
All right, you go to her and you tell her
to write you a prescription.
I'm telling you, she's got me, like,
on these antidepressants right now,
and I'm like...
I'm sailing, man.
No.
My first idea is best.
First chance I get, I'll murder Glynn.
GUARD: Look out.
-No.
[GROANING]
HILL: Donald Groves.
Convicted August 21, '97.
Murder in the first degree in the death
of corrections officer Lawrence Smith.
Sentence: Death.
This is genocide.
Killing murderers is genocide.
Groves?
They beat me. GLYNN: Who?
Groves, you have been condemned to die
for the murder of Officer Smith.
The state gives you the right to choose
any method you wish to die.
I shouldn't even be talking to you.
You should be dead.
You were the one
that was supposed to die.
How do you wanna die, Groves?
Lethal injection? Electric chair?
-Firing squad.
-Firing squad?
Isn't that what they do to assassins?
Fine. I'm going to personally
paint the target on your heart.
Warden. Warden.
Me killing you wasn't personal, you know.
It just had to be done.
When your shift's over,
come to my office.
I want you to tell me
why I shouldn't fire your asses.
Lawrence Smith
was an outstanding officer.
He was an outstanding human being.
And he died
for what he truly believed in:
Justice.
I think it would be easier to get angry.
To punish all the inmates
for a crime committed by one of them.
[YELLING]
But knowing Lawrence, I don't think
that he would want his death
to bring about more pain, more suffering.
[YELLING]
I think that he would want his death
to bring about...
...peace.
[GUARDS LAUGHING]
-Wanna get a drink?
-No, no, I got a press conference.
Oh, that sounds like fun. GUARD: Warden?
Yes, Eddie?
Did I hear right?
Groves wants a firing squad?
Yeah. The sick bastard.
Do we have a firing squad?
No, I gotta put one together.
Well, I'd like to volunteer.
-Why?
-Smitty was my friend.
You know, in this case, I'm not sure
that's a good enough reason. I mean,
this isn't about revenge,
it's about the law.
But I'll get back to you.
-Gloria, you wanted to see me?
-Yeah. You're done.
Look around. We've got a bumper crop
of officer-related injuries.
O'Reily. What happened?
He hit me. I wasn't doing dick, I swear.
-Just ups and hits me.
-Who?
Yeah, right. I tell you,
and next time I get hit worse.
Leo, look, since Smith's murder,
this ER's SRO.
Your officers are out of control.
You gotta do something.
I know, I know.
I know.
You know. Jesus.
Are you saying that random
reprisals are justified?
Yeah.
Well, one person killed Lawrence Smith.
Groves. The other inmates are innocent.
Innocent? Christ.
-I didn't expect you to understand.
-What do you mean?
You were never a guard, huh?
You didn't come up through the ranks
like Leo, me or the rest.
So I don't understand the anger,
the frustration that COs go through?
-That's fucking bullshit.
LENNY: Look, Leo,
you can't keep suspending these guys
because they slap some dipshit.
-I can't condone it either.
-We're understaffed as it is.
You take experienced officers
off of the rotation,
what are you leaving us with?
Newbies who can't handle a crisis.
So, what do you suggest I do?
Just let our guys get through
Groves' execution.
Once he's in a body bag,
this whole thing will fade away.
So in the meantime,
they whale on whoever they want.
Reality's hard for you,
isn't it, McManus?
[ALARM RINGING]
Hi.
I'm Officer Gordon Wood.
Here to replace Vogelsang.
Well, hi.
Vogelsang is a good man
but he can't control his temper.
-How long you been working in Oz?
-Three weeks.
-Veteran, huh?
-Hm.
Okay. If you got questions, ask.
It doesn't make you stupid.
It may save both our lives.
I hear you. Is that Kareem Said?
WITTLESEY: Yep, in the flesh.
He don't look so tough.
WITTLESEY:
Yeah, well, looks are deceiving.
My laundry interest you?
Yeah, I always wondered,
a famous guy like Kareem Said,
is he a Fruit of the Loom or a Hanes man?
-I don't wear underwear.
-Oh, I see.
-You like the wide-open spaces, huh?
-That's right.
Oh, well.
[SPEAKS IN ARABIC]
It is with enormous sadness and respect
that I present to Loretta Smith
the Fleishman Medal of Honor
in memory of her son,
Officer Lawrence Smith,
who died in the service
of this great state.
MAN: Do you believe
justice has been served?
I would like to be able
to watch the execution.
Mrs. Smith, I don't think
that's a good idea.
Besides, the state doesn't allow
family members to be present.
If I could help, believe me, I would.
Can I see Groves?
I'm not sure what good that'll do.
I'm not sure either.
But you're gonna kill him.
And he'll be dead and buried,
and I won't get another chance.
I'm Loretta Smith.
You killed my son.
You're a handsome fellow.
Thanks.
You broke God's law: Love thy neighbor.
I wanna hate you but I can't.
I feel pity, tears, but no hate.
I didn't realize that until this moment.
You are my neighbor and I love you.
And I forgive you...
...with all my heart.
That's all.
I wanna thank you gentlemen
for volunteering
to serve on the firing squad.
Since we announced to the press
that Groves chose this method,
we've been swamped with phone calls
from sharpshooters all over the country
wanting to sign up.
But the warden and I felt it best
if we handled this internally.
GLYNN: Warden?
There hasn't been an execution by
firing squad in this state since 1872.
Fortunately, Lenny Burrano worked
in Utah before coming to Oswald.
-Lenny?
-Thank you, warden.
Now, many people will tell you
that firing squads are barbaric.
But in fact, it's a lot more humane
than the electric chair.
In any case,
the protocol for a successful execution
is proper lighting, proper distance.
LENNY: But you must prepare yourself
for the emotional burden
of actually pulling the trigger.
Now, you should know,
that one of the rifles will carry blanks,
so that none of you will ever know
who actually fired the fatal shot.
[PHONE RINGING]
Hello? He what?
I'll be right down.
MAN: Name is Donald Groves.
-Let's put down an NG tube,
-pump his stomach.
-What happened?
GLORIA: Overdose.
-Is he going to live?
Ask me again in 200 minutes.
Save him, doctor.
Did you strip-search him?
-Yes.
-How the fuck did he get pills?
-I don't know.
-Find out!
We're losing him. Start CPR.
-Save the little prick.
GLORIA: What's the difference?
He's scheduled to die anyway.
The law says he has to be aware
that he's being executed,
he has to know why he's
being executed. He has to be alive.
So save him.
Save his goddamn ass.
Yo, Rebadow,
what are you doing in here all day?
Hiding.
Any word on Groves?
Yeah, Dr. Nathan
brought him back from the dead.
A resurrection, huh?
Yeah. They delayed execution
for a couple of hours.
-You miss him, don't you?
-Groves?
No.
I've learned over the years
not to make attachments.
If you do, you spend
all your time grieving.
You know what,
I ain't grieving, but it's a hell
of a lot better than hiding, man.
Hail Mary, full of grace,
the Lord is with thee.
Blessed art thou amongst women,
and blessed is the fruit of thy-
-Father?
-Yeah?
Yeah, I've been thinking
a lot about my final words.
And I decided what I wanted to say.
And I'd like you to write it down
and give it to Mrs. Smith.
It'll maybe make her feel better. Okay?
Will you do that for me?
Of course.
I think that she'd appreciate that.
GLYNN: It's time.
The sky's a nice color of blue.
May the blessing of God, the Father
and the Son and the Holy Spirit,
come upon you
and remain with you forever.
-I just have to hear his last words.
-You can listen through this.
Great.
[GROVES HYPERVENTILATING]
GUARD [OVER INTERCOM]: Last words?
What's wrong?
GROVES [OVER INTERCOM]:
I just wanna say that I did...
[STATIC OVER INTERCOM]
-What's he saying?
-I don't know. I can't-
Can you fix that?
[GUNSHOTS SOUND]
He's dead.
No, what did he say?
What were his last words?
I don't know. I wasn't really listening.
[BUZZER SOUNDS]
WITTLESEY: Drinking on the job, Eddie?
No.
I'm off duty,
as of ten minutes ago.
Want some?
No, I never developed
a taste for Mogen David.
Snob.
To Lawrence Smith.
A fine man who died too young.
Yeah. Amen.
Here's to Donald Groves,
a freak of nature who lived too long.
Yeah, probably.
I killed a man who killed a man.
I killed a man.
Only maybe I didn't kill him, because
they put blanks in one of the rifles
so maybe-I mean, I can never
know for sure if I killed him or not.
Only not knowing
is maybe worse than knowing.
-Because at least if I knew-
WITTLESEY: Eddie.
Go home. Sleep it off.
[CHUCKLES]
Sleep, yeah.
[GROANS]
Something tells me I'm not gonna
sleep much tonight either.
"The best laid schemes of mice
and men..."
I don't get the mice part.
Were the mice back in Burns' time
smart enough to make a plan?
We got mice in Oz
but they don't seem too bright.
It's the rats you gotta look out for.
Our rats come in all shapes and sizes.
[PLAYING CLASSICAL MUSIC]
Who the fuck's that?
Some hotshot highbrow cellist.
I guess he's a hotshot, because
McManus gave him permission
to practice for an hour every day.
So I gotta stay in here
and listen to him.
-What's he playing?
-I don't know. I'm a Beck fan myself.
HILL: Prisoner number 97D403,
Eugene Dobbins.
Convicted August 18, '97.
Murder in the second degree.
Sentence: 22 years.
Up for parole in eight.
This cello was made in 1744
by a man named Johannes Kipers
in Amsterdam.
HILL: It's good, huh?
Yeah, it's good. It's priceless to me.
That's why we keep it locked
in the chaplain's office.
It sure is beautiful.
Beautiful but lonely.
Lonely? How does a cello get lonely?
I have no one to play with.
You sound great by yourself.
You don't need anybody to play with.
DOBBINS: I'm used to playing
with orchestras,
90 to 100 other musicians making music.
A cello by itself is just...
It's just not the same.
Kenny.
You got any tits, man?
-Hey, where you going?
-I'll catch you later, man.
Come hit this before you go.
-I gotta go to the bathroom.
-Come on.
-Brother, I gotta pee.
-Don't be a pussy. Hit it. Come on.
Hit it good.
There you go.
-Everything I say stays here, right?
-You have to ask?
-Jackson Vahue.
-Yeah, the basketball star.
Yeah, when he got to Em City,
I was excited, you know.
I mean, he's always been my hero.
You don't want him to think you're
a wimp so when he snorts, you snort.
Something like that.
But I'm not hooked again,
Sister, I swear.
Well, you keep doing it, you will be.
-I'm gonna talk to Vahue.
-No.
No, no. It's okay.
I'll figure out a way to confront him
about his drug use
without implicating you.
And you, meanwhile,
you come to the counseling session
on Thursday.
And stop doing heroin,
no matter what Vahue says.
-Okay?
-Yes, ma'am.
You know, maybe it's time
you got yourself another hero.
Because, to be honest,
the one you've got sucks.
You gonna do what I tell you to do
or I'm just gonna fuck you up.
Yo, Jackson,
you leave Dobbins alone, man.
VAHUE: You butt out of this, all right?
-I'm telling you, man.
VAHUE: Yo, fuck-Fuck you.
Hey. Aah!
Get the fuck out of here, man.
-What the fuck was that about?
-You're so wired on tits
-you was hurting him for no reason.
-I don't need no reason.
He got a gift, man.
If you fuck with it, it will go.
What about my gift, huh?
What about my fucking gift?
-I'm dying in here, man.
-We all dying, Jackson.
That ain't no comfort.
HILL: We all got problems.
Impossible problems.
And then we meet someone who's
got bigger problems than we have.
Or at least, they can't handle
their problems as well.
And somehow,
their weakness gives us strength.
Simple truth number 62:
You help someone, you help yourself.
So I did what Sister Peter Marie said.
I got myself another hero.
And who'd have guessed?
It's me. Yeah.
I'm proud because my plan worked.
I did my best.
HILL: Unfortunately for Dobbins, my best,
it ain't good enough.
Hey, Nino, you wanna play some pinochle?
I'm in the middle of a conversation here.
What fucking bog did you grow up on,
you stupid mick bastard?
Now get the fuck out of here.
ROSS: Hey, O'Reily?
-What?
-What are those two talking about?
-How the fuck would I know, Ross?
Seems strange to you?
Nino Schibetta, fucking mob guy,
chatting with the nigger of Islam?
Get lost. Come here.
-I've been hearing shit.
-Yeah, me too.
-The Muslims are gonna start a riot.
-Yeah.
Rumor has it
that they're armed to the teeth.
I'm talking guns.
They've organized every cell block.
They take charge, me and you
can kiss our white asses goodbye.
Well, maybe Schibetta's
making some kind of deal with Said.
How come we don't know about it?
Maybe the old wop's saving himself
by giving you up.
You're right. We need to get organized.
Definitely. And you got a card
in your deck nobody knows about.
What, Adebisi?
He hates Said as much as we do.
Wouldn't hurt to have
a couple of homeboys on our side.
All right, I'll talk to him.
-You ready?
-Almost.
Look, I saw Said talking to Schibetta.
You think Said knows about the two
of us putting glass in Schibetta's food?
How would he know?
Listen, you hear any rumblings about
the Muslims wanting to start a riot?
Stop that.
-Sure, you know.
-Well, if it happens,
where you gonna land?
On my feet, as always.
Hey, we supply tits
to this whole fucking prison, all right?
Those doily heads are gonna gun for us.
-Don't worry, bro, I got your back.
-That's all I needed to know.
How long is it gonna take before he dies?
I don't know. It's not exactly an exact
science, you know what I'm saying.
I want him...
...dead.
[BUZZER SOUNDS]
Here you go, Nino.
-What, you don't like it?
-No.
-I'll get you something else.
-I'm just not hungry.
-Is your stomach still bothering you?
-Yeah.
I told you to go to the doctor.
We got a huge pair of tits
coming in tomorrow.
Tell your-
Tell your pal, Adebisi,
to get his boys ready to run.
You got it. Say, Nino,
anything going down I should know about?
You know, between us and Said, I mean?
No.
But you would know...
...when you're supposed to know.
I'm gonna go lie down.
Hey, Dobbins, you want a salad?
Flush and 40 jacks.
I got a marriage and I got 100 aces.
Nino.
Jesus Christ.
What the fuck is that?
NINO: Jesus.
What the fuck?
O'REILY: Nino. Nino.
SIMON: Hey, you don't look so good.
Christ.
Hello, Kareem.
Guess you heard
what happened to Schibetta.
Oh, yes. Now, that was unusual.
The man was hemorrhaging
throughout his body.
Now, I wonder what caused that.
-Bad diet.
-Too much garlic.
[LAUGHING]
Is the man gonna recover?
The doctor says he's got a chance.
But meanwhile...
...we are in charge of his operation.
So any business you had with him,
has to go through us.
Business?
I had no business with Schibetta.
-Yeah.
-Better not be lying.
-Is that a warning?
-Yeah.
Well, I have a warning
for the two of you.
Change your ways
or you will suffer the wrath of God.
God? I don't see any God.
-He's not here.
-All I see is you.
You have a bad heart.
You have it so wrong.
I have a weak heart.
And you...
...have the bad heart.
You can keep my watch.
He's right. You do have a bad heart.
What can I say?
I'm a bad-heart motherfucker.
I'll take this one.
Hey, Nino.
Remember when you called me
a stupid mick bastard? Huh?
I ain't so stupid now, am I?
Open up.
Sorry, we're out of tomatoes.
If you listen to the poets,
they'll tell you that a big bad event
in someone's life changes them.
If you lose the woman you love
or your legs,
you suddenly find
a kind of beauty inside yourself.
That's what they say, the poets.
Truth is, you don't.
After a big bad event,
you only become
more of the person you already were.
BEECHER: Yeah, motherfucker!
-You're gonna die, fucking bastard!
Fucking bitch! How's that feel, you fuck?
SCHILLINGER: You're a dead man!
McMANUS: If you're afraid
Schillinger's gonna kill you,
-I'll place you under Protective Custody.
BEECHER: Fuck off. Fuck off.
Fuck off, fuck off, fuck off.
BEECHER: Fuck off.
HILL: It's after a big bad event
that you find out the real person
you always were inside.
[GRUNTS]
Look what that cocksucker did to me.
Turned me into Jolly fucking Roger,
only I'm not
feeling real jolly right now.
Well, Dr. Nathan says that there's
a chance they can still save your eye.
Always looking for the upside,
huh, McManus?
Beecher's gonna get out of the hole soon
and it's very clear that I can't have
both of you in Emerald City,
so I'm trying to decide who stays.
Well, let's see now. He's the crazy fuck
who came at me.
He's the fuck who shattered the glass
that went into my eye.
Are you saying his actions
were unprovoked?
-If I say yes, would you believe me?
-No.
The two of you,
you're the same fucking guy.
What? Me and Beecher?
You know what it's like
being able to see out of one eye?
Your point of view gets twisted.
SCHILLINGER: You can see straight
but you can't see as far around.
What you see is not only what's there.
What's that got to do with me
being like Beecher?
You eggheads think the world really is
the way you see it.
And then when you finally figure out
that it's not, that you weren't close,
then you get a little bitter.
You get mean.
I think you better go live in Gen Pop
for a while.
Fine.
Well, well. Look who's back.
[MEN WHISTLING]
Hey, prag, Schillinger sends his love.
Get the fuck off.
Hey.
Break it up.
[WHISTLING]
[JEERING]
Beecher, you wanted to see me?
I need you to move me
to another cell block.
All the cell blocks are full.
Then move me to another prison.
Do I look like a travel agent to you?
Beecher.
What?
Nothing.
[YELLING]
[SPEAKING INDISTINCTLY]
You're gonna die.
Not today.
-That hurt.
-Ha-ha!
O'REILY: That was nice.
Tie that Nazi bastard up.
Tie that motherfucking Nazi up.
SIMON: Beecher. Come on, baby. Come on.
[SCREAMING]
BEECHER: Hey, motherfucker,
you remember this?
Oh, shit. He's shitting on his-
[MEN YELLING AND LAUGHING]
[LAUGHING]
Sieg heil, baby.
Sieg fucking heil.
We think we know what we need.
We spend our time figuring out
how to get what we want,
who can help us, who's in the way.
We make our moves,
and sometimes we get lucky.
We get exactly what we want.
And life gets worse.
Simple truth number 22:
Be careful what you wish for, brother.
Be very, very careful.