[THUNDER RUMBLING]
HILL: Floods.
You know how you always hear
about them people in Iowa or Missouri
or wherever,
how some big river overflows?
The fucking water keeps pouring
over its riverbanks, out of control,
taking out farms and towns
and everything in its path.
Everybody tries to stop it,
but nobody can.
Everybody's lives are wiped out.
Completely destroyed.
[THUNDER RUMBLING]
And the fucking river,
it don't give a shit.
It just keeps rising.
Year after year after fucked-up year.
My question is, are them heads
in the Midwest whacked out or what?
This one joker I seen on TV,
his home had been washed away four times.
Four fucking times.
Why don't he just leave?
Why don't he jump in that pickup
and drive to higher ground?
Or is he like us in Oz?
There ain't no higher ground.
[SNIFFING]
[LAUGHING]
Hey!
McMANUS: What I'm saying is
that your officers are doing a shit job.
The whole concept behind Emerald City
is that we never
take our eyes off anyone.
WITTLESEY: We don't.
McMANUS: Then how do you explain Beecher
getting a swastika burned onto his ass,
or Miguel Alvarez
cutting his face all up,
or inmates using classrooms
to snort fucking heroin?
WITTLESEY:
It's life. Shit slides through.
If you got a problem
with the way I run things, replace me.
McMANUS: You know
I'm not gonna do that, Diane.
Why? Because we're fucking each other?
McMANUS: Sorry we're late.
GLYNN: If you ever
got here on time, McManus,
I think I'd have a heart attack.
WITTLESEY: What we talking about?
REIMONDO: Drugs.
My favorite topic.
The more we try and stop the drugs,
the more the drugs get in.
What do you expect?
Outside, they're sentencing dealers
to much longer prison time.
Yeah, we got a prison full of guys
who are experts
at moving shit through any system.
Schibetta's got the biggest operation.
We stop him, we make a major dent.
McManus, you wanted Schibetta in Em City.
-You said you could reach him.
-I will, in time.
Unfortunately, that's one
of the many things we don't have.
I know. When it comes to drugs,
there are two major players involved:
Nino Schibetta and Kareem Said.
-Muslims are anti-drugs.
-Exactly.
McMANUS:
We want your help stopping the flow.
That's your job, not mine.
You know everything about this place.
You could tell us
the whens and the wheres.
Yeah, and end up dead.
No, thank you.
I have to take care
of this disease my own way.
REIMONDO: Which is...?
-By fighting the addiction.
Well, you see, that's what I'm trying
to do with my counseling sessions.
You know, you and I
have exact same goals, Kareem.
Only because of who we are, we can't
help each other achieve these goals.
So more inmates get hurt. It's-
It is so frustrating.
Sister, we both believe
in a greater power.
His will be done.
His will or yours?
Yeah, well, in my experience,
God isn't too helpful
unless you give him a little nudge.
REIMONDO: What now?
Schibetta's drugs
fuck with people's heads.
It's time I start fucking with his.
McMANUS: The last couple of weeks
have been tough on you, Nino.
Your wife dying,
Dino murdered,
Joey D'Angelo out of commission.
Overall, your troops, they're thinning.
They're getting older,
they're more anemic.
Now, the blacks and Latinos
are taking over,
on the street and in here.
So we gotta face it,
the days of the Mafia are over.
[NINO SPEAKS IN ITALIAN]
Okay, okay.
Let's just say that you're of an age,
you ought to start to relax a little bit.
Now, I got a friend, DEA.
He says you wanna talk,
he'll make a deal.
A deal?
What's he gonna do,
put me in Witness Protection?
You are a fool, McManus.
Now, you can try
for the next thousand years
not to be a fool,
but you'll always be one.
Well, I can't change neither.
I can't turn my back on who I am.
Certainly not for you.
Certainly not for some dumb-ass DEA deal.
-You done with me?
-For now.
[BUZZER SOUNDS]
Attention. The following inmates
are to be transferred immediately.
As I call your name,
gather your belongings
and form a line by Officer Vogelsang.
88P715, Ottovino.
91J224, Jenbro.
85P661, Pellicano.
94R511, Ricatta.
[PRISONERS LAUGH]
Arrivederci, baby.
Bye-bye.
PRISONER: Looks like Nino's all alone.
[BUZZER SOUNDS]
Get out of here.
Chocolate bars.
-With almonds or without?
-Both.
You got it.
NINO: Grazie.
You've been handling things pretty good
around here since Joey's accident.
-Hey, you do what you gotta do.
-That's right.
The bad blood between you boys and us,
well, with Jefferson Keane cold,
I'm willing to let bygones be gone.
Yeah, me too.
-You like tits?
-Who doesn't?
My tits are firm and round.
Maybe you could suck my tits.
I know a lot of brothers
who would love to.
If you fuck me over,
I'll cut this hand off.
What was all that about?
The future, my brother.
Us owning the future.
Tits.
That's what we call drugs.
Sixty percent of the violence in prison
is due to tits.
Either people not paying their debts,
or people trying to control the traffic.
The traffic.
Here in Oz, the last few days,
the traffic has been bumper-to-bumper.
[SIRENS WAILING]
HILL: Prisoner number 94P442,
Ronald Poklewaldt.
Convicted March 8th, '94.
Arson in the second degree.
Sentence: 25 years. Up for parole in ten.
[SIRENS WAILING]
[WHISPERING] -so that we can have
a couple of fucking hits.
Just couple of tits.
[TALKING INAUDIBLY]
Don't touch me.
KENNY: So you're hiding behind
the bitch's skirt now, huh?
-You hurt me, she'll see you.
-Just want our money.
RONALD: Next week I'm getting a check.
See, you said that last week.
I know, I know, I know, but I can't
be held responsible for the U.S. mail.
-Ah! Shit!
-Yo, Adebisi. Yo, let's go.
-No money, no tits.
-Yeah.
[KENNY CHUCKLES]
Tomorrow we get healthy.
I want you boys ready to-
-Who you calling "boys," old man?
-Shut the fuck up. Take a walk.
-How you gonna let him just call-?
-Be gone, little nigger.
Look, Nino, I wanna be there
when the shit comes in.
-Where's it happen?
-Sorry.
It's an old family recipe.
We don't share.
Hey, if we gonna be partners, yo,
we just ought to be up
on how big a risk we gotta take.
-Just knowing it works ain't enough?
-No, man.
All right.
So how's it work, Nino?
We know it doesn't go
through the kitchen,
otherwise we'd have seen it.
Kitchen's the first place
the cops would look.
No, we use the post office.
Hold this.
A box of socks from my sister.
Versace.
It's an old trick.
It still works.
-Yeah, but where do you cut it?
NINO: Here.
Here? Here, where?
[NINO SPEAKS IN ITALIAN]
I ain't telling you everything.
At least not until
we've been in business a little longer.
All right.
Cool.
Fuck him. I don't wanna do
no business with no dago.
O'REILY: How's it going?
-Man, we won't be for long.
Look, Schibetta's weak.
He done already lost a lot of his men.
All we got to do is find out
how his operation works,
then we take it over.
-Nino?
-Yeah?
My offer still stands.
I wanna be here for you.
-I wanna help you any way I can.
-Okay, kid, thanks.
-I said "okay," okay?
-Okay.
RONALD: I'll testify against Adebisi,
Markstrom and Wangler.
We need to figure out
how the drugs are getting in.
You got any idea
how the gangsters are doing it?
No. No, I don't. I don't.
You find out, you let me know.
Oh, I'll find out all right,
and then I want you
to bust Adebisi's ass.
McMANUS: Ronnie.
Been to drug counseling recently?
Sure, sure. I go all the time.
Sister Peter Marie says
you haven't been there for two weeks.
I'll go today. I promise.
[CHUCKLES]
[SNIFFS]
Oh.
[BOTH CHUCKLING]
Get lost, punk.
You aren't squeezing my tits anymore.
-You never pay.
-No, no, no, that's not why I'm here.
Markstrom and his crew,
how do they get their shit into Oz?
What are you doing?
You doing market research now, huh?
No, man, I'm looking
to fuck those niggers up.
Well, I don't know how they do it,
but I got a couple of guesses.
Sit your ass down.
[BUZZER SOUNDS]
Nino, let's talk about this, man.
Come on.
-You stay out.
-It's all right, Kenny. It's all right.
Me and my associates are very
unhappy about this morning's events.
-How did this happen?
-Nino-
My operation's been running
smooth as a silk shirt.
Then I tell you what's what,
suddenly the hacks know.
I gotta wonder
if one of your boys is the jabber.
-Oh, come on, man, that's impossible.
-Anything is possible.
You wanna stay in business with me?
Find the leak and plug the leak today.
Nino, don't worry about it.
We'll take care of it, all right?
Come on.
Adebisi, stay.
KENNY: What's that?
-I don't know, man, but watch him.
HILL: Secrets. We all got secrets.
Mostly our secrets are tied
to our addictions, our obsessions.
You like that bourbon too much?
You get off eating chicks with dicks.
You gotta do it in hiding.
You say you somebody
but you really somebody else.
Only things that matter to us most,
do we keep our secrets?
And sometimes...
...those secrets will kill you.
McMANUS: Fuck.
GLYNN: Cut him down.
GUARD 1: All right.
McMANUS: Markstrom didn't
strike me as the suicide type.
GLYNN: He wasn't.
-I'm sorry, Leo.
-For what?
-He was your cousin.
-Not my cousin.
McMANUS: What are you talking
about? That's what you told me.
That's why you wanted him in Em City.
He's not my cousin.
He's a narc, undercover cop.
You put an undercover cop
in my cell block
and you don't even
fucking mention it to me?
Look, I'm trying to put some brakes
on the drug traffic.
I get city Narcotics to send in a man,
I figure the less people
know about it, the better.
Even so, you should have told me, Leo.
And what? Listen to you lecture
on prisoners' rights?
About entrapment? No, thanks.
So let me get this straight.
Markstrom's been
feeding you info all along.
The idea was to get him in good
with the gangsters,
get him to find out
about their operation.
-But somebody gave him up.
-Yeah, who?
One of his bunkies in Narcotics
must be talking to the mob.
[PHONE RINGS]
What? Oh, yes, governor.
Yes. Yeah, I know.
Goodbye.
This time, he wants a lock-down.
Oh, Devlin's fighting
for his political life.
Trying to take the focus off him,
put it on us.
Yeah, I know. But the bottom line is,
I was gonna do it anyway.
Until we nail whoever's responsible
for Markstrom's murder,
I'm locking Oz down, tight.
RONALD: Man, who would have
thought Markstrom was a cop?
-Makes you sick, don't it?
-Yeah.
Makes you wonder who else is undercover.
Could be anybody.
Could be you.
Hey, Nino.
The hacks didn't buy Markstrom's suicide.
I didn't they think would.
It was more a sign to Glynn:
Don't fuck with us.
Yeah, now they're gonna lock down
this whole fucking place.
For a little while.
And your smuggling operation,
it's busted.
The post-office thing?
That's not the way we really do it.
That was just a test
to see what you boys are made of.
The truth is,
I'd never tell you the truth.
SIMON: Oh, yeah?
-Now,
the fastest way to end this lock-down
is to pick one of your gang
and have him cop
to the Markstrom hanging.
Okay.
I always thought Keane and Markstrom
were holding you back.
From the get-go, I knew you were a guy
who sees how the world gets made.
Adebisi.
Ends in I. You sure you're not Italian?
Schibetta ends in A. Maybe you African.
Lock-down, gentlemen, lock-down.
GUARD: Today, Adebisi.
"Lock-down, gentlemen, lock-down."
Man, I fucking hate lock-downs.
Not because of being trapped
in this fucking fishbowl.
Man.
I start fiending for some fucking tits.
You a tit boy, Groves?
-Drugs are bad.
-That's bullshit.
Man, you had to be fucked up
when you ate your mother.
-Mom told me that drugs were bad.
-Right.
I bet you was, like,
a good little boy, right?
Did everything your mama told you to.
I like your scars.
Now I know why McManus
put us in the same cell together.
You're the only motherfucker in Em City
who's more fucked up than I am.
Here.
I don't wanna write
anybody a fucking letter, all right?
-I wanna get fucking high.
-You lick the back.
Yeah. Lick the back.
It's...
...liquid LSD.
ALVAREZ: Groves. Groves.
You give stamp collecting
a whole new meaning, baby.
I don't have to tell you, drugs ain't
the only things to get addicted to.
Some people mainline their work,
some people...
[SNIFFS]
Snort ESPN.
Some people needle-pop gambling.
There are those that shoot up
junk foods, fine wines, Cohibas, baby.
Some people get hooked on love.
And like any fiend on the street,
you always need another bump.
Just one more bump, man,
just one more bump.
-Hey.
-Hi.
What's the matter?
Markstrom was murdered.
He was a cop.
I feel responsible.
Diane, Van Harris confessed
to the murder.
Yeah, well, even so.
Maybe you're right.
Maybe I am doing a shit job here.
You know what? I got an idea.
Tonight after work, you come to my place.
Oh, I can't, I gotta drive home.
Mom says Didi's been acting up.
I wanna meet your daughter.
Why don't you bring her into town,
three of us will go to dinner?
Then what do I do with her?
This isn't exactly
a take-your-daughter-to-work
kind of place.
-I love you, Diane.
-Do you?
No, you're supposed to say,
"I love you too, Tim."
The night of Keane's execution,
you know, what we did...
...it was really fucked up.
And I don't know why.
I don't know if it's loneliness.
Why does the why matter?
Well, it doesn't, does it?
[DOOR CLANGING]
I came up here to get the file
on the new arrival.
-His name is Scott Ross.
-Scott Ross?
-Oh, shit.
-Is there a problem?
No, it's nothing I can't handle.
HILL: Prisoner number 97R518, Scott Ross.
[POLICE SIRENS WAILING]
Convicted June 4th, '97.
Possession of marijuana
with intent to distribute.
Third conviction.
Sentence: life without parole.
Three strikes, sucker!
WITTLESEY: Wait here. MACK: Sure.
Since when you been working Oz?
About six months.
-This is great.
-No, no, it's not.
Always dreamed of you having me in cuffs.
Look, just because we knew
each other in a former life,
doesn't mean you're gonna get
any special treatment.
-I love it when you play tough.
-I'm not playing, Scott.
Mack. Mark Mack, Scott Ross.
Mack is your sponsor. He'll help you
get acquainted with the rules.
Take him to Em City.
MACK: You knew her on the outside?
Yeah. Me and her ex
used to ride together.
GUARD: In there. Top bunk, all right?
All right, gentlemen,
the lock-down is over.
Hey.
I'm gonna give you ten minutes
to get your hands off my dick.
[LAUGHING]
-Schillinger, you fuck.
-Scotty, how long you in for?
Life.
Oh, man.
What?
Come on. You got any cigarettes?
[BOTH LAUGHING]
WITTLESEY: No smoking. Put the butt out.
Diane.
I'm not asking for any special favors,
but we've known each other
for a long time.
Have we? I was married to Glen
for four fun-filled years.
During that time, you were finishing off
a six-year sentence.
We were on the road together
maybe five months?
They were a great five months.
All you did was come on to me.
If Glen hadn't been so fucked up
on coke, he'd have noticed.
I was a man in love. I still am.
Oh, please. Save it for the shower room.
Diane, I know what your life is like now,
raising a kid on your own,
working in this shithouse.
I hear you're doing double shifts
just because you need the money.
I got a way to make you money.
WITTLESEY: You're looking out
for my best interests, huh?
Yeah.
Like I said, save it.
Get your ass back to Em City.
Next item: overtime.
The good news is,
based on the successful conclusion
of negotiations
between the Department of Correction
and the Officers' Union,
we have a contract.
[ALL CLAPPING]
The bad news is, because
the overtime rate is now so high,
the commissioner has decided
to no longer allow officers
to work double shifts.
What? This sucks.
The department gave in
to the union's demands,
knowing they never intended
to pay any overtime?
Hey. That's how deals get made.
Hey, what are you complaining about,
Lady Di?
It frees you up to spend more time
with your boyfriend.
[MAKES KISSING SOUNDS]
What are you talking about?
Yeah, Healy, what are you trying to say?
You two wanna pretend
you're not fucking each other, fine.
You're a funny guy, you know that?
-Knock it off, you two!
-Come on, tough guy.
GLYNN: McManus. McManus, sit down.
You fucking prick. GLYNN: Sit down.
Healy, keep your comments to yourself.
Next item.
McMANUS: Fuck them.
-No, Timmy, it's not that easy.
Like it or not,
we work with these people.
If they don't respect us,
it makes the day ten times harder.
Are you saying
we can't see each other anymore?
Look, this job is all I have.
Do you understand that?
You have a college education,
a big time reputation.
If I lose this, it's back
to cleaning other people's houses.
It's welfare.
I have a daughter to feed
and a mother getting old.
-I can give you money.
-You have alimony and a mortgage,
you can't afford to take me on.
And I wouldn't want you to.
Please... No, I'll see you, Tim.
You and me both know
cigarettes is money in the joint.
Want someone to do your laundry,
a couple of sticks.
Want someone to get rolled,
a carton or two,
depending on who it is.
Problem is,
they got a really short shelf life.
You can't hoard them,
you gotta keep them moving.
Supply and demand, baby,
that's what I'm talking about.
-I bring them in, you sell them.
-A carton a day, that's it.
Come on, what do you say?
Okay.
-Put the cigarette out.
-That's my baby.
HILL: Not all drugs are recreational.
Some are benign, or supposedly benign.
I got the final results back
from your tests.
You're suffering from hypertension.
Curse of my people.
African-Americans are genetically
predisposed to the condition.
No, doctor, it's not genetics.
High blood pressure is caused by racism.
There are some studies out
suggesting a link
between racial discrimination
and hypertension,
but the data is inconclusive.
Well, it may be inconclusive
to the scientists,
but I know that it's a fact.
Men of color in the working class
have a higher blood pressure than whites,
or even black professionals. Why?
Because we are forced
to accept unfair treatment, doctor.
I'm not really interested in the politics,
Said, I care about your health.
And if we don't do something,
you're headed for heart disease,
stroke, damage to the other organs.
So I'm going to prescribe some Tenormin.
What are the side effects?
Low heartbeat, light-headedness
if you stand up too quickly.
That won't do.
Daily, I kneel and I pray to Mecca.
-What else do you have?
-Calan.
Constipation, nausea, dizziness.
No. My mind must function clearly.
All drugs have side effects.
Perhaps that's God's way of telling us
we shouldn't be taking them.
You have to take something or you'll die.
Believe me, doctor,
I have no intention of dying.
Can I go now?
Sure.
I'm sorry that you're ill.
-And who told you that I was ill?
-God.
Oh, yes. You talk to God.
When he's in town.
Well, in Islam, we believe that only
two people spoke to God directly:
Mohammad, and praise be to him,
and Moses.
So, you see,
you are in excellent company.
-You think I'm lying or deluded.
-Oh, yeah.
I may well be.
I do know sometimes
I can see inside men's souls.
And can you see into mine, old man?
-Yes.
-And what is there?
-Anger.
-Yes, I am angry.
I am angry at a society
that cripples my people,
that infects their bodies.
No, you're angry at God.
I am not.
My illness is Allah's will.
And I accept the bad as well
as the good that God gives me.
Still, you're angry at him, and afraid.
Afraid of dying.
That is not true.
You watched Jefferson Keane die,
die gladly.
Keane embraced death like a lover,
like a traveler going home.
You saw that and were afraid.
You realized you aren't as willing to go.
Get out of here, old man.
Get out.
[MUTTERING PRAYERS]
The ever-increasing scandal
surrounding Governor James Devlin
accepting kickbacks
took another bizarre turn today,
when his wife, Evangeline Devlin,
moved out of the governor's mansion.
Though no official word has been given,
sources say that Mrs. Devlin
has learned of an affair between-
-The doctor told me what's going on.
-That is not your concern, McManus.
He told me
you won't take your medication.
I haven't decided anything as yet.
Well, you don't have a choice.
Take the drugs.
And what if I refuse?
-I'll force you to.
-How?
I'll open up your mouth
and stuff the pills
down your throat myself.
-Okay, let's make that deal, McManus.
-You know what I want.
I can't tell you much about
how the drugs come into Oz,
except to say look at your own house.
What's that mean?
-That's a pretty big accusation.
-Not really.
Look, there are plenty of examples of
officers smuggling drugs into prisons.
Soledad, Attica, here at Oz in '82.
I remember. I was working solitary.
-Two of my best friends got busted.
-So then...?
-I'll start an investigation.
-Good.
Of the entire staff. Everyone
from the officers to the librarian to you.
I'll take it slow, because if it's true,
I don't wanna spook them.
I wanna be able
to make the charges stick.
-Hey, Roger.
-Hey, morning, Mike.
-See the Toronto game?
-Yeah, Gaston's a spaz.
-How much you lose?
-Don't ask.
Hey, Diane.
-You heading out?
-Yeah.
These graveyard shifts are killing me.
SIMON: O'Reily.
-Yeah.
SIMON: Go see Schibetta.
Since when are you his Western Union?
Since we partners,
he and I.
You're the monkey
chained to his organ grinder.
Better watch that pretty little ass.
No need.
You're too busy watching it for me.
And keep your fucking hands off me.
I'm scared of you.
You wanted to see me, Nino?
Yeah, come on in.
No, thanks.
I've never been big on tomatoes.
You Irish. You got no appreciation
for the simple things in life.
-What's simpler than a potato?
-Sit.
You been saying if I need it,
you'd be willing to help out.
Anything. You know Adebisi's gonna
shank you the first chance he gets.
Don't you worry about Adebisi.
He's a mongrel, but effective.
From you, I need
a more sophisticated favor.
I need to close down
Healy's drug operation.
Healy? Officer Healy?
Don't say you know nothing about it.
Your brother and Healy are friends.
Healy's been your archangel
since you got to Oz.
-You've been running tits for him.
-You know, I don't know what you're-
I don't hold it against you.
I'd have done the same.
Only Healy's business
is starting to cut into mine,
and that I can't have happen.
So I am looking to you for assistance.
-You want me to set him up?
-Yeah.
If you do,
I promise I'll take care of you.
What do you say?
He's been good to me.
Is that your answer?
I'll do it.
[SPEAKS IN ITALIAN]
So, what's the plan?
The plan is up to you.
I don't care about the hows.
Just get it done.
All right.
-I need more tits.
-Oh, yeah?
I gave you a huge pair
a couple of days ago.
What can I say?
We go bra-less in Em City.
When can you get me some more?
Later.
-Yo, you looking for me?
-Yeah.
-How'd you like some tits for free?
-I don't kill.
-You don't have to kill.
-What do you want me to do?
Go see your pals upstairs.
And tell them what?
Tell them that you found
another drug connection.
-Well, who you gonna bust this time?
-Me.
HEALY: What the fuck is this?
What the fuck is this?
GUARD 1: I got him, I got him. Hold on.
GLYNN: Take O'Reily to the hole.
HEALY: You're fucking dead!
O'REILY: You're a fucking fag!
GLYNN: Hey, McManus! Get him out of here!
Hey. That's going on your record.
McMANUS: Big fucking deal.
I gave this place everything I had.
And then you decided it was time
to take everything you could.
Look, I know working here's no paradise,
but you swore an oath
and you broke that oath!
I got no sympathy for you.
-Get him away from me.
-You wait, warden.
Wait till you need somebody like me
to back you up. I won't be here.
Then you can kiss your ass goodbye.
-Will you testify against Healy?
-No.
I jabber on him,
every other hack will be waiting in line
to take a whack at me too.
Fine. Officer Hunt?
See you in a month, O'Reily.
Hey, O'Reily,
any idea who ratted on Healy?
Beats the shit out of me.
But if I were a betting man,
I'd put my money on Poklewaldt.
MEDIC 1: Coming through.
Come on, back up. Back up.
Patient's name is Ronald Poklewaldt.
-It's severe head trauma.
-How are the vital signs?
MEDIC 2: Got a lot of blood.
Gonna have to get blood.
[GASPING]
[GROANING]
Ah!
Let me out of here!
[SOBBING]
GUARD: You're done.
Piece of cake.
No. Who is this fucking Pinocchio?
I don't play games.
How do you keep that hat
on your head? Velcro?
-Deal me in.
-You play Pinochle?
No, I can learn.
Adebisi, I'll see you later.
Okay, each player gets 12 cards.
One card face up, that's the trump card.
There's two ways to score.
KENNY: You're in a mood.
[SNIFFS]
I'm in a mood, all right.
I'm in a mood to kill.
Anybody in particular?
Mick and dago.
Yeah, well, I could go
for a piece of Schibetta's ass myself.
Yeah? Well, stick around, little brother.
When the time is right, he's all yours.
He's all mine.
You take a drug, right?
The chemicals,
they rush through your body,
rush through your brain.
And the sensations,
you want the sensations
again and again and again.
But let me tell you, you can also
get addicted to grief, to guilt, to hate.
Because when you feel dead inside,
even bad sensations
make you feel like you're alive!
[BUZZER SOUNDS]
SCHILLINGER:
What, that's it? No good-night kiss?
I'm beginning to think
you don't love me anymore.
I do.
-Say it. Say you love me.
-I love you.
No, you see, you said it
but you didn't mean it.
I do mean it, sir.
No, I'm telling you, the romance
has gone out of our relationship.
But I have the cure.
I was saving this for your birthday,
but, hell, I think we need it now.
No, thanks.
Come on, you're gonna hurt my feelings.
You know what happens
when you hurt my feelings.
Put some on.
No.
Okay.
Hey, I understand. You wanna surprise me.
Gonna wait for a special occasion
to get yourself all prettied up.
That is so sweet.
Hey, I can wait.
Not too long.
[KNOCKING ON DOOR]
What? A nun can't look beautiful?
-Tobias, are you all right?
-Sure.
Think I'm blind?
I'm a drug counselor, for God's sake.
If I can't spot the signs,
I might as well tear up my license.
I don't know what you're talking about.
Listen.
I know how hideous life is in Oz,
especially for a man like you
with no street skills,
no preparation for the reality of it all,
but Tobias, Tobias,
drugs are not the answer.
They only make the questions
more difficult.
I want you to start coming
to counseling sessions.
Whatever.
I'm not sure when he started,
but my sense is not too long ago.
I'm hoping we can nip this in the bud.
Well, I'll have the officers on duty
monitor Beecher carefully
and I'll see who he's hanging out with.
Well, it can't be Schillinger
who's supplying.
He's so anti-drug, he makes me
look like Robert Downey Jr.
Yeah, maybe we should
also talk to members of his family.
Well, his wife took the kids
and moved away,
but he does have parents and siblings.
-What about an intervention?
-I think that's too much, too soon.
Why don't we invite one of his relatives
to visit him and see what happens?
You know, on the outside, Beecher
had a history of alcohol abuse.
Oh, I know. How pathetic is that?
The man gets jailed for one addiction
and we watch him get hooked on another.
[BELL RINGS]
You smell good, Mother.
Same old Chanel, I'm afraid.
Yeah, I remember you and Dad
getting ready to go out,
him putting on his tux,
you wearing the latest gown,
and that scent wafting through the air.
But that was a long time ago
in a galaxy far, far away.
Toby...
...I had a conversation
with the man who runs...
-...the place where you live.
-McManus?
He told me that he suspects you
of using drugs.
Mother... Heroin.
Mother, you don't know
what it's like in here.
-I can imagine.
-No, you can't!
And I thank God every night for that.
So if you wanna tell me about
how Angus is doing in law school
or about Dad's most recent fishing trip
or Grandmother's lumbago, fine.
But if you came here to lecture me,
tell me to "just say no"...
...don't.
Don't put that final knife in my heart.
Toby.
[SNIFFS]
GUARD: Get out!
REIMONDO:
Hello, Tobias. Come on in. Sit down.
Okay, we've got a new member
to our group, Tobias Beecher.
Tobias, I think you know
Augustus and Ron from Em City,
and that's John and Bill
and Whitney Munson.
Beecher. I knew a Beecher.
-Cyrus. Are you any relation?
-No.
Good. The man was a cocksucker.
Okay, the idea here
is for us, in this small group,
to talk about ourselves,
our feelings, our addictions,
in the hope that we can find the cause.
RONALD: I know the cause.
-I like the shit.
REIMONDO: All right, that's fine.
Pleasure plays a very strong factor.
But underneath,
maybe there's something else.
There's a deeper need, a deeper hunger,
an emptiness that has to be filled.
So, Tobias, why don't you tell us
what you're addicted to?
You know.
They know.
Yeah, okay. Augustus,
you wanna talk about your addiction?
I was a crack addict.
Been squeaky clean 22 months.
REIMONDO: Yes. Ron?
RONALD: Speed's my fave.
REIMONDO: How long you been clean?
A year.
Whitney.
I quit seven times
over the last 52 years,
this being my longest period:
five years, three months and six days.
REIMONDO: What are you addicted to?
WHITNEY: What, since I been inside?
REIMONDO: Yeah.
Anything I can get my hands on,
but originally opium.
I had been decorated
with the Purple Heart for valor.
Valor.
Only I knew I was really a fraud.
Even after I was discharged,
I couldn't take the uniform off.
During the war,
while I was in the Orient,
I got hooked into opium.
My true self
lay in that quixotic little drug.
Prisoner number 45M242, Whitney Munson.
Convicted March 7th, '45.
Murder in the first degree,
criminal possession
of a controlled substance.
Sentence: 1100 years.
Up for parole in 60.
Question: why'd you strangle the whore?
I didn't think I was.
I thought I was being affectionate.
Her neck was so pale,
so thin, so fine.
REIMONDO: And you've been
in prison for 52 years, right?
That's right. I only got eight years left
until my parole.
Come the year 2005, I'm out of here.
I can't stay here anymore and listen
to any more of these fucking stories!
-Tobias, sit down.
-No, it's not helping.
REIMONDO: Sit down.
-It's not helping!
GUARD: Hold it!
-Hello.
-Yeah, yeah.
I'm here to give you a makeover.
BEECHER: Huh?
Your boyfriend told me to.
He said, "Don't take no for an answer."
[SNIFFS]
My God.
You're even prettier
than I thought you'd be.
[BOTH LAUGHING]
He really is a beautiful baby.
[SPEAKING IN SPANISH]
Miguel.
Your baby is dead.
Aw.
[SOBBING]
I ain't saying drugs are good.
But when your past is past
and your present sucks,
your future holds nothing
but broken promises and dead dreams,
the drugs, they kill the pain.
Listen up, America.
You ain't never gonna get rid of drugs
until you cure pain.