Hello!
Hi, Mom.
You want me to do that?
In gloves?
The blender was broken at the diner.
And you wouldn't dare
deprive them of dessert.
You look swanky. Fundraising?
Much better.
We had dinner with the dean
of Fairfield University.
Some distant Rockefeller.
Actually, I'm planning on enrolling in the fall.
Master's degree.
Really? In what?
Psychology.
I know it's beyond your experience,
but people love to talk to me.
They seek me out to share their confidences.
It should be fascinating
for everyone involved.
Hello, Don.
We're making chocolate shakes.
I should go.
Don't rush off. You can finish your milkshake.
Make Henry one.
You give him a sip of yours.
Bye-bye.
Maybe I'll make my own.
Did you have fun?
Hello?
You're home.
I was expecting the service.
I just walked in.
I wanted to let you know that
the movers are gonna come on
Wednesday to pick up my furniture.
What time do you want me to be there?
Just tell the doorman.
We're coming at 10:00.
Does that give you enough time?
You know what time I go to work.
There's one other thing.
It's the 24th already.
How could you be out of money?
Between the movers and the flight...
Why am I explaining myself to you?
I'm tired of asking for an allowance.
Can we sign the papers and be done?
Your lawyer's very aggressive.
That's not how I heard it.
I'm starting to think you're enjoying this.
Well, my finances are a mess
since the McCann deal.
You were a millionaire when I met you.
Just tell your lawyer he won.
I'll sign whatever you want.
I can't live like this.
This is what they do, honey.
How much do you need right now?
I'll leave a check.
Five hundred.
Who's moving you, the New York Jets?
I have to go.
I'm ready, Caroline.
What's she doing here?
It's too much. I can't do it by myself.
Well, you should have asked me.
You're too busy!
Sit down, Shirley.
Well, this morning,
immediately following this,
you have a meeting with
Mr. Campbell and Mr. Torkelson
regarding Lester Chapman.
Who's he?
Secor Laxatives.
I'm sorry, but actually, he's at Life Cereal.
This is working out already.
They want to set a call for 4:00.
Hold on a second. Isn't he NAC?
I'll check the Rolodex.
I'm sorry, what's NAC?
No afternoon calls. Lester's blotto after lunch.
He is indeed.
Well, let's call him now.
So, it's 7-9-8...
This certainly is a two-man job.
...3...
So you just fly to Los Angeles
for the weekend?
Isn't that tiring?
What's tiring is coming back here.
So beautiful. You should go sometime.
I don't know if I'd like it.
How do you go to sleep at night
knowing the Manson brothers
could be running around?
- Good morning.
- The Manson family.
- Are they coming in?
- No. A quick word?
Coffee.
So, I got a strange phone call.
Well, not strange, but unexpected.
Megan called me.
Really?
I guess she's coming into town
and she wants to buy me a drink
to see if I can help her find a new agent.
Can you?
Of course, I can. I do it all the time.
It's just... Well, I wanted to let you know.
Been down this road before
and you always find out.
Because you always tell me.
Yes, but she didn't want me to.
It's never stopped you before.
So should I meet with her?
She's not my wife anymore, Harry.
You have a call
from a Nicholas Constantinopolis.
Probably Greek.
Yes. I need to take this.
I'm sure that's a story.
Nicholas, it's Don.
Good evening. Can I get you
something from the bar?
Or are you expecting...
Hello.
How are you?
I'm surprised.
This isn't a coincidence.
I was looking for you.
What do you want?
I want to eat dinner with you.
Even if it's five minutes at a time.
No.
You're making me uncomfortable.
This is my phone number.
Call me when you get off work.
I'll meet you somewhere.
I'll show you her work.
You will absolutely recognize it. Ed!
All I'm saying is you dug pretty deep
to find a woman.
Do you know where
Samantha Ryan's portfolio is?
She calls herself Pima.
Pima Ryan?
Exactly.
She came and spoke
at RISD when I was there.
She's a very sexy lady.
I thought you were queer.
Where's Pima's portfolio?
I took it home. Does she want it back?
Does she need it?
No, I need it. Peggy forgot
this is my account, too.
We're really lucky. She's never done an ad.
Stan, I'm sorry, but you do not
have any of the qualities
that either I or Cinzano are looking
for other than being cheaper.
It's hard to keep my balls at this job.
Ed, what do you know about vermouth?
No.
Hello?
Hello. It's Diana.
You know, the waitress.
I'm glad you called.
I didn't think you were gonna.
I don't know anybody in New York.
So strange to see somebody that I know.
I'm just pleased you're not cross.
I was pretty mad. How did you find me?
Are you a private detective?
You kinda look like one.
Why don't we have a drink?
I've already got one. Let's talk now.
I waited a little,
maybe too long,
and you were gone.
So I told Nick at the diner to
let me know if you ever came back.
I went home.
Where's home?
Racine, Wisconsin.
I had to get a divorce.
I'm divorced.
Well, I happen to be in the same boat.
Right now I'm in the boat.
I must have known that.
Come over.
Where are you?
I'm at work.
I don't have a phone yet.
Fine, I'll come there.
Welcome.
Do you sleep like that?
I'm vain.
May I?
It's a very lovely apartment.
It's like Architectural Digest.
My...
She decorated it.
It's what I pictured.
So you were picturing it?
I took a cab to some stranger's
apartment with $6 in my pocket.
I was hoping it was like this.
I'm gonna sell it.
I was just apartment hunting.
It's gonna be hard to beat.
Can I fix you a drink?
I don't know how I feel about
getting to know you better.
It's 3:00 A.M. You know why you're here.
Do you want a drink or not?
I'm already drunk.
Would you like a glass of water?
Hey, I can't sleep like this.
You were.
I don't want to.
Do you want to go?
No.
Are you really divorced?
Yes, I am. Really. Why?
You got a lot of coats in that closet.
She lives in California. She didn't need them.
Do you want one?
I was going to go to San Francisco.
I flipped a coin.
I always wanted to live here.
It was in all the movies, all the magazines.
I haven't seen any of it.
It's a great city.
How long were you married?
Twelve years.
I don't know why I thought it'd be easy.
It's never easy.
I've been through it before.
There's no children this time.
You?
No children.
You smell incredible. What is that?
Shampoo.
Avon.
I bought it in my living room.
In my ranch house.
And my two-car garage.
Diana?
They're here every other weekend.
Well, not my little girl. She's at boarding
school, but the boys come.
Are you okay?
No.
What's wrong?
I lied to you.
Already?
No, I left home because I have a little girl.
I had a little girl.
I'm so sorry.
Yes.
When?
Two years ago.
The flu. Can you imagine?
I'm so sorry.
I don't want to talk about it.
Obviously, I'm in New York City.
You should go.
It's my house.
Don't you have to get ready for work?
I don't feel like it.
Gentlemen, I'm going to be strict,
but this is Torkelson's law.
Take a good look.
You got your models, you got your bottles.
If you make it to lunch
without bothering anybody,
we'll let you have whichever you want.
Well, if you'll all excuse me.
Come on, I'll introduce you.
Pima Ryan, this is our art director Stan Rizzo.
So you'll be cutting up my work, will you?
Well, I try to treat it like art
even though it's just selling something.
All art is selling something.
No, we're actually selling something.
Today, it's vermouth.
I apologize the models have so many teeth.
I know you're not used to that.
Pleasure to meet you.
I'm sorry about that. He has a hard time with
new people.
No, he hates himself.
I don't think so. He's got a huge ego.
And he's a photographer.
Men like him don't bother me,
and they shouldn't bother you either.
Look at all you're doing here.
It's just my job.
Good morning, girls.
Could you take your places?
- Good morning.
- It's 11:30.
Where were you? I was worried.
I was sleepy.
Mr. Sterling's in there.
He's not to be disturbed.
Who are you hiding from?
I got two secretaries and three telephones.
I feel like Marlin Perkins
is chasing me on the savannah.
Hiding is pointless.
I've got work to do.
That's the other reason I'm here.
McCann represents Derby Foods.
Peter Pan Peanut Butter.
They're making a cookie.
Sounds delicious.
McCann also represents Nabisco.
National Biscuit Company.
They got the word "cookie" in their name.
No, they don't.
Do we have a shot at Derby?
No, it's just a cookie.
McCann's clients are
our clients. We're helping out.
You and Peter are taking them
golfing tomorrow.
I can't make it.
There's a messenger
here from your attorney's office.
He needs your signature.
Since when can't you go golfing?
Since Burt Peterson's the account man.
Good news or bad news?
Good news. It's almost over.
Well, don't settle until
you get the number you want.
Take it from me, no matter what she says,
you have given her the good life.
She'd never have had it.
Megan is not Jane.
So she never said you squandered
her youth and beauty?
Used up her childbearing years?
Thwarted her career? What career?
She's a consumer.
Mr. Sterling, are you
still at lunch? They're wondering.
She made her choices.
You're very good.
Can I help you?
Well, I've been told that my negatives
belong to the agency
and therefore processing
has to be done at your lab.
I'm not comfortable with that.
I hate to break it to you,
but it's not really yours anymore.
Don't you have a darkroom here?
Yes, but I can't do that.
I started off as a clerk
with a newspaper in Sarasota.
All I wanted was to get in that darkroom.
It's a nice thing to have, especially in the city.
So, you're a photographer.
I do everything.
I'm an art director.
You must show me your work.
I don't know.
I can feel the tension
of your need for my opinion.
I wouldn't mind you taking a look
if you promise to be honest.
Let's see how brave you are.
Hello? Mother? Marie-France?
- Bellman.
- Please come in.
Please, just put the bags here.
Thank you.
For you to enjoy and for him to pay for.
I'm not changing rooms.
Well, she's made plans for us.
Absolutely not. This isn't a vacation.
We'll have a contest.
We'll see if we can get drunker than Mama.
Evening, Doctor.
Can you hold that?
- Hello, Don.
- Hello, Arnold.
Good evening.
This is Diana. Arnold and Sylvia.
Hello.
Brought the whole restaurant home, did you?
You're not on call, are you?
Mitchell's CO got married.
The girl, very young, but very homely.
Good night.
Don, we should play squash sometime.
You know, if you have the energy.
- Arnold!
- Sounds like fun.
How many girls have you had in this elevator?
That's not what that was.
Hello?
I said hello. You didn't even grunt.
Are you in a creative mood or a bad mood?
I don't know what I'm doing.
Everything good I have
is from a long time ago.
So what? You think Picasso looks
at Guernica and says,
"Ignore that. It was a long time ago?"
I got nothing to show her.
Who cares about her?
You should see what she does.
It's so sensual.
Get your camera.
Why?
I want you to take my picture.
No, you don't.
No touching the model.
In here?
Well, I'm not going outside.
You must sit out there all the time.
I wanna see where you live.
How could I be nervous at this point?
I know.
There's a twinge in my chest.
A pain?
No, it's not that. I'm positive.
Are you hungry?
Not really.
Hello?
Of course.
Yes.
Thank you, Meredith.
Everything okay?
Yeah.
We have to get out of here.
She's coming to take her things
and I don't want to be here.
- Okay.
- No, look.
What?
I think if I were you,
this would bother me,
and it shouldn't
because it's almost over.
Good.
I want to see you tonight.
At my place, okay?
Let's go.
Shit.
We'll swing by your place on the way.
I'll rent.
You're going to rent pants?
I'll throw my tie over my shoulder,
and roll up my sleeves.
They'll love it.
Probably will.
What's the difference now?
Stop it this minute.
I have to go change for lunch.
It's $200 including the tip.
He gave me a check for $500.
Like a whore?
In the States, it's the 20th century.
People get divorced all the time.
Exactly. You can still get an annulment.
I'm not like you.
I don't spend my whole life feeling ashamed.
Marie-France, don't be a bitch.
I am not a servant here to wait on her
while she goes for lunch.
I know you don't understand this,
but it's for my career.
Good luck with your bright future.
Wait.
No.
It's not much. It's just the boxes,
Granny's cabinet, that chair, and the mirror.
Go. Have fun. I'll take care of this.
Hey, where's everybody going?
My mother's here. Thank you so much.
Do you have to smoke in here?
It's taking my mind off your driving.
I don't know why we couldn't
swing by your apartment?
What will the clients think?
That you're renting clubs?
I'll buy a set in the shop.
Megan's moving her things today.
I didn't know that was still going on.
They want to punish you.
And then you get mad
and you want to punish them,
but you know it's your fault.
I've been through it before.
How did you handle client dinners?
I got a date.
I don't have a steady,
so it's too unpredictable.
You don't know how much
they're going to drink
and suddenly you're with a floozy.
Golf is better.
Jiminy Christmas.
You think you're going to begin your life
over and do it right,
but what if you never
get past the beginning again?
Watch the road.
You filled the whole truck,
that wasn't what we agreed.
I told you it was gonna be more.
More than double?
- Fine, how much you got?
- I have $350.
That's enough for me
to leave it on the sidewalk.
That's extortion!
Lady, you are a pain in my ass.
Donald Draper's office.
I need to speak with him
immediately. It's Marie Calvet.
Well, I'm sorry, he's not available right now.
Interrupt him.
I can take a message.
May I say what this is regarding?
No.
There's a Marie
something on the line.
Marie who?
I got it. Get off the line.
Bonjour.
I am in desperate need of you.
Well, hello to you, too.
I need you to come to Don's
apartment with $200
and not a penny more!
Calm down. I'll send someone.
What did I expect?
Every time you get
what you want, you run away.
Don't say that.
Bring cash!
It's fine.
Look where you are.
Don't. I'm not ready.
Your subject certainly is.
That's Elaine. She's...
Overdeveloped?
She's not worthy of you.
You can see it in her eyes.
She doesn't want to tell you the truth.
Drawing is a much more rare talent.
I expected more.
- Holy shit.
- What?
- Where is everything?
- On the truck.
Pay him.
One hundred and eighty bucks.
My pleasure.
Don agreed to this?
He was very generous.
And you are a true gentleman.
Let's get outta here. I'll buy you a drink.
I hate what he did to my daughter.
Mon Dieu, I'm trembling.
You really are. It's okay.
What are you doing?
You already emptied the place.
You wanna defile it as well?
Please.
Take advantage of me.
- You look ravishing.
- Thank you.
I'm really sorry I'm late. You know that office.
- Should we get some wine?
- I already did.
I am certainly picking up the check.
I insist.
It's just, you had such good
advice for Miranda and Jill.
Well, they didn't have agents at all.
My advice was get one.
Well, whatever you did.
To whatever I did.
So, give me the lay.
You know, of the land.
There's not much to tell.
I haven't booked anything
in the last few months.
Not even pilot season?
Well, I turned down some
smaller parts because
Alan thought they'd take me
out of the running for leads.
I'm not in his business,
but I find it hard to believe
that you're losing any contest.
I bet he doesn't know how to get you in one.
I read all the time, Harry.
Do you read for lead parts?
That's just getting your name on the right list
with the right casting director.
Good agents with real track
records can make that happen.
Alan represents Angie Dickinson.
You are every man's fantasy.
You're like Ali MacGraw
and Brigitte Bardot had a baby.
You should be the most
famous person in the world right now.
Oh, my goodness!
You should be in this business.
I can't believe Don threw you away.
He's not a loyal person, but I am.
You don't think he could have helped you?
I'm willing to put my money
where my mouth is.
It would be much appreciated.
I'm gonna be honest, I'm not hungry.
I'd rather get to work on this immediately.
Well, we can work and eat. I have a pen.
Well, I have a room upstairs.
It has a phone. I could make some calls.
Harry.
I'm not interested.
Megan, you're a big girl.
Maybe you're in this situation
because of how you're reacting to this.
Hold on. Forget all that.
Come on. Have another glass of wine.
Caroline, I was busy, okay?
Now, how about at least giving me a pat
on the back for remembering I had a meeting?
Hello?
What are you doing here, Megan?
Where the fuck is everything?
Roger...
He came to help me.
I should go.
Why are you here?
I told you to go to the hotel.
I felt guilty that I left
you here, but obviously...
I'm late for a meeting.
I guess you don't care
that she's married to my father.
It wasn't my idea.
You don't get to stand in judgment of me.
Could you give us a second, honey?
No, thank you. Have you spoken with Megan?
I just walked in.
Well, I think I should warn you.
We had lunch and, uh,
she's not stable, Don.
She said a lot of crazy things
and I'm sure will continue to say them.
And what will she say about you?
Crazy things. You know, all I can say is
she really wants a job.
What does that mean?
Don, come on, nothing happened.
You know she hates me.
You know what? It's none of my business.
Well, I don't think I could have
helped her anyway.
She quit her soap and left New York.
It was a really dumb idea.
Pima?
Could you come in? I have the selects.
Could you get the door?
I put the ones that I like best
on the top row here.
I like this one,
but Stan doesn't.
Stan already showed these to you?
He was eager to share,
but he knows nothing about women.
What does that mean?
It was just his opinion.
Well, mine's the only opinion that
matters here. It's my account.
Of course, you're in charge. I know that.
Which one do you like?
I think number three. Top row.
You've never been married.
Nope.
Me either.
The adventures I would have missed.
Number four.
I would love to take your picture.
I...
I don't know about that.
The way you're looking at me right now...
I would capture that.
How are you?
Where is he? He was right behind me.
I don't want anything of yours.
I wasn't going to say a word.
I wasn't gonna give you the satisfaction
of knowing that you ruined my life.
Megan.
Why did I believe you?
Why did I believe the things you said to me?
Why am I being punished for being young?
I gave up everything for you
because I believed you...
And you're nothing but a liar.
An aging, sloppy, selfish liar.
You're right.
You're gonna write me a check?
I want you to have
the life you deserve.
Are you kidding me?
No.
A million dollars?
Why are you doing this to me? It's not funny.
I don't want to fight anymore.
Well, I know it's not real.
Nothing about you is.
It is real.
Please take it.
Megan, I'm sorry.
Send me the papers.
I want you to be honest.
Should I let my hair grow out?
Good night, everybody. Ed, you were right.
Pima's a treasure.
Is she?
You don't like the work?
Because I was thinking, you know,
she'd be right for Butler shoes.
Or maybe Topaz pantyhose.
She's got a thing for legs.
Women's legs.
Sorry to disappoint you.
I'm not disappointed.
Neither was she.
Really?
Does that bother you?
No,
But I bet it might bother Ellen.
Elaine.
This is none of your business.
No.
It's Pima's business,
which turns out to be more
advertising than art.
She's a hustler.
You're jealous.
She tried the same thing with me,
but she didn't get as far.
And that's why I'm not going
to give her another job.
I don't believe you.
Which part?
Not particularly.
So you ordered room service?
I don't care.
She's leaving Papa.
I'm going to pack.
I don't want to hear about it.
You know it's a sin to be a ghoul
and feed on everyone's pain?
She's been very unhappy for a very long time.
At least she did something about it.
I'm exhausted.
Me, too.
Did you print anything?
They're drying.
You did?
How were they? What did Pima say?
She loved them.
How about you?
Do you want a drink? I just have vodka.
Yes, please.
I got you something.
Open it.
It's a New York City guidebook.
Finally start your tour.
Go on.
Can't you see I don't want anything?
Look, I'm pretty sure
I had a worse day than you.
Please don't be in a mood.
I'm not in a mood.
And you've never had a worse day than me.
You don't think I've felt grief?
You knew that about me
the first night we met.
I've been trying to talk myself out of it.
Don't.
No.
Talk myself out of what I have to say.
You're scared. I understand.
But I took care of everything today.
I've been separated a long time.
You're not
the first thing to come along.
I'm ready.
You're fooling yourself if you think
this'll make a difference.
You don't think I know what's going on here?
Look at this dump.
I know you think you deserve this.
I've done it.
I left my daughter.
Stop blaming yourself.
No.
I had two children. Two girls.
One died and one...
My oldest is in Racine with her father.
Why? Don't you want to ask why?
No.
I told you about my heart.
I don't want to feel anything else.
When I was with you, I forgot about
her.
I don't ever want to do that.