CHUCK: Hi, I'm Chuck.
Here are a few things to know.
Is there any way
Intersect images can be taken out?
-Removed? Only Orion would know.
-Orion.
ORION: It's good to finally
see you face to face.
The cards are the schematics
for the new Intersect. Study them.
Find Fulcrum's intersect,
you could get your life back.
I promised Ellie that I'd find our dad,
but I've tried everything. He's nowhere.
It's like he's fallen
off the face of the earth.
Dad?
-I'm sort of freaking out here.
-I know.
But he's your father.
He seemed happy to see you.
CHUCK:
You think?
I thought it was lack of recognition
followed by shock.
STEVE: You take cream?
-Huh?
Yeah. No.
Whatever's fine.
[WHISPERS]
I can't remember if I take cream.
-Just relax.
-How?
I haven't seen my dad
for, like, 10 years...
...and now I'm sitting in his living room
slash kitchenette...
...while he's making us coffee.
Plus let's just say the last time
I saw him he was kind of--
I mean, he tended to be a little--
What's the word? Crazy.
Here we go.
[IN NORMAL VOICE]
Thanks.
Thank you.
It's good to see that face again.
Yeah, yours too.
So...
...you been doing okay?
Who cares about me? Tell me about you.
Well, I-- There's not much to tell.
Graduated from high school.
Went to Stanford, work at Buy More.
Stanford. Not bad.
He was always a genius, this one.
-Well, not like you.
-You're right.
He was smarter.
-What about Ellie, how is she?
-Really great, actually.
She's a doctor now.
And in a few weeks,
she's gonna get married...
...to, well, an awesome guy.
Ellie's getting married?
She is.
That's actually mainly why we're here.
Ellie was really hoping that you might be
there to walk her down the aisle.
Oh, I don't think
she would want me there.
I mean, of course she does. We both do.
It's not a good idea.
But tell her that I'm happy for her.
Are you joking?
You have to do this.
She's your daughter.
Charles, I can't.
I don't wanna hear what you can't do.
I've seen what you can't do.
I'm sorry. I....
-That came out wrong.
-No, it didn't.
You're mad.
I left, and you're mad.
Look, Dad,
I'm not even here for me, really.
Okay? Right now, I just--
I want you to come home for Ellie, please.
I like you coming up here
and fighting for Ellie.
Makes me happy you...
...at least had each other.
Let me get a few things together.
Are you okay?
Yeah, I think so.
I mean, I'm glad we found him for Ellie.
And for you?
Yeah.
Maybe he's not as crazy
as I remembered.
Okay,
let's go get your sister married, huh?
Maybe we should wait till dark.
They're....
They're tracking my every move.
Rat bastards.
This would be perfect
for the rehearsal dinner...
...because if I wear that dress
this will match.
Sounds good.
Or we could--
-Ellie, hey.
-Hey, Chuck, just a sec.
We could do the cranberry,
which would really bring out your....
Hello, Eleanor.
Aren't you gonna say something?
Pancakes.
Oh, boy.
You said
you were gonna make pancakes.
[DOOR SLAMS SHUT]
Well, that went well.
-Hey.
-You must be Devon.
Yeah.
Big TV.
Ellie, I'm sorry. I should've called first.
A surprise of this magnitude
wasn't the best idea.
No, it's not your fault. Just....
I'm so mad at him. Our crazy old dad.
Aren't you mad at him?
I was. Yeah.
But then I realized that...
...we can hate him for the rest of our lives
or we can choose to forgive him.
It's easier to hate him.
Well, that may be,
but he's all we got left, El.
This could be our last chance
at being a family again.
Let's go.
I guess I was just surprised
to see you, Dad.
Yeah.
I'm sure you were.
God, Ellie, you look just like your mother.
Sorry I left you two alone like that.
No, no, it's fine.
Your dad was just explaining
our television to me.
I was just telling Devon...
...that I practically invented your TV.
I came up with these
helix-shaped plasma crystals...
...back in high school.
Never saw a dime for it.
Okay, well, who's hungry?
I'll order pizza.
Touch-screen technology.
That was one of mine.
Ted Roark and I came up with it
back in grad school.
Ted?
You went to school with Ted Roark?
The Roark Instruments guy? Awesome.
Yeah, he took all my ideas.
And I never got anything.
The guy's a lying thief.
How about I order the pizza. Pepperoni?
Roark's releasing
a new software this week...
...that I guarantee has components
that I helped develop.
Pepperoni sounds great.
I still have my original
touch-screen schematics.
I wanna show you.
Dad.
ELLIE:
Okay, guys, I am really trying here...
...but he is obviously
as crazy as we remember.
It seems Chuck's flash
matches a lot of chatter...
...we've been hearing
about Roark Instruments.
The CIA now believes
Ted Roark's latest software...
...may contain a virus that, if released,
could cause irreparable damage...
...to the world's computer networks.
Why don't we just contact Roark
and tell them?
We can't, out of fear of alerting
those who might be involved.
Instead we're going to send in Chuck
as a new RI employee.
You will see
if you flash on anyone or anything.
Your interview is in one hour.
-You okay with that?
-Why wouldn't he be?
His dad went to school with Roark.
There could be some history.
Your daddy issues
gonna jeopardize our mission?
No, no, I'm fine.
I mean, forget Apple, forget Microsoft.
I've dreamt of working for Roark
since college.
Although does it qualify as a dream
come true if I go in as a janitor?
You're going in as Charles Bartowski.
Your name, your résumé,
your Stanford degree.
Really?
You're perfectly qualified
to go in as yourself.
Me at RI?
Hey. You must be Chuck.
I'm Drew.
Welcome to Roark Instruments.
-Where the future happens first.
-I love it here.
DREW:
Everyone does.
Please, have a seat.
-Oh, right, here, yeah.
-Yeah.
Sorry.
[BALL SQUEAKING]
Ahem. So I see you went to Stanford.
Me too. Class of '07.
'07. Wow, you've only been out
a couple of years.
That's eons in the software game.
Come on, where you been?
Seriously, tell me what you've been
up to since you graduated.
Well....
What have I been up to? Uh....
Chuck, just be honest.
I've actually been working
at a Buy More...
...in the Nerd Herd division...
...which has given me
quite a bit of experience...
...working with computers,
operating systems, technologies.
I've gotten the opportunity to work...
...with many different,
unusual personalities.
-Good morning, Big Michael.
-Whoa!
-Where did you come from?
-We have a proposition for you.
-I'll pass. Excuse me.
-Wait, wait, wait.
Two words. NextExpo.
-That's one word.
-Stop counting.
Tomorrow is Roark's
Next Technology Expo...
...where they're gonna be releasing
their new operating system.
Now, we believe
that attending that release...
...will make us better employees.
And better human beings.
-NextExpo, huh?
-Yeah.
Good thinking.
Send Bartowski.
-Chuck's not here.
-As usual.
Okay, fine. You both can go.
Have fun camping out
at the weirdo convention.
I would say my greatest weakness is
how little I've pushed myself since college.
I've been trapped in a job, a life...
...that I don't really want,
but don't really see a way out.
Being here's a good start.
Well, clearly you're qualified.
It doesn't hurt
that you're a fellow Stanford alum.
I'd love for you to take the job.
Really?
Thank you so much.
-Congratulations, Chuck.
-Oh, thanks.
Hey. Here we go. Here we go.
-There we go. There we are.
-Okay.
We'll work on those ball skills.
[CHUCK CHUCKLES]
-Hey, what's that?
-The lobby.
-What's that?
-Elevator.
-The bathroom.
Man, this place is awesome.
Over there is R & D and that hallway
leads to our testing facilities.
Sorry about the shortened tour.
We've been so busy with the software.
All right.
Right around here is....
[INAUDIBLE DIALOGUE]
Hey, Ted, this is Chuck,
our new employee.
Hey. Welcome to RI.
Never wash that hand.
I never will, sir.
No sirs around here.
Except for her.
[LAUGHING]
Okay, Ted.
It's just an honor to be here
and working for your company.
Easy. You already got the gig.
Ready to take over the world?
Only 24 hours of camping,
and NextExpo is ours, because....
CHUCK: I don't know what to say.
I'm speechless.
Welcome to the team.
Happy to have you aboard.
Oh, yeah.
Wow. Think Morgan knows
that Chuck's cheating on the Buy More?
LESTER: You know your boyfriend
just took a job at Roark?
Yeah. I was the first one he told.
-You guys are over.
-Yeah, okay.
[WHIMPERS]
It's weird. Even though I know it's not real,
I'm excited about this job.
Chuck, you gotta remember
it's just an assignment.
No, I mean, I know, I know what it is.
I just--
If I had gotten this job at Roark
right after college...
...maybe I never become the Intersect.
When my dad comes back
after 10 years...
...I'm not just another loser
working at Buy More.
Chuck, he knows you're not a loser.
Well, I'm sure he hoped I'd be doing
something bigger than Nerd Herding.
You are.
DEVON:
Cheers.
[LAUGHING]
-Charles.
-Perfect timing, you two.
-Wow. This looks great.
-Been sitting, waiting.
CHUCK:
I'm sorry.
-Hi, Sarah.
SARAH: Hi.
Where you been?
Well, working, saving the lives
of small technological devices.
[CHUCKLES]
ELLIE:
How about a toast?
To family.
Dad, we are extremely grateful
to have you home.
Yes, we are.
DEVON: Welcome.
MORGAN: Stevie.
Thank you. And here's to you and Devon.
May you live happily together forever.
You deserve it.
-Thank you.
-Thanks.
When's the bachelor party?
I already had it.
STEVE:
And how was it?
I don't really wanna talk about it.
Well, okay, I got one.
How about to Chuck's new job?
-What?
MORGAN: That's what I hear.
Lester tells me that you're leaving
your old buddy and the Buy More behind...
...to go all corporate
over at Roark Instruments.
Which I-- Pretty cool.
So good luck, buddy.
Chuck, that's amazing.
You're going to work for Roark?
The man who stole everything from me?
Either this is a mission or you are very good
at hiding your hobbies.
We're going to retrieve the code
for the operating system.
Without it, Roark can't release the virus.
It's gonna take time
to break into the vault.
We need you to keep an eye on Roark
in case anything goes wrong.
-Keep an eye on Roark? What--?
-Have a nice first day.
MAN:
Everyone, welcome to NextExpo 2009.
Please, one at a time.
Please stay in line.
This-- Hey.
Guys, everybody calm down, okay?
[INAUDIBLE DIALOGUE]
Chuck. Chuck.
Hey, Chuck, over here. Chuck.
Charles. Chuck.
He's already forgotten us.
It's like he looked right through me.
Not to add any pressure,
but there's a Fulcrum agent here.
He's some computer terrorist.
If Fulcrum is here, it's even more vital
that we stop this launch.
[SPEAKING IN JAPANESE]
Well, then you better hurry up.
Roark is about to take the stage.
COMPUTER:
Access denied. Have an amazing day.
Damn it. I'm gonna need to do a patch.
Dad, you're really not gonna watch that,
are you?
I have to watch Chuck's first day.
Even if he is working for Roark.
[CHEERING]
MAN:
Ladies and gentlemen...
...please welcome
the architect of the digital age...
...and TIME magazine's man of the year,
Ted Roark.
Thank you. Welcome to NextExpo 2009.
Or as I like to call it:
Ted greets the little people.
I'm just kidding, just kidding.
You believe this guy?
TED: We've done some amazing things
this year.
At least I have. I mean, I...
...traveled around the world
in a hot air balloon...
...and bought another island.
It's private. Don't visit.
What else? Let's see.
And we invented
a new operating system...
...that's going to change the world.
Let's not waste time.
You have any idea how much money
I'm losing just standing here?
With a press of this button,
RIOS will be released.
The whole world will have access.
-Free access to our latest software.
-What's happening?
We're encountering security
we've never seen before.
COMPUTER:
Access denied again. That's twice.
Maybe I should call security.
[ALARM WAILING]
-Uh-oh.
-Tell me that was a good "uh-oh."
TED:
You know I love a countdown.
I'd like you to join me. Ready?
-Ten.
-There's a countdown happening.
Okay, listen.
We cannot access the source code.
-You have to stop the release.
-I could get fired.
This is not your real job. Hurry.
ALL:
Six. Five.
Four. Three.
-Two.
-No, wait.
What the hell are you doing?
STEVE: Is that Chuck?
-Wow, he's on stage.
He must have gotten promoted.
No autographs right now, okay?
[WHISPERS]
Get off the stage.
I can't. I can't.
-I'm so sorry.
MAN 1: Get off the stage!
MAN 2: Come on.
MAN 3: Don't deny us our new software, jerk.
[WHISPERS]
You can't press that button.
The CIA believes that your software
has been infected with a virus...
...that when released
will cause worldwide computer damage.
[IN NORMAL VOICE] Do you have any idea
how crazy you sound?
Yeah, I do. I do.
But please, you have to believe me.
No, I really don't.
I'm sorry for the little technical delay.
Must be my rock-star magnetism.
Drives some people batty.
Hey.
Go, Charles.
-Go, Charles.
-No, Chuck, stop.
That's right.
That's my boy.
[GRUNTS]
Oh, no.
[COUGHS]
You call yourself a Stanford man.
[AUDIENCE CHEERS AND APPLAUSES]
TED:
Let's get back to it.
Three, two, one.
-Have you heard from my brother?
-Was I supposed to?
Not picking up. Think he's in jail?
Do you get a phone call?
In the movies, you get a phone call.
I gotta call 411.
Who do I ask for? County jail?
Ellie, I just worked an 18-hour shift.
Slow down, honey.
Tell me what happened.
Chuck freaked out.
He hopped on-stage
at some computer convention...
...and tried to attack his new boss.
-What? Why would he do that?
-I have no idea.
Although we should probably ask my dad,
since obviously he put him up to it.
What? I didn't tell him to do anything.
Why else would he throw away
a job of a lifetime?
Ted Roark isn't worthy
of your brother or his talents.
It was a lousy job.
And what do you call
working at the Buy More, Dad?
Don't you get it?
Chuck has been waiting for 10 years
to impress you.
Now this opportunity comes along...
...where he can follow through
on some crazy made-up vendetta of yours.
Trust me, sweetie.
Your brother knows what he's doing.
You want me to trust you?
Maybe your dad's right.
Maybe Chuck
has got a good explanation.
Sure. I'm sure he does.
He probably forgot
the whole thing happened.
Just like at your bachelor party.
I'm sorry.
I don't wanna drag us into this.
I'm just really worked up right now,
so I'm gonna take a walk.
-Ellie.
-Let her walk, Devon.
Drink?
No. No way. That's what got me
in trouble in the first place.
-What do I do?
-You're asking the wrong guy.
-But she's your daughter.
-Well, I can't take credit for her.
The only thing Ellie owes me
is a few well-deserved trust issues.
You really want my advice?
Don't walk out on your kids when you
promised them pancakes for dinner.
They tend to take it badly.
You're a real straight arrow, aren't you?
I used to be,
before this damn bachelor party.
God, I'm such a jackass.
Maybe.
But that's not why Ellie's mad.
She just doesn't want you
to turn into me, which...
...take this as a compliment,
seems pretty damn unlikely.
So come on.
Have a drink.
To straight arrows.
Okay, Orion.
Show me what you want me to do.
CHUCK:
Why did you send me these cards, Orion?
Do you want me to build an Intersect
or find an Intersect?
How can I use these cards
to find an Intersect?
[DOOR KNOCKS]
Hey, I'm a little busy right now.
Just give me one minute...
...and then you can get back
to whatever you were doing.
Ellie thinks you did
what you did at Roark for me.
And if that's true,
I'll never forgive myself.
-Dad.
-Still my minute.
I ruined every good thing
that ever happened to me.
My family, my job, my entire life,
thrown away.
I won't stand by
and let the same thing happen to you.
That's one torch...
...I'd rather not pass.
If working for Roark...
...is that important to you,
then I think you should fight for it.
And don't let my past
destroy your future.
I miss getting advice from you.
Well, my minute's up.
You were in the middle of something.
Oh, my God.
Roark has an Intersect.
-What?
-An Intersect. Roark has one.
Roark is hiding a supercomputer
the size of a football field inside his office?
Yes.
-Well, maybe.
-What exactly did you flash on?
I--
I didn't flash on anything, technically.
I was just thinking, but it makes sense.
We know that Fulcrum is working
on trying to implant intel into their agents.
But they need a supercomputer,
an Intersect, to crunch all that data.
-Only someone like Roark could do that.
-Ted Roark is working for Fulcrum?
I know it sounds crazy,
but what if RIOS is a Trojan horse...
...like a virus designed to steal intel
from the government...
...corporations, anybody, everybody?
And you just thought this up
out of the blue?
No flash, no proof?
Beckman will laugh in our faces.
The apple doesn't fall too far
from the crazy tree, does it?
SARAH:
I'm sorry, Chuck.
Sarah. Sarah.
Think about what it could mean
if Roark has an Intersect.
I could get this out of my head.
I need your help
to break into Roark's office.
Beckman's orders are clear.
So are the consequences
of not following them.
I'm sorry.
Cute outfit, Bartowski.
-Give me that back.
-First you tell me what it is.
Interesting question.
Those are designs for the Intersect.
You stole Roark's designs?
Orion's.
He sent them to me before he died.
There's a map in the plans
that matches Roark Instruments.
-Orion contacted you and you didn't tell us?
-I think he wanted me to break in.
Yeah, and I want you to take off my gear
before I break your geek neck.
I know what I'm doing.
You have no idea.
You're entering a world of pain.
I want this Intersect out of my head.
You gonna help me?
You gotta be--
Is that a tranq gun?
You don't have the courtesy
to threaten me with a firearm.
-What's your answer, Casey?
-Put the toy down and get your ass--
[FIRES]
[GRUNTING]
I'm gonna kill you when I wake up.
Sorry. I'm sorry.
Ooh.
[DOOR OPENS]
STEVE:
Are you kidding me?
Oh, come on.
That's the oldest excuse in the book.
Yes, he knows.
-I wanna see Ted Roark.
GUARD: Sir, just calm down.
He screwed me, but I'm not gonna let
that son of a bitch screw my son.
Get your hands off of me.
Listen, you tell your boss
I'm not leaving this building...
...until my boy gets his job back.
[WHISPERS]
What are you doing, Dad?
What do you want me to do with him?
MAN:
Bring him in. We'll deal with it in private.
Excuse me.
Are you in charge of these meatheads?
[GRUNTS]
[YELLING]
Dad. Dad. Dad, we have to go.
We have to go right now.
I can explain all of this to you later.
For now, all I can tell you is,
I'm not who you think I am.
It's good to see you again.
Good to see both of you.
Don't worry, Charles.
-I'm not who you think I am either.
-Hands up.
[ALARM WAILING]
[ALARM STOPS]
Are you coming?
We should go, Charles.
Oh, my God.
You're Orion.
We should hurry.
[GROANS]
Casey, where's Chuck?
In a world of pain.
I can't believe this.
My father invented the Intersect.
That's not true. I didn't invent all of it.
Just the really cool stuff.
Come on.
Granted, I can understand
how this might complicate a few things.
Complicate a few things? I saw you die.
I saw you explode in a helicopter.
I see how I could have
given you that impression.
I've had to die quite a few times.
One of the perils of being Orion.
This isn't what I wanted, Chuck.
When I realized what the government was
gonna do with the Intersect, I had to run.
I knew our guys wouldn't be the only
ones looking for me. More importantly...
...I knew I had to stay away
from you and your sister.
Wait, Dad.
You were protecting us?
I knew I'd have to spend
the rest of my life hiding from the Intersect.
But I never imagined
that it would find you.
It must be such a curse to have
all those secrets trapped in your head.
That's why I came back.
That's why I let your handlers find me.
It's my fault
that Fulcrum's after both of us now.
You wanted me to flash
on your crazy schematics.
To break in here.
Why didn't you say who you were?
Would you have trusted me?
After not seeing me for 10 years,
I just appear and bring you to RI...
...tell you I can get the Intersect,
which I built, out of your head.
What would you have said to that?
-That you were a little bit crazy.
-Exactly.
Now punch in the code
or we'll be a little bit dead.
No, Dad, it doesn't work like that.
-Unless it's in here, I can't do it.
-Yes, you can.
I designed that computer
in your head, son.
Flash, and it will be the last thing
you ever have to flash on.
Aces, Charles.
-That's the Intersect?
-Two point zero.
My baby. My greatest creation.
After you and your sister, of course.
Let's make that the hot seat.
We need to make some minor
modifications to Roark's software.
So, what exactly
does your new program do?
Usually the Intersect
works in the other way around...
...but I don't see any reason why
it shouldn't be able to take out information.
In theory, at least.
What you're gonna see
are encoded images...
...that will cancel out
the ones that you originally uploaded.
Wait.
Are you saying
you're gonna overwrite my brain?
That's a good way of putting it. Yes.
-Ready?
-No.
-Your glasses.
-Oh. Yeah, right.
Good luck, Charles.
Something's wrong.
No, no, no.
It's not working.
No, it doesn't work.
But I'm sure you'll have it
up and running in no time.
You always did have
a way with machines, Orion.
And remember, I always had--
Well, I always had a way with the girls.
Remember?
Hey, come on, man. What's the matter?
No hug for your old partner?
No?
I've been looking for you for a long time.
The years have been unkind.
I could offer you a good moisturizer. Huh?
No? Okay.
Put him on the helicopter.
Kill the CIA agent.
He's my son.
He's your son?
Congratulations, that's great.
I had no idea. Kill his son.
Wait, I'll-- I'll build anything you want.
Give Fulcrum their Intersect.
But my son walks away from here.
-You'll build it either way.
-You're gonna torture me?
After 10 years away from my family?
My son walks away.
All right, all right.
I'm not a monster.
Maybe I'm a little bit of a monster.
Today is his lucky day.
Shotgun on the chopper. Let's go.
Charles.
-Take care of your sister.
-No.
-And take care of yourself.
-Dad.
-You can do this without me.
-I'm not gonna leave you.
Remember when I told you
not to trust your handlers?
Maybe I was wrong.
If his son's gonna walk,
he should do it now.
Goodbye, Chuck.
CHUCK:
No!
In our raid of Roark Instruments...
...we failed to retrieve
either the Intersect or Stephen Bartowski.
Clearly, we recognize
that Fulcrum's possession of Orion...
...poses an unparalleled security threat.
You mean,
Fulcrum's possession of my father.
I promise you, no one at the CIA...
...knew your father's secret identity.
I also promise to entrust
his recovery to our best team.
General, we are your best team.
I can't believe I'm gonna say this.
Chuck's right.
You cannot put Chuck in the field.
It is too dangerous.
Fulcrum knows that he is Orion's son.
Look, as soon as my dad
finishes the new Intersect for Roark...
...I'm worthless to you, obsolete,
and Fulcrum wins.
The only thing that matters now
is getting my father back...
...and you need me to do that.
Very well, Mr. Bartowski.
The assignment is yours,
provided your personal entanglements...
...do not interfere with the mission.
Dad?
Ellie, I don't know how to tell you this,
but I think your dad may have split.
His stuff's all gone.
Hey. Hey, I'm sure he's planning
on coming back for the wedding.
No. No, he's not.
Well, if it's any consolation...
...I'm not going anywhere, ever.
I mean, no matter how hard
things get between us.
Because that's what
married people do, right?
Just think, in 50 years...
...we'll look back at my bachelor party
and laugh about it.
No. No, we won't.
Probably not.
ELLIE:
Chuck. Are you okay?
Yeah. Yeah, I'm fine.
Only my career was injured.
Chuck, Dad's gone.
I yelled at him
about what happened at your work today.
-I said some things that--
-It's not your fault.
Well, no, it's my fault
that I asked you to find him.
I needed him
to walk me down the aisle.
I thought that he would be different
from that guy that walked out on us.
I guess I just expected too much
from him.
Don't count him out yet.
[ENGLISH SDH]