CHUCK: I'm Chuck.
A few things you need to know:
I'm not a Fulcrum agent.
I'm Ml6 working undercover.
BECKMAN: I want to apologize
to you directly, Agent Barker.
We had no record you were Ml6.
Locked in this dungeon?
It's like keeping a Botticelli in the basement.
No one can appreciate the beauty.
-I'm moving out.
-Yes!
-Moving in with Morgan.
-No!
-I'm the Intersect.
-No, he's not. It's me.
If you know who Chuck really is,
then you pose a security threat.
If I've proved anything to you by now,
it's that I can keep my word.
Cole's been captured.
We have to go into protective detail.
-What's that mean?
-We move in together.
-He's a tough guy. Maybe he won't talk.
-Chuck, everyone talks.
[SHOUTING]
What's your real name?
Bond. James Bond.
So how much does the CIA know
about Perseus?
Oh, come on, not the face.
DUNCAN: I'm only gonna ask you one more
question. You answer it and we're done.
Who is the Intersect?
[ALARM CLOCK BUZZING]
Morning, Chuck.
How'd you sleep?
Fine, thank you.
Well, busy day.
Lots to do.
-So shower. Do you wanna go first or...?
-I'm good.
You know, I know this whole 24-hour
supervision thing isn't exactly great...
...but when the CIA
finds us a new apartment...
...at least we'll have separate rooms.
-Sounds great.
-I mean, consider yourself lucky.
At least you didn't have to move in
with Casey.
[LAUGHING]
Yeah.
Lucky me.
-Mm, spearmint okay?
-Yeah, fine.
Traditionally, I'm a peppermint man,
but I'm living on the edge.
-Sarah, can I ask you a question?
-About the toothpaste?
Ha, uh, no.
Are you, uh, worried about Cole?
Uh, of course I'm concerned about Cole.
But Agent Barker
can certainly take care of himself.
I get that.
It's just, you know,
you guys had this connection.
He saved your life,
and you shared a bit of torture.
Uh, our connection was purely professional.
That's it.
Oh, okay.
DEVON: Thanks, honey.
ELLIE: Mm-hm.
[DOOR CLOSES]
Ah, hi. Good morning.
-Oh, oh!
CHUCK: Hey.
Sorry. Sorry, I'm just--
I'm very excited for Chuck, for the both
of you, to be moving in together.
That's still happening?
-Oh, yeah.
-Absolutely.
Great. Did you find a place yet?
Not that I'm, uh, trying to rush you
or anything, heh.
DEVON:
Take your time, bro. No pressure.
You two lovebirds need to find a nest
where you can let the worm wiggle free.
Thank you, Devon.
Do you need any help packing
or throwing things away?
Sarah, please tell Chuck that not everything
in that room has to survive the move.
-I'm making a list.
-Making a list, are you?
-And of what, may I ask?
-Oh, well, uh, where should we begin?
Maybe the Tron poster that you've had
since you were 12.
[CHUCKLES]
Dad gave me that poster.
I know. He loved that movie.
Have you had any luck finding his address
for the wedding?
No, not yet.
But, you know, I'm working on it still.
So, uh, how did Morgan take the news...
...that he wasn't gonna get you
as a new roommate?
I didn't tell him yet.
I don't have the heart.
Morgan Grimes is so tired of listening
to Big Mike punch his mama's time clock...
...that he actually showed up for work
on time today.
[ALL CHEER]
Okay, okay, well,
Morgan Grimes is so disturbed...
...by what Big Mike is doing
to his mama...
...the thought of Jeff doing the same thing
to Anna is actually sweet, sweet relief.
[ALL LAUGH AND CHEER]
JEFF:
Oh, snap.
That's good. Laugh it up, fuzzballs.
That's right, sure.
But guess what. I just landed the whale.
Me and Chuck, we're gonna be roommates.
So yeah, have your fun. Have at it.
But don't expect
any housewarming invitations from me.
[ALL GROAN]
-Don't give me that face.
-Morgan, buddy. Hey, we gotta talk.
You're just the man I wanted to see.
Listen, I found a place, dude.
Two bedroom,
one and a quarter bath, half a fireplace.
-About the apartment--
-I know, you and I, roommates.
We're living the dream.
It's what we always talked about.
-The thing is that there's one--
-Bartowski, my office, now.
When did you get an office, John?
CHUCK: What's going on? Are we moving?
-It's no-tell motel time for Chuck.
-Secure bunker at an undisclosed location.
-Seriously, what's with the boxes?
Cole Barker was picked up by Fulcrum.
We spent the entire night looking for him
and failed.
Langley thinks when he talks,
they're gonna come here for you.
We're taking you off the grid.
-What about my sister? Awesome? Morgan?
-First priority is to get you safe.
Then we're gonna come back
and make sure everybody else is okay.
[ALARM BLARING]
If we get that far.
It says 240-27.
We have a perimeter breach.
CHUCK: This is it.
I'm gonna die underneath a yogurt shop.
Back door, now. Move, move, move.
Sarah, we need to talk.
If I knew this was gonna happen--
Later, Chuck.
[CLATTERING FROM BEHIND DOOR]
CASEY:
Chuck, get back.
Cole?
Take this.
Did you miss me?
Don't worry.
I didn't say a word.
Look at that.
Maybe you're not going away after all.
Lucky you.
Yeah.
Lucky me.
[ON SPEAKER]
After that, it was eight...
...maybe nine guys until the door.
CHUCK:
Oh, come on.
We're supposed to believe
that he took out nine guys...
...and escaped a Fulcrum holding facility
all by himself?
-I don't think we can trust this guy.
-I've done nine before.
-You've taken out nine guys?
-I'm just saying it's doable.
So when they questioned you
about the Intersect--?
I didn't tell them anything.
It's not my first dance, Walker.
If I talk, then Chuck, Casey, you...
...all in the crosshairs.
Not an option.
Why come back here after you escaped?
I wanted to make sure you were safe.
ANNA:
You are the sexiest man in the world.
For you. It's our 16-month anniversary.
Wait a minute. We had a no-gift policy.
I didn't get you anything.
Morgan, you're the worst person
at keeping secrets.
I already know what you got me.
You left the lease for our new apartment
in the fax machine.
A life together is the best present ever.
And when we move in,
I'm gonna show you...
...your mother isn't the only one
who can be noisy in the bedroom.
I gotta go call my parents.
-I thought you were moving in with Chuck.
-I am. We are. Anna misunderstood.
She found the lease, and now she thinks--
Oh, my God.
Oh, buddy, you are screwed.
I think if I tell her the truth, it'll end
the sexual component of our relationship.
-And I'll be there to pick up the pieces.
-What?
Shh, shh. Relax, Morgan.
All you have to do is convince Anna
that moving in with you is a bad idea.
-Okay, but how am I gonna--?
-Shh, shh, Bubele...
...you've come to the right place.
Repulsion is our business.
And business is good.
Thanks to information
provided by Mr. Barker...
...we now know that Fulcrum is protecting
a man that goes by the code name Perseus.
Perseus is the head scientist behind
Fulcrum's effort to build their own Intersect.
Anything, Chuck?
I spent the year
trying to get close to him...
...but only the inner circle
is ever allowed contact.
Intel tells us Perseus
is attending a formal event tonight...
...at the Swiss Consuls office.
The State Department
has arranged invitations for the two of you.
-Um, the two of who?
-Agent Walker and Agent Casey.
[CASEY HUMS MOCKINGLY]
COLE:
Are you sure, general?
-I'd be happy to accompany Agent Walker.
-I bet you would.
-Uh, I'd be happy to go too.
-Well, aren't you popular?
I mean, you know, I am the Intersect.
Neither Agent Barker nor Bartowski
will be going.
Fulcrum is still actively searching
for the two of you.
Both of you will stay in Castle
and monitor by remote feed.
If you recognize anyone,
you'll have radio.
Well, at least no one's telling us to--
-You heard the general. Stay in the bunker.
-And there it is.
MORGAN: Phase 1 of Operation Repulsion:
the obscure and disturbing hobby.
[GRUNTING]
JEFF:
Take that, you chauvinist pig.
-Told you not to mess with Billie Jean.
-Bitch.
Hey, Morgan, I'm done for the day.
You wanna take me over,
show me the new apartment?
Uh, you know what? I'd love to, hon...
...but we're re-creating the best tennis
matches ever played, and I'm up next.
-McEnroe, Stockholm, '84.
-You can't be serious.
JEFF: Yes!
-Look on the bright side.
When we move in together,
you can play too.
It'll be like a nonstop Wimbledon final
in our living room.
[MEN CHUCKLE]
-Seriously.
-Doubles, anyone?
[GAGS]
[MOUTHS]
Thank you.
LESTER [WHISPERING]: One down.
-Cool.
-No, man.
-That's 95 percent alcohol.
Don't touch me with that.
-Radio check. Do we have a signal?
-Yup, we got you, and you look fantastic.
[OVER RADIO]
Is that dress CIA-issue...
...or do you just make everything
look that good?
Ahem, let's stay focused here, people, huh?
We are on a mission.
You do look gorgeous, Sarah.
This is Chuck speaking, by the way.
Okay, too many cooks in the kitchen.
You get in Casey's ear. I'll get in Sarah's.
Okay, you two, split up.
Sarah, you've got an unsecured exit
at 2 o'clock.
And the guy in the bad suit standing
in front of the Swiss flag is packing.
Casey, you got a bogey.
Tray of crab cakes coming in on your 10.
I'm just trying to be helpful, okay?
He works up an appetite on missions.
Grab that little one. That looks very tasty.
-There's-- Or the-- Yeah.
-Thanks.
The Italian minister for trade
is headed your way.
[OVER RADIO]
He can get a little handsy.
Hello. I am Paolo Giordano.
I saw you
and couldn't help but admire your beauty.
His wife's name's Isabella,
and he has three little bambinos.
Thank you.
How are Isabella and the children?
[SPEAKING IN SPANISH]
COLE: Nicely done.
-Not so bad yourself.
Thanks. Thank you. Just doing our job.
Me and Cole, Cole and me.
Take your victory lap later, Bartowski.
Who else haven't we seen?
I don't know.
Look at the people by that ice-goose thing.
Ahem, okay, I just flashed.
The shorter, balding gentleman
wearing the glasses.
-That has gotta be Perseus.
-I have a visual. Moving in.
His name is Howard Busgang.
He's a research scientist
with the Department of Defense.
Good job, Chuck.
Yeah, got a few skills of my own, now,
don't I? Heh.
So nine guys, huh? Really?
You're not fudging that number?
It sounds harder than it is.
Always go for the knee.
You mean like sweep the leg?
I'm sorry. Excuse me.
-That's him.
-You're a little late to the party.
-I just flashed.
-No, not Busgang, him.
-Oh, no--
-The guy was torturing me. He's Fulcrum.
You two have a nice evening.
Where'd they go?
-Where'd they go?
-Where?
My guess is, if Fulcrum made them,
then they just jammed the signal.
Oh, uh, Dr. Busgang,
I don't believe we've met before.
How do you do?
-Your friends are in trouble.
-I gathered.
-We have to call General Beckman.
-For what?
-So she can tell us what to do.
-I'll tell you.
We go to the consulate
and we save them.
No, no, no. Sarah and Casey
specifically said for us to stay here.
Sometimes things don't go
according to plan. You have to improvise.
You can't just go run off
and be the hero all the time.
It's not about wanting to be a hero, Chuck.
It's about needing to be.
Two guns, huh?
Wow, you really are a badass.
No, Chuck, one gun.
The other one is for you.
Let's go.
So we're gonna need a cover.
Normally we stay in the service arena.
Waiter, busboy, maybe valet.
How about we mix it up this time?
What about dentists?
Dentists? At a consulate party?
-Oh, you got a better idea?
-I say we go as spies.
A little obvious,
but I guess we can do it your way.
But the data acquisition problem
in Minsky's Society of Mind theory...
...was addressed in large measure
by Singh's EM-ONE paper back in 2005.
-Sounds fascinating.
-Mm, yes.
-More champagne?
-Please.
-Radio's still out. Let's grab this guy.
-Now where was I?
Telling me about the work you do
for the government.
-Yes.
-That sounds fascinating.
I'd like to hear about that too.
You gonna knock him out too?
There are civilians everywhere.
We have to find another way in.
Oh, we should've called Beckman,
had her send a team.
And miss out on all this fun?
Come on, get in the game, Chuck,
before Fulcrum takes out your team.
I think they already have.
No, no, no.
There's gotta be a ground-floor option.
No, this is good. We're going up here.
-Damn it.
-Cole, you're bleeding.
-No, I'm fine.
-You're not. Get down.
-What are you doing, Chuck?
-What do you mean? I'm doing this.
BUSGANG: Duncan, what's with the guns?
Who are these people?
Not your concern, Howard.
-We work for the government, Dr. Busgang.
-So do I.
-Tell them, Duncan. We work for the CIA.
-The men you work for are terrorists.
Terrorists. We're patriots, Howard.
You're a patriot.
You're spies that turned your back
on the country.
You couldn't have it more wrong.
Who do you think we are?
We do what needs to be done to preserve
this nation's rightful place in the world.
Someday you'll thank us.
Well, not you. You'll be dead.
I swear, I'm just a scientist.
They said I was helping the country.
Unfortunately, Howard,
that was the wrong thing to say.
BUSGANG:
Wait. Duncan, please, I don't understand.
What's going on?
Hey, Cole. Cole. Hey.
I found them, I found them.
The guy who tortured you is inside
with other big goons with guns.
Okay. Give me 20 seconds.
Then you go in there,
start taking guys out, okay?
No, no, wait, wait, wait. Listen.
About the whole gun thing...
...Casey and Sarah,
they've never really let me--
I don't-- How do I say this?
-I've never fired one.
-It's point and click.
-Point at the bad guys, pull the trigger.
-Yes, I get the concept. Still--
-Twenty seconds.
-Wait.
[WHISPERING]
We're dead. Bartowski's got a gun.
DUNCAN: It's a shame, Howard.
-Five, six....
You really do have an incredible mind.
Uh, twenty. Freeze. Federal agent.
[CHUCK SHOUTS]
[BUSGANG SHOUTS]
-I'm hit. I'm hit.
-Man down. Man down.
[GRUNTING AND SHOUTING]
I'll take care of Chuck. Get the doctor.
COLE:
Sarah.
[COLE GRUNTS]
Sorry about that.
I'm really not normally this aggressive
with women.
Oh, my God. You've been shot.
COLE:
I'm fine.
Hey, hey, hey.
Hey, guys,
I think I might need medical attention.
My ankle is seriously....
Cole took a bullet to save Sarah.
Wow, uh....
-Are you okay, buddy? What happened?
-Nothing. Nothing. I'm-- I'm fine.
Really, never mind, I'm....
What is that, mahogany?
SARAH: You don't look so good.
-I can't say the same for you.
Be gentle, now. I bruise easy.
Well, then maybe you should consider
taking better care of yourself.
This might hurt a bit.
[COLE GRUNTING]
You know, I've been poked at by more
spook doctors than I care to remember.
Nice to be looked after
by someone who treats you...
...as more than just a name,
rank and serial number.
I know what you mean.
Okay, now just relax.
[COLE SHOUTS]
Hold that.
Thanks, doc.
Well, thank you for saving my life.
What was I gonna do, not see you again?
[CHUCK CLEARS THROAT]
Hey. Howdy. How you doing in here?
Right, absolutely. Sorry about that.
I was just coming by
to see if you guys need anything.
Cole, soup? A bisque of some kind?
Or an Us Weekly?
-I don't read it, but when you're sick--
CASEY: Walker. Barker.
Bartowski.
Briefing in five.
Also that, briefing in five.
That was kind of a business today.
I'll see you in five.
It's like four and a half now.
MORGAN:
What are you reading?
Did you know IKEA sells 17 kinds
of home shelving?
I can only pronounce two of them,
though.
[MORGAN CHUCKLES]
Yeah, it's silly.
Listen, you know what?
I wanted to apologize about last night...
...and the whole Wimbledon thing.
I was trying to set boundaries
before we move in.
And I realize there is a more mature way
to handle this, you know.
So, well, here you go.
ANNA: A Morgannuptial?
-Right.
I had Lester's cousin draw it up for us.
A little something to ensure
there are no cohabitating conflicts.
"No pets"? What about Chico?
Oh, that's right, Chico. Guess you're gonna
have to put him down now, huh?
ANNA: The only cheese allowed
in the house is string?
-Or Gouda. On weekends.
-Are you insane?
Just a teensy-weensy bit particular.
And listen to me.
I would totally understand
if you're having second thoughts.
Are you kidding me?
Morgan, you're hilarious.
I'll sign whatever you want.
Maybe it makes me nuts too,
but I love you, ridiculous quirks and all.
-I should have that framed.
-Totally.
Damn it.
I should've went with provolone.
Mr. Barker, I understand you were hurt
protecting Agent Walker.
-I'm told you showed great courage.
-Just doing my job, general.
Actually, it was Chuck
who showed great courage on this mission.
He was also injured in the line of duty.
He got clipped by a windowsill.
It's as pathetic as it sounds.
Is there any new intel on Busgang
or his Fulcrum handler?
We now know that the man Chuck
identified last night, Dr. Howard Busgang...
...is in fact code-named Perseus.
He's a former DARPA scientist
who worked on the original Intersect.
Uh, why was that information
not in my flash?
As a precaution...
...anything about the creators
of the Intersect was redacted from our files.
Did you say
this guy created the Intersect?
BECKMAN: He was part of the team
that developed its underlying architecture.
He knows as much about how it works
as anyone.
That means he might know
how to get it out of my head.
BECKMAN:
We don't know, Chuck.
But it's possible.
Perhaps.
We gotta find him.
We gotta find this guy before Fulcrum.
We are putting
every available resource on it.
Walker and Casey,
prepare for a video link.
Brief our field agents.
Bring them up to speed.
-Good luck.
CASEY: Roger that.
SARAH:
Oh, let me fix that for you.
Hey, what are you looking at there?
CHUCK: Oh, just, you know,
footage from the consulate.
Maybe there's something I missed.
I don't know.
You did great tonight, Chuck.
Thanks.
You were your usual superhuman self.
-You saved Sarah's life.
-No.
-It was a team effort.
-I get what she sees in you, you know.
The fearlessness in the face of danger,
the imperviousness to pain...
...the super-cool tank tops.
-Stop me whenever this is uncomfortable.
-No.
SARAH:
Hey.
-The briefing is about to start.
-Great. I'll be right there.
On my way.
Oh, you meant him.
Of course you meant him. Why...? Heh, heh.
Right.
LESTER:
My God, could she really be...
...unrepulsable?
-I'm beginning to think so.
-No, sir. Not on my watch.
-What are you suggesting?
LESTER: Mm-mm.
You're going to need a quart of peanut oil,
some bubblewrap...
...and as much yarn as you can find.
CHUCK:
Hey, guys.
-Hey, Morgan, we need to talk.
-Yeah. What's going on, man?
-What's with the limp?
-Nothing.
No, I twisted my ankle. Yeah, jogging.
Which I do occasionally. I'm fine.
Uh, we need to talk about--
The Anna situation?
Not a problem, Charles. We are on it.
You're looking at three individuals
gifted in the art of repulsion.
Anna doesn't stand a chance.
-Why are you trying to repulse Anna?
-No, no, no. Lester, that's ridiculous.
What I was trying to do
was simply test her, that's all.
Testing her why?
Because, Chuck, because she's trying
to get all serious with me...
...and I wanna make sure
that she loves me for me...
...and not other things.
Excuse us.
Are you crazy?
What other things
could she possibly be loving you for?
I mean, honestly,
you know that I love you...
...but you're lucky to have a girl in your life
who loves you for you...
...even though you are, in fact, you.
-Fair.
-If you don't stop testing her...
...she's gonna choose
to be with someone else.
And then you will have realized,
unfortunately too late...
...that you lost the catch of a lifetime.
Counterpoint:
She's not the catch of a lifetime.
She's a scheming tart who will harvest your
organs and sell them to the highest bidder.
Chuck's right.
Lester, wrong.
Chuck, what happened?
Nothing. It's a flesh wound.
It's nothing, I'm fine.
Well, let's see. Sit down.
-Up, up.
-Aah! Aah!
-Sorry, sorry. Devon, can you help?
-Promise not to go all crazy doctor-sister.
DEVON: What's up, babe?
-Oh, we need to get Chuck to the hospital.
-We gotta x-ray this leg.
-No, we don't, I'm fine. Aah!
-Pretty swollen there.
-I'm tougher than people think.
I know you are, buddy.
But it takes a real man to admit you're hurt.
-Ouch. That actually hurt.
-I didn't think anything hurt you.
Oh, no, there are some things.
The clinical disinterest
of a beautiful woman, for instance.
-Any word on Busgang?
-Not yet.
Casey and I are headed to the airport.
They think Busgang
might try to leave the country.
All right, then.
Rest up.
Wait. Listen.
You know, I meant what I said earlier...
...about being around people
who really care about you...
...and who you really care about.
-Doesn't happen often for people like us.
-No, it doesn't.
And if we're lucky enough
to find that person...
...we're supposed to just walk away?
Doesn't seem fair, does it?
No.
Because it isn't.
Is the cast absolutely necessary?
Yes. It could be a hairline fracture.
Better safe than sorry.
I'm gonna go find you some crutches.
BUSGANG: No, absolutely not.
I wanna be released immediately.
DOCTOR: I'm sorry, sir, this is a
gunshot wound. We have to report this.
BUSGANG: This is outrageous.
I don't care about your rules.
I don't care about what you have to do.
I am leaving.
DOCTOR: I suggest you stay overnight
in case your leg gets infected.
I can't do that. I have to go.
[CELL PHONE RINGS]
-Yeah?
CHUCK: It's Chuck. Look, I found Busgang.
He's here at the hospital.
Westside Medical.
You found him? Great work.
All right, we'll have a strike team there.
-No, no, he's leaving.
-Don't follow him. It's too dangerous.
He might know how
to get the Intersect out of my head.
Listen, do not go after him on your own.
Do not be a hero here, Chuck.
Look, I don't wanna be a hero,
but sometimes you need to be.
Besides, this is doable.
[GROANING]
I've got them both.
Hi. Hi. I'm looking for a Mr. Busgang.
-Do you have an appointment?
-No.
Yeah, well, uh, the thing is,
see, I'm a computer tech.
Um, Nerd Herd? That's me.
And apparently, Mr. Busgang
has some major hardware problems.
-Constellation Science, second floor.
-Thank you.
RECEPTIONIST:
Can I help you, gentlemen?
[GROANS]
[GUN CLICKS]
BUSGANG:
Turn around.
Slowly.
-You're the guy who shot me.
-It was an accident.
The first time I had handled a gun,
and first time I had shot someone.
Clearly, those two things
must be connected.
Hi, I'm Chuck.
Sit down. And don't move.
-I'd hate to accidentally shoot you.
-I didn't come to hurt you or take you in.
I just want some answers
about the Intersect.
What do you know about the Intersect?
A lot, actually.
Who are you?
Orion.
Did you just flash?
Hey, cover the stairs.
You're the one they've been talking about,
aren't you?
I didn't believe it could be true.
A human Intersect.
[SIGHS]
-Extraordinary.
-Maybe for you.
But you have to understand, for me....
For me, it's a nightmare.
Living with this thing in my head
is ruining my life.
Is there any way that Intersect images
can be taken out, you know?
-Can a person be de-Intersected?
-Can it be removed?
Possibly.
I don't know.
-Only Orion would know.
-Orion. Who is Orion?
It was his idea, his vision.
Everything is based on his work.
He put the team together,
he drove the research, until he realized--
DUNCAN: Put the gun down, Howard.
-Who's Orion? Where can I find him?
Please, I need to know.
CASEY:
Split up.
I haven't told him anything.
No! No, no.
[GRUNTING AND SHOUTING]
-That's the second time you've shot me.
-Let's hope third time's the charm.
Sweep the leg.
-Hey, are you okay?
-I'm fine. The gun.
-What?
-Chuck, the gun!
CHUCK:
Help.
[GUNSHOT]
-Are you okay?
-Yeah, I think so. I think so.
Oh, you were talking to him.
You weren't-- You were talking to him
because he's been shot again. Right.
-My bad.
-No, I was talking to both of you.
-We're okay, right? We're okay.
-Yeah. Right.
Absolutely. We're okay.
Excellent work, team.
While we would've preferred
to take Busgang alive...
...by capturing his work,
we've set back...
...Fulcrum's ability
to build their own Intersect.
Uh, what about that name, Orion?
Busgang said that Orion
could get the Intersect out of my head.
As of now, we have no leads,
but our best people are on it.
Agent Barker, medical transport for you
back to the UK has been arranged.
Thank you, general.
So it seems my work here is done. Again.
Agent Casey,
it's been a real pleasure working with you.
Yeah, likewise.
Let me ask you something.
When you escaped from Fulcrum,
did you really take out nine guys?
-The truth?
-Professional courtesy.
It was more like 12.
I just don't like to boast.
[CASEY CHUCKLES]
Eh, so, what's next?
Wing back to London
and jam with the Stones?
I have to say, Chuck,
you are truly the most...
...special agent I've ever worked with.
Heh, heh. "Special."
Good luck with getting that thing
out of your head.
Thanks, but, uh, I'm beginning to think
that's never gonna happen.
You know what?
I got a not-so-secret secret for you.
You want something bad enough,
don't ever take no for an answer.
And for God's sakes, man, carry a gun.
Maybe two.
Wow, nice cast.
-Ellie go to work on you?
-Yeah, yeah.
I'm just happy it's not full-body.
-We gotta talk about the moving-in thing.
-I know we do, Chuck.
I just don't know how to say this. I....
-You should have a seat.
-Okay.
Sometimes things happen
between, uh, two people...
...who care about each other very much.
Um, and it doesn't mean
that they don't belong together.
Belong together?
What are you talking about?
Oh, uh, no, no, no.
I can't move in with you, Chuck,
because I'm moving in with Anna.
She loves me...
...and she wants to move in with me,
and I wanna make her happy.
-But I want you to understand, you know?
-I do, buddy.
Seriously, I totally understand.
And furthermore, I think that you
are absolutely making the right decision.
That's awesome. Thank you.
Is she gonna be okay
with your string-cheese habit?
I know she will be, bro. Heh.
Hey, and, uh, you and I, you know,
we'll still be friends.
-As opposed to what?
-That's an excellent point.
[MORGAN CHUCKLES]
Okay.
COLE:
Dr. Walker.
Uh, my superiors agree that I need 24-hour,
round-the-clock medical assistance.
Our jet awaits.
I'm sorry, I have yogurt to serve.
You'll have to find somebody else.
Oh, no, you see, that's not gonna work...
...because no one else
is gonna make me feel like you do.
Believe me, I've looked.
I'm serious.
Don't pack your bags, don't say goodbyes.
Just close your eyes and say yes.
Come with me, Sarah.
I'm sorry.
What's the matter?
I thought you were a girl
who liked adventure.
I guess I'm not the type of girl
who cheats on her cover boyfriend.
-Is that all he is? A cover?
-What do you mean?
I saw the way you looked at him
when his life was in danger.
Been doing this a long time,
Agent Walker.
Well, who'd have thought it?
Cole Barker loses the girl
to Chuck Bartowski.
When you meet somebody you care about,
it's just hard to walk away.
I couldn't have said it better myself.
How's your foot?
Uh, throbbing, thanks.
Did Cole leave?
Uh, mm-hm.
He's quite a guy.
Uh, yeah, that he is.
You know, I understand
what you see in him. He's a great spy.
Tough. He's one of the good guys.
Truth is, you two would make a great team.
-Chuck--
-Please, let me just finish.
[CHUCK CLEARS THROAT]
Sarah, I'm not gonna move in with you.
Because I can't.
And you know why I can't.
I'm crazy about you,
heh, and I've always been.
But having a fake relationship,
that's one thing.
But living together is....
I mean, every day,
being around each other and....
And that's why I can't do it.
And I hope you understand.
I do.
Thank you.
Oh, and, uh, just so you know...
...I am gonna get this thing
out of my head one day.
I will.
And when I do, I'm gonna live the life
that I want with the girl that I love.
Because I'm not gonna let this thing
rob me of that. I won't.
Hey, how's the ankle?
I picked up some boxes
in case you wanted to start packing up.
Change of plans.
Not moving out. Talk later.
[ENGLISH SDH]