CHUCK: I'm Chuck. Here are a few things
you need to know.
-Don't hurt him.
-I won't.
The hotel's booked,
so we should probably go.
With this, it's a matter of time before
we learn the identities of Fulcrum's agents.
Oh, wow.
Chuck, look at this view. It's amazing.
[SIGHS]
Chuck, it's just a Ferris wheel. It's fine.
[LAUGHS NERVOUSLY]
Yeah, it's not the--
It's not the wheel so much as it is me.
What? What does that mean?
I kind of sort of bribed the carnie
to stop us at the top.
Well, for someone who's afraid of heights,
that was pretty moronic.
I was going for romantic, but....
Okay, here goes. Uh....
Jill, we've been friends
for like a semester now, right?
And it's been really fun. Ha.
And I was just thinking
that maybe, you know...
...uh, you and I, we could....
I don't know.
You know what? You're right.
What am I thinking? This is moronic.
You're happy being friends
and I'm happy being friends.
-And I just thought that--
-Chuck.
There is a problem.
You talk way, way too much.
BECKMAN:
Jill Roberts is Fulcrum?
And she has Chuck?
How is that possible?
Well, the LaFleur list contained
a code name our computer translated...
...to one Jill Roberts.
By the time we saw it, they were gone.
His cell is switched off
and his watch is still in the apartment.
Find him. I don't care how, just do it.
It doesn't matter.
Fulcrum's working him over now.
He's not gonna last an hour.
No, they don't know Chuck's the Intersect
and they don't know Jill has been burned.
Well, if it ain't torture...
...what are they doing to him?
We have ways to make you talk,
Mr. Bartowski.
Do your worst.
[CELL PHONE RINGING]
I....
There's gonna be yelling.
Was it worth it?
It was so worth it.
[BOTH CHUCKLE]
I'm gonna take a shower.
You deal with the yelling, okay?
Okay.
Have fun.
[SIGHS]
Oh, that's not good.
[JILL'S CELL PHONE BUZZING]
-Jill, your phone's buzzing.
-What?
No, no, not now.
This can't be happening.
-What was that, Chuck?
-Nothing.
Um, nothing at all, actually.
I was just saying I'm a little, uh, parched.
Because, well, last night was incredible,
you know?
Like, we had some fun, didn't we?
Hey, do you want some coffee?
-Oh, yeah, that'd be great.
-Okay, great, great.
Oh, God.
Oh, God. Oh, God.
[GRUNTS]
CASEY:
You idiot.
You sad sack, bleeding-heart idiot.
-She's-- She's--
-Chuck, never do that again.
It's Jill. I think--
BOTH: We know.
-Wait.
This has got to be a mistake, okay?
I've known Jill for eight years since college,
and we had this really amazing night--
Look, she's not a spy
and she has no Fulcrum code name.
-The code name is Sand Storm.
-Wait, don't say it.
Oh, my God.
Jill's a spy.
I'm sorry, Chuck.
-What do you mean I have to go back?
-Think, Bartowski.
We don't want Jill to know
that we know she's a spy, right?
Oh, okay, look, okay, Jill is Fulcrum.
Fulcrum is looking for the Intersect,
and the Intersect just happens to be me.
Chuck, they don't know that.
Trust me, we're right here.
-Everything will be fine, you will be safe.
-Buck up, soldier.
Fulcrum pulled one on us.
Let's return the favor.
[GLASSES CLINKING]
Settle.
JILL:
Aw.
Thank you, sweetie.
[CHUCKLES NERVOUSLY]
You're welcome, darling.
JILL:
Chuck, are you sure everything's okay?
Huh? Yeah, everything's fantastic. Great.
This is me
on the verge of total happiness.
Okay. You wanna do something tonight?
Um....
Yeah, I would love to.
But the problem is
the apartment is not safe.
My sister's back
and I can't blow my cover, so....
Well, we can go out.
Okay. All right.
-Okay. Bye.
-Bye.
Drive safe.
[CASEY TAPPING ON WINDOW]
Are you okay?
For a few days, I thought things
were gonna be different.
I could have a life,
I could have a girlfriend.
I could be a regular human being.
I thought Jill was....
-Different?
-No, normal.
-How could this happen?
-Jill must have been recruited at Stanford.
Fulcrum uses leadership seminars
to look for possible agents.
Excuse me. Uh, I'm sorry, general,
but who in my life isn't a spy?
My sister? My best friend?
Should I start asking people that
when I meet them?
"I'd like the value meal,
and while we're on the topic...
...do you covertly work
for a government espionage faction?"
Your flash in Jill's room
referenced an agent called Leader.
Use your relationship with Jill,
see if she makes contact with him.
General, Chuck is not ready for this.
He could barely handle a goodbye with Jill.
She's gonna see through him.
This is our best opportunity
to infiltrate Fulcrum.
-But if you don't think he's ready--
-I'll do it.
Jill betrayed me twice.
You bet I'll do it.
Whoa, whoa, whoa. Don't sit down.
Why? What? What is it?
Devon's parents are coming
for Thanksgiving.
And the couch is perfect. Okay.
The Awesomes?
The Awesomes are coming here?
Yes, the very Awesomes
are coming here.
They make their son
look mildly impressive.
Sis, you've got nothing to worry about.
They love you.
I guess when you're a doctor
and you marry a doctor...
...and you raise three awesome boys,
you tend to judge people a little harsher.
I guess that's how I feel
when Mrs. Awesome is around.
I've never heard you use the nickname
that many times.
I know. I know, it's okay.
I'm just a little stressed right now.
But we all have our burdens to bear.
MORGAN:
Hey, Chuck.
Hello.
Hey, yo.
-What?
-Anybody here?
Like whom?
Like the other woman, dude. Jill.
Morgan, there is no other woman.
Really? That's great.
I thought I was gonna have to
do some sort of intervention.
Help you with your addiction
to really attractive women.
-What's that smell?
-Uh, probably Ellie.
-She's doing practice cooking for tomorrow.
-Naturally, tomorrow's Thanksgiving.
So that smell is...
...turkey.
ELLIE:
Morgan.
-I need you to try this.
-Mm-hm, mm-hm.
Oh, my God.
-It's heaven.
-No, no, it's too--
It's too dry.
Test Turkey Number 1 is too dry.
Uh, three hours, seven minutes.
What are you doing?
No, no, no. The hell...?
Oh, my God.
Okay, Morgan, we need to talk.
Fine, but just don't hurt
another turkey like that.
Morgan,
this Thanksgiving is very important.
-Sure.
-And things need to run smoothly.
I know, I know. You're so stressed.
Everything's great. What can I do?
-Ahem. Morgan?
-Yeah.
You're....
I'm not invited.
I can't believe this. I mean, how?
Uninvited to T-day.
Morgan, relax. I don't know
how many times I have to tell you.
It's gonna be okay.
I'm gonna talk to Ellie, sort it out.
Anna's out of town.
-If I don't have Thanksgiving with you--
-Morgan, breathe.
-Hi, can I help you?
-Grimes, with me.
Okay.
Did I just hear you don't have Thanksgiving
plans? That's terrible. Damn terrible.
I'm amazed to find so many staff members
without plans for Thanksgiving.
Like these two poor creatures.
Sir, are you inviting us to dinner?
No. God, no.
I need you lonely bastards
to stand guard here at the store...
...on Thanksgiving.
-Stand guard?
MIKE: Because of Black Friday.
We have more product than ever before.
You three are gonna make certain
nobody steals it.
[CELL PHONE RINGING]
-Answer it.
-Not on the first ring.
It implies an eagerness
that I'm not really feeling right now.
Ow. Whoa.
Hi, hi, hi, Jill.
A date?
Tonight? Yeah.
Sounds great. Where?
It's a surprise?
Of course I can tell my bodyguards
to take the night off so we can be alone.
Just the two of us.
I'm looking forward to it as well.
Mwah.
Ow! Ow.
What are you doing? What was that for?
The kissing noise. Have some self-respect,
Bartowski. You're a man.
I gotta go talk to Sarah.
[FOOTSTEPS APPROACHING]
-What? What is it?
-Sarah, I need your help.
How am I gonna survive tonight?
Well, a good spy
knows what their mark wants.
And what do we know about Jill?
She's a spy.
She wants you to be under her spell.
Okay. How do I do that?
She's gonna test you.
When the time is right,
she's gonna make certain that she has you.
That you love her.
-How is she gonna do that?
-When you're most exposed.
Emotionally exposed,
like, uh, an intimate moment.
Say, a kiss.
Okay. Imagine that I am Jill.
The moment is romantic,
she's close to you.
She's looking into your eyes.
Got it, okay. I got the--
I'm trying not to be distracted
by the oh-so-romantic secret base.
[SIGHS]
[CLICKS]
Concentrate. Keep looking into my eyes.
Don't look up.
If you can't hold Jill's stare,
look at her lips.
Good.
Now move her hair back over her ear.
And when you start to kiss,
focus again on her.
Then just before your lips
are about to meet...
...close your eyes.
Okay, good.
Good. You're all set.
Huh?
Oh, yeah, good.
CASEY:
Hey.
NSA just picked up a purchase
on Jill's credit card.
Two tickets to some stupid concert
down at the Music Center.
Better not be another freaking opera.
Well, we'll be there waiting for you.
Look, just remember,
Jill is capable of anything.
You look great.
Sorry to keep you waiting.
JILL:
So, what do you think of my surprise?
Uh, wha--? What were you--?
-This wasn't--
-What?
Nothing, nothing. If I seem tense,
it's just my irrational fear of carnivals.
JILL: Right.
-Acting up on me.
JILL: Come here.
I got another surprise for you.
[WHEEL WHIRS]
[WHEEL CLUNKS]
You saw this coming, didn't you?
You bribed a carnie. Ha.
You know what happens next?
You get really, really nervous...
...and then you ramble on
for a couple seconds, and then...
...I have to kiss you.
I'm sorry, Chuck.
For what?
[GUN COCKS]
-What are you doing?
-I work for a group called Fulcrum.
You know who they are,
don't you, Chuck?
-They plan to eliminate you.
-Jill, please don't do this.
I don't want to, I'm not a killer.
This isn't what I do for a living.
You pull that trigger
and it is what you do for a living.
You already broke my heart.
Is it necessary for you to shoot it as well?
You're right.
Okay, Chuck, here's the truth.
There's a Fulcrum operative down there.
He's watching now.
I'm supposed to transport you to a car.
If I don't follow their plan, they're gonna
eliminate you and me as a precaution.
CASEY:
Almost to the Music Center.
What's the ETA
on Chuck and the Fulcrum agent?
Wait, I lost him.
His signal just dropped off the grid.
-What?
-It was a ghost.
Turn us around, Casey, now.
They're not at the Music Center.
North 101, go.
[TIRES SCREECH]
Chuck, you have to do
exactly what I say, okay?
You should know
that my rational fear of carnivals...
...has spread to ex-girlfriends.
How do I know I can trust you?
How do I know you're not gonna
take me to the parking lot?
Oh, no.
That's him.
Who's him? Him who?
JILL:
Leader.
Okay, come here.
Um, excuse us, person we don't know,
you're blocking us.
His handlers are closing in. Eliminate him.
-What, here?
LEADER: Don't think.
Shoot him in the head and let's go.
-Did you just say--?
-Let's talk about this.
Can we actually just leave if we--? Aah.
This is a test, Jill. Do it now.
Too late.
[GUN COCKS]
You're making a big mistake.
[GRUNTS]
Sorry, sorry, excuse me.
[PANTING]
LEADER: Mr. Bartowski.
-Aah!
You need to come with me.
Um, you told Jill to shoot me.
Why would I ever go anywhere with you?
I'd rather not leave your body
here on the ride.
-What if some kid saw it?
-Huh.
Wow, that's, uh, strangely considerate
of you.
[GRUNTS]
[GROANS]
[BOTH SCREAM]
[PANTING]
[GRUNTS]
This is exactly how I feel.
JILL: Chuck, you have to trust me.
-Jill?
I'm not gonna hurt you.
Where are you? Jill, where are you?
Why are you doing this?
When did you join Fulcrum and why?
JILL:
It started at Stanford.
They sponsored a leadership seminar.
After school, whatever job we wanted,
they got us.
Made our dreams come true.
Couldn't you get out?
When someone controls
every part of your life...
...you have to do what they say.
After a while,
I found myself doing things...
...I never thought I would have done...
...but by then it was too late.
Too late for what?
Jill?
Jill.
I'm impressed, Mr. Bartowski.
I wasn't really certain you were a spy,
but now I see.
God. Unh!
Goodbye.
[GUNSHOT]
Come on.
[CHUCK STAMMERS]
Chuck, come on.
Don't move.
No, no. Wait, wait.
Don't hurt her. She saved my life.
So one more time. What's the plan?
We stay here in the store all day.
-Anything goes wrong, call you.
MIKE: Good.
Remember, you three
are the last line of defense against--
-Yeah, but isn't this a bit overkill?
-Overkill?
Grimes, my first store
was the Husky Lad Big And Tall.
For the more than average man.
It was robbed Thanksgiving of '88.
That was a dark day, Morgan.
Husky lads throughout Burbank
went without britches for Christmas.
The store closed before the New Year.
So no.
It's not overkill. It's business.
Sure.
Um, but before you lock us in...
...um, isn't there some sort of law
about locking us in the store?
-What if there's a fire?
-I'm not worried about a fire.
I'm worried about thieves.
All right, Lady Big Mike
is cooking with the family.
I got fish to catch.
Lady Big Mike?
[LOCKS CLICK]
Everything's gonna be all right.
Answer all of our questions
with a yes or no.
Okay.
Is your name Jill Roberts?
Yes.
[BEEPS]
SARAH: Did you attend Stanford University?
-Yes.
Can I ask a follow-up question?
-You're about to leave through that window.
-I rescind.
-Do you have a degree in molecular biology?
-Yes.
[BEEPS]
-Are you a Fulcrum agent?
-No. Wait.
I'm sorry.
Telling the truth is new to me.
Yes, I am a Fulcrum agent.
SARAH: Do you know the current
whereabouts of your Fulcrum handler...
...code name Leader?
Do you know the whereabouts
of your handler--?
-Yes.
-Give us the location now.
Tell me now or I lose my calm.
Jill. Jill, just tell him.
Please, just tell him.
Okay, I'm not supposed to know this,
but Fulcrum has a mobile medical unit.
You'll find Leader recovering in an
office building in downtown Los Angeles.
Is this a trap?
No.
[BEEPS]
CHUCK: Sarah, what about Jill?
-I know what you're thinking.
That Jill is the same person
you went to school with...
...and the same person that you dated,
but we cannot be certain.
Trust me, Chuck. You can't trust her.
[DOOR SHUTS]
-Is he setting a trap?
LESTER: Mm-hm.
Good friend Jeffrey's been doing this job,
for, give or take, 15 years.
-This is his Thanksgiving tradition.
MORGAN: Amazing.
How many traps has he set?
Just the one tripwire.
It's kind of sad, he tripped over it last year.
Anyway, bon appétit, buddy.
Mmm.
Turkey in plastic?
No, no, Les, this is all wrong.
This is not what Thanksgiving's about.
This is pathetic, dude.
Um, what?
-What else is there?
-There's so much more, man.
Yeah, there's fun and food and friends.
That's just the F's.
-Where?
-Out there.
Morgan, heh, we can't leave.
Dude, what if I can bring it back here?
-A turkey.
-We--
No, not like this.
-A real turkey?
-Yes.
What do I have to do
to get this real turkey?
Okay, motor's off. Come on.
-Dude, we gotta push harder here.
-I'm trying, I'm trying.
This is such a fire hazard.
-Look, look.
-Okay, okay.
-I'm gonna go.
-Go, go, go.
Yeah, hold.
Ow! Oh!
Jeff!
-Open the door!
-Open.
-Okay.
-Oh, my Lord.
MORGAN: Jeff!
-Got it.
Okay. Nice, Jeff.
Now, can you open the door
that is currently chopping me in half?
My bad.
[SIGHS]
Did he make it?
[GRUNTS]
[ALARM BLARING]
[CELL PHONE RINGING]
WOMAN [OVER PHONE]:
Security breach at Buy More.
Location 2453.
T-time is 45 minutes.
What time are your parents getting here?
Okay. Mm-hm.
I love you too.
Babe, I got some news.
My parents can't make it. Ha, ha.
Don't toy with my emotions right now,
Devon.
Honey, I wouldn't dare.
-You're serious?
-Yeah. Ha, ha.
That's great.
-Oh, that's so great. Oh, my God.
-Ha-ha-ha.
-Now, can we just have some fun?
-Yes.
Listen to Chuck's stories.
Laugh at Morgan as he O-faces through
his mashed potatoes and stuffing.
Oh, no.
I uninvited Morgan.
He's the one person who loves this dinner
more than anyone.
[GARBAGE RATTLING IN TRASH CAN]
Oh, man. Some animal has gotten
into the trash again.
[MORGAN HUMMING]
Ow! Unh.
Wha--? I saw you put it in the bag.
You know, I figured it was still good,
so I--
Okay.
Morgan, I'm so sorry
that I uninvited you to Thanksgiving.
Please, please forgive me.
Forgive you? Yeah, of course.
Yes, I understand.
I completely understand.
You've been so stressed.
And with our new boss at work,
and this Chuck and Jill thing is like:
[WHISTLES]
-What Chuck and Jill thing?
-Hmm? Jill thing? I didn't say--
-You tell me everything that you know.
-Mm-hm, absolutely, I will.
Can I just get one favor?
I need to invite a couple of guests over.
Chuck?
-Hey.
I was just seeing
if you needed a water or something.
No, I'm good.
Are Casey and Sarah
ready to start again?
Um, no.
No, not just yet.
But before they do, I was wondering
if I could maybe ask you a few things.
-Do you know how to work all this stuff?
-Yeah, totally.
I, uh, read the manual.
You read a lie-detector manual?
No, this is the manual
for the entire Castle base.
Oh. You read a manual for a base.
Well, you know, I mean, um....
-I skimmed it.
-Heh.
Would you--? Uh, would you mind
if I asked you a couple of questions?
Go ahead.
Um....
Back at Stanford when we were dating...
...was that for real?
Yes.
[BEEPS]
You really liked me?
Those were real emotions?
Yes.
[BEEPS]
Well, then why did you sleep with Bryce
after I got kicked out?
It has to be a yes or no question
or it won't work.
Did you love him too?
No.
[BEEPS]
Great.
Great. That makes it even worse.
There's a question you're not asking.
It's right there and you're not asking it.
Did you sleep with Bryce?
No.
I didn't.
[BEEPS]
[GROANS]
Everyone freeze.
SARAH:
Stop right there.
CASEY:
Take them all out of here.
But this one on the table, he's mine.
[AGENTS YELLING INDISTINCTLY]
So you're telling me
that for the last six years of my life...
...I've been believing
that you betrayed me?
Why would you do that?
When you got kicked out,
my Fulcrum advisor said...
...that I had to let you go.
You weren't talking to Bryce
so that was the easiest way.
I'm so sorry, Chuck.
I don't believe this.
Fulcrum told you to dump me?
I didn't have a choice.
In your defense,
when they told you to kill me...
...you didn't do it...
-...so I guess that means something.
-It does.
I never wanted to hurt you, Chuck, ever.
You were my first love.
Do you think that when this is all over...
...we could try again?
Get me out of these.
Yes.
[COMPUTER BEEPS]
Chuck, we have Leader.
We're taking him back to the Castle.
CHUCK [OVER PHONE]:
Great. See you when you get back.
I'm sorry, Chuck.
Chuck? Chuck, what's the matter?
You promised
that you wouldn't hurt them.
Put the guns on the table.
Take the cuffs off now.
I'm sorry.
I'm sorry I let her out.
It's my fault, I'm sorry.
Now, I believe we were headed
to a holding area.
Show me the way.
Chuck, do what he says
and you'll be okay.
-What about my friends?
-Just do what he says.
-How could you do this, Jill?
-Chuck, it's complicated.
Listen, I know complicated, okay?
How could you do this?
You did an excellent job, my dear.
Show me access screen
for the Joint Intelligence Database.
-Um, I'm sorry, I don't know how.
-Do it now or I'll kill your friends.
Starting with the blond.
[BEEPING]
Thank you, Chuck.
This was all a trick, wasn't it?
You guys just did this
to get in and access our computer?
You let her shoot you.
Devious, aren't we? Move him.
Oh, baby.
-Jill, you're making a big mistake.
-I have to do what he says, Chuck.
Why? What is your boss searching for?
-What secret is worth this?
-We're searching for someone.
-Who?
-Bryce Larkin.
Bryce.
-Why are you looking for Bryce?
-Don't protect him.
We know he's CIA.
He stole something from us.
-They're looking for the Intersect.
-I'm sorry, Sarah.
I should have listened to you.
-We'll figure something out.
-Actually, I have a plan.
Hey, what are you doing?
That's the Castle manual.
I told you that's top-secret.
Yeah, I know. So am I.
Chuck.
What did you do?
Like I told Jill.
I read the manual.
What did you do?
I locked you out of the system...
...using the remote console that every
room in Castle's equipped with.
It's in the manual.
Unfortunately,
said manual is in here with me.
And since I overrode
Castle's primary controls...
...we're now safely locked
within these bulletproof cells.
Devious, aren't I?
I make one call and my men
will be here in 20 minutes.
I'm so glad you brought that up
because I also activated...
...the base's communications jammer,
so no calls out.
Sorry about that.
And because I triggered
the CIA's trouble alarm...
...I think the cavalry's gonna be here
in 10 minutes or so.
The nerd in me really, really
wants to say checkmate right about now.
-Never say that.
-Why?
Because you don't know
who you're playing against.
These cells might be bulletproof,
but they can't withstand that.
The blast will kill them,
but I'll bet your cell will be fine.
-Chuck, don't do anything.
-Stay in that cell, Bartowski.
-Jill?
-Just do what he says, Chuck.
Open the door or your friends will die.
Goodbye, Mr. Bartowski.
Wait, wait, wait.
Wait.
Now show me the way out of here.
Jill, if you hurt him, I swear....
[CASEY SIGHS]
[CONSOLE BEEPS]
It's a message from Chuck.
[BEEPS]
[LOCK CLICKS]
[COCKS]
[GRUNTS]
Drop it.
[CASEY GRUNTS]
Sarah, don't hurt her.
[CASEY GRUNTING]
Jill. Jill, hey.
I can help you.
Come with me.
Come on.
[PANTS]
And you thought you were gonna
take me down?
MIKE:
No, baby, I am.
[GROWLING]
[PANTS]
I hate thieves.
Grimes put you in charge?
Hmm? Yeah.
Smart boy.
JILL:
What's going on? What are we doing?
Look, you're taking the Matrix, okay?
All-wheel drive, touch-screen navi,
iPod capability and a full tank of gas.
It's the perfect getaway car.
Just get in and drive as far as you can.
I won't call it in, I swear.
Thank you.
Come with me.
We can still be together.
How?
Just you and me, no secrets.
No spies.
Come with me, Chuck.
No, I can't, I can't.
I....
Look, obviously, there's the whole
opposites-attract-chemistry thing...
...that we have, and I....
It's just there's one small problem.
What are you doing, Chuck?
[LOCKS CLICK AND RADIO BEEPS]
What's going on?
Don't do this to me, Chuck.
You should know I wanted to help you.
-I was gonna let you get away.
-Chuck, no.
But you were about to kill Sarah.
You made the decision for me.
You're under arrest, Jill.
And I'm breaking up with you.
I'm sorry, Sarah.
I should've listened from the beginning.
You were right.
I wasn't ready for this mission.
No one is ready for this type of mission.
Your girlfriend being Fulcrum isn't
something they teach you in spy school.
I'm just too trusting.
Ever since I was a kid, I really wanted
to believe what everybody told me.
I'm just getting used to this new job,
all the spying and lying.
Don't get used to it.
What makes you special
is you're not like every other spy.
You're a good guy
and you wanna help people.
Leave the deception to me.
I'm glad I have you.
Yeah, we're better as a team.
Oh, yeah.
MORGAN:
Happy Thanksgiving.
Can I borrow you? I'm stealing him.
Oh, no, that's okay.
Are you absolutely certain
that Jill is not with Chuck?
Yeah, that's what he told me.
-Think Chuck's gonna break up with Sarah?
-Well, I hope not.
Yeah, me too.
-You know what we need here?
-What?
A Thanksgiving miracle.
Chuck and Sarah
are gonna walk through that door.
They'll be as happy as can be
and everything's gonna be fine.
Ha, ha. Well, good job, Morgan.
-Hi.
-I could've asked for anything.
-Happy Thanksgiving.
-Hi, happy Thanksgiving.
First time we can experience
a turkey, dude.
Ellie, do you realize that Lester and Jeff
of the Nerd Herd are at our table right now?
-Everything okay?
-The Awesomes couldn't make it.
So you know me.
Just expand Thanksgiving.
-Okay.
-Happy Thanksgiving.
You too.
-Are you okay?
-Of course. Yeah.
Why do you ask?
Because Morgan told me
about you and Jill.
I'm sorry, I just--
I was worried about you.
Um, no. Yeah, everything's good.
She wanted to see if we could work it out
and give it a second try.
And?
And I realized that Jill, Stanford and Bryce,
that's the story from my past.
But my new story is you and Sarah
and these freaking yahoos.
And sometimes,
it can be a really fun story.
Swedish Bikini Team.
-Flying DeLorean.
CHUCK: Hey, Morgan.
Come on, buddy.
Anyway, where was I?
You were saying
how the turkey's made.
-Saying that this turkey is voluntary.
-It's more of a draft.
Toast to, uh, some of the great, uh, faces
that I know...
...and new ones to Thanksgiving.
LESTER: We don't know each other.
JEFF: Hear, hear.
DEVON:
Happy Thanksgiving.
Great job, baby.
[ENGLISH SDH]