-Sweet wheels.
-Right back at you, dawg.
Love the smell of the day
before Christmas in the morning.
There's just nothing quite like
the sweet scent...
...of desperate last-minute
shoppers in the air.
-Jack our prices up 10 percent?
-15. Snooze, you lose.
We're gonna rob them blind.
-Merry Christmas!
[BOTH LAUGH]
[DOORBELLS CHIME]
Hey, sure is quiet around here.
Bad guys taking a holiday too?
Not that I mind, by the way.
Because the Intersect could certainly use
some down time as well.
Speaking of which, we have a cover date
tomorrow. Christmas at the Bartowskis'.
Oh, uh, thanks for the invitation, Chuck.
But I don't do Christmas.
[CHUCKLES]
I'm sorry, I think you just said
you don't do Christmas.
Look, I would rather not get into it.
But it's Christmas. Look,
I'm not buying the whole Scrooge act.
Okay? Underneath that spy cover
is a regular person just like the rest of us.
I mean, honestly, how weird
could Christmas have been for you?
Christmas at the Burton household
meant the annual Salvation Army con job.
Okay, well, it's a-- Okay, you're
a little different than the rest of us.
But Christmas at the Bartowskis'
means eggnog, p.j.'s...
...a fake gas fire place, and that's right,
Twilight Zone marathons.
I'm not taking no for an answer, Walker.
So prepare to be heart-warmed.
[CHUCKLES]
Oh, thank God you're here, Chuck.
Thank God.
Anna won't speak to me...
...after I balked at the whole
moving-in-together thing.
She thinks you're immature,
afraid to grow up and be an adult?
Exactly, yeah, exactly.
And that's ridiculous.
Do I not look like an adult to you?
[SCOFFS]
[SNICKERS]
[BELLS JINGLING]
MAN [ON TV]: It's been about an hour.
The chase continues through the valley.
Twenty large says this ends
with the pigs making that punk eat lead.
I say he crashes. We end up
with a stand-off, maybe hostages.
-Never gonna happen.
-Please, you're amateurs.
-This has beat-down written all over it.
-Bring it in, bring it in, everybody.
It's nice to see everyone's
in the Christmas spirit this morning.
-This is how we roll--
MIKE: Bartowski!
Doors open in an hour.
Round up the freaks.
Have everyone meet me
in Santa's village, pronto.
This is it, people. D-day.
You ready for war?
You got what it takes?
Take a sniff, Grimes!
[SNIFFS]
Tell this band of misfits
what you smell.
Absolutely. Uh, coffee, hazelnut, maybe?
Uh, glazed bear claw.
[SNIFFS]
-Cream-filled perhaps?
-I'm not talking about my breakfast.
I'm talking about profits. People are lazy.
They'll be looking to purchase
last-minute gifts.
Which is why
we raised our prices 15 percent.
We're looking at a record sales day,
as long as you people don't screw it up.
So don't!
-Hey, thank you.
-Hey, what's going on?
We, uh, decided we beat the rush...
...and, uh, take advantage
of the friends and family discount.
Oh, don't worry
about getting me a gift, babe.
-You already did.
-I did?
Yeah, I took it upon myself
since you never know what to get me.
Oh, that's great. What did I get you?
Weekend sky-diving trip with the boys
in Crested Butte, 10,000-foot free-fall.
-Awesome.
MIKE: Chuck!
-Santa's village.
-Uh, yeah.
Hey, great, I gotta get back
to work. You kids have fun.
Great. So, uh, my present to my fiancé
is a ticket to death.
Babe, it's completely safe.
Besides, I need the adrenaline rush.
A little sense of danger in my life.
[SIGHS]
What?
MAN [ON TV]: Okay, the suspect
has just gotten off the 5 freeway.
-And right now....
-Oh, man, the cops look pissed.
-I'm so winning the pool.
-Christmas sucks.
[POLICE SIRENS BLARING ON TV]
MAN [ON TV]:
Action News reporting as police continue...
...their chase
through downtown Burbank.
If anything, he appears to be picking up
speed in this residential neighborhood.
We'd like to warn anyone in the area that
this is an extremely dangerous situation.
[POLICE SIRENS BLARING NEARBY]
It appears the perpetrator
has just turned off Burbank Boulevard...
...into a shopping complex, he's not
slowing down, he's not slowing down!
[ALL SHOUT]
God.
MAN [ON TV]:
Wow, an unbelievable ending to a pursuit...
...that lasted the better part of an hour.
We'll continue to keep you updated.
Let's hope that everyone inside is okay.
All right, nobody move.
Pay up, suckers.
Hi. Welcome to the Buy More.
And merry Christmas.
[INDISTINCT CHATTER
OVER RADIO]
[SIRENS WAILING]
Not good, not good. Oh, boy.
Okay, Ned, just calm down.
Think, think, think.
Hi, hi.
Uh, my name's Nathan Edward Rhyerson.
Uh, people like to call me Ned.
I'm sorry about the entrance.
[NED GROANS]
Can someone please tell me
who's in charge here?
[IN UNISON]
Chuck!
Actually, I'm not technically in charge.
I don't wanna hurt anyone, Chuck.
So as long as no one gets brave,
no one gets shot, okay?
Okay, okay....
I think we're safe. Yeah.
Um, this store has a very strict,
no-bravery policy.
Okay, okay.
Everyone, uh, get over there
by the Santa's village.
Now, come on!
Uh, Chuck.
Where's the security system?
It, um....
Okay, just follow me.
Right over here.
Are there any other ways
in and out of the store?
Um, yeah, they're all locked down
because we technically haven't opened yet.
Good, then lock it down.
What's going on?
Oh, great. I step out of work
one time, I miss all the fun.
The suspect's name is Nathan Rhyerson.
He is a civilian. No record.
Not even a speeding ticket
in the past 10 years.
Well, Nathan picked himself the
wrong place to be naughty instead of nice.
I get to play with my new toy
I got myself.
General, if we go in guns blazing,
Chuck's cover will be blown.
The guy seems timid,
not someone local P.D. couldn't handle.
-What are you saying, Agent Walker?
-Chuck has family and friends in there.
And if we blow Chuck's cover...
...then not only he will have to go
underground, but so will everyone else.
We'll try it Agent Walker's way first.
Slip into Buy More from Castle
and see if you can remove Chuck...
...without calling attention to yourselves
or the asset, understood?
Understood.
Are you okay, major?
Hmm?
Oh, uh, just paper cuts.
I'm on gift-wrap station right now,
general.
It's an electronics store, major.
Not Basrah.
Get it under control.
[SIRENS WAILING]
This is Maureen Mitsubishi,
KPFW news...
...reporting from the Buy More,
where unlucky employees...
...are spending the day before Christmas
with a gunman instead of their loved ones.
-Who's in charge here?
-Well, I am, sir.
Al Powell, Burbank P.D. Who are you?
Lieutenant Mauser,
hostage negotiator, L.A.P.D.
-Mm-hm.
-So, what's it look like in there?
Well, all indications are everybody's safe.
This guy's an amateur.
Good news is that my cousin Mike
is the store manager.
And if I know Mike,
he'll have everything under control.
Hmm.
MIKE:
Why today?
You know how much money I'm losing?
Our shoppers are gonna go to Large Mart.
There, there, big man. Just eat.
-It's gonna be okay.
-It is?
Of course it is.
Every news outlet is out there.
Any publicity is good publicity.
Yeah.
Besides, my cousin Big Al's a cop.
Half of L.A.P.D. will be here.
We can get this store back open
for business by lunch, right?
Hmm, maybe.
Hey? Hey, Ned, it's Chuck.
That's a terrible picture of me.
Hey, you can put your hands down.
You know, truth is I'm really not a bad guy
once you get to know me.
When you're not crashing your car into
electronics stores and waving a gun around?
Yeah.
Look, I know it's no excuse,
but I lost my job, man.
All I wanted was to get a few gifts for
my kids so we could celebrate Christmas.
And the next thing you know,
I'm the next O.J.
What am I gonna do, Chuck?
They're gonna put me in jail, aren't they?
No. No, maybe not.
Maybe not, you know?
Uh, I mean, you haven't
hurt anyone yet, right?
So maybe if you give up...
...they'll work out some sort of deal,
probation or something.
Oh, why would they do that?
Look, keep this between us,
but I know some people.
People who could make all this go away
as long as you don't do anything stupid.
Like who?
[PHONE RINGS]
-Who's calling?
-Um, that's probably the police.
Maybe they wanna know
what's happening.
I don't wanna talk to anyone.
You think you can answer it?
Yeah, I'll just....
Nerd Herd. How can I help you?
This is Lieutenant Mauser, L.A.P.D.
Who am I speaking with?
Uh, this is Chuck Bartowski.
Nerd Herd supervisor.
Chuck, I'm gonna need to talk to Ned.
He wants to talk to you.
He doesn't wanna talk to you.
[SCOFFS]
Okay, then you and I are gonna
have to work through this ourselves.
-So tell me, is there anyone hurt in there?
-No, nobody's hurt, everybody's okay.
Uh, Ned--
Uh, is it okay if I call you, Ned?
-Sure, Ned's fine.
CHUCK: Okay.
Uh, Ned explicitly told me
that he wants absolutely no trouble.
Tell him to send out a hostage
as a sign of good faith.
He says that you should send out
a hostage as a sign of good faith.
Good God, pick me, pick me, pick me.
Pick me. Oh, sorry.
My 86-year-old mother
is dying of a very rare disease.
It's leukoplakia.
And she needs me, her bo-bo.
Uh, okay, fine, send him.
Oh, thank you, thank you.
Oh, ho, ho. Can I give you--?
[EMMETT SIGHS]
Oh, thank you, thank you. Thank you.
We're sending someone out.
We got one hostage coming out, folks.
That scoundrel.
I bet Bartowski worked out a deal.
Yeah, Chuck let Emmett go
so he could get better lunch shifts.
He's selling us down the river.
Making a sweetheart deal for himself.
Guess it's prison rules now.
Every man for himself.
EMMETT:
Aah! Oh, my God.
Oh. Who's got a phone?
Who's got a phone?
I need to call my lawyer, my therapist.
I need to call my mother,
and I need to call my yogi.
Maureen Mitsubishi continuing to cover
the story at the Burbank Buy More...
...where it seems a hostage
has just been released.
I'm Lieutenant Mauser, L.A.P.D.
Who are you?
I'm the assistant manager,
Emmett Milbarge.
-Hmm.
-That's two T's, two M's--
Tell me, tell me, Emmett,
uh, what's going on inside there?
What's going on inside
is the greatest sales event of the season.
That's right. We have got the best deals
in town on all your electronic needs.
MAUSER [ON TV]: No, no, no, Emmett,
I meant the perp. Is he dangerous?
EMMETT [ON TV]:
Oh, ha-ha-ha. Dangerous?
The only thing dangerous
is how low we have slashed our prices.
God bless that man.
Uh, so, uh....
Hey, Chuck, where are these people
that can get me out of this?
[DOOR CLICKS]
Um....
They're, uh, closer than you think.
Can I use the bathroom?
I mean, the store's already locked down.
So I can't really go anywhere.
Hey, yeah. Sure, of course.
All right, well, be back in a sec.
About time the cavalry showed up.
So, what's the plan?
Lock you in the Castle until this is over.
Come on.
Whoa, hey, what about Ellie,
Morgan, everyone else?
We're instructed to remove you
and only you.
There's a team coming
to extract the rest.
-They'll be in good hands.
-I'm not gonna leave my sister.
There are rules, and we have
to follow them. Let's go.
There are rules,
but there's a time to break them.
Get in the hatch, Bartowski.
Your emotions cloud your judgment.
Nothing bad will happen.
-Now, please, come on.
-I can't take that chance.
NED:
Chuck, is that you?
[WHISPERS]
Shut it, shut it.
-Aah!
-No, no, no, Ned.
-Chuck, what's going on?
-Ned, please, please, don't shoot that gun.
-Who are they?
-They're harmless, okay?
Look, they heard your crash, and they hid.
This is Sarah.
-Hi.
And this is John Casey.
Who's even more harmless.
-John Casey.
-Ned, please, just uncock the gun.
Okay. Uh, how do I do that?
Because, uh, truth is I've never used
one of these before.
-There's probably a button, like a safety.
-No, no, no!
[GUNSHOT]
Oh, my God, Chuck.
We have gunfire.
I repeat, we hear gunfire.
NED: Oh, my God!
-Oh!
-I'm so sorry. I'm so sorry, are you okay?
-Ah.
I didn't mean to shoot you. I promise.
We need a SWAT team
down here pronto.
It's okay, everyone. It was a mistake.
An accidental shooting.
But Casey is gonna be just fine.
Idiot. You owe me a toe, Bartowski.
[LAUGHS]
DEVON:
There.
You're gonna be okay, John.
A lot of people get by with nine toes.
-I'm getting by fine with eight.
-How much is a toe worth to Casey?
-Why?
-Maybe there's a finder's fee.
[WHISPERS]
You know, I survived three wars...
...without so much
as losing a finger nail before I met you.
Look, I'm really sorry
about your toe, John.
But I had the situation under control.
You're the one who scared him.
-You okay?
-I'm just scared.
I've never been this close
to a gun before.
Yeah, me neither.
You know what, we'll be okay.
We just have to stick together.
Big Mike, Morgan, Jeff, Lester.
Come here, get over here.
I don't know about you guys,
but I've had enough.
We need to take him out
before anyone else gets hurt.
He's right.
The store closes at midnight.
We got lots of merchandise to move.
Fellas, I don't know, man.
Time to be a man, Morgan.
Yeah, I'll do it, I'm in.
-So am I.
CHUCK: Wait, hold on, wait.
This is a very bad idea, okay?
Ned shot Casey on accident.
He's not trying to hurt anybody.
-Let the police handle this.
-Let the cops handle this.
I know you guys work at a Buy More,
but I'm a doctor.
Okay, I take risks every day.
This is a matter of life or death.
Someone needs to man up and take action.
Someone needs to be a hero.
No, they don't, Devon.
Being a hero is being alive
to take care of your friends and family.
[PHONE RINGING]
Chuck, Chuck.
-They keep calling, you better answer it.
CHUCK: Yeah, coming.
Don't do anything, do nothing.
I will be right back.
Hey, hey, I, uh, feel terrible
about shooting your friend's toe off.
No, no, no, that's okay.
Sometimes I feel like shooting him myself.
-This is Chuck.
-Okay, okay, talk to me, Chuck.
We heard gunfire, what's going on?
Everything's under control.
Everything is just fine.
There was an accidental shot fired.
And someone lost the majority of their toe,
but besides that, everything's okay.
[GRUMBLES]
-I wanna talk to him now.
-He wants to talk to you.
Huh? Well, ask him what he wants.
MAUSER:
I wanna know his demands.
-He wants to know what your demands are.
-I don't know.
Uh, I have to think about it.
-Can you call back in like five minutes?
-Yeah, yeah.
So, uh, what are you gonna do, Ned?
Well, maybe I should call my wife.
She always knows what to do
in these situations.
Yeah, that's a great idea.
Maybe you could let everyone else
make a call too.
Check in with their loved ones.
Let them know that they're safe.
Okay, Chuck. Yeah.
Hi, honey. It's me.
Uh, I'm okay.
Look, uh, I know
this is gonna sound bad, but....
-Hey, Mom and Dad.
-Hi, guys.
Yeah, everything's awesome.
Well, not really, but we'll be okay.
[PHONE RINGS ON LINE]
WOMAN [ON RECORDING]: Hi there,
you've reached the love chat line.
Looking to chat with someone special?
Press 1.
[BEEPS]
MAN [OVER PHONE]:
Lompoc correctional institute.
Yes, I'd like to speak to prisoner 27318.
A.k.a. Mom.
-Hey, baby.
-Save your breath, Morgan.
Hey, Big Mike.
How you holding up in there, partner?
Surviving, partner.
Any shoppers lining up out there?
Mother? Johnny boy.
[CELL PHONE RINGING]
Hi, Chuck.
-Where are you?
CHUCK [OVER PHONE]: DVD's.
I'm in the romantic-comedy section.
Although for irony's sake, I suppose
I should probably be in hostage-thrillers.
[BEEPS]
So, uh, Ned let everyone call
their loved ones.
That was pretty smart to call me.
Protect our cover.
Yeah, well, you are my girlfriend.
Sort of.
So does that mean your offer
still stands for Christmas?
See, I knew you could be heart-warmed.
[CHUCK CHUCKLES]
I actually, um....
I have something for you.
I was gonna give it to you tomorrow...
...but considering the circumstances,
I kind of wanna give it to you today.
Chuck, we're gonna get out of here.
We'll be fine, I promise.
Wow. Ha, ha.
That's beautiful.
It's good luck.
It was my mom's charm bracelet.
My dad gave it to her
when Ellie was born.
Oh, Chuck, I can't take this.
This is something real.
Something that you should give
to a real girlfriend.
I know.
[PHONE RINGING]
Chuck.
Duty calls.
-Hey, this is Chuck.
-Chuck, what does he want?
It's Lieutenant Mauser.
He wants to know what you want.
I wanna go home
and spend Christmas with my family.
All right, tell him I'm coming in, Chuck.
I'm unarmed.
I just wanna talk so we can get him
and everybody else home for Christmas.
Okay.
Okay, all right, yeah,
I'm gonna come open the door right now.
[PANEL BEEPING]
[DOOR SHUTS]
I'm completely unarmed, Ned.
Just wanna talk this out.
Chuck, you come back over here.
-Okay, I don't wanna go to jail.
-It's okay.
We're gonna work on that.
But in the meantime, what do you say
you and I make a trade, okay?
Me, for two of your hostages.
It would make people out there
feel a whole lot easier.
Yeah, in here too.
Okay, okay.
-Two people can go.
-Okay, good, good.
Um, what do you say
we start with the injured man?
He looks like he needs medical attention.
I'm fine, I'm good.
-Let Ellie go.
-No, no, Casey.
Thank you, but you need to go,
your toe could be infected.
Chuck, you've been a good friend to me.
So I'm gonna return the favor.
I'm gonna let your girlfriend go.
No!
Chuck?
-Ouch.
-Yikes.
Gonna be a cold Christmas
at the Bartowski's.
Oh, no, he didn't.
Heh, I didn't-- I don't--
I don't mean
I don't want my girlfriend to leave...
...because clearly I would really like for
Sarah to leave and be out of harm's way.
That's not what I'm saying,
what I'm saying is that....
I'm not your only friend here, Ned.
You've endeared yourself
into the hearts of everyone here.
I think we're all friends. We're a family,
we've gone through a lot, haven't we?
So we should all leave,
why don't we all leave together?
-No, just those two.
-Okay.
[CASEY GROANS]
[WHISPERS]
Our team just arrived.
Don't do anything stupid.
Maybe the rest of us can get out of here
without losing an appendage.
Uh, Chuck, it's okay.
[SIGHS]
[WHISPERS]
Trust me, I'll never let anyone hurt you.
Okay.
[SIGHS]
[HELICOPTER WHIRRING]
[DOOR SHUTS]
-Good to finally meet you face to face.
-Yeah.
Did a hell of job.
Pretty impressive for a retail jockey.
I just want all this over
as soon as possible.
Well, so do I, Chuck. So do I.
Hey, don't worry about it, buddy.
I'm a pro.
Everything is gonna be just fine, okay?
Wait, wait, wait.
Chuck, look, you did a good job,
but I'll take it from here, okay?
Yeah, but you know what?
Um, Ned is really uptight.
So maybe I should go over there
and tell him that you're taking over.
Kind of put him at ease
so he doesn't get upset.
-You've developed a little trust, did you?
-Yeah.
Okay, well, yeah. Good idea.
Go-- Good.
Ned, you have to listen to me
very carefully.
This guy Mauser, he's no good.
He's not a good guy.
-We cannot trust him.
-Why not?
We've to let everybody out
of the store right now.
Well, if I let everyone out,
then I won't have bargaining chips.
I can't go to jail, Chuck.
Okay, look, the people I was talking about,
the people that can help?
They work for the government, see?
They'll protect me.
That's the only bargaining chip
that you need.
You have to trust me.
You need to let everyone go.
I haven't let you down yet, have I?
Thanks, Chuck. I'll take it from here.
Okay, okay.
Well, Ned?
It's time the rubber hits the road.
What do you say we make a deal?
Hmm?
[ALL SHOUTING INDISTINCTLY]
OFFICER: Here you go, sir.
-Hey, no, that's okay, that's okay.
-You need medical attention.
-No, I'm fine, let's end this.
How's it look in there?
He seemed to calm down
after he talked to his wife.
Yeah, where is she?
I mean, you didn't bring her down here?
Wife, what wife?
There's no record of Ned being married.
He's right.
There's no record of him being married.
We saw him make a call, trace it and see
if we can find out who he's speaking to.
DEVON:
Look, boys.
This guy is tired and frazzled.
I say we take him out.
Anyone else play ball in college?
-Linebacker.
-I did not.
I played "Madden" on PlayStation 3,
does that count?
Be bold, Morgan.
-All right, I'm in.
-All right.
Listen up, it's called the picket fence.
Big Mike and I'll be the flanks, all right?
Morgan, you're the sacrificial lamb.
Jeff, Lester, coming up from behind.
Why are we coming from behind?
It seems awkward.
-I need everybody--
-Hey, hey, what are you doing?
Well, we're taking this guy out. You in?
No, and neither are you.
This situation's way too dangerous.
Please, Devon.
If you love Ellie, don't do this.
Okay, Chuck. You win.
Chuck, can I talk to you a minute?
[SIGHS]
Remember, don't be awesome.
Hey.
Well, Chuck. Looks like Ned and I
worked the whole thing out.
That's great. I'll just go tell everybody
that we can leave.
No, no, no, not just yet, but soon.
First you and I
need to work something out on our own.
I don't understand.
You see, Fulcrum knows
John Casey's NSA.
Person he called is in the Buy More now.
MAUSER:
The, uh, yogurt girl's CIA.
Oh, my God. Chuck.
MAUSER:
We've lost agents to these two.
We knew they were here protecting
someone, we didn't know who.
So we caused a little ruckus.
Sent Ned inside to see
who they would rush to protect.
Turns out they're protecting you.
[CHUCKLES]
I have no idea
what you're talking about, lieutenant.
Do you see, uh, Ned over there?
I'd hate to see him
shoot your pretty little sister...
...if he thought you were not
cooperating with me.
Look, um, I'm just an analyst.
Okay, please, don't hurt anyone.
Chuck, you're way more
than just an analyst.
We did a background check on you.
Turns out you were
college roommates with Bryce Larkin.
The same Bryce Larkin
that stole the Intersect from us.
-Bryce Larkin is dead.
-And I'm done negotiating.
[GUN COCKS]
Wait, wait, wait, stop him.
Stop him, please stop him.
What do you want?
I wanna know where Bryce Larkin
and the Intersect are.
And if I think you're lying,
even a little bit, your sister dies.
Where's Bryce Larkin?
-I don't know.
-Then I'm really sorry.
But I know where the Intersect is.
Where?
It's right here.
All right, Chuck,
this is how it's gonna play out.
Ned's gonna release
another hostage. You.
Then you and I are gonna go out
and get into an ambulance...
...which will take you
to a secure Fulcrum facility.
Where you'll stay.
I'm never gonna see
my sister again, am I?
No.
Well, then, would you mind
if I said goodbye to her, please?
Okay.
But if you say or do anything
to call attention to me or your situation...
...Ned's gonna shoot her, capiche?
Yeah.
Oh, good, good.
Go ahead.
-They're letting me go.
-Oh, thank God.
[LAUGHS]
[SIGHS]
Goodbye, Ellie.
You know how much I love you, right?
Hey, hey, ha-ha-ha, cheer up.
It will be okay.
You're acting like you're never
gonna see me again, it's okay.
See you in a bit, Chuck.
Listen, there's a time to be brave
and a time to be timid.
This is the time to be brave. Do it.
Right on, bro.
MAUREEN: Sir, sir, over here,
can we get a statement, sir?
Maureen Mitsubishi
back at the Buy More...
...where apparently another hostage
has just been released.
We're not sure of his identity,
but he does appear to be unharmed.
Fulcrum's got Chuck.
-Everybody ready?
-Yeah.
Hands in.
[IN UNISON]
Break.
-Oh, I hope they're not doing anything risky.
-Morgan's with them.
Trust me,
you've got nothing to worry about.
[SCREAMING]
ELLIE:
Oh.
CASEY:
Go, go, go.
[BOTH PANTING]
They're getting away with Chuck.
[CASEY GRUNTS]
[PANTING]
MAUSER:
Get back here!
He's breathing, he's fine.
That was really stupid, Devon.
Well, at least he's not afraid
to take risks, like Morgan.
Finally, this is getting interesting.
Okay, who's next?
You?
[SHOUTS]
[MIKE GRUNTS]
[GUN COCKS]
MORGAN:
Anna, did you see that?
Lester, are you okay?
[WHIMPERS]
That was so brave.
In times of crisis,
a man needs to step up.
Come on, be a man. I think they say.
[SHOUTS]
-Lieutenant Mauser's Fulcrum, so is Ned.
-I know.
-Everyone in the store is in danger.
-Our team's moving in now.
I need you to run back
as fast as you can to the Castle.
-I can't leave you alone.
-Your safety's more important.
Now, leave and don't turn back. Go.
Go.
[GRUNTING AND SHOUTING]
[GROANS]
[CHUCKLES]
[GUN COCKS]
[SIGHS]
You may have beaten me,
Agent Walker, but Fulcrum's won.
I know Chuck Bartowski's the Intersect.
Chuck's secret is safe.
And you're going straight
to a CIA detention facility...
...never to be seen or heard from again.
Well, you go right ahead, Agent Walker.
Arrest me.
[SIGHS]
But say goodbye to Chuck.
You see, I'm not like those
other Fulcrum agents.
They'll do whatever it takes to find me.
And when they do...
...every Fulcrum agent we have
is gonna know Chuck's the Intersect.
It's gonna be the end
of his pathetic existence.
So take me in, Agent Walker.
I'm ready to go.
[GRUNTS]
-How you doing?
-Okay.
I thought I was gonna lose you there
for a minute.
Ha-ha-ha. It was hell, but I survived.
-Hey, you hungry?
-I could eat.
DEVON:
Ellie.
I thought you'd like to know
that I cancelled my trip.
Are you sure?
I thought you needed more excitement.
I've had all the excitement I need, honey.
-Thanks.
-For what?
Staying with me.
I would've been alone tonight.
Mm, me too.
Gross.
[CHUCKLES]
Chuck.
[CHUCK SIGHS]
SARAH:
Mm.
It's okay, you're safe.
I got the Fulcrum agent.
-What happened to him?
-I arrested him.
Casey's taking him
to a secure facility as we speak.
It's okay, he's gonna go to jail.
He'll never bother you again.
DEVON:
Merry Christmas, guys.
SARAH: Merry Christmas.
ELLIE: Merry Christmas, ha-ha-ha.
Merry Christmas, Chuck.
It's not gonna be one
we're gonna forget soon, ha, ha.
Yeah.
ELLIE: Oh, that looks fantastic on you.
-Thank you, ha, ha.
ELLIE: I'm so glad that it fit.
-Yeah, me too.
Let me ask you something.
What do you do when you see
your girlfriend do something so horrific...
...it gets permanently burned
into your brain?
[MORGAN SCOFFS]
I don't know, buddy.
But I know exactly what you mean.
[ENGLISH SDH]