Whoa! Whoa, whoa!
No.
[MUFFLED GRUNTS]
Freeze. Drop him.
Take your masks off. Do it.
Untie him.
MORGAN: Stay still. Hold still.
-Aah!
-Man up, Charles.
-Why would you do this to me?
I'm sorry. It was a practice run for when
we kidnap Awesome for his bachelor party.
You guys aren't invited.
What finer way to be invited
than to kidnap the guest of honor?
A bachelor party is a mythical place
where booze and women are free.
It's Xanadu.
MORGAN:
That's the-- We were just--
-I had that dream.
LESTER: We were--
No, no, no. I think that-- Oh, my God.
Stop. Jonathan, stop.
MORGAN: Please--
LESTER: Stop.
CHUCK:
Okay. I'm going to bed.
[TV BEEPS]
BECKMAN [OVER TV]:
Chuck?
Ahem. Bartowski?
General. Hey, what are you--?
What are you--?
I wanted a private word with you.
Pardon the intrusion.
On this moment, or my life in general?
I'd like to know if your relationship
with Agent Walker...
-...is compromising your job performance.
-How do you mean? What does that mean?
-Has your situation gotten too complicated?
-What? With Sarah?
No. God, no.
No. Sarah Walker is a pleasure
to work with.
A delight, even.
I want facts.
I don't care about your feelings.
-What feelings?
-These feelings.
-Sarah, you wanna go on a date?
-A real date?
You're the greatest thing
that's ever happened to me.
I wouldn't mind some time
to sort out my feelings.
It's my mother's charm bracelet.
My dad gave it to her.
I'm crazy about you,
and always have been.
My job is to make sure you're protected...
...without interloping
emotional complications from my team.
We're going to have to do a 49-B.
Okay, if you could tell me what a 49-B is,
that would help--
[ALARM CLOCK BEEPING]
[KNOCKING ON DOOR]
DEVON:
Chuckster.
Time to flush out your system, dude.
Oh! Oh!
God, no. I'm good with my clog.
Hey, about your bachelor party.
Do you still wanna do that camping thing,
or, uh, something more traditional?
Hey, Chuck, uh, this came back in the mail.
It's from Dad.
I'm so sorry, Ellie. I'll keep searching.
You know what? Don't worry about it.
You can't get disappointed
if you don't have expectations, right?
So, um, I was overhearing
about the bachelor party.
For the record,
I don't care what you guys do...
-...because I trust you completely.
-Which is why I'm marrying you.
Oh, pbbt. What is that?
That is the taste of a healthy colon.
[GROANS SOFTLY]
-Who's General Beckman?
-What?
Video-game stuff.
Yeah, it's video-game stuff.
Top-secret stuff that I'd be breaking
all kinds of rules to talk about it.
-Morgan, huh?
-Yeah.
So if Morgan's General Beckman,
who are you?
Uh, well, I am Special Agent Carmichael.
Huh.
Carmichael. I like it.
Sarah? Hey, Sarah, I messed up.
General Beckman, she called me,
asked me about our relationship.
And you know that conversation,
the one where I might've...
...maybe mentioned
that I'm crazy about you?
Well, I tried to cover,
but I'm not so sure that she bought it.
-Wha--? Where's Sarah?
-I'm Agent Alex Forrest.
General Beckman sent me. I'm your 49-B.
I'm sure you've all had a chance
to welcome Agent Alex Forrest.
-Of course, general.
BECKMAN: Then on to the matter at hand.
We're familiar with the elusive leader
of a terrorist group...
...who has been hiding
in the Afghani caves for years:
Hassan Khalid.
BOTH:
I dream of finding him.
A member of Khalid's inner circle
is this man, Rashad Ahmad.
Ahmad is privy
to all of Khalid's nefarious plans.
While on banking business for Khalid
in Los Angeles...
...a man we believe to be Ahmad
had a heart attack.
He needs a pacemaker...
...and has checked into a hospital
under the pseudonym Harry Lime.
-You believe this man to be Ahmad?
BECKMAN: That is the mission.
Intelligence has only been able to obtain
grainy satellite images of Ahmad.
Mr. Bartowski, using his unique skill set...
...must infiltrate the hospital
to confirm Ahmad's identity.
-Questions?
-Sounds straightforward, general.
Yeah, I have a question.
Yeah, just a teeny little one.
What exactly is a 49-B?
BECKMAN [OVER MONITOR]:
Mind fielding that one, Agent Walker?
Agent Forrest is here
to assess my performance.
And during the evaluation period...
...she will assume the role
of the asset's handler.
Thank you. That will be all.
What...?
What is this all about?
I'm sorry. To discuss this further
would be a breach of protocol.
"To discuss this would be
a breach of protocol?"
Is it possible that someone kidnapped Sarah
and replaced her with some soulless replica?
-Wanna talk about your feelings?
-Please.
Wrong. That's what got the 49-B involved
in the first place.
-How come--?
-Chuck.
We are here to plead our case
about Awesome's party.
Not now. I'm in the middle of something.
The world revolves around the sun, Charles,
not you.
-Ooh, astronomy snap.
-Okay, hold--
It's just that--
We'd just like you to reconsider.
Reconsider what?
You guys aren't even invited.
[CHUCKLES]
You tell him or I will.
Jeff and I,
we've never been to a bachelor party.
Never known anyone qualified enough
to land a woman for life.
-So please, please.
-Please, please, please.
LESTER: Please do this.
-No and no.
Okay, how about this? As a plus...
...since Big Mike has been dating
my mother, he's made me lock up.
So we can use this place for the party,
save cash...
...and guess what,
spend it on lady dancers.
[SCATTING]
Pow.
-Lady dancers.
LESTER: Pow.
-Chucky Chucky Chuck.
-Hey now. Hey now.
-We're talking serious--
-The answer's no.
Hey. Oh, please. Don't say no.
Say you'll wrap your mind around it.
-Hey, does the new girl know about, uh--?
-No.
She won't know that information
unless her position becomes permanent.
What do you mean, permanent?
It's not gonna happen.
The 49-B will come in, make her findings,
and be on her way.
Hey, uh....
-I'm sorry, Sarah.
-For what?
I didn't mean to get you in trouble at work.
I didn't know I was being taped that much.
-No, it's fine, really.
-I've just been stressed out.
I promised Ellie I'd find our dad
to walk her down the aisle.
I've tried everything.
It's like he's fallen off the face of the Earth.
You've got clearance.
You mind running dad's name
through the Castle computer?
-That's impossible.
-Damn right.
If Agent Walker did that,
not only would she be fired...
...but potentially face charges of
misappropriation of government intelligence.
Enough personal time.
We have work to do.
The asset and I will enter the facility,
obtain uniforms to assimilate...
...and attempt to confirm
Ahmad's identity.
-Is there anything I can do, Casey?
-I got it.
-Casey, uh, what is that?
-You confirm Harry Lime is Ahmad.
I'll sneak into the high-security area where
the equipment and donor organs are kept.
Why? Aren't we just gonna arrest him?
Don't underestimate the gamesmanship
of the U.S. government.
I'll place this GLG-4000 inside
Ahmad's pacemaker before it's implanted.
When he returns to Hassan Khalid's
secret cave, he'll be a high-tech human bug.
Not only will we know the secret location,
but we'll be one step ahead of their plans.
[IN UNISON]
Checkmate.
Get the door.
Are you crazy? I can't go in here.
This is where Ellie and Awesome work.
We checked their schedules. Ellie's not
working today, Devon is mid-surgery.
Hey, you're here to observe.
Stay in the van, Walker. That's an order.
[WOMAN SPEAKING INDISTINCTLY
OVER PA]
Aha. And what were you little kids
doing in there?
A little hanky-panky? Ha-ha-ha--
[TRANQ GUN FIRES]
What? Why? Why would you do that?
Relax, I only tranqed her.
She'll be awake in six to eight hours.
Now, grab a leg.
Oh, hey. I didn't think you were
on call today, Dr. Bartowski.
Well, they keep switching
my shifts around.
See you.
That grandma was no threat.
-I don't get why you decided--
-I don't decide.
Protocol dictates my actions.
-Chuck?
-Shh, shh, shh.
Your sister is 30 feet northeast of you.
Doctor?
ELLIE: Yeah?
-You forgot your pen.
ELLIE: Thank you.
-Now or never.
[WHISPERS]
Ahem. It's him.
-Are you his doctor?
-[IN NORMAL VOICE] Of course.
Am I not wearing a doctor's coat?
Who else would I be
if not one of this man's doctors?
Doctor, I am Harry Lime's private physician,
Dr. Mohammad Zamir.
-Ah, doctor.
-Doctor.
And doctor.
Nurse, would you excuse us for a moment?
I'd like to consult the doctor privately.
Yes. We'll be discussing doctor things
that only doctors understand. Please go.
-Please don't go.
FORREST: Ahem.
Be right outside, doctor.
Major, what's your 20?
-In position.
-Identification affirmative.
-Roger that.
-Proceed.
[BEEPS]
Hey. You.
Yeah.
Hysterectomy in 806
didn't make it to the toilet.
You mind?
You got it.
Ahem. Just....
Ow. Ahem.
Well, heart sounds appear to be normal.
For a patient with this type
of atypical cardio cardiac condition.
You should know that this patient
is a very important man.
Well, I took an oath
to treat my first patient...
...with the same kind of care
as every subsequent patient.
It's a very dangerous job
to be the surgeon of a very important man.
You understand my meaning, doctor?
I'll do the best job
that I know how to do.
Your life depends on it.
If I have to eat an apple a day to keep that
doctor away, then bring on the fresh fruit.
Hey, the security system's been updated.
I'll either need 40 minutes
to decrypt the code or 4 ounces of C4.
Maybe I could take out some doctor
and steal his card key.
I like the cut of your jib.
Wow, you two are a match made
in a very frightening part of heaven.
All we'll need is some idiot doctor with
a key card to get us into the restricted area.
No way. No, no way. Absolutely not.
Not Awesome.
No. Uh-uh. I am not getting
my soon-to-be brother-in-law...
...involved in a government mission.
No way.
Fortunately, you, like felons and children,
don't get a vote.
Is there a different doctor?
This mission does put Chuck's cover close
to the action, risking potential exposure.
The words I was thinking just came out
of Sarah's mouth. Connected professionally.
No time. Only a couple docs have that card
key. Your sister's Ken doll's one of them.
Well, how are you gonna do that?
You can't just walk up and ask for it.
-I'll handle things my way.
-No, wait. There will be no tranqing.
I think I might know how
we can have our spy cake and eat it too.
DEVON: What the--?
MAN: Hey, careful.
Let's go!
ALL:
Surprise!
[CHUCKLES]
-You guys are awesome.
-To the bachelor.
[ALL CHEERING]
-Whoa, what are you doing?
-Visual souvenirs, dude.
He does quite a bit of scrapbooking.
You gotta be kidding me. Listen to me.
What happens in the Buy More,
stays in the Buy More.
Oh, right, yes. No, I got it. I'm sorry.
Bachelor-party virgin.
-Lock it down.
-Okay, okay.
[CAMERA CLICKS]
Hey, hey, hey.
Uh, happy bachelor party there, captain.
Well, thanks for your help throwing it,
General Beckman. Heh, heh.
Nothing gets by me. Ha, ha.
Okay.
Based on my observations...
...Agent Walker is too emotionally entwined
with the asset.
Her decisions weren't made
with respect to established protocol.
She always places
the subject's feelings above orders.
-Is that your final assessment?
-It is.
Agent Walker.
Thank you for your dedication
to this mission.
General, please, I--
But as of right now,
your services are officially terminated.
Report back to Langley at 0900.
Please take good care of him.
I'll do my job if that's what you mean.
Well, I'll be on my way as soon
as I say goodbye to him.
I don't think so.
You've already done enough damage here.
Chuck's my mission now.
No further contact. That's an order.
To finding the love of your life.
[CHEERS]
Happy bachelor party, my friend.
We got you half a dozen $5 foot-longs
from Subway, that's six feet of meat.
-Five. I ate a foot.
-What is the matter with you?
Thanks, boys.
Gonna be quite a tasty event.
Thank you.
-Here we go.
-See? This is what I'm talking about.
He's gonna be so drunk
when you steal his key, he won't notice.
No tranqing necessary.
-How we gonna distract him?
-I'm one step ahead of you, my friend.
I had Jeff hire
some exotic female entertainment.
Hmm?
-At least the sandwiches are fresh.
-Wait, Jeffrey, isn't that your sister?
She gave us a deal.
[PHONE RINGS]
-Hello?
-Hey, babe, it's me.
Chuck and the boys kidnapped me
for my bachelor party.
ELLIE [OVER PHONE]:
Wow, lucky you.
I am lucky knowing
what's waiting for me at home.
Hey, great party, huh?
ELLIE: That's charming for a man
so close to temptation.
CASEY:
Damn it.
How could I be tempted by hamburger
when I have steak?
[OVER PHONE]
Seriously, babe, I love you.
All right, you've sucked up enough.
-I trust you. Have fun.
-Thanks, honey.
Got Woodcomb's wallet,
but came up empty.
[OVER PHONE]
No card key.
-Must still be around his neck.
-I have to get it another way.
FORREST [OVER PHONE]:
Don't worry. Got a backup plan.
You're still here, Walker.
I thought I made myself clear.
I'm just tying up some loose ends.
Make it quick.
-Freeze, boys. You're all in trouble.
-Five-0. Gotta flush my stash.
No, don't, Jeff. This is what you've been
waiting for. This is Xanadu.
I understand one of you's been
a naughty, naughty boy.
Me. Oh, my God, pick me. I'm so bad.
I'm a bad person.
I'm a terrible person. Ouch.
I broke eight and a half commandments
on the way to work this morning.
This is your guy. This is him.
-I'm gonna have to strip search you.
-Oh!
-Help?
MORGAN: No.
DEVON: A little help here.
-No, you're under arrest.
I can't help you.
LESTER: This is the law.
-The law.
-We're not gonna go against the law.
-Be gentle with him. Oh, my....
Are you kidding me?
I know the guys
probably put you up to this.
But we really don't have
to be alone in here.
We just-- Oh, my.
-Wait, wait.
-Why don't you just take this off?
That way,
nothing's gonna come between us.
I can't. I lose it and I, uh-- I get fired.
Ooh.
DEVON:
No, no, no. Hold on. Hold on, stop.
Stop.
I love my fiancée.
I would never do anything
to jeopardize that.
I guess romance is alive and well
and living in Burbank.
[TRANQ GUN FIRES
THEN DEVON GRUNTS]
No, no, no.
I said no tranqing.
That is not no tranqing.
Can't you keep
your stinking CIA darts out of people?
[GROANS]
Good work.
Now I can access the area
and plant the bug before Ahmad's surgery.
-I'm trying to sell it for the friends.
-Whoa, have I no rights?
You can't just go around willy-nilly,
knocking out my family members.
-Looks like we can.
-Sarah never would've done this.
-You've gone too far.
-Back off.
-What are you gonna do?
-I'm calling the general.
-Is that so?
-No one's calling.
This 49-B stuff is over. From now on,
the only person I work with is Sarah.
Walker's gone. She's been dismissed.
What?
-What are you talking about?
-I'm your new handler.
[PHONE VIBRATING]
BECKMAN: With the use of
Dr. Woodcomb's card key...
...Major Casey entered
the hospital's restricted area...
...and planted the GLG-4000
on Ahmad's pacemaker.
-General Beckman?
-One moment, Mr. Bartowski.
Turn up the volume.
[HEARTBEAT POUNDING]
-That is the sound of success.
-General?
Soon Ahmad and his men
will be on their way back...
...to Khalid's Afghani hideout and we can
begin our covert surveillance in earnest.
General, I understand
this is an important mission, I do.
But what about Sarah?
How can she be gone?
-It's the way it is.
-No.
Why didn't you tell me
that this could happen?
I was under the impression
Forrest was here to evaluate Sarah.
-You lied to me.
-It's a job, Chuck.
No, for you it's a job.
For me, it's my life.
BECKMAN: We disclosed everything
that was pertinent to you.
That's the way
the National Security Agency operates.
Get used to it.
I'm gonna go clean my weapons.
[GROANS]
[COMPUTER BEEPS]
When it comes to security,
one can never be too cautious.
[BEEPING]
Who is Rashad's doctor?
One of his surgeons put a bug inside him.
Dr. Devon Woodcomb.
You two go bring me the doctor.
When the doctor woke up this morning,
he didn't know that today--
I'm gonna die.
Oh, my God, I'm going to die.
I would love to feel sorry for you,
but you brought this one on yourself.
How'd I get so wasted?
I don't remember a thing.
Well, you drank a little bit, you cut loose.
No harm done.
I remember our neighbor John Casey
carrying you home at 4 in the morning...
...smelling like booze and cheap hairspray.
Does that ring a bell for you?
Honey, I mean, please,
don't even say the word bell.
-Honey?
-Huh?
-Did I have my key card on me last night?
ELLIE: What?
-Did you take my key card off me or not?
-No, I didn't take your key card off.
-I'm sure it's here somewhere.
-Oh, God.
It's always around your neck,
under your shirt.
-Why did your shirt come off?
-Uh....
Do you want to tell me
if your pants stayed on?
Ellie, please, will you just help me
look for the key card?
Guys, guys, it'll turn up. I just know it.
Yeah, I'm really sorry that you don't
remember what happened last night.
I hope whatever it was, it was worth it.
Dude, I wish I had a do-over
for last night.
I'd take it all back.
Can you believe Walker?
-What about her?
-Being all wrapped up in the asset.
Clearly her feelings
have jeopardized your missions.
You must be relieved that she's gone.
Things can now finally be professional.
Agent Forrest, for the record, I--
[HEARTBEAT STOPS
THEN ALARM BLARES]
-Something's wrong with our equipment--
-Or something's wrong with Ahmad.
Hey, Casey, it's me.
Look, we gotta get Awesome his key card
or he's gonna be in trouble.
MAN:
We must find this doctor at once.
Which one is his apartment?
CHUCK: Oh, this is not awesome.
Very not awesome.
Okay.
[POUNDING ON DOOR]
Hi, I'm Dr. Woodcomb. Can I--?
[MUFFLED GRUNTS]
[BEEPING]
Government issue.
Doesn't make any-- This--
Oh, my God, it smells like heaven.
Okay, that means either someone's
baking sugar cookies or that is--
-Morgan.
-Ellie.
-I need to ask you a favor.
-Anything.
-Anything. You can have my first-born.
-Heh.
I need to know what happened last night
at Devon's bachelor party.
Come on, El, you can't ask me that.
There's a bro code.
Please, Morgan.
I'm sorry, I can't. I have to lock it down.
I just-- That's what I-- Listen to me, I....
-Oh, my God.
LESTER: I know.
Can you believe our first bachelor party
was so freaking awes--?
Ellie. Wait, wait, wait, Ellie.
Ellie. Ellie. Ellie. Elizabeth. Eleanor. Elton.
[GRUNTS]
-I got nothing.
-Me neither.
Casey, I can't get in.
I don't have access.
-She's off the assignment.
-Look, I think Chuck's in trouble.
He never goes anywhere
without his phone.
CASEY:
She's right.
Now, Forrest, I was gonna say earlier,
I disagree with your assessment.
-About what?
-Walker.
She's a pro. Not only that,
she's the best damn partner I ever had.
I found this when I went
to say goodbye to Chuck.
Which directly disobeyed an order.
You were fired for exactly this reason.
Then there's nothing stopping me
from kicking your ass.
FORREST:
Chuck's in the courtyard. He's fine.
We lost the signal from Ahmad's heart.
Gotta be a connection
between the disappearance and Chuck's.
Isn't the GLG-4000 specifically designed
to track deep inside the Afghani caves?
You'd need six feet of steel
to block that signal.
This is the last location
his heart registered before going off-grid.
Overlay the satellite image.
SARAH:
Wait a minute.
CASEY: A bank vault.
-Yeah, that would do it.
CASEY:
Good work, Walker.
Okay, Dr. Woodcomb.
Time for you to remove the bug
you placed inside my friend.
If you don't save him...
...nothing can save you.
The patient is now fully under.
[CLEARS THROAT]
Cool, cool. Good, good. Well done there.
That's how we do things.
I'm gonna need to take a minute
just so that I can center myself, if you will.
I, uh, need a mellow headspace
when I operate.
-It's how--
-Quit stalling, Dr. Woodcomb.
I'm out of practice, honestly.
Maybe if you could do it?
Cut him open, or I'll cut you open.
Oh! Ow! Argh.
Oh, my God. I'm bleeding.
-Oh, my God, I'm bleeding. I'm bleeding.
-Come on.
I'm sorry.
I get woozy at the sight of blood.
-A surgeon who's afraid of blood?
-I know. Little ironic, right?
[SILENCED GUNSHOT]
SARAH: Chuck.
-Get the door.
Get the door. Get the door.
SARAH:
Chuck.
-Who the hell is Chuck?
-Huh? Chuck? No clue. I have no clue.
-I'm-- I am Dr. Woodcomb.
-Oh, yeah?
Or Devon or doc
or sometimes Captain Awesome.
But I have no idea who this Chuck is.
-Oh, you mean that Chuck.
-You're a dead man, Chuck.
[GRUNTING]
Now Chuck is locked inside
with Interpol's most wanted.
It is your job to protect him, damn it.
I've got nitroglycerin
and a blasting cap in the van.
-I'll have this door off in no time.
-Hold on. I saw a nitrous setup in there.
You're gonna bust the door open
and kill Chuck.
Come on. Come on.
What makes you think
he's not already dead?
Come here.
Aah! Aah!
[YELLS]
[ZAMIR CHUCKLING]
What?
What? What is it?
I forgot why I was mad at you.
[LAUGHS NERVOUSLY]
I was....
I was gonna cut you.
That's odd. I think I hear Chuck laughing.
-Here, give me the walkie.
-I'll handle it.
You're lying.
No, I'm not. Think about it.
Ladybugs can't all be ladies.
I mean, that's just crazy.
How would we get little ladybugs,
know what I mean?
FORREST [OVER RADIO]:
Chuck, can you hear me?
Oh, your pocket's talking.
Hey, can I get that?
-Yeah, get it.
-All right, thank you.
-Hi. Oh, hi.
-Hi.
Hi, yeah, I'm fine. I'm fine.
I'm also high from nitrous,
but so is my man Zamir here, so--
I'm not coming out until you find Sarah
and you bring her back.
That's right. Stand your ground.
Like Hassan Khalid.
Hey, where is that guy, anyway?
Because I haven't seen him around.
He's in the Eastern Karakorum caves.
-All right.
-Yeah.
-Good for him.
-Nobody knows.
CHUCK [OVER RADIO]: He's a bad dude.
-Hey, Chuck, turn off the gas, idiot.
-You inhale too much of that, it'll kill you.
-We're gonna die.
[BOTH LAUGHING]
You're gonna die.
Open this door right now.
-No. Look, I'm not listening to you, okay?
-This isn't working.
I can't risk this going any further.
I'm getting the nitro.
Forrest, we can do this your way
or we can actually save the asset.
Look at that.
-Chuck, get up.
-Sarah.
[HISSING STOPS]
Is it really you or am I super stoned?
Uh, both. Heh.
BECKMAN: Both Rashad Ahmad
and Dr. Zamir are in custody.
Though the mission didn't go
according to plan...
...Chuck was able to ascertain the
hidden location of terrorist Hassan Khalid.
-Thank you, Agent Forrest.
-Just doing my job, general.
Agent Walker, despite your heroism...
...you have directly disobeyed
several orders--
CHUCK:
Wait, general. Um....
I'm sorry, but isn't the important part of
being my handler making sure I stay alive?
-It's okay, Chuck.
-No, it's not.
Let him finish.
Thanks.
Um, general, what I'm trying to say...
...is that I think that maybe because
my relationship with Sarah is so....
You know, we're close.
We care about each other.
That's why I'm trying to say.
And I know it's not protocol or whatever...
...but it's those feelings
that wound up saving my life.
Agent Forrest diagnosed
your emotional connection as a liability.
But I suppose it can also be
an asset to the, well, asset.
You may resume your post, Agent Walker.
We hope not to see you too soon,
Agent Forrest.
That's all.
Um.... No, this isn't what you think.
Yes, it is, Chuck.
It's exactly what I think it is.
I can't believe
that you were covering for him.
Nothing happened.
He didn't do anything. I swear it.
Chuck, I saw the photos, okay?
I'm sorry.
I know you're trying to protect him.
Bro code, whatever.
But, Chuck, I am your sister.
You're supposed to protect me.
[KNOCKING ON DOOR]
Hey, Sarah. I am freaking out, okay?
I don't know who to talk to.
I don't wanna get you in trouble.
It's okay. This is my residence.
-There is no surveillance.
-I don't know what to do.
Ever since you guys rolled into town,
my life has been spinning out of control.
My whole world is about juggling lies.
It's like this.
I bet this is a what? A submachine gun?
No, it dries my hair.
Okay, fine. But everything else
is completely screwed up.
I just wanna be able
to tell Ellie the truth.
About who I am and what I do.
I can't believe how much the United States
government has hurt the people that I love.
Well, maybe it's time for
the United States government to help you.
Chuck. You saved my life, man.
Thanks for finding my key card.
Dude?
Special Agent Carmichael?
Well, you, uh, probably had to break
a few rules, huh?
Go on. Knock.
I couldn't find him.
The man didn't want to be found.
I mean, you had to illegally access
the government's master database to--
Chuck...
...it'll be good to see him.
I'm sorry.
[DOOR OPENS]
Dad?
[ENGLISH SDH]