[GRUNTS]
-Get up.
-I'm actually good down here.
Grow up, Morgan Grimes.
You were spying on me in Gym class.
-I'm going to kick your--
-Help.
CHUCK:
Don't worry, Morgan, I got your back.
Suzy, I'll take it from here.
Morgan, maybe you should stay away
from girls for like 15 years.
MORGAN:
All right, check it out.
A picture of your ex-girlfriend? That--?
That's why I had to come in here
on my coffee break?
Anna Melinda Wu.
-Five-two, 96 pounds, of Chinese descent.
-Why are we in here talking about your ex?
Because, today,
I need your help on a mission.
What kind of mission?
-A spy mission, Chuck.
-Can you handle it?
See, I'm afraid
Anna may be seeing a new guy.
Whoa, whoa, hey. Time out.
-You want me to spy on Anna?
-Of course not, Chuck.
You're not skilled in spy craft.
No, that's where Lester and Jeff come in.
Does it shock you that 80 percent
of my encounters with women...
...have been completely without
their knowledge?
Honestly, I'm more surprised
by the other 20 percent, Jeff.
I know you're going through a tough time,
but I don't feel comfortable...
...stalking another human being.
Dude, it's not stalking, okay?
It's caring enough about someone to learn
things about them they won't tell you.
-Which is stalking.
-And I really need you on this one, so....
ELLIE:
Please, Devon. I really need you.
DEVON: Only got a couple minutes,
but if you don't mind a little drive-through...
-...when you're used to fine dining--
-No, no, no. Not for that.
I just need your help.
This is our to-do list for our wedding.
Ooh, less fun.
There's not enough hours
for me to do everything myself...
...plus work night shifts, plus be a sister
and a friend and a girlfriend.
-Fiancée.
-My point is...
...that I need you to start
pulling your weight around here.
So you can deal with the flowers,
the music and the cake.
-I will handle the rest.
-Babe, babe.
A marriage is a partnership,
a wedding should be too.
Yeah.
[LAUGHS]
Whoa.
What is this place?
LESTER: Whatever Jeff doesn't guzzle down
his throat, he spends on spy gear.
-Incredible, right?
-Incredibly creepy.
Hey, ladies. Let's go. Man your posts.
CASEY: Babysitting the freak show.
This should be enlightening.
[CAR ALARM BEEPS]
-We have visual acquisition of the target.
-We got ears on.
Subject is on the move.
Idiots on the move.
Guys. Guys, we can't do this.
We shouldn't be doing this right now.
-I mean, we're like crazy stalkers.
LESTER: Shh! Charles, please.
What the hell
are these crazy stalkers up to?
Looks like some pretty decent spy work.
Would you think about
what you're doing?
I know what I'm doing.
I'm getting answers, man.
-But there are other ways of doing that.
-No, we tried cloning Anna's cell...
...but she's got a CDMA carrier,
so we couldn't copy the SIM card.
Wait, wait, wait.
There's a guy just showed up.
LESTER: Morgan, let me see,
let me see, let me see.
Ooh.
Maybe it's her brother.
[SIGHS]
JEFF:
Still....
-Could be her brother.
-All right, let's pack up. Abort mission.
I can't compete with this guy.
He's got healthy hair, a clean smile,
and a killer car.
Look at him.
I mean, he's my worst nightmare.
Yeah, I trust your instincts, pal.
Uh, the general will be available...
...to talk about the Jason Wang situation
momentarily.
Hey, how come you guys have these
in here, anyway? Do you play?
They're not toys. If you pop the top,
they're white-phosphorous grenades.
-They can melt iron.
-Okey-dokey.
What are these? Mini flamethrowers?
Uh-uh.
Mint-flavored knockout spray.
Oh. Do you think I can have one of these?
I'm always, you know,
vulnerable out there.
[GROWLS]
Jason Wang, Anna Wu's new boyfriend.
Wang's a car importer,
and while he has no criminal record...
...he runs with a dangerous crew
of local Triad gangsters.
A gang responsible for smuggling drugs
and weapons in and out of Los Angeles.
Correct, Agent Walker. We've been
watching the local Triad for a while...
...but didn't know about Wang
before Chuck's flash.
Well, you're welcome.
You really don't have to thank me.
Not that you are thanking me. I guess
you're just making a statement. Continue.
BECKMAN [ON MONITOR]: Determine
the depth of Wang's connection to Triad.
Chuck, use your social connection
to infiltrate the suspect.
Um....
Excuse me, general, but just to clarify...
...you want me to befriend my best friend's
ex-girlfriend's new boyfriend?
-Is there a problem, Mr. Bartowski?
-No. Nope. No. Not a--
Not a problem.
I got a big problem here.
[BEEPING]
[MOANS]
[BEEPING STOPS]
DEVON:
Sleep well last night, Chuck?
What--?
Actually, no. I was having nightmares
about people spying on me...
...which now feels all too real.
My point was that
while you're still here asleep...
...I'm just now getting home from work.
Tough night. Saving lives
can get pretty gnarly sometimes.
-Tell me about it.
-So, what are your plans for today?
Well, you know, I mean,
I probably have to go to work.
-You know?
-Mm-hm.
And, uh, I might get a pizza with Sarah
afterwards...
-...or something, you know?
-Cakewalk, huh?
Considering your mellow sched...
...what do you say you help out
your soon-to-be brother-in-law?
-What'd you have in mind?
-Ellie wants me to find a band...
...for the wedding, and I know how much
you love music, and how busy I am.
So I was thinking this could be
a win-win situation for both of us.
You want me to find a band
for your wedding?
That'd be awesome, dude.
Thanks a lot.
I can't do this.
How can the general ask me to do this?
Was the woman born
with stars on her shoulders?
Has she never had a friend before?
I can't go hang out with my best friend's ex
and her new boyfriend like it's no big deal.
I understand that this may be difficult
with regard to Morgan--
No, no, not difficult. Not happening. Morgan
has been my best friend since kindergarten.
I don't know what he'd do
if he found out.
I'm sorry, this is not optional.
It's a direct order.
I can't betray my best friend.
How come nobody gets that?
Hmm. Semper fidelis.
Means "always faithful" in the Marines.
In civilian life, it means putting
your friends' well-being above your own.
I salute you for that, Bartowski.
Well done.
Yeah. Thanks, Casey.
Yeah, semper fi, semper fi.
It's a pretty upside-down world...
...when this guy's the one picking up
on the emotional nuances around here.
-Let's go tell the general.
-As much as I respect your code of honor...
...nothing I can do about it.
Orders before honor this time, Bartowski.
Go befriend Anna's new boyfriend.
[RINGS]
So, um, how would you--?
How would you categorize your music?
I mean, who are kind of
your more major influences?
Uh-huh.
You know, I'm actually not familiar
with your Uncle Max's klezmer band, so....
Thank you anyway.
What was that about?
I'm helping Ellie and Awesome
find a band for their wedding.
-Then this, sir, is your lucky day.
JEFF: We'll handle it from here.
-You're gonna help me find a band?
LESTER: You misunderstand.
You've found your band. It is we.
We'll play your sister's big day.
Um, wait. Wait a minute.
You guys have a band?
-Jeff.
-Lester....
BOTH:
Jeffster.
That seems very fitting.
Originally, we were gonna go
with the name Jester...
...but we didn't want people
to associate us with a couple of fools.
Obviously not.
-So, what'd you do last night?
-Went out.
Mm-hm. Where'd you go?
Please, I'm with a customer.
I mean, did you go by yourself?
Um, yeah, my sister,
her taste runs a little more classic.
But you haven't heard us.
Charles, I'd hate to think you'd prejudge us.
Don't be a musical bigot.
Um, I'm sorry, but the answer's no. It just--
It's no. It's a flat-out no. I'm sorry.
[SIGHS]
I'm seeing someone, okay, Morgan?
Well, well, well. The truth comes out.
A new man. Or am I assuming something
here? I mean, it is a man, right?
We all know about
your very, very colorful past.
-God. Grow up, Morgan.
-Oh, please.
Hey. Hey, buddy. There are some customers
over in Refrigerators...
...that might need some helping.
All right, I clocked out a couple hours ago,
so I'm on my own time here.
-Enough, buddy.
-I'd--
You should probably go.
All right, well,
I hope you and your new boyfriend...
...are very unhappy together.
I'm sorry about Morgan.
You've spent your whole life
apologizing for him.
Don't you get it?
He's never going to grow up.
There's a million reasons to love him...
...but, unfortunately,
maturity is not on that list.
So I hear-- I heard that you have a new guy,
a new boyfriend, or, ha-ha-ha, whatever.
Jason's great. Plus, an evening out
doesn't involve me on his handlebars...
...and the Taco Bell drive-through.
I know what you mean.
I've been riding those handlebars for years.
[CHUCK CHUCKLING]
Hey, how would you like to go
on a double-date or something sometime?
-Really?
-Yeah.
Jason's having a party tonight
at his showroom.
And the only thing more expensive
than the champagne will be the cars.
-You and Sarah should stop by.
-Sounds great. Yeah.
-Can't wait to meet your new boyfriend.
-Okay. Wow.
-[WHISPERS] Good job.
-[WHISPERS] I hate you.
Can't believe
I have to meet her new boyfriend.
Chuck and I will enter as our cover couple,
get close to Wang.
See if the skin-covered robot
flashes on anything.
Is that supposed to be me?
That's real nice.
Figure out any connection Wang has
to the Triad.
Try to plant this GLG-20.
I'll be in the van monitoring your activity.
All set? Let's go.
-You know what? I've been thinking--
-Stop that.
If our mission is to betray Morgan...
...I think we should convince Anna
of what she's missing without him.
-There's only one mission here, moron.
-Oh, "moron." That's--
You know, sticks and stones
may break my bones--
-You wanna test that theory, Bartowski?
-Not particularly.
Oh.
Ha-ha-ha.
So, uh, Anna,
what's the occasion for all this?
It's a car preview
for an auction Jason's having tomorrow.
-Sort of an open house for cars.
-Oh.
Anna, these cars
are almost the price of a house.
Your boyfriend must be very successful.
Although, the true measure
of a man's success...
...is not in dollars,
but rather his ability to love.
And if that's true,
Morgan is stinking rich, ha, ha.
-I mean, wouldn't you agree, Sarah?
-I do miss you guys together.
-You do?
-I'm sure Jason's a great guy.
But I'll always think of you and Morgan
as the perfect couple.
CHUCK:
She'd say it all the time:
"Cute couple alert:
Here comes Morgan and Anna."
Cut the infomercial on the bearded loser.
Wang just walked in.
Hi. How are you?
-Ha. That is so strange.
-What's strange?
That I was touching my ear?
No, that's eczema.
Which is totally normal, not strange.
People have it.
No, strange Sarah even thought
about Morgan and I as a couple.
To be honest, I didn't think
you ever really noticed me much.
That's not true, Anna.
I have always thought of you as a friend.
ANNA: Honey, can you come here?
-Oh, excuse me.
Jason, this is Sarah and Chuck.
They're my friends.
JASON: Well, any friend of Anna's....
-Hi.
Though this is our first time meeting,
I feel as though I know...
...every teeny-tiny little thing about you.
All good, I hope. Ha-ha-ha.
MORGAN:
Hello, douche bag.
Okay. Okay.
What do we got here?
No, no, no. It can't be.
Judas.
[PHONE RINGS]
Nerd Herd desk.
Download me on your computer emergency.
Hi. Hi. Uh, this is Ellie Bartowski.
Is my brother around?
Devon and I were in the middle
of our guest list, and the computer froze.
Uh, hey, Ellie.
I think Chuck is out on an install right now.
I'll leave him a message. Okay.
-We'll be right over to fix it.
-Oh, thank you, thank you. That's great.
Wow, it finally pays
to have a brother in mediocre places.
-Um, Jefferson?
-Dude. You almost blew our big chance.
We're going over there to audition.
-What do you mean? Like, right now?
JEFF: Come on, man.
If you had one shot, one opportunity,
to seize everything you ever wanted...
...one moment, would you capture it
or just let it slip?
-Jeffster lives, man.
-Yes.
Great. Fantastic.
Oh-- Oh--
Oh, my God.
I just flashed. Her name is Smooth Lau,
and they're all Triad.
Okay, let's follow them.
Hey, uh, can I talk to you?
I could really use a friend right now.
Oh, sure.
-I'll catch up in a second, sweetie.
-Okay.
[WHISPERS]
Wait for me.
Ha.
-Thanks, Chuckles.
-I'm all ears.
Rebooted it and ran a disk utility.
It's as good as a non-new computer can be.
-Oh, thank God.
-The woman can replace an aortic valve...
...but a frozen computer screen
makes her panic.
Uh, excuse me,
why are you touching my things?
I'm setting up to rock you hard.
-Uh, rock who hard?
-Our audition.
Jeffster is going to play
the biggest gig of your life:
your wedding day.
Is he drunk? You didn't really set them up
to audition, did you?
-Of course not. Chuck must have.
-Sibilance. Check.
-Wait. Did you outsource your to-do list?
-No. I--
I know how much Chuck loves music.
Thought it'd be fun for him.
Oh, you did.
[LESTER VOCALIZING]
Uh, excuse me, guys.
We just have a lot to do.
-Oh, okay. Cool, cool.
-Sure. Sure. We're all set. Let's do this.
-Now or never.
-Hang on.
[LESTER VOCALIZING]
This is what we've always wanted
for Jeffster.
We start at a small venue like this.
Pretty soon, we're playing the big time.
Yeah, sure, we're gonna blow their minds,
but, uh, where does all this lead?
Stadiums? Groupies? Drugs?
Creative differences? And then what?
Jeffster breaks up?
That's you and me, Jeff.
Then what's my fate? Some chambermaid
finds me accidentally asphyxiated...
...while making love to myself?
It's just not worth it.
He's such a tortured artist.
ELLIE:
Mm-hm.
JASON:
Look, I'm having a very important party.
LAU:
Yeah, yeah. Just give me the keys.
JASON: I think I've earned
the right to know what's going on.
What's in the container?
You mind your business, I'll mind mine.
You're getting paid either way.
CHUCK:
Come on, flash.
Flash, damn it.
JASON:
I can.... Oh.
JASON: Look, this is way too risky.
I'm out after this shipment.
LAU: If all goes well, we won't need
another. What are you worried about?
[OVER RADIO] Customs didn't suspect
a thing with that Rolls-Royce in the crate.
CASEY:
Where the hell is he?
THUG: Doors are jammed.
JASON: I'll go get a crowbar.
Hey, wait.
-[OVER RADIO] Quiet. I heard something.
-Damn it, Bartowski.
Did you just hear that?
I like Jason, and, you know, on paper,
he's everything Morgan's not.
-So that's good.
-No, no.
-That's bad.
-Why?
Because Morgan's the guy
you keep comparing him to.
Sarah, you're totally right.
Oh, my God.
Do you think that means I still love him?
MAN [OVER RADIO]: Attention, Security.
We found an intruder on the premises.
Chuck.
MAN [OVER RADIO]:
We got him. Meet us in the parking lot.
Oh, no.
Casey.
-Hey.
-Wait. If Chuck hasn't been captured, then--
-Who's the spy being held by Triad?
Ow. Hey, hey, wait, wait, wait.
Let me explain what I'm--
MORGAN: Hey, hey, hey.
-Oh, my God, that's Morgan.
-They got Morgan.
CASEY: Hey, whoa.
What? We gotta help him.
No. We cannot just start
pulling out weapons.
-We're gonna blow our cover.
-Then what's the next option?
Think it's easy for me to do nothing?
Goes against everything I believe in.
Then don't do nothing. Do something.
We can't just stand here
while my best friend gets tortured or killed.
MORGAN: Hey, come on.
Don't stretch out the hoody.
Fine, if you're not gonna save him...
-...then I will.
SARAH & CASEY: Hey.
Who are you?
Nobody. I'm--
My name is, uh, Marlamin Stoneheart.
I'm a 60th-level gnome warrior.
-The truth.
-Okay, okay. Wow.
-Fifty-ninth level. But I'm like this close.
-I found him spying on us.
You've got one second
to tell me why. One.
Wait, wait, wait! He's not a spy.
-Who the hell are you?
-Wait. What's going on?
ANNA: Morgan?
-This is your ex from Buy More?
-What are you doing here?
-Tell me before I break your neck.
No, no, no. Don't--
You don't wanna do that,
because I know why he's here. He's here....
Chuck....
-He's here because he's stalking you.
-What?
That's right, that's right.
He's not a spy, okay? He's a stalker.
Which is a thin, but very key difference,
in my opinion.
I see why Anna dumped you.
This guy is a profoundly
disturbed individual, okay?
He just can't let go of her.
He's an obsessed,
but totally unthreatening...
...sicko.
Grow up, Morgan Grimes.
-Sicko freak.
LAU: Let him go.
Go secure the shipment.
I don't want any more distractions.
-Well, you just saved your best friend's life.
-At the expense of his dignity.
Well, at least he's still breathing.
Come on.
Look what I just found, boss.
Guess that little freak
wasn't just a stalker after all.
Kill him.
[GRUNTS]
CHUCK:
Hey.
Hey, buddy, you need some help?
Nope. I gotta learn to do things
on my own from now on.
Just....
Morgan, I know that I hurt your feelings,
but I was only trying to protect you.
-We've been friends for a long time, right?
-As long as I can remember, buddy.
-Enjoy the memories.
-What? Buddy.
You got any idea what Ellie and Awesome
thought about Jeffster?
I mean, we didn't fully play out,
but if you could put in a good word....
I don't understand anything
that came out of your mouth.
But I don't care.
I know you think my concerns...
...are no bigger than the weather
or whatever's new in the snack machine...
...but I have the weight of the world
on my shoulders.
So if you don't mind,
figure out your own crap.
Good. I need you to crosscheck
these customs docs...
...with the bill of lading that you saw
on the container yesterday.
How could you make me choose
between Morgan's life and his friendship?
That wasn't going to happen,
because Anna vouched for him.
-You don't get who he is to me.
-No, I get it. He's your best friend.
You know, you say that, but I don't think
you have a clue what it means.
Look, Sarah.
I don't have parents.
I mean, not really. I don't talk about it...
...because that's just the way
that things are now.
But it wasn't always this way.
Morgan was there
the first day that my mom took off.
He didn't say much, because, honestly,
what is a fifth-grader supposed to say?
But we sat and split a cherry cheesecake
and played "Legend of Zelda" all night long.
And my dad, well,
that's a whole other story.
But Morgan was there for that too.
Morgan is more than just my best friend.
He's my family.
Before you got here,
and long after you've gone...
...Morgan is my family.
Last night, we failed to learn
the contents of the Triad's container.
We don't know what drugs or weapons
are floating around the city.
And while I appreciate
your friendship with Morgan...
...losing sight of that container
endangers many people's best friends.
Not just yours, Chuck.
[KNOCKS]
Not a good time, bro.
[GRUNTS]
Dude, you're supposed to stop a door
with your foot.
Have you ever had a dream
that's never come true?
Hmm. No.
Okay.
Have you ever had a best friend
with a dream that's never come true?
Lester was scared to sing yesterday,
but he has a voice that makes angels cry.
Please give Jeffster another chance.
Jeff, you're a weird dude.
But I guess even a weird dude like you
can have a friend.
I don't know how I'm gonna convince Ellie,
but you got another audition.
You want me to talk to her?
We have a rapport.
Hey, Morgan, will you please
just talk to me for one second?
I have nothing left to say to you, dude.
Oh, one question, though,
before I never speak to you again:
How did you betraying me
turn into you saving me?
Sorry for betraying you.
-No, dude, you don't get to say sorry.
-Sorry isn't good enough.
-It's a cheap Band-Aid--
-Stop it, dude. You don't get it.
This whole thing is my fault, man.
It's me. I made this mess.
You warned me not to spy.
I went and did it.
I'm sick of you being right,
then having to bail me out.
You've bailed me out plenty of times.
I can't count on you to fix things
my whole life.
-Of course you can.
-Look...
...it's time for me
to pay for my own mistakes...
...fight my own battles.
Um, buddy, I would maybe start
with a different battle.
CHUCK: Look, just keep it down,
remain calm, and this will all be over soon.
No, dude. You know what this is?
This is you saving me again.
No. No, it's not.
This is two best friends...
-...hiding from a terrible beating.
-Look, the time is now, okay?
Time for me to stand up for myself.
I need to go out there to these thugs...
...and take it like a grown man.
A grown man who spies on women, fine.
But still....
I'm done, Chuck, okay?
I won't have you saving me anymore.
No. Wait, wait, wait.
Morgan, Morgan, wait.
Wait. You can't just go out there
with your breath stinking like garbage.
Way to kick a man
when he's about to be beat down.
I have dandruff in my beard.
You wanna riff on me for that too?
No, I wouldn't....
You have dandruff in your beard?
All I'm saying is that maybe
you should freshen up first, you know?
Why poke an already pissed-off bear?
Huh? Ah, ah.
I just--
That's strong. What is that, pepp--?
Is that just peppermint?
That's quick.
Hey.
See that stalker
from the party the other night?
Yeah, yeah.
I think he actually went out the back.
Uh, ahem.
Talking about getting a slice
or something like that, so....
Take it easy.
[ALARM BLARING]
-Hey. What is it?
-Chuck's in trouble.
-Let's go.
-So much for my day off.
Chuck, I want you to see something.
No time. I'm actually right in the middle
of moving this cumbersome appliance.
-Come on.
-Anna, Anna, Anna.
Look, my boyfriend's on TV.
REPORTER [ON TV]:
--from downtown...
...where I'm standing
with entrepreneur Jason Wang.
On the auction block today,
a collection of very fine automobiles...
...the likes of which
have never been seen before...
[MORGAN SNORING]
...but, thanks to Mr. Wang,
are here today.
Celebrities and dignitaries are everywhere,
with one thing in common:
a passion for cars.
-Oh, my God, the auction.
-Don't rub it in. I have to work.
-Chuck. What is it?
-I flashed. We have to get to the auction.
Triad's are gonna kill
the Chinese ambassador.
-Why would he walk into a Triad den?
-Wang's got a legitimate business.
-Ambassador doesn't know Wang's Triad.
-It's not a safe place for him.
Look, we just gotta get Morgan.
Wait.
-Morgan?
SARAH: Chuck, wait.
SARAH & CASEY:
Stay in the car, Chuck.
How can I stay
when I have to go save Morgan?
SARAH:
Please, Chuck, just follow orders.
Bartowski, you're like the poster child
for friendly fire.
Whoa, whoa.
Oh, my God. Oh, my God, it's a bomb.
JASON:
Ambassador.
-Congratulations on your new Rolls-Royce.
-Thank you.
It's always been my dream to own one.
LAU:
Did you take care of last night's problem?
-He dead?
THUG: Not yet.
What do you want us to do with him?
LAU:
I got a great idea.
He can hitch a ride with the ambassador.
Kill two birds with one bomb.
Listen. Triads have planted a bomb in the
Rolls-Royce and put Morgan in the trunk.
-[OVER RADIO] We've gotta stop it.
-Chuck, stay right where you are.
-I'll get the car. You get Chuck.
-Yeah.
Casey, the container is empty.
And the car has already been dispatched.
Casey, do you copy?
[BOTH GRUNTING]
Pretty girl like you is a cop?
Phew.
Shame I gotta mess up that face.
Wait, wait. Stop. Stop. Stop.
There's a bomb in your car.
-It's a Triad trap. Move.
-No. No.
CASEY:
Learn to follow an order, Bartowski.
Hey.
-Let me in.
-I can't.
-You're not gonna let me save Morgan.
-Proving you're not a complete idiot.
-Let me in.
-Nope. Casey, you'll just have to hang on.
[CHOKING]
Look, he's my best friend, Casey, all right?
It's like you said, leave no man behind.
Tell you what. If you let me in, I promise
to help you save the bearded loser.
-You promise?
-I promise.
-Semper fi?
-Semper fidelis.
What are you doing?
You promised you'd help me.
I didn't promise I'd let you drive.
What? Huh!
There's a remote control for this thing?
That's crazy. This is crazy.
[LAU SCREAMS THEN CAR HONKS]
Watch the Rolls. The Rolls.
Don't-- Oh, oh, oh! Casey!
[TRUCK HORN HONKS]
Whoa, whoa, whoa! Major John Casey,
National Security Agency.
Just my badge. Sheathe that weapon.
It's cool. Relax.
We're here to stop an attempt
on the ambassador's life.
BODYGUARD: Hands on your head.
-We're just trying to help.
BODYGUARD: On the ground. Don't move.
-Bomb!
BODYGUARD:
On the ground, now, now.
-You're risking your life.
-No, I'm saving Morgan's.
CASEY:
Don't be an idiot. Unh!
BODYGUARD:
Easy.
Hey. CIA. Let him go.
-Where's Chuck?
-Heroic imbecile took off with the bomb.
-Get out of there, Bartowski.
-Oh, my God. Chuck.
Oh.
That was pretty sweet, huh?
What?
Did you think that I was...?
-No. I was just using the....
CASEY: Give me that.
Sorry.
Last favor. Do you mind helping me
getting something out of the trunk?
[MORGAN MUMBLING INDISTINCTLY]
Whoa. Oh, oh.
CHUCK:
Oh, yeah. Hey.
Hey.
You okay? You really had me worried.
Oh, man. I'm so embarrassed.
I can't even get my ass kicked
with any dignity.
Dude, I can't believe I fainted.
Yeah. Yeah. Yeah.
You fainted.
I'm such a coward.
I don't know. I guess just the fear of a fight
must've been too much for me.
And I'm sorry, Chuck.
I'm sorry that you had to save me again.
Come on, Morgan.
Don't you know who you are to me?
Don't you know what you mean to me?
All that you've done?
Thank you.
You're welcome.
Think you could butch it up just a bit,
though, bro? Just, like....
Smooth Lau and her band of cohorts
were apprehended at the scene...
...and Jason Wang
has just been taken into custody.
They will be spending a lot of time
in prison, thanks to all of you.
Thank you, general.
Furthermore, this incident
has left Ambassador Mei Sheng...
...with a renewed vigor to crack down
on Triad crime, both here and overseas.
Now, if you'll excuse me,
I'm late for my evening plans.
Uh, general,
um, if you don't mind me asking...
...what exactly is your version
of evening plans?
Bartowski.
BECKMAN [ON MONITOR]:
It's not top-secret, major.
I'm meeting Condoleezza for cosmos.
Even I have friends.
Sorry about delegating
the music stuff to Chuck.
But an apology is just words
if it's not followed up by actions.
So I got the flowers, I bought the cake,
and I took care of your half of the to-do list.
That's very sweet, Devon.
I'm also back in charge of finding the band,
which is why we're here.
What?
Partnership is trust, babe. Come on.
[PANTS]
-Partnership is trust.
-I can't do this, man.
-You can. I know you can.
LESTER: No.
You see, before, Jeff, I wasn't really scared
that the band was gonna break up.
-The truth is, I was just sc--
JEFF: Shh.
Ever had a dream
that's never come true?
I'm asking you to sing.
Not for yourself.
Do it for me.
[FEEDBACK OVER SPEAKERS]
[JEFF PLAYING TOTO'S "AFRICA"
ON KEYBOARD]
[LESTER SINGING "AFRICA"]
Honey, you're not seriously considering
this lame band for our wedding day?
[MOUTHS ALONG]
No, but let a man have his dream,
even if it is for five minutes.
I wanted to apologize.
I could've been more sensitive before
about your friendship with Morgan.
It's just-- It's difficult.
I don't really have anyone in my life
like that who cares about me.
Yeah, you do.
Anna.
Listen. I should've said this to you
a long time ago, all right?
Um, but, Anna Wu...
...I lo--
I like you very, very much.
[CHUCKLES]
Hey, guys.
Look at us, man. We both got girlfriends.
This is as good as it gets, man.
[ENGLISH SDH]