The Sabre Code of Conduct
outlines the governing principles
key to establishing and maintaining
trust with our employees, clients...
Oh, my God, kill me.
Hey. All right, obviously,
we all want to die,
but we have to get through
this, so Gabe, go ahead. It's okay.
Oh, is it...
Is it okay with you?
Because if it's not,
you work for me, so...
Comply with all
applicable laws,
regulations,
policies and contracts
governing our business.
Be honest, fair...
I'm going to do it.
...trustworthy in all your business
activities and relationships.
Treat one another...
Oh! I'm going into labor!
Okay. She's going into labor!
Oh, my goodness.
Make way, everybody!
I know it's wrong to
fake going into labor
just to get out of things,
but sometimes,
it's necessary.
I'm going into labor.
But should I
have corn dogs or...
I'm going into labor!
Okay, three reasons you
are wrong about True Blood.
Number one...
I'm going into labor.
Here we go!
Hey, guys, you can't keep
saying you're going into labor.
Everyone knows
you're full of it.
Yeah. OSCAR:
It's not fair, you guys.
- Pitiful.
- So stupid.
Never cry wolf.
Okay.
Oh. Oh! Oh, my gosh!
Oh, my God, Pam!
I'm really in labor!
This is happening.
Okay, guys.
Okay.
Here we go.
We'll see you.
How do you feel?
Drive carefully!
Good luck!
- Bye!
- Good luck!
False alarm.
What? They took
another client from us?
Okay, bye.
Man, business is war.
Customers, clients,
it's like a war out there.
I am a leader,
but you can only inspire people
so much in a place like this.
So today, I'm turning
the inspire factor up to 10.
With a little help from my
friend, America's bloodiest battle.
Why even read business books?
We should be studying war.
Going to places like
Gettysburg. Where is that?
It's right here in PA.
Ah!
Well, we should take a field trip
there. I mean, that would be so cool.
I wonder if that
bus downstairs is...
Okay, Andy. We get it.
It's a trip to Gettysburg.
That sounds super inspiring!
I'm in!
Gettysburg? Hmm.
Could be interesting.
Second most northern
battle in the Civil War.
Actually, it is
the northernmost.
Hal
The Civil War history industry
has conveniently forgotten
about the Battle of Schrute Farms.
Whatever. I'm over
it. It's just grossly irresponsible.
Charge!
Well, this could be fun.
Yeah, well, the bus
has free Wi-Fi,
and I made special low
sugar lunches for everyone.
And is anyone
kosher or halal?
What's the halal option?
Dates, tabouleh
and bagel with cream cheese.
Out.
You know, it's the same as the
kosher option. There's a lesson in there.
I mean, I can't force you
to go, you're not my slaves.
Thanks to Gettysburg.
But who's coming with me?
I'm in.
I'm in, too.
I guess I'm a sucker
for historical fiction.
Anyone who's not going,
you're dead to me.
You're uninvited.
I don't want you to come.
But FYI,
there will be leftover
turkey and pesto
sammies in the fridge.
Yes!
One for you.
Cool, thanks.
And one for you.
Oh! You missed your head.
There you go.
Phyllis, think fast!
All right, guys, a little
foreplay before we do it.
Fans of Ken Burns' Jazz will
most certainly enjoy The Civil War.
You know, I just got
Limitless on my iPad.
I bet I could
get it on the TV.
Oh, isn't that the one where
the guy becomes limitless?
It's just not appropriate. If we were
going to visit Bradley Cooper's birthplace,
I'd be the first one suggesting
that. I'd be rooting for it...
Limitless, Limitless,
Limitless, Limitless, Limitless!
All right,
all right, all right!
Here.
Like it? KEVIN:
Oh, by the picnic table?
Then you've got to
get the fire pit.
I can't get a fire pit,
I have two babies.
But the fire pit is
a no-brainer. Oh, hi there.
Hi, Robert. Hey. Um, how are
you doing? Good to see you again.
Where is everyone?
Where is Andy?
Andy took some of
the other people
on a corporate
retreat to Gettysburg.
Well, I was hoping to talk
out some ideas with Andy.
But what we have
here is perhaps better.
By not going on the trip,
you've shown
you're the free
thinkers of the office.
Robert, you've got your sheep,
and you got your black sheep.
And I'm not even a sheep.
I am on the freaking moon.
So, here's what we can do.
Game changers.
Changes to the game,
such that the game
can never be played
the same way again.
Everyone,
brainstorm some innovations.
Don't be afraid to
get weird with it.
Meredith!
Excited.
Okay.
You guys, get excited!
Movie's almost over.
All right, we're here.
Limitless can wait.
Fun fact. In France,
they call Limitless
"The Man with
Many Capabilities."
Whoo-hoo! Ladies and
gentlemen, the 1800s await you.
We can watch
Limitless on the way back.
I got Source Code
on the way back.
Whoo!
Where are you going?
Visitors' Center. Going to grab
a map for the memorials, right?
We're not going to the Visitors'
Center. We're not tourists.
No, of course
we're not tourists.
We're just people that aren't
from here who are taking a tour.
Yeah, the sign says,
"Begin tour here."
Unless you're going on
the very specially created
and meticulously researched
Andy Bernard Tour.
After Chancellorsville,
Lee brought his army up the
Shenandoah Valley, right through here.
They stopped in this field for a
picnic, which they called "lunch."
Yeah,
but I'm confused...
Total deaths
belongs to Gettysburg.
But when you're talking about
DPA, that's deaths per acre...
Uh-huh. ...nothing beats
the Battle of Schrute Farms.
Oh, DPA sounds way
more important... Oh, it is.
And you should read some of these
letters that the soldiers wrote home.
I mean, it makes
the Battle of Gettysburg
sound like a bunch of schoolgirls
wrestling over a hairbrush.
I'm telling you, they're heartbreaking,
too. So beautifully written.
Dwight, what are
you telling this girl?
The truth.
Stop filling her head with nonsense,
okay? She doesn't know any better.
Oscar, I'm so glad
you just got here.
I would have
believed everything he said.
No, no, no. You're filling
her head with nonsense.
You and the history books.
I'm telling the truth!
Interesting.
Yes, thank you.
All of history has
been whitewashed.
Really? Why don't you tell us
the real history, Gore Vidal?
Okay, I will.
I don't know who that is,
but I'm going
to tell you this.
He's a historian.
Gettysburg was very important.
Credit where credit is due, okay?
Big mad props to Gettysburg.
Was it, however, the most
northern battle of the Civil War?
Yes, yes...
Not by a long shot!
No!
Yes!
No, it was not! No, it
was not!
Was it the second
most northern?
What?
Sure! I would cede it was the
second most northern battle...
Erin!
Was it the northernmost?
No! Get out of here, Oscar...
Get out of here!
I am so eager to hear your game
changers. Let's dig in, shall we?
May I go first?
Absolutely.
Raw fish. The disgusting
food from Japan
that Americans
would never want to eat.
Now, we can't
get enough of it.
From movie stars to construction
workers, sushi is what's for dinner.
Let me throw another
idea at you. Origami. What?
The crazy art of paper
folding from, that's right, Japan.
Don't you wish you
could go back to 1980
and open the first sushi
restaurant in Manhattan?
We can do that with
origami,
it's the sushi of paper.
This idea hasn't gripped me.
What else did
you come up with?
I had to memorize
the presentation, Robert,
and it took a long time
to build the swan, so.
That was bad.
If your woman is like mine,
I bet you come home to hear
the same thing all the time.
"This paper is so hard.
It scratches.
"Why can't there be
a paper just for me?"
Well, now there is.
It's pink,
scented and silky soft.
Now, you can watch the game,
and she can write a letter to her sister.
The situation you described, returning
home to a wife complaining about
her paper being too masculine,
is not one that I'm familiar with.
In the African
American community.
Thought it was worth a try.
That's fascinating.
Tell me, what's the significance
of the peach orchard, though?
Well, that's a great question.
Actually, some of the most...
Excuse me,
I've got a question for you.
Can you tell us about
the Battle of Schrute Farms?
Oh, I haven't
heard of that one.
Really?
Okay, follow-up question,
how much are they paying you
to keep your mouth shut?
I apologize for my friend. And for the
Republicans who are cutting your funding.
We don't need to
bother this poor gentleman.
I know exactly where
we're going. Giddy-up!
Tallyho!
Are you Lincoln?
No, no, I'm...
Apparently, I bear a passing
resemblance to Abraham Lincoln.
It makes it kind of
hard for me to go to places
like museums,
historical monuments,
elementary schools.
I don't see it.
Chelsea, give Mr. Lincoln
your hat so I can take a picture.
Okay, quick.
Hey, Lincoln's starting.
Oh, no. No, no, no, no. I'm
actually with a tour group myself, so...
Hello, I'm Abraham Lincoln.
Some people call me
the "Great Emancipator,"”
but you might know
me from the penny.
Okay, you know
the test booklets
that they give out
in all the schools?
I was thinking that we could
put a coupon in the back
that people
would mail in to us.
And as, you know,
as I tell it, I don't like it.
Unless, of course, you are
responding to it. I am not.
Um, excuse me, I'm going
to go to the bathroom.
At this point,
when you're this pregnant,
it's kind of
like senior spring.
The other day, I spit my
gum out on the carpet.
Kevin. You've been quiet.
I'm curious to know
what your game changer is.
You know how
in the vending machine,
they have the chocolate
chip cookies in the A-1 spot?
They do that
because they think
A-1 is the best spot
for the best cookie.
But the real best spot is D-4.
Right? That's where
the eyes go.
So...
Cookies. Cookie placement.
Yeah. But not just
the cookies, though.
That was just a for instance.
Who else agrees with Kevin
that we're wasting facilities,
manpower on our underselling products,
when we should be pushing
our top performers?
There you get consensus.
Okay, we are
now on a planet where
Kevin is the most
creative person around
and I am just some
good looking guy.
I just don't understand.
It's 1865, victory is ours,
I have saved the very soul of our
nation and yet, happiness eludes me.
Oh, perhaps a trip to the
theater will enliven my spirits.
No!
So, another thing about oatmeal
cookies. Who even wants them?
I mean, I've seen
Toby eat one like once,
but other than that,
forget it.
Interesting.
So what is Dunder
Mifflin's oatmeal cookie?
What is the product
that no one wants?
How about that
two-hole punch letter?
Only the lawyers want that
punch at the top, and they use legal.
That's the oatmeal cookie.
Fantastic, Kevin, fantastic.
Thank you.
By the way, did we leave
all the food on the bus?
Let's talk about food for a
second. Food for thought.
Yeah, that's what I
had for breakfast,
and I think that's
probably why I'm still hungry.
Hunger. Hunger for victory.
Hunger for honor, hunger for pride.
Hunger for hamburgers.
Hunger for
chicken chimichangas.
Right, Darryl?
That's good.
Exactly. Now, do you know what
the Civil War soldiers were hungry for?
Pride. Now, each
battalion had its own flag,
and they guarded these
flags with their lives.
Colonel Harrison Jeffords
of the 4th Michigan Infantry
saw his flag
being carried away,
chased it down with
nothing but a sword,
fought tooth and nail at the
foot of that flag until he died.
He wasn't about to
let them have that flag.
Pride. Right, guys?
I commissioned this flag for
Dunder Mifflin. It cost me $200.
Only $2007?
We are all branches on this tree.
And from the tree comes paper.
We're all part of a business,
but business is war.
What's that I hear?
Oh! A rebel paper company
is coming to take our flag.
What's going on here?
Whee-hoo!
Come and get it! Who's going to get
the flag? Who's getting it? Whoa, hey!
Don't look where I am, look where
I'm going. Jerk right, jerk left, jerk...
Andy, this is inappropriate.
People died here, man.
Get the flag, get the flag!
Come on, Big Tuna.
What are you going to do about
it? We've got a flag right here!
Whee-hoo!
Spangler's Spring
is a mile this way.
Oh, wow. So, that's two miles
if you incorporate the walk back.
It's... I mean, come on.
Oh, I don't think I
should walk anymore.
All I had for
breakfast was oatmeal,
yogurt, coffee,
orange juice and toast.
Two poached eggs and then
that half a sandwich on the bus.
I can't.
All right, fine.
You know what?
I guess this place
just hasn't rubbed off
on you the way
that I hoped it would.
I'm still going, and I'm
not going to ask anymore.
I'm not even
going to look back,
I'm just going to
assume that you're with me.
You said you weren't
going to look back.
And why is BlackRock
suddenly the paragon by which all
hedge funds must now be compared?
Yeah, I don't know.
Right? I mean,
you're an accountant,
those bogus prospectuses
must drive you insane.
Yes, I am an accountant.
Dwight, this is one
of the archivists here.
I thought maybe
we can consult him.
Really?
Yeah.
Well, anyone employed by the
Gettysburg industrial complex
is certainly going
to want to keep quiet
about the Battle
of Schrute Farms.
Schrute Farms, did you say?
That is a fascinating little
chapter of the Civil War.
You've heard about it?
Yes! Ha! Prepare to be
refuted. Go on, come on.
There you go.
Families
and sweethearts back home
waited desperately for
letters from the front.
"Dearest Mother, I'm sorry it
has been so long since my last letter.
“It is three months since I
arrived at Schrute Farms,
"and I fear I may never leave this
place alive. Melvyn Fifer Garris.”
Hallowed ground.
But the battle at
Schrute Farms was no battle at all.
It was a code used by pacifists
from both North and South,
who'd turned
the Pennsylvania farmhouse
into an artistic community
and a refuge from the war.
You have to understand,
poets, artists, dancers,
these kinds of men
preferred peace to war.
These delicate, lovely men
found a place of refuge
among the Schrutes
of Schrute Farm.
Amidst the macho
brutality of war,
this was a place where dandies
and dreamers could put on plays,
sing tender ballads
and dance in the moonlight.
I like to think of Schrute Farm
as the Underground Railroad
for the sensitive and,
well fabulous.
Wow, this is so much better
than the story you made up.
I've seen enough.
You're right, there should
be a monument to this.
Never trust a cookie
with a woman's name.
Pecan Sandy.
Lorna Doone. Madeleine.
Oh...
They'll just break your heart.
Kevin, you are...
Robert, I hate to interrupt, but I
would love to pitch you one last idea.
I call it the Big Mac idea.
What? No.
Big Mac idea.
Sounds encouraging.
It's really, really good,
Robert. Let me explain.
No, this is not fair.
This is my idea.
He's trying to steal it
because he's jealous of me.
Well, what is the idea?
Every time you buy a Big Mac,
you set one ingredient aside.
Then, at the end of the week,
you have a free Big Mac.
And you love it even more, because
you made it with your own hands.
You know what? Now I remember.
That was your idea.
That is 100% your idea.
Oh, my.
It was just actually
cookies the whole time.
Damn it.
Hey.
You guys came.
Where's everyone else?
Back at the bus.
We were locked out.
Phyllis is sitting on the
ground, eating a dirty sandwich.
Yeah, I asked
the bus driver to lock it
because our stuff was in
there. I guess he follows orders.
Yeah, sorry everybody else
didn't come. I think they're just tired.
With holes in their
shoes and their dysentery.
Even without an audience,
you're still at it.
What are you talking about?
Our office has a disease,
and it goes by many names.
Sarcasm, snark, "wisecracks."
You take things
that people care about,
and you make them feel
lame about it with your jokes.
That's what you
did with this trip.
Andy, this whole
idea of our situation
being just like war,
it's just not true.
We just work at
a paper company,
and you're our
regional manager.
And guess what, man? You
don't have to prove anything.
We like you as
regional manager.
Andy, if you don't believe me,
take a look at what's on my head.
I'm wearing a very pink hat.
I've been getting weird looks
all day, because I'm pretty sure
"DM does GB" means
something kind of sexual.
But guess who's wearing them?
All of us.
Just for you, man.
That's huge.
You don't like the hats?
They're terrible.
I hate myself.
They just didn't turn out how I
wanted. In my head, they were cooler.
But they do look weird.
The world
will little note
nor long
remember the fight that
Jim and I had
here at Gettysburg.
And that's good,
because I was basically wrong.
I wanted my team to be like
this army and I was their general,
but I guess it's
really just more like
they're people who work in
an office and I'm their manager.
Yeah, that's really probably a better
analogy. Now that I think about it.
Abe and Mary are
seated watching the show.
Oh, Mary, this is wonderful.
Okay, Mary, stop your
scolding. I'll be quiet.
I need her like I need
a hole in the head!
Mmm. Oh...
Bang!