Approved.
Chef from South Park.
It's genius. Just some chef.
I've decided to pre-screen all of
the Halloween costumes this year.
I have three simple rules,
don't be offensive,
don't be cliché
and don't take the first
two rules too seriously.
The gorilla from Rise
of the Planet of the Apes.
Huh?
The one who
sacrifices his life.
Whoa! Oh.
Spoiler alert. It's
been out for ages, man.
Costume vetoed.
Uh...
It's... Somebody's
already called that.
Who? Kevin has a gorilla
suit you could borrow.
This is ridiculous! Why can't
there just be two Kate Middletons?
Guys, I know, I mean I
wish there could be too.
It's like I can't choose.
They're both
amazing, it's just...
Look, I stayed up all night
and I watched that G.D. wedding
and then I came to work and I
made everyone else watch it all day.
Meredith wasn't even here.
Because I was there.
You're the
people's princess! Diana was nothing!
I thought you were
at your sister's funeral.
What I said was, "My sister's
funeral is this weekend."
Didn't say
I'd be there.
Why is it such a shock
that I follow the royal story?
Warms my heart, thinking
about them two kids...
...doing it.
Can I maybe
squeeze through?
Here you go.
There we go. Thank you.
When they talk about all the
nice things about dating a co-worker,
they don't mention
one of the best parts.
After you're done dating, you still
get to work together every single day.
Jim, put it on.
Put it on, man.
I don't know if I can.
Come on, the Three Amigos.
Three Kings.
All right.
I know, I know, I know. But
Darryl and Kevin needed a third.
They bought me
this jersey. I said no.
Kevin started crying, so
I am Chris Bosh.
If you get into
season one, you know, really...
Oh, my God, what the hell
is wrong with you?
It's called a costume.
What are you? Some kind
of Jamaican zombie woman?
Ryan, will you please tell her
who I am? Whoopi Goldberg.
Has no one here heard
of Kerrigan, from StarCraft?
Queen of blades.
It's all Toby's fault.
Every Halloween,
I tell him the same thing.
You can't bring weapons
into the office.
And every year he says
the same thing.
"As soon as I get my weapons
back, I'm going to kill you."
But there I am at
Thanksgiving alive, you know?
I'm a lucky turkey.
Everybody looking good?
This is the best we can do?
I'm not judging. I think
you guys look great, I just...
...want to make sure
this is the best we can do.
I just got a text
from Broccoli Rob. "Boo!"
It scared me.
And then I got this text
from Robert California.
"Looking forward to Halloween
party. Expectations are high."
Scared the
out of me.
G'day, Pameroo. Could
you shoot this off for me?
Yeah.
Australian accent.
What are you doing? I just
wanted to see how you do it.
If you're doing
something I don't.
Are you... That
Andy, so hot and cold.
One day he's like,
"Fax these documents, please."
The next he's like, "Pam, you fax them.
Who cares what Erin's feeling." Right?
Oh, Erin.
Pam,
how would you rate me as a
receptionist on a scale of one to three?
Um.
Two?
It's like the second to
last thing I wanted to hear.
No, I mean
you're doing great
and Andy put you in charge
of the whole party, right?
Yeah.
Send completed. You are
the best in the biz. I can't deny.
Bob and I are doing this
Scranton haunted walking tour.
I always wondered what kind
of people went on that thing.
Hey, if you go
by the Banshee Pub,
tell the Man in Black
I say hello.
What happened, Pam?
Okay.
When I was 22, I worked there and
everybody said the place was haunted.
I didn't believe it until one
day, before we opened,
I look up into the mirror,
you know, behind the bar?
And I see this old man
dressed all in black,
but when I turn around,
there's no one there.
So, I tell the cook my story...
Wait, they have food there?
...and he said,
"That's what everyone sees.
That's the Man in Black."
No. My wife does not
believe in ghosts.
Hey.
Oh.
This Man in Black thing. What
do you think that was about?
What do you mean? Was
it like trickery in the lights
or maybe you were so primed
to see it, then there it was.
I saw a ghost.
Mm-hmm.
What I'm saying is, like, do
you ever wonder what it was?
It was a ghost. I told you
this on like our first date.
Yeah, I had just told you about
the day that I met the Blue Angels.
I figured you had to top it. I
don't know what to tell you, Jim,
but I saw a ghost.
Hey!
Uh-oh.
Looks like we're under a Jack
attack. - Yes, Andrew.
And you, on this day
of fantasy, are a laborer.
Yes. Everyone,
this is Bert, my son.
Bert, this is
a paper company.
Hey, Bert!
Hello.
Can I use a computer?
I need to check a hurricane.
Here, use this one.
All right.
Oh, look, pin the word
on the witch.
How did you know
I was bringing my son?
I didn't. It was for us.
But he can play.
Berty Boy, would you
like to play this game?
That stuff's for babies.
Perhaps this party will
awaken the baby in all of us.
Wow. Who shot our grownup
party with the kiddy ray gun?
We're still getting it set up.
It's going to be really cool.
Extraordinary.
Did you plan this?
Well, Toby and I did, yeah.
And I overheard and thought,
"Hey, that'd be fun, don't mind if I do."
If you turn out the lights,
we'll do a little dance.
One, two, three.
Dem bones,
dem bones, dem dry bones
Now we're the skeleton crew
Delightful.
Thank you.
Now then,
how are we today?
Fine.
Great.
Just fine, Kelly?
Everything all right?
Mm-hmm.
You feeling fulfilled
in your life?
I guess.
You guess? So there is
something you want that you
do not have.
Try not to think
about it.
Because it's too
terrifying to imagine.
Now we're cooking.
What is it, Kelly? What
is this great fear of yours?
Never marrying. Yes. Dying
alone, that is very scary.
And how are you, Toby?
So great.
Oh, I put those up. I
know. I'm taking them down.
I almost wonder if
putting nothing on this wall
is more Halloween-y.
I don't know
about this, guys.
Andy put me in charge of
the Halloween party, so.
Well, Andy sent us
in here, so which is it?
Oh.
So can we speak our minds now?
Or are we still sparing feelings?
Because I hate
all of this.
Very low pressure
in the Sargasso Sea.
Warm air from South America.
Cold air from Greenland. All
signs point to the perfect storm.
Perfectly mediocre.
What are you, anyway?
I'm a Jamaican zombie woman.
Leave me alone, ghoul.
If you had some really big
wings with blades on the end,
you'd kind of look like
Kerrigan from StarCraft.
Damn it! I am Kerrigan from
StarCraft. I've been censored.
If you're going to be a
Zerg, at least be a lurker.
Not some girl. Kerrigan
is ruler of the Zerg swarm.
Yeah. She also has boobs.
Yeah, but no nipples.
Hey, what's up?
November's sure creeping up,
ain't it? You can't stop that month.
Hey, what's the jive with Angela and
Phyllis helping with the party, you know?
Um...
I just thought you could
use some help, you know?
"Cause Robert came in and
thought the party seemed a little kiddy.
And I guess I agreed.
And maybe we could
mix a little more 13
into the PG.
But that's it?
There's nothing
about me or I?
Can we talk about it
at the end of the day?
I got a call.
I got to make a call.
Yeah, sorry.
Yes, we can.
Yes. I don't know.
Mm-hmm.
Gabe?
Sweet Erin.
I'm throwing the Halloween party
and I just want to amp it up a little.
I think it could use
some extra pizzazz.
Okay. Where does
Gabe factor in?
Remember that Halloween
party you took me to once?
The one where I started crying
as soon as I walked in
and I didn't stop crying?
Yes. Lars and Takako's.
Okay, well let's say that I
wanted this party to be a tiny,
tiny bit like that one,
just more adult,
more scary and sexy.
I will make this sexier
than you could ever imagine.
No, just scary. If we
wanted ideas for scary stuff.
No, that'd be scary.
What are you thinking about?
All right, let me go get it.
Pam Halpert.
Hey. It's Jim Halpert.
I was wondering if you
wanted to see a movie tonight
'cause I've read a lot about
this really great documentary.
Is it called Ghostbusters?
It's called Ghostbusters.
It didn't look like that.
He didn't have
a buster sign around him?
Why don't you draw him?
Why don't we see this old man?
Okay. Yeah. Fine,
I'll draw him. Okay.
I ain't afraid of no ghosts.
Whoa.
Mm-hmm.
Dwight, are you eating
a stick? It's a root, idiot.
Okay.
Everyone hates you.
That's really rude.
I don't tell you hurricanes
suck even though it's true.
What do you like,
tornadoes? Try influenza.
Yeah? What's the vaccine you
could take to avoid a hurricane?
Open up a newspaper.
Look, a hurricane's coming.
I suppose you're going to tell
me the scariest animal is a shark.
Try box jellyfish.
What are we talking about?
I was talking about my wife
and how she believes in ghosts.
Then we had a little debate and then
Meredith said that she believes in them too.
You seem unimpressed.
Ghosts don't scare you?
I'm only scared of real things,
like serial killers and kidnappers.
Not things that don't exist
like ghosts or mummies.
Mummies are real. There
are mummies at museums.
Yeah.
You prank.
It's true. They've
been preserved for
thousands of years.
They're all over.
Why on Earth would a
museum put a mummy in it?
A little
witch's brew?
I grew this party
up real fast.
Get out of here, little kid
party. Nobody loves you.
And clean up your room!
Grownups are going to use it later.
The party looks fun,
doesn't it?
Everybody seems to be in
there having a great time.
So maybe now would be a great time
for me to pop back on the computer.
I'm using it. I'm about to
play StarCraft with him.
You serious?
Yeah, I'm serious.
Hey, hey. That's funny.
Okay.
Loser.
Pam, do you think anyone's going to
notice I've worn this costume before
when I wasn't pregnant?
You know, I guess nobody
would believe it still fits.
Hey, guys, I'm
an Oscar Liar Weiner.
Oh, my God.
Party's tight, E.
Fog is cool. Thanks.
It's on medium.
Perfect.
It really looks great.
You did a great job.
Oh. So we don't have
to have that talk?
We should still
have that talk.
Maybe you could come
by my office at like 4:457?
Cool.
Okay.
Okay, everybody,
be prepared
to be scared.
Okay.
The Cinema of the
Unsettling is a growing film movement.
The most well known film in
the genre is an hour long shot
of a squirrel
with diarrhea.
Okay. Ew.
Is that my grandmother?
- What's the story?
- There is no story.
Yeah, seems like
there isn't a narrative.
Maybe the filmmaker realized
that even narrative is comforting.
What the hell
is going on here?
Okay, I think
we've seen enough.
- You can turn it off now.
- Yeah.
Yeah, Kill it. Go ahead
and turn it off.
Thank you. STANLEY:
How'd you get in my car?
Where is this from?
That is so upsetting.
That was awful.
Robert, I apologize.
I'm sorry. I got confused.
I heard that you
wanted to make the party more
adult but, I think I know what to do now.
This game is called
"Pecker Poker."
It's the
game of cards that gets you hard.
What we have here is a
classic misunderstanding.
Why didn't you simply
ask Andy to clarify?
Asking is a very
easy thing to do.
The two of you are
obviously very close.
Oh, I see. This no longer
seems like my business.
All I knew is that
you wanted to have a talk
with me at the end of the day
and I got nervous, so...
You were going
to talk at the end of...
I'm not here.
Did you think I was
going to fire you?
No, I wasn't.
I'm sorry. This must be
really uncomfortable for you.
I'm never uncomfortable.
Okay.
Erin, I think you know
I've been dating someone.
Sure.
And it's getting
a little more serious.
She's never come by, so.
And she's never called here.
Unless it's your mom.
No, I didn't want her to call because
I thought it would be weird, but,
now it's weird
that she's not calling.
Two dates?
Three dates?
Thirty-one.
Wow.
I'm so happy
for you guys.
Um. Let me know
when you get to 40.
I'll see you guys.
I should go.
I just don't get it, Pam.
I mean, you're a rational
person. Thank you.
Jim doesn't let me wash his
NFL jersey during the playoffs.
How is this any less
logical? Careful. Whoa.
First of all, it's not like I think
that's going to help the Eagles win.
Really?
That is just a bunch of people
participating in a collective thing.
And maybe the Eagles will hear about
it and want to play better. It's not...
Exactly.
Thank you.
Go! Get up there
right now.
Got it.
Dwight.
You want to attack, or let
them come to us? Your call, B.
- Unleash the hell storm.
- Dwight.
Nice.
Dwight.
Got 'em. Go!
Is she Asian? I don't know.
She's from somewhere, I bet.
Maybe from the forest.
Forest?
Did Andy say his girlfriend's
from the forest?
I don't know, Phyllis.
Maybe she's from the city.
Looks terribly real,
doesn't it, Creed?
Are you scared of snakes?
No.
You don't live
as long as I have
without a healthy fear
of snakes, Bobby.
Yeah, I guess sometimes I have
nightmares about being buried alive.
Honestly, Jim gives
me the creeps.
What am I up to?
Like a few years
down the road, Cece says,
"Mom, there's
a ghost in my closet."
Now you say one of two things.
One, "You're just having a bad dream."
Or two, "Let's go see
what it wants."
I'm not going
to freak her out, Jim.
Okay. I'm not going
to lie to her either.
Oh, come on.
When I was a boy,
there was an empty house,
just up the hill from my family's.
It was rumored a man
committed suicide there
after being possessed
by the devil.
One day, a young woman, Lydia,
moved into the house
with her infant child.
That very night Lydia was awakened
by a loud, heinous hissing sound.
She walked to the nursery and
there in baby's crib was a snake
wrapped around baby's neck,
squeezing tighter and tighter.
Oh, my goodness.
The crib was full of dirt,
baby struggled to free
itself from underneath,
reaching and clawing,
gasping for air.
Embalmed bodies rose
from their sarcophagi,
lurching toward baby.
For they were mummies.
No.
Amongst them was a man.
Tall, slim.
Jim.
Almost instinctively
she turned to her husband.
"Wait," she thought,
"I don't have a husband."
For Lydia and her husband had had
an argument, one they couldn't get past.
Each night they slept one inch
farther apart until one night Lydia left.
It was about this time she
lost herself in imaginary worlds.
She had quit the
book club, the choir,
citing something about
their high expectations.
Her lips slowly
grew together from disuse.
Every time she wanted
to act, and didn't,
another part of her face
hardened until it was stone.
And that fevered night,
she rushed to the nursery,
and threw open the door.
"Baby, are you okay?"
Baby sat up slowly,
turned to mother
and said,
"I'm fine, bitch. I'm fine."
Fear plays an interesting
role in our lives.
How dare we let
it motivate us?
How dare we let it into our
decision making? Into our livelihoods.
Into our relationships.
It's funny, isn't it? We take a day a year
to dress up in costume and celebrate fear.
Toby. Hey, Bert.
Want to see the dance?
Dem bones,
dem bones, dem dry...
You're fired.
What?
You heard me.
Pack your things.
What? You can't...
Gabe? Are you...
I'm the CEO's son.
Pack your things.
You're done.