Are these my favorite
nail beds I've ever seen?
No, but they're fine.
Okay.
You know, I wasn't actually
going to come here,
but then I thought, you know,
I could use a walk.
And, urn, well, l'vejust been working on this
peer-to-peer Internet thing.
- And, um, well, lthink better when lwalk...
- Mm-hmm.
...but if I'm going to be thinking and walking,
I might as well walk somewhere specific.
Hey, when was the last time you slept?
Um...
I don't know.
Well, I know I was going to sleep last night,
but uh... (CHUCKLES)
I thought I had this solve
for this computational trust issue
I've been working on,
but it turns out I didn't have a solve.
But it was too late,
I had already drank the whole pot of coffee.
Okay. But, you know, I'm busy,
I got to see patients all the time.
- Sorry, I don't want to interrupt you.
-lnteresting. What are you doing?
Sorry, Just one second.
- I just had a quick thought.
- Why are you writing it on there?
Well, I mean, you change these
between every patient, right?
I guess I'm going to have to now.
You know, all the guys at the house,
they think I'm nuts. But I'm not nuts.
Hey, you know, they say that after
Alan Turing was chemically castrated,
he got a lot less annoying.
- What was that?
- Hmm?
Nothing, that's just something to think about.
Okay. Sure, yeah.
- Pen, please.
- Right, yeah.
Go ahead and pay the lady out front.
Cash is always appreciated.
How the hell does this thing work?
(THEME MUSIC PLAYING)
Question for you.
What are better than octopus recipe?
Answer for you.
Eight recipes for octopus.
My grandmother give me a family recipe
before she died in a horrible way.
Wait, what?
Sorry.
We knew Jian-Yang's app
was in the food space,
but we assumed that it was camera-based.
Like you take a photo of food,
the app returns
nutritional information or recipes,
or how it was sourced.
Yeah, like Shazam for food.
Exactly. But this, I mean, this is...
Shazam for food.
No, Shazam is not my vision.
Of course, they know
that you're not pitching Shazam.
That already exists.
This would be a Shazam for food.
- No.
- Sorry, language barrier.
Do you speak Mandarin? Anybody? No?
(SPEAKING MOCK-MANDARIN)
- That's not Mandarin.
- He's a stickler for the accent.
No. My app is a seafood. Like a food
-in the sea.
- That you can see.
- See food. S-E-E food.
- Oh.
- See food.
- Now, that we like.
- Seafood. It's like a food in the sea.
-(SPEAKS MOCK-MANDARIN LOUDLY)
(CHATTERING)
GAVIN: (MUTTERS) Fuck.
Oh, Gavin. Gavin.
I heard about your PiperChat issue,
those COPPA fines are no joke.
Could be billions.
I'm acutely aware, Jack.
Listen, after all you've done for me,
bringing me into the Hooli sandbox,
letting me play here.
What if, hypothetically,
I had a way to delete the underage accounts
and the chat data in question?
Hypothetically, I could blame it on
a malfunction of my EndFrame box servers.
The board would have
nothing to blame you for.
Jack, I'm speechless.
I'm embarrassed to say it,
but I was beginning to question your loyalty.
(MUTTERS) Yeah.
(BUZZING)
Well, you should've.
I said it was hypothetical.
Didn't say I'd do it.
4BEEPS)
-¢OCKCUCKS
Why don't you go ahead
and take a seat, Gavin?
Uh, you guys, Gavin Belson just got fired.
- JAREDI Richard.
- BIG HEAD: Wait, what?
GILFOYLE: Shit, that's huge.
"There are unconfirmed reports
that Belson violated Hooli protocol
"in the acquisition of a company
that contained toxic assets."
Oh, that's us.
Oh, my God. Gavin's been fired?
Did you fall in the pool?
On. (CHUCKLES)
No. No, ldidn't. lwas, um,
dangling my feet in,
'cause it was cool and refreshing
and just helping me think.
And then since I was wet anyway,
I purposefully started
to wade around in the pool.
Uh... But don't worry, no. ldidn't fall in.
Uh... (CHUCKLES) I'm not a spaz.
"Belson will be succeeded by
'Action' Jack Barker,
"a veteran tech CEO.
"Barker commented, 'We at Hooli pledge to
work with the Federal Trade Commission
"'to resolve this matter and commit ourselves
to earning back the public trust."'
RICHARD: Wow, Dinesh,
you really stuck it to him.
- God, they're pinning it all on Gavin.
- Holy shit.
Dude, you're moist.
Oh, I'm sorry. Yeah, I'll go and get a towel.
I mean, Dinesh, you're a giant slayer.
As long as he's the one taking
the fall for these underage users,
I thought I'd have to, like,
answer to Congress or something.
Yeah, that makes sense.
You were worried sick about the wrath
of a bloated and inept bureaucracy,
but feel totally comfortable having crossed
a spiteful and vindictive megalomaniac
with unlimited funds.
Shut up.
Gavin wouldn't come after me personally.
I think you might be the first Pakistani man
to be killed by a drone
inside the United States.
People don't have people killed in the Valley.
Not even Gavin Belson. Okay?
(SCOFFS)
Right, Jared?
I once saw him throw a sloth
down a flight of stairs after a presentation.
And he said it was an accident,
but he had this look in his eyes.
- I can't rule it out.
-(DOOR OPENS)
"A legacy lost.
"CEO and chief innovator,
Gavin Belson, exits Hooli."
The end of the Gavin Belson era.
And if all goes well,
is the beginning of the era of Erlich Bachman
and his funky Asian dude friend.
Jian.
Jian?
ERLICH: Jian-Yang!
Coleman Blair and Associates just offered us
a seed investment of $200,000
for the Shazam of food.
All we have to do is dazzle them
with the demo on Monday,
and, uh, the check will...
- What the fuck?
- Huh?
Is that my vintage Corona Club beach towel?
Yes. Um, lwas in the pool, but I got out.
ERLICH: That's a beach towel,
not a pool and...
Where were you? I was referring to you
as my funky Asian friend.
The passenger door's all fucked up.
I told you there's no demo.
I'm making my recipe app.
You're going to walk away from $200,000?
You know who walks away
from that kind of money, Jian-Yang?
Richard, a crazy person.
Crazy? No. Opposite.
He walked away from $10 million,
now look at him.
Wet pants, stealing towels,
babbling about technical issues
that he can't solve.
I am one computational trust issue
away from solving this thing.
Is this how you want to end up?
(SIGHS DEEPLY)
No.
He's a cautionary tale.
RICHARD: Nope, not true.
Not a cautionary tale.
Got a lot of work to do.
I'll be in the pool. Not crazy.
- I mean, it's like... Wow. (LAUGHS)
- JARED: Richard.
Hey, uh, Erlich, just FYI,
I actually did some, um,
image recognition stuff on NipAlert,
so maybe you could hire me
to help on the demo.
'Cause my dad's been, like,
kind of on me lately to, like, get ajob,
or go to school,
'cause he's upset
that I lost all that money on PiperChat.
And then also you helped me
lose that 20 million on Bachmanity.
Big Head, um, Jian-Yang's culture,
he's... (WHISPERS) Chinese...
(NORMAL VOICE) ...won't allow
him to accept outside help.
Oh, right. 'Cause of Chinese.
Okay, well, that makes sense.
If either of you could aid in the construction
of this image recognition software,
I can pay you handsomely.
Huh. Five years at ASU, then you dropped out.
No degree?
BIG HEAD; Mm-hmm.
Pretty solid C's in all of your CS classes.
Right.
But really more incompletes than anything.
Yeah, a lot of those classes
were at 11:00 a.m., so...
I'm sorry.
But I don't think
you're Stanford CS material, Mr. Bighetti.
Yeah, that's totally fair. Thanks so much.
Have a nice day.
Oh, hey. Did you get this
at a party on Alcatraz?
Yes.
Oh, cool. I got one there, too.
Or, I mean, I guess technically
I bought one there. (LAUGHS)
I bought everything there.
Excuse me?
Oh, Bachmanity was my VC fund.
(GASPS) What?
- It stands for venture capital...
- I know. I'm...
(GASPS)
Wait, Nelson Bighetti.
Were you on the cover of Wired Magazine?
Yeah. And actually inside, too. (CHUCKLES)
Can I get you some coffee?
GAVIN: The last 24 hours
have been very painful.
But in the days to come,
what I will be thinking of most is all of you,
the good people of Hooli,
and what we've built together.
And yes, we built great products here,
great products.
But I like to think we built
an even greater connection,
so in the spirit of that connection,
if any of you would like
to say something to me,
positive or negative, this is the time.
I encourage you to be completely honest.
(MAN COUGHS)
(SIGHS)
Don't be shy.
This is most likely
the last chance we have to talk.
Anything at all?
(SCATTERED COUGHING)
Ah. Here we go.
Todd, our senior systems engineer.
(FOOTSTEPS ECHOING)
I'm sorry, but it's my official duty
to escort you off the property.
I understand. Thank you for your dedication.
And relieve you of your badge.
Yes.
I guess this is it then.
Good bye, Hoover.
Your parking hang tag.
RICHARD: I mean, do you think I'm crazy
for chasing this thing?
Don't ask me,
I'm hardly in a position to judge.
I mean, you do realize I'm literally
the only person in this entire grocery store
who's actually buying stuff for myself.
I don't know. Maybe these people are right.
Maybe I just drop this one,
move on and become some
pathetic fucking TaskRabbit, you know.
Hey, I have a family, asshole.
Oh, sorry, not you. The other ones.
Look, if you can't crack this idea,
there's no shame.
I mean, a lot of really smart people
have gotten stuck on it.
Please. Like who?
Peter Gregory for one.
Peter was thinking about
a fully decentralized Internet?
Why wouldn't you mention this to me?
Because he walked away from it
and you seemed so excited about it.
I thought you had a new angle.
I didn't want to discourage you.
Oh, what, 'cause I'm some delicate
little flower, I couldn't handle it?
The thing is, Peter tended
to cling to things and he gave up on this.
I mean, he must've had a reason.
Wait, Peter was
a compulsive note taker, right?
What about his journals?
I mean, do you guys still have them?
Richard, I am on thin ice as it is at Raviga.
No, Monica, listen to me, okay?
I haven't slept in days.
I'm walking into pools fully clothed.
This is all I think about.
Please.
Fine. Butjust this once.
- Yes. Thank you.
-(CELL PHONE BUZZES)
- Fuck, it's Erlich.
- What?
He wants me to help spin up this demo for
Jian-Yang's bullshit "Shazam for food" app.
Wait, the thing that Coleman Blair
just bought? That was them?
Yeah. But they haven't bought it yet.
I mean, they sign the deal on Monday.
But it's all contingent on a working demo,
which they do not and will not have.
- Interesting.
- Oh, you're doing great work, by the way.
- Fuck you.
- Definitely. Thank you.
I'll have those forms to you by Friday.
Yeah, so it's called SeeFood,
but it's S-E-E food, get it?
Yes, Erlich Bachman showed me a demo
and, I mean, this thing is incredible.
Yeah, and Coleman Blair is going to get
the whole deal for only 200K.
But here's the thing,
they don't close until Monday.
I mean, ifl had Laurie's ear,
I would tell her that we should
pay them today and close the deal.
And Bachman would jump on it in a second.
(SCOFFS AND MUTTERS)
Go choke on that, bro-han.
DINESH: Very funny.
- What's funny?
- This message.
"Hey, I'm a big fan of
what you did to Gavin Belson.
"L've seen your photo and think you're cute,
"would love to meet up. Mia."
- Fuck you.
- I didn't send that.
- Oh, you didn't?
- My hand to Satan.
Before you go ahead
and get a little brown boner in your pants,
you might want to consider
that it's not a woman.
I bet you're being catfished by Gavin himself.
Oh, fuck.
- But“
- But what?
On the off chance that this is
an actual, real woman,
getting murdered
seems like an acceptable risk.
(DOOR OPENS AND SHUTS)
- Oh, hey.
- Hey.
BIG HEAD: Let me ask you something.
Do you think wearing the name of the college
you're going to to class
is, like, the same thing
as wearing the name
of the band you're going to to a concert?
What?
- Did you get into Stanford?
- Yeah.
And this is totally going
to get my dad off my back.
And they said they liked my story.
So I'm going to take a CS class there,
and they're so nice.
I was asking if it was going to be pass/fail,
and they were like, "lt's up to you."
And then I said,
"ls there going to be homework?"
And they were like, "Only if you want it."
And so then, I guess
I have to decide if I want it.
Which kind of already feels like homework.
But do you think...
RICHARD: Holy shit.
It's like we just walked
right into Peter Gregory's brain.
Actually, I think Peter's brain
is in a cryo-locker in Menlo Park.
Oh, hey, I, uh, remember
this photo from Peter's office.
It's still so weird to me
that he and Gavin Belson were ever friends.
(WHIRS)
- AUTOMATED VOICE: Select destination.
- No, no, no.
- Optimizing route to Ara/Ion.
- No, thank you.
Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa.
Hold on. Wait, are all these
Peter Gregory's notebooks?
MONICA: Um...
- Are they? Are they his thoughts?
- Richard,
remember you promised
you were going to get some sleep tonight.
Yeah, lwill.
All right, I'm, uh,
going to leave you guys to it.
Oh. Uh,
Erlich didn't get a call
from Ed Chen today, did he?
Yeah. I, uh, heard them on speakerphone
'cause Erlich was Neti Potting.
I think, uh, they're meeting tonight.
Good to know.
- What?
-lt's sesame seeds.
- To SeeFood.
And to a fully expensed meal on Raviga's tab.
And to you, Ed Chen,
who pulled the wool over Laurie Bream's eyes
and got us two hundo-thou.
Sight unseen.
Well, she had some concerns
about getting into business with you again,
but I can pretty much talk
that broad into anything.
- Ha! Cheers to that.
-(LAUGHS)
(J IAN-YANG LAUGHS)
You're a con man, like Erlich.
(CHUCKLES) What does that mean?
It's a little term of endearment
we have around the house.
Uh, a confident man.
He sees me as a confident man,
and he looks up to me.
You know, you have to be patient with him,
'cause he's a bit of a moron.
- Moron?
- No, no, no.
I mean, he's not in tech,
and how about this palapa, huh?
Are we in the islands or what?
Sorry. This app isn't going to suck, right?
If it sucks, it's my ass.
You guys have a working demo, right?
(LAUGHING)
We're going to slow down on the, uh...
(STAMMERS) ...servings for the little one.
So, he's from China, a small town,
not used to our big city liquor,
and no, no, no, no...
Jian-Yang.
(SPEAKING MAN DARIN)
It's really very important.
You gotta provide us with a profitable app.
- No, I've never made any demo.
- No? Why?
(IN ENGLISH) Boys, boys.
Let's speak in English. It's the law.
(SPEAKING MAN DARIN)
What I wanna create is an octopus recipe.
An octopus recipe?
What I'm gonna say is...
(SPEAKING ENGLISH)
I'm a big fat fucking asshole.
Okay, now. That's me.
ERLICH: Why would I call myself
a big fat asshole?
The liquor's gotten to the little fellow.
And I wouldn't listen to a word he has to say.
(GUN FIRING ON VIDEO GAME)
Oh, uh, hey, Gilfoyle. This is Mia.
Are you going to murder Dinesh?
No.
Bummer.
Wait, Gilfoyle?
Are you the Gilfoyle from Bovine Dawn?
Maybe.
I'm M-l-four.
GILFOYLEI N0 shit.
I always thought you were a fat, bald weirdo.
Well, she's not. She's a thin, hairy regular.
You know, you were totally wrong
about the dump of all the
hacking team's best exploits.
No, if you look at what happened
with the Equation Group,
it was basically the same thing.
She's right. You're wrong.
Um, should we head out?
Don't wait up.
Oh, my God.
- Oh, my fucking God!
- Richard? What is it?
Jared, look. It's all here.
Peter Gregory knew the value
of a completely decentralized Internet.
I mean, look, look.
-(RICHARD READING)
-(CHUCKLES)
I mean, look.
Even back then, Peter was worried
that the Internet would become
this shitty corporate-controlled thing,
that Hooli and all these
other companies manipulate today.
But the idea is real.
It's just that Peter didn't think it was feasible
unless compression surpassed
the theoretical limit of a 2.9 Weissman Score.
We shattered that limit at TechCrunch Disrupt.
- Yeah, baby! Exactly.
- Ha!
I mean, God damn it. I always knew there was
a perfect application for my algorithm.
These notes, all this,
this is going to save me months, this is it.
I mean, lwas right all along, lwas right.
Can I try something?
Yeah.
(LAUGHS) W00!
- Okay.
- I don't know.
- Woo!
Woo! Woo!
Woo!
- Sorry.
- That's okay.
(MUSIC PLAYING FROM SPEAKERS)
So,
do you like movies?
It depends on the movie.
I'm the exact same way.
It being a movie
doesn't mean I'm going to like it.
Would you care for some wine
or a cocktail tonight?
Uh, just water, please.
Just water, please.
I love water. I do.
Oceans, rivers, lakes.
When does a pond become a lake?
I wonder if it's depth.
Where are those waters?
I felt like we ordered waters a while ago.
- And they're... What?
-(CELL PHONE BUZZES)
(MUTTERS) Fucking prick.
What?
Oh, nothing. It wasjust a text from Gilfoyle.
Gilfoyle isn't a prick.
- Yeah, I'm sorry.
- He's a motherfucking prick.
- What?
- That guy sucks.
Everyone hates him on the message boards.
You know, putting a face to the name
made so much sense.
- Right, 'cause his face sucks, too. Yeah.
- Totally.
I have to find this one post of his,
it was insane.
You know, he has no friends.
He pretends like he's all dry and witty,
but he's just a monotone piece of shit.
And being a Satanistjust means you're ugly
and you're leaning into it.
(LAUGHS)
- That's right.
-(LAUGHS)
You know what, can I get a glass of Malbec?
Unless, do you want to get a bottle?
Yeah, let's get a bottle of Malbec.
- Fucking Gilfoyle.
-(LAUGHING) Right?
(STUDENTS CHATTERING)
Mr. Bighetti. When you're ready.
Uh, ready for what?
(CLASS LAUGHS)
I'm like the class clown already. (CHUCKLES)
Why is my name on the board?
(CLASS LAUGHS)
(MUTTERS) Oh, n0.
Laurie, you wanted to see me?
Oh. Yes, Monica. Sit.
Are you pregnant?
Yes.
Congratulations.
- On?
- On being pregnant.
Oh.
Yes.
Friday afternoon, Ed Chen convinced rne
to bid against Coleman Blair
on an app entitled "SeeFood."
It's run by Bachman,
and the one who smoked in the offices.
Well, Ed is very persuasive.
This morning he made the case
that since you have a longstanding
relationship with Bachman,
and since you are a talented VC
who deserves a second chance,
his words,
you should take lead.
What?
RICHARD: I mean, look at this drawing.
I drew the exact same thing
on my doctor's butt paper.
I mean, Peter had the exact same idea,
he was just waiting
for compression to catch up.
Which it did, thanks to me.
(LAUGHS)
Cheer up, Richard.
Yes, but here's the best part, okay.
Peter never foresaw the ubiquity of
Internet-connected computing devices.
Right?
Cameras, refrigerators, TVs, baby monitors,
not to mention the billions-plus smartphones
that are floating around the world.
I mean, who here has a smart phone, right?
You, you, me, Jian-Yang, Dinesh, Monica.
Richard, you don't have to name
everyone you know.
Point is, you all thought I was crazy
when lwalked into the swimming pool
with my clothes on.
- But it turns out I was fucking right, okay?
-(DOOR OPENS AND SHUTS)
So not crazy.
Opposite, you poor idiots.
(LAUGHS)
How was school, Timmy?
Oh, not great. They made me teach.
Teach what?
Stanford.
You're a professor
at Stanford now, Big Head?
No, that would be crazy. I'm a guest lecturer.
-(DOOR KNOB RATTLES)
-(KNOCKING ON DOOR)
(POUNDING ON DOOR)
What are you doing?
It was open. And you have the keys.
Huh.
Strange, did you change the locks?
'Cause the keys were working last night
when I went for my date.
'Cause I haven't come back
to the house since my date. So...
I did sex on her.
- Good.
- Cool.
Yeah, that's great.
Nice, man. Who is she?
Um, her name is Mia.
And she is a-Mia-zing.
Um, she hates Gilfoyle
almost as much as I do, so...
Huh.
Jumping headlong
into a sexual relationship with M-l-four.
Ballsy.
But I'm sure you've thought
through the consequences.
Well, we weren't really doing a lot of thinking.
You know what I mean?
Oh, wow.
Mia is a legit hacker.
People say that she's taken
on the Chinese government,
and here you are after one meal
in an intimate relationship.
So?
So, what do you think she'll do
if you try to break up with her?
GILFOYLE: Or disagree with her?
Or disappoint her in any way?
Like by confessing
that you're badass takedown of Gavin Belson
was a total accident.
Unless you've already told her.
It didn't come up.
Well, I'm sure that when she finds out
that your entire relationship
is based on a lie of omission,
she'll be very understanding.
So what? We just won't break up.
Ever?
- Even
-(DOOR OPENS)
Erlich, do you know how badly Ed Chen
just fucked me with Laurie?
Let me tell you something,
a threesome is always awkward,
especially the first one.
- Laurie being a little bit older...
-l'm talking about SeeFood.
What do you and Jian-Yang have?
Oh.
A whole lot of nothing.
-(SIGHS)
- Are you... No. No, no, no.
SeeFood has to be great.
Myjob depends on it.
Ed Chen bailed
and dumped the whole thing on me.
Richard, can I speak with you
in the kitchen for a moment?
Yep. Sure.
So, what's up?
Well, here's the thing.
Remember that phone number
you were curious about in here?
Well, it's not a phone number,
it's a patent number.
A patent for exactly
what you were planning to build.
Uh, so Peter patented it.
No. I, um, spoke to Brian Fong.
Who?
- JARED: Brian Fong.
- Oh.
He told me that Peter
was very excited about the idea,
but there was some resentment
that he wasn't focused more
on what the team was working on.
So, one of them went out
and got a patent on it.
Why didn't this guy pursue it?
Well, the patent was just a roadblock
to keep Peter focused
on the company they were starting.
A company that went on
to be known as Hooli.
Wait, wait, wait.
(INHALES DEEPLY)
So you're telling me
that the perfect application of my algorithm
belongs to Gavin fucking Belson.
I'm afraid so.
Richard? Are you okay?
-(CLATTERING)
Uh, yes, just putting something away.
(CLATTERING)
(PANTING)
(DOOR CLOSES)
Yep, not crazy.
Qpposite.
-(POUNDS ON DOOR)
- JARED: Richard, you got to let me in.
I have your shoe.
All right, I'm sorry to barge in here,
but you have to eat something or you'll...
(INTERCOM TRILLS AND RINGS)
-(cucl<s)
- MAN: (ow INTERCOM) Hello.
Uh, hi. It's Richard. Hendricks.
Uh, Richard Hendricks.
I'm here for Gavin Belson
and we really need to talk.
(INTERCOM BEEPS)
(GATE BANGS, CLAN KING)
(BLUE FLOWERS PLAYING)