(INSECTS CHIRPING)
(KNOCK ON DOOR)
I know it's the middle of the night. I
reallyjust need five minutes of your time.
RICHARD: Holy shit. What happened?
GAVIN: I was working through some issues.
Mind the glass.
What the fuck is this?
It's a license for your
peer-to-peer computer communication patent.
It's very standard stuff.
Uh, essentially, in
exchange for your patent,
you would get a royalty and equity
in the new company that I'm starting up.
So, if you just sign there,
by the Post-it note,
and lwill take it, and leave,
and you will never see me again.
Are you joking? (CHUCKLES)
Uh, well, I guess we could hang out.
Richard, stop talking.
I was just ousted from my own company,
a company I built from the ground up.
My legacy is in ashes.
Come on. I wouldn't say that.
- Well, The Wall Street Journal said that.
- Oh.
I lost everything
because of something you did,
and you're here at 3:00 a.m.
asking me for a favor?
Really? You're a mean person, Richard.
You know that?
You're a bad guy.
No, no, no, no. lwouldn't say that.
I think maybe what's happening is that
you're just not understanding the
technology I'm trying to build here.
Oh, so, now I'm stupid, too?
I know what the technology is, Richard.
I have a patent on it.
What the fuck is the matter with you?
So, you're not gonna sign it?
No, I'm not gonna sign this!
Jesus, you're a fucking sadist,
you know that?
You're demented.
I'm almost tempted to let you have a run at it,
just to watch you waste your fucking time.
This technology did not work
when Peter theorized it,
and it doesn't work now.
It... It actually does work now.
- It does.
- Oh, really?
When did the laws of physics change?
When I exceeded the theoretical limit
of compression at TechCrunch.
- You were there.
- I know I was there,
thank you for bringing up
that very painful memory.
Okay.
Can I... Can ljust...
- What?
- Draw on this?
Sure. Why not? It's
shattered, just like I am.
I read Peter's notes, all of them.
And, uh, he knew that a peer-to-peer
Internet was possible, in the future.
But he was also basing that
on what, old desktop computers?
He never, ever, foresaw the ubiquity or
power of all of our modern-day smartphones.
He was also dealing with
a completely different Weissman limit.
So, uh, yeah. Yeah, okay.
What is that?
Is that number correct?
The delta in mean device efficiency?
Yeah, it is.
See, eventually, over time,
this will render every server
that Hooli operates obsolete.
Which would make Jack Barker shit himself.
- Holy shit.
- You know what, actually, I'm gonna...
Welcome to the future, Gavin.
Whoa! Oh, no! Oh, no!
- Son of a bitch!
- L'm sorry.
(THEME MUSIC PLAYING)
MONICA: Wow, Dinesh.
This front end design looks great.
- Thank you.
- Nice work.
What's in that?
Uh, that is a burrito for the test.
- Good to know.
- Oh.
Let him have it.
Gilfoyle thought
he was too good to work on SeeFood,
and now he's about to lose a fortune.
- So...
- Okay.
Ready for test.
After you, milady.
Oh, this is weird. Miajust texted me,
"Good luck with the demo."
Did any of you guys tell her about this?
Your hacker girlfriend
wouldn't happen to know
the model of our router, would she?
Yeah, actually.
She complimented your choice.
Why didn't you say anything?
Why would I tell you
she said something nice about you?
Dammit!
We have to assume she's everywhere.
Okay. It's ready.
Please, God.
What would you say if I told you
there's an app on the market...
We're past that part! Just demo it.
Okay. Let's start with a hotdog.
(CHIMES)
Holy shit!
- Yes!
- MONICA: It works!
- ERLICH: Motherfuck!
- Huzzah!
Jian-Yang, my beautiful
little Asiatic friend,
I'm going to buy you the
palapa of your life.
We will have 12 posts, braided palm leaves.
You'll never feel exposed again.
I'm gonna be rich.
Fuck you, Gilfoyle.
- Do pizza!
- Yes, do pizza.
- Yeah.
- Do pizza.
Pizza.
MONICA: "Not hotdog"?
- Wait, what the fuck?
- Huh?
That's it? It only does hotdogs?
No. And not hotdog.
- Gimme that. Give it to me.
- (LAUGHING)
(SIGHS) Jian-Yang.
Motherfuck.
I gave you the ability to spin gold,
and instead you spun pubic hair,
with shit in it and gravel and corn.
Hold on, hold on.
Jian-Yang's actually put together
a pretty good classifier.
You know, I mean, the core tech is valid.
Itjust needs to be trained.
So, what he did for hotdogs,
he needs to repeat
for every food in existence?
No. That's very boring work.
That's scraping the Internet
for thousands of food pictures.
You can hire someone else.
We can't, because we just spent
a big, fat stack of cash
on little Dinesh over here.
And there are other expenses.
Legal, marketing, operating fees,
those goddamned AWS charges.
Fucking Bezos. (INHALES SHARPLY)
And so, we do not have the funds
to hire scut workers
to do your scraping for you.
And thus, you will scrape the Internet.
You and you alone.
I'm sorry, the time to back out
was before you signed the term sheet.
I'm gonna tell Laurie
that this was a smashing success.
Go make it one.
Erlich was right.
You're a white witch.
Uh...
(SIGHS)
Oh.
Good. Yes, you are all here.
Um, I think it's probably time
we all had a chat.
About what?
Well, I'm pretty sure
you're all wondering where I've been.
- You were gone?
- Yes. I was gone all week.
I saw you come out of the shower yesterday.
Okay.
Uh, well, obviously,
I've been sleeping here at night.
But I've been gone during the day.
Pretty sure that shower was in the morning.
- That's part of the day, Richard.
- Okay, Gilfoyle.
I've been sleeping here at night,
and then I've been here for some mornings,
but I've left the house during the day.
We all leave the house
during the day, Richard.
That's not weird.
I went to get coffee this morning.
Yeah, I went to the dispensary.
And then I'd smoked the weed
before I got home,
so I went back to the dispensary.
You know what?
I just realized
I haven't left the house in six days.
Now that's worth exploring.
Okay, I get it.
Look, every day this week, I have been
- at Gavin Belson's house.
- What?
Gavin has offered
to go into business together.
(JARED SCOFFS)
But, look, ljust came there for the patent.
And he was the one
who wanted to be full partners.
(LAUGHS) What did you say?
We talked about it, and we agreed
that it would be the best thing to do.
Oh, good Lord. Richard. No.
Guys, look. I have the patent.
I also have funding.
And real, genuine insight
into the whole thing.
Let's not forget here
that Gavin is a co-founder
of a bajillion-dollar tech company.
Are you out of your fucking mind?
When you don the skin of the beast,
the man within dies.
What is that, Nietzsche?
One of the boys at my group home
always said that.
He died.
You're not pulling Dinesh off SeeFood.
And I am not leaving SeeFood
to go work for Gavin fucking Belson.
I'm not asking you to.
You're not?
Guys, do you not remember
the last time we talked
about us all working with Gavin Belson?
Gilfoyle, you told me
to chortle your balls.
And everybody else walked out of the room.
I know how much you hate him,
which is exactly why I told Gavin
if we were gonna do this thing,
that you guys wouldn't be coming with.
So, we have hired a recruiter
to find people to replace you guys.
Even me?
Well, no.
You don't really need to be replaced.
It's true. I can't be replaced.
Well, when you left video chat, you did
keep the rights to the algorithm. So...
I mean, it's weird, but I guess
it's really none of our business.
It's my fucking business.
- I now own 10%...
- 5%, actually.
- What?
- 10% of my half of the company is 5%.
But I mean, look, your shares are gonna be
worth a whole lot more than they ever would,
now with the patent
and Gavin being involved, so...
So, then we're all good
here, I guess. Right?
I think that's right.
Weird.
All right. Well, thanks for understanding.
You're welcome.
I don't think we need to
be afraid of the Wi-Fi.
It's pronounced "Wifey,"
and clearly you don't understand
the threat level of the person
that you're sexually disappointing.
We're going hard wire.
What about my phone?
You mean the thing
that tracks your movement,
and every interaction you have?
Literally, your fingerprint?
The second you're on Wi-Fi it's like
you're leaving her alone with your phone.
So, actually leaving her
alone with my phone,
that would be bad?
You fucking idiot.
I was in the bathroom.
For how long?
Awhile.
(INDISTINCT CHATTER)
Who's that?
Oh, Richard's meeting with Brett Saxby.
GILFOYLE: From Hooli?
Formerly. The recruiter sent him over.
He's interviewing him
for Head of Engineering.
Why? That guy sucks.
Why is Richard in there with Brett Saxby?
He was in Gavin's inner circle.
Is Richard aware of that?
Is anyone taking notes?
Does Richard even have a pen?
That's so funny.
It's 10:00 a.m.
Why are they drinking beer?
Because he sucks.
Did Dick say who else he was meeting with?
The recruiter sent him
like a whole big list right there.
Gonna be late for class.
How's that going?
Uh, it's okay.
I'm just a little nervous
I might run out of material soon.
We already watched the Facebook movie,
A.I., The Net, and half of Tron.
Which Tron?
What? No, Tron.
There's two Trons.
Oh, shit. That's awesome.
Should get me through another week.
Thanks!
This entire list is a
shitshow of shitheads.
Why would Richard trust a recruiter
to source him recruits?
- It doesn't make sense.
- Huh.
- What?
- You guys seem like super-invested
in who Richard hires
to work with Gavin Belson, that's all.
Are you insinuating jealousy?
- This is just concern for Richard's vision.
- Mmm-hmm.
If Richard wants to saddle himself
with mediocrity, go for it.
You did not.
- BRETT: I swear to God, bro. I swear to God.
- (LAUGHING)
Well, I tell you what. Next time you bust
out the old Sea-Doo, give me a call.
Uh, guys, you know Brett?
Nope.
It's great to meet you guys.
We've met.
Uh, okay. Well, it has been a pleasure.
I shall walk you to your car.
All right, after me.
- Yeah.
- Okay.
I hate him.
Gentlemen, ljust paid
the palapa contractor.
The palapa piper, so to speak.
The dream is a reality.
We will no longer be
exposed to the elements.
Hey, Erlich.
You wanna guess
who's on this list of availables
that Richard just got from his recruiter?
Who?
Your boy Jian-Yang.
- What?
Jian-Yang!
You already have a fucking job, Jian-Yang.
You have to finish SeeFood.
Now get to food scraping.
I fucking hate SeeFood.
I have to look at different hotdogs.
There's Chinese hotdogs,
Polish hotdogs, Jewish hotdogs.
It's fucking stupid.
Well, here, here's one more for ya.
See? Hotdog.
Doesn't even fucking work right.
You should hire someone
using company money,
not build a roof over nothing.
The palapa was budgeted for, Jian-Yang.
That's what you do when you get funding,
you upscale your workspace
to help with recruiting.
You just said you recruit no one.
Because we spent all the
money on upscaling.
Why is this so confusing?
You stealing.
If you can steal, I can quit.
I have meetings at Periscope, Airbnb,
good companies.
The fuck you do.
We still have $150,000
of Raviga's money left.
That's three months of burn.
So, 'til we are dick up and flat broke,
this is your life.
Get to it.
This is no life.
I want to live.
Erase that dick picture.
TOM HAN KS: (AS JOE) You've got mail.
MEG RYAN: (AS KATHLEEN) Yes.
TOM HANKS: (AS JOE)
Those are very powerful words.
- Sorry.
- No, it's okay.
Your phone has technology inside it.
So, you're double learning.
- (ENGINE ROARING)
- (MUSIC PLAYING OVER SPEAKERS)
Jian-Yang, what in the good fuck is that?
It's called business expense.
You buy a hut.
I buy a car.
You say keep doing SeeFood
until money is gone.
Now, the money is gone.
Dick
is up.
Where'd you get those sunglasses,
did they come with the car?
These are from your mom.
Listen, Jian-Yang.
You can'tjust blow the rest of our runway
on a Corvette.
- Who's gonna scrape the Internet?
- (MUSIC PLAYING)
Twelve-speaker sound system.
It's very loud. Very expensive.
What the fuck was that?
Oh, just three months of runway being
driven off by 90 pounds of asshole.
Spoken by a 280-pound pile of shit.
The fuck are you gonna do now?
Professor Bighetti, a word if you please?
Richard.
I know it's none of my business,
but I worked
with that Brett Saxby fellow at Hooli.
He's a talented engineer,
but in an office environment,
he can be both tardy and fresh.
Uh, I'm not hiring him.
He uses spaces, not tabs.
I see. Okay.
Well, that's a relief.
But, Richard,
what about the next Brett Saxby?
Or the Brett Saxby after that?
And even if you vet them all,
you are still in a room with Gavin.
So? We're partners. What's your point?
He and his posse of bandits and cutthroats
will turn on you in a second.
You need me.
The half-crazed, half-Apache
who will do anything to get your back.
I'll scalp Gavin ifl have to,
and all the rest of those
pale-faced sons of bitches.
I'll kill them with knives.
I'll kill them With guns.
I'll kill them with my hands.
I'll talk them into suicide.
It doesn't matter.
All right, Jared.
I think what you're asking is...
You want a job?
If you think you can find a place for me.
Yeah. Of course, Jared.
You're more than welcome to work on this.
(EXHALES)
Butjust to be clear,
you're not gonna stab anyone, are you?
(LAUGHING)
Oh, it feels good to laugh.
(SIGHS AND CHUCKLES)
So, that's a no, then?
(LAUGHING)
Richard.
So, we're not gonna finish the movie?
Yeah, sorry.
But my colleague here was pretty adamant
that a better use of class time might be
to learn while accomplishing something.
Now, take one, pass it all the way down.
We're supposed to scrape the Internet
for thousands of food images?
Yeah. So, you'll find like five,
or 30,000 pictures of your food.
And then put them in a folder
with that food's name on it.
And it's good if you get like,
weird angles or lighting of your food.
So, it should be pretty fun.
So, we're gathering training data
to run through a convolutional neural net.
Like an image classifier?
Who wants broccoli?
Broccolini, for the ladies? Broccoli.
Just so you know,
this does not mean I don't trust her.
I'm just doing this so you'll,
like, shut up and leave me alone.
Mia, if you're listening, you're so pretty.
Oh, you're both headed to Gavin's?
Indeed we are.
Together again.
Butch Cassidy
and his head of business development.
RICHARD: Oh, wow.
Another Western reference.
Yaw! (CHUCKLES)
Let's go.
You know, he'd hire you, too.
What?
All you have to do
is admit that you want the job.
And like, get down on your knees and beg.
Says the guy who's romancing a woman
through a phone that isn't even on.
A woman that he described to me in private
as a skinny little fuck factory.
Oh! N0, ldidn"t! God.
Mia, lwould never do that.
Richard, Brett Saxby
ran my data analytics team for three years.
Respectfully, I think passing on him
is a mistake.
Yes. Well, I met with
Brett Saxby and, um...
Uh... To be honest...
To be honest, I don't think he's our man.
Fair enough. There are
plenty of good alternatives on this list.
Although I'm a little confused
by your notes on some of these people.
"David Burnham.
"Annoying slob, fucked-up face, I could
write better Python with my asshole."
You know what, I think, you have my list.
Yes. I have a very weird shorthand.
Yeah.
Okay. Next.
Becca... No, guys. That
goes in the sun room.
I'll show you. All right. Back in a flash.
Come this way, gentlemen. Here.
God, there are pages of
graphic insults here.
Fucking Gilfoyle.
Right?
Richard, would you be open
to having Gilfoyle on the team?
Oh, yeah. Of course.
I mean, I'd hire him in a second,
but he'd never do it.
Richard, Gilfoyle is a
man of intense pride.
So, when he refers to a potential employee
as a "pig-faced fuck nose,"
what I hear is, "l need to be needed."
Well, what I hear is pig-faced fuck nose.
Exactly.
I mean, Gilfoyle's insults
are normally well-crafted, almost poetic.
Last week, he referred to me
as Frankenstein's bulimic daughter.
Yeah. I get what you mean. (SCOFFS)
So, what do you want me to do, Jared?
Beg him?
Well, I think a little outreach
would be in the company's best interest.
And really, "butt-dick"?
The man's in pain.
Hey, I know this system is super-confusing,
but we don't see any completed assignments.
Cut the shit. Where's the work?
Well, we all got to talking
the other day after class.
We couldn't figure out
if you were like a TA,
or why you were giving us assignments,
but we all agreed we didn't like the way that
you were speaking to Professor Bighetti.
I'm used to it.
So, we searched your name on PitchBook,
and that SeeFood app
you got funded at Raviga popped up.
PitchBook?
How do you have access to PitchBook?
Your idea was so simple,
it was like something you could come
up with in the room during a meeting.
Which is what Garrett from Coleman Blair
told us at the CS undergrad mixer on Friday.
Hey, Erlich. Here I am.
Class of '06.
Go Cardinal.
Anyways, we founded our own
Shazam for food company,
- and he's funding us.
- Mmm-hmm.
- Congrats!
- Wait, that's stealing.
No, it's exactly what Mark Zuckerberg did
to the Winklevi in that Facebook movie
Professor Bighetti had us watch.
And he was the hero of that film.
And with all of us working together,
we'll easily beat you to market.
So, that's how it goes, huh? Hmm?
You steal a man's idea,
rendering his company worthless?
I've read a number of disparaging articles
about your generation in The Atlantic
and Slate.com summaries.
It's all true.
Trigger warning, fuck you.
Professor Bighetti, I'll see you at home.
You apologize?
In this case, yes, I apologize.
Who am I to advise you
on your very valuable company?
It's time to let you go, like a bird.
So, go out there, without me.
Make your recipe app.
Take your meetings.
Live.
That being said, since there's no cash
to buy me out, I propose this.
Allow me to keep the palapa,
and give me the 'vette.
You're cashing out?
Dinesh, stay out of this please.
Car and a hut for 10%.
It's a palapa.
Okay. It's a deal.
You know, the car was a mistake.
I was driving next to a store window.
And I stop and look in my reflection.
I look like an asshole.
Yes, I'm sure it was just the car.
A little piece of advice
regarding American culture.
A Corvette takes a certain sort of man
to be able to pull off.
Like a fedora.
Anyway. keys?
Oh, and now that I'm out of the company,
you'll need to tell Monica what transpired.
Thank you.
Gentlemen, I'm off to be
out and about in the 'vette.
Be back for supper, that is, of course, unless
I get fucked to death by the fairer sex.
Gilfoyle, Richard would like a moment,
if you don't mind.
You guys need me to go somewhere else?
No, it's fine. You can stay.
You can hear this. Uh...
Okay. Well, Gilfoyle,
I have reviewed the candidates
and it is very clear to me
that our company cannot succeed
without your unrivaled talents
as a systems architect.
So, would you please, please, please,
please come work for Pied Piper?
Thanks for asking.
I'm going to put this
as delicately as I know how.
You can chortle my balls.
Okay. Wow.
So, who do we want to run front-end dev?
"Cunt-ass" or "fuck-jerk"?
Listen.
This thing with Gavin
isn't gonna work without me.
So, because I feel bad for you, and because
I'd hate to see you fuck up good tech,
which will happen if I'm not there,
I'm willing to help you.
That's a beautiful gesture.
So, you're back aboard?
FYI, Becca Thorton is a cancerous prolapsed
anus of a human being,
but as a systems engineer,
she's not all bad.
Laufle?
Oh! Yes. Monica, come in.
Ljust heard the good news.
About...
Jian-Yang's nimble pivot.
Back away from the glass, please.
Special occasion!
He told me the whole story.
His interview at Periscope,
his discovery of the photo
of Bachman's genitals on his phone,
when demonstrating the app,
and his eureka moment.
When it turned out
that his "not hotdog" technology
outperformed Periscope's own technology.
He said all that?
Not quickly.
The eventual point, Jian-Yang
unwittingly crafted an amazing tool
for the real-time detection
and filtering of penile imagery.
I mean, Periscope does have a dick problem.
Monica. Ugh.
Jian-Yang went to Periscope for a job,
and walked out
with a $4 million acquisition offer.
Given our liquidation preference,
we have 10-X'd in two weeks.
So, hats off.
Well, thank you so much...
To Ed Chen for his shrewd call,
both to invest in this and make you lead.
He is quite astute.
Which is why
we've promoted him to senior partner.
Yeah.
(PHONE RINGING)
Monica, you've got Erlich.
I'm here with Jian-Yang and he just told me
that you traded 10% of the company
for a used car and a...
A hut.
A hut?
A palapa. And so what?
What do you mean
it's a half-a-million-dollar palapa?
JIAN-YANG:
Erlich, is the refrigerator running?
It's Mike Hunt.
And he's rich.
Shit!
Oh, hey, um,
when you begged Richard for the job,
did you actually, like,
literally lick his boots?
Or did you just go,
like, "Pretty please, Richard?
"Please, can I have ajob, Richard?"
Whatever I did, it was worth it
for the chance to work without you.
Speaking of, did your deal with Periscope
ever close?
Yep.
If I stay a year,
I vest a big chunk of Twitter stock.
- Great.
- DINESH: Great.
And what exactly are you working on?
Oh, you know, we're tuning our algorithm.
We're reconfiguring our
classifier from food to
another purpose.
Uh-huh.
In other words, you sit around
and look at dick pics all day long.
Don't let me stop you.
Wow.
I would say not safe for work,
but this is your work.
For a year.
At least.
Is that one
actually a hotdog?
Nope.
Not hotdog.
(THEME MUSIC PLAYING)