(LAUGHING)
That's a good one, Richard.
No, but seriously, what
brings you in today?
No, I am serious.
I would like an STD check.
What, did you graze your penis
against a toilet seat?
- No. I had sex.
- Sex with what?
- Female.
- A female what?
A female human.
And I don't know this woman very well,
and we didn't use a condom.
Now listen, Richard,
I wouldn't worry so much.
People don't really get STDs anymore.
We'll get your test back soon,
and I would tell you not to have sex
before then, but let's face it,
lightning ain't gonna strike twice, is it?
- (LAUGHING)
- lt's possible.
- Huh?
- Lt's possible.
No.
Hey, here's something strange.
Would you mind hopping up
on that scale for a sec?
Okay. Why, am I gaining weight?
I have been working like crazy,
eating like crap.
I haven't been exercising
at all really, so...
Yeah. Look at that.
You are an inch shorter
than you were this time last year.
You're shrinking, my friend.
(STAMMERS) How's that possible?
Well, you just told me.
It's your unhealthy lifestyle, Richard.
It's a loss of mineral bone density.
So, what do I do?
I'm gonna put you on calcium supplements,
and I'm gonna have you come back
in about three weeks.
I'll see you then.
Or whatever's left of you.
(LAUGHING)
(THEME MUSIC PLAYING)
MONICA: So, Erlich, good news.
Keenan Feldspar signed his term sheet
and we are now officially negotiating
the finer points of his deal.
Fantastic!
Well, now, the real work begins.
To that end, we would like to clarify
our arrangement with you.
We feel that a generous finder's fee
will be more than satisfactory.
This meeting is over.
This is very generous,
but I was under the impression that, um,
I was going to be hired here.
And I've actually told quite a few people
that I was hired,
so if I wasn't,
then it would look like I was fired.
That is fine.
No.
Laurie, I will not allow you to make
the same mistake
that Uber, Palantir, Zenefits,
and in my earlier years, Chipotle
made by not hiring me.
All right. Don't hire me.
But can you hack this finder's fee
into 52 installments,
paid weekly over the
course of the next year?
You mean, a salary?
Those are your words, not mine.
The finder's fee and 10,000 to go away?
You know, looking around at Bream-Hall,
I see a lot of the same.
Same gender...
Both partners happen to be female, Erlich.
Great catch. What's your point?
There is a grotesque gender imbalance
in the VC field right now.
I can help you navigate the toxicity
of this male culture,
which is encroaching on
our feminist island.
I mean, for instance, there's something
called mansplaining.
- Have you heard about this?
- We know what mansplaining is.
Mansplaining is when a man will
condescendingly explain something
to a woman that she already knows.
Mr. Bachman, we have work to do.
All right.
Laurie, half the finder's
fee for me to stay.
I don't think that you'll
find an associate,
um, with my track record at a better price.
It's my final offer. Take it or leave it.
I need this.
Fine. You may start Monday.
Okay. Ooh.
This Monday?
That's fine. Of course.
(KEYBOARD CLACKING)
What's that?
SonicWall SonicPointA.C.E.,
paired with the T.Z. 600.
Top-of-the-line firewall protection,
built-in intrusion prevention,
SSL decryption and inspection,
application control, and content filtering.
Saying "new router"
would be so much quicker.
Dinesh, the one good thing that came
out of you slapping your body
against that cyberterrorist
in a vulgar parody of the act of love
is that we finally have a network
with real security value.
Why would we need it?
Mia is in a federal facility
with no access to the Internet.
Right.
And she has never shown a proclivity
for getting around infrastructure.
Did you see this?
We've only been live for two weeks
and we just cracked the top 500
in the Hooli app store.
Oh, look at that.
Ranked 499.
Of utilities.
Yeah. Subgroup mobile, subgroup storage.
True.
But, overall, we're firmly in
the top 30,000 HooliPhone apps.
I mean, we may not be a global epidemic yet,
but we've leapt from bat saliva to humans,
and we've just killed our
first few villagers.
JIAN-YANG: This warm.
This warm.
- This warm.
- I get it, Jian-Yang!
The refrigerator's broken.
The ice cream is melting.
Let me guess, is it because it's warm?
- Yes.
- Fine.
I'll call the repairman,
and he'll come here and fix it posthaste.
No.
I want a new fridge.
A smarter fridge like this.
$14,000 for a smart fridge?
Unlike you, I now work for a living.
I'm not gonna drop that kind of dough
on a fridge.
I ordered already. I buy it for myself.
Then why are you talking to me about it?
To make you feel bad.
Because you're fat and poor.
- (PHONE RINGING)
- (SIGHS)
Go for Erlich.
ED: E. Bachman. E. Chen.
Got your message.
Bream-Hall, huh?
Yes. Starting today.
I hope that this doesn't create
any tension between us,
us now being competitors and all.
ED: Hey. None-zo.
Hey, while I have you, some of the boys are
part of the ownership group of the Warriors.
We have an extra spot on the floor
at Oracle Arena. You a hoops guy?
Oops. Uh, sorry, you broke up.
Could you, uh... Could you say that again?
We have an extra spot on the floor tonight
at Oracle Arena.
You a hoops guy?
What red-blooded American male
in the VC boys' club isn't?
Okay, cool. I'll text you the deets.
Later, man.
VVeH, boys.
I've been in the VC game forjust one day,
and already I have floor seats
to watch the Warriors.
But you hate basketball.
I'll concede that spending all my time
inside of a house
with you scrawny code jockeys,
the Incredible Shrinking Hendricks,
- and whatever the fuck Jared is here...
- (JARED CHUCKLES)
may have blunted my conventional
masculinity a hair.
- But it's always been there.
- Uh-huh.
Well, try and get a
selfie with Steph Curry.
I will, assuming she's there.
Hey, Jared, um, look at this e-mail here.
Uh, "Dear Richard, I recently became aware
of your Space Saver app.
"L think your app may infringe upon
my own patented technology.
"If your schedule permits, I would love to
discuss this with you as soon as possible.
"Sincerely, Stewart Burke."
What, I thought we handled the
patent stuff. We own it, right?
Yeah. I'll send him a harshly worded
cease and desist letter.
Actually, uh, his work address
is some house in Mountain View.
He's probably just working
out of his garage, just like us.
Why don't I go over there,
walk him through the app,
you know, coder to coder.
I'm sure it'll be fine.
You've got a big heart.
Or maybe just seems big,
'cause the rest of him is shrinking.
(KNOCKING ON DOOR)
Hi. Richard Hendricks.
- We exchanged e-mails?
- No.
- Are you Stewart Burke?
- L'm sorry. Does Stewart Burke live here?
- Yeah. (SIGHS)
Okay.
Is he in? Can I speak with him?
Grandpa! Some guy's here.
My grandson is the software expert.
I couldn't tell a computer from a toaster.
Oh. So, you're not a coder?
Oh, no. Not at all.
I am an attorney.
I started out in the medical field,
then the auto industry,
and then the music business.
Did you represent all these people?
No, I sued them.
Look, that's me with Stevie Wonder.
He never saw it coming.
Do you get it?
Yes, because he's blind.
- (CLICKS TONGUE)
- Right.
I'm sorry, I don't know
what this has to do...
You see this?
This is a song I bought
at a copyright auction.
It's an old mariachi number that cost me
practically nothing,
and so far has bought me two houses
and put my village idiot grandson
- through six years of Emerson.
- Oh.
All that from Cancion de Amores?
- Was it a popular song?
- No.
I used the copyright on this song
to sue writers of all kinds of songs.
Anyway, the writers usually settle, pay
me off, or give me a chunk of their song.
Thanks to Cancion de Amores here,
I now own 10% of Katrina and the Waves'
Walking on Sunshine.
- Mmm.
- Lt's a classic.
And when it runs next month
on Mazda's new Super Bowl spot,
I print money.
But sadly, all the good music copyrights
are gone.
That is so sad.
And that's why I moved into tech.
And now I sue people like you.
What?
So, he's a patent troll?
Yep.
Guys like him buy a ton of super broad IP
from failed startups at auction,
and then threaten litigation against
accused infringers, i.e. you.
So, uh, how much is Burke asking for?
$20,000.
Ah. You're getting off easy.
Well, no. Look, his patent covers
"storage of media files on a network."
I mean, that cannot be enforceable.
It's probably not. (SIGHS)
But to find out, you're gonna have
to fight him in court.
For a good litigator, we're talking at least
(BLOWS RASPBERRY) couple hundred grand.
Just pay him the 20 grand, Richard.
I could get creative and take some money
out of the Melcher deal.
There you go.
RICHARD: No. We need that money.
This is a shakedown. He's a crook.
And right when our app
is getting off the ground.
Well, that's how he found you.
Guys just landed on the
app store top 500 list,
- right?
- Yeah.
So, Burke starts at the bottom of
those lists, works his way up.
The more settlements he gets,
the stronger his case.
Higher you are on the list,
the more money he asks for.
It's like... It's like limp biscuit.
He sued those guys, too?
Not the band, the thing the band
is named after.
Limp biscuit's an old frat ritual
where all the brothers race to
stroke one out onto a biscuit,
and then the last guy to nut has to eat it.
(CHUCKLES)
Right. Sometimes it's a Wheat Thin.
Look, Richie. I get it.
It's embarrassing to pull your pud
in front of the whole pledge class.
Just pay the 9W-
Or maybe we convince the entire pledge class to
not play the game at all in the first place.
(CHUCKLES) lr only...
- (CLEARS THROAT)
- (FRIDGE CHIMES)
This must be the new fridge.
You like this?
Look, it has a screen so you can see
all the food that's inside.
Mmm-hmm. Kind of like that one?
This one has an app, so you can actually
watch the food on your phone.
All it needs to do is keep
my fuckin' beer cold.
(FRIDGE CHIMES)
MALE VOICE: Hmm. You're
running low on beer.
Fuck you.
(FRIDGE CHIMES)
MALE VOICE: Whoops!
Did you forget to scan that bar code?
Yes, I did.
On purpose.
- (FRIDGE CHIMES)
- MALE VOICE: Ah, there we go.
GILFOYLE: It's bad enough it has to talk.
Does it need fake vocal tics like "ah"?
Well, itjust makes it sound more human.
GILFOYLE: Humans are shit.
This thing is addressing problems
that don't exist.
It's solutionism at its worst.
We are dumbing down machines
that are inherently superior.
Whatever. You gave your server
a human name.
You named it Anton.
Yeah, but Anton doesn't call me anything.
He grimly does his work, then he sits
motionless till it's time to work again.
We could all take a page from his book.
- (FRIDGE CHIMES)
- MALE VOICE: Uh-Oh!
That yogurt is expired!
See? This could have killed me.
Now I can give it to Erlich.
(FRIDGE CLOSES)
(CHIMES)
MALE VOICE: Hmm.
I'm not quite sure what you're doing.
Is there something I can help you with?
Yeah, how do I shut you the fuck up?
MALE VOICE: Aw.
Is somebody having a rough day?
Did that fucker password protect
the settings?
His fridge, his rules.
Fuck.
- (BASKETBALL BOUNCING)
- (SN EAKERS SQU EAKING)
My man, I was told I had a spot
on the floor tonight,
but it seems that I've committed
the cardinal sin of being early.
What time does the game actually start?
MAN: It's about to.
Wait, when he said a spot on the floor,
did he mean on the floor?
I wasn't part of the conversation.
ED: Come on, baby. Come on, bring it.
- (MEN CHEER)
- I cannot do that.
All right. You guys go shirts.
We'll go skins.
And I can definitely not do that.
Will not.
ED: Don't let him drive on you.
- All day!
- (CELL PHONE RINGS)
Yo, Erlich. Where you at, dog?
ERLICH: Yo, what up, what up, what up?
Which one of you pussies, uh,
put sugar in my gas tank
to prevent me from housing you
on the hardwood?
What?
Yeah. My car won't start.
It's a real fucked situation.
So, I guess I'll have to miss this
once-in-a-lifetime opportunity to...
Dude, we play every Tuesday.
I'll see you next week, Broseph.
(BUZZER ECHOES ON PHONE)
(THUD5)
Hey. Let me in. Let me get in.
Let me get in.
Hey, I squished those front-end bugs.
- Um, did you finish your networking issue?
- Nope.
(FRIDGE CHIMES)
MALE VOICE: Hmm.
I'm sorry, wrong password.
You're sitting here trying to hack
Jian-Yang's password
instead of doing your actual work?
Well, good luck, it's a
10-digit alphanumeric.
Ten digit? Fuck.
And you have one underpowered laptop,
so you know, you should have the answer...
In 9,000 years.
Time to pull out the big gun.
Well, maybe you should
pull out the bug gun.
'Cause of the network bug.
As in the bug you're supposed to be fixing.
If you were programmed to have
a good sense of humor, you'd laugh at that.
- (FRIDGE CHIMES)
- MALE VOICE: Oh, I'm sorry.
I didn't see any Good Humor ice cream bars.
Shall I add them to your shopping list?
- You know what? Yeah.
- (FRIDGE CHIMES)
MALE VOICE: Good Humor ice cream bars
added to your shopping list.
JARED: Come on.
- God, you believe this? I'm still on hold.
- With?
Microsoft Azure.
Yeah, I'm trying to negotiate
a lower cloud storage rate,
'cause we're gonna need it if,
or more realistically,
when, Richard finally decides to pay
that patent troll.
Ugh. I mean, I'm still on hold.
It's like they don't even care
about small businesses.
Jared, they don't care about
small businesses.
That's why small businesses have to lie.
Like, um, Google named theirfirst building
"Building 40"
so that people would think
they were already huge.
When I worked at my first startup,
I would transfer people to "my supervisor"
and then I'd just get back
on the phone myself.
Oh. Uh, yeah, hello.
No, no. I'm not gonna go on hold again.
Um, in fact, could I transfer you
to my supervisor?
(CHUCKLES) Uh...
(WHISPERS) Oh, no, no, no.
I have to take a shit.
Just, um, do your best Ed Chen impression.
One moment please.
(IMITATING) What's up?
You've got Ed, uh, Chambers.
Hello, everybody. Thanks
again for making it.
And thanks to Gus of
Gigglybots for hosting.
No problem.
My name is, uh, Richard Hendricks, uh,
of Pied Piper.
You're the guys working for Gavin Belson.
Was working with Gavin Belson, yeah.
- So, he's not coming?
- No. No, not at all.
But I'll have you all know that without
any involvement from Gavin Belson,
Pied Piper, just like yourselves, has
reached the Hooli app store's top 500 list.
And you guys are aware that you are all
directly above us on the list,
which is why you should know that
a patent troll named Stewart Burke
has recently demanded that I pay
a $20,000 licensing fee.
And ifl pay, he's gonna come
and ask you guys for more money.
He starts With the little guy.
Not that I'm little. I'm, uh...
- I mean, I'm not.
- (CHAIR CLATTERING)
I'm actually, uh...
Above average height.
Isn't this something that could have been
done over e-mail?
RICHARD: I mean, lguess.
(SIGHS) But look, if we
don't stop this guy,
he's gonna just keep asking
for more and more money
until someone is stuck
with an unpayable bill.
It's kind of like that old fraternity game,
the limp biscuit.
Sorry, I wasn't in a fraternity.
Uh, what is that?
I don't think we need to get into...
It's where guys stand in a circle
and masturbate onto a cracker.
And then the last guy eats it.
What?
Again...
I don't really know
why he would mention that.
It's super gross.
Is this why Gavin Belson
stopped working with you?
RICHARD: N0.
The important thing is here,
my lawyer has actually drafted
a partnership agreement.
Why don't you all just...
Essentially, we all band together
and each contribute $20,000.
We should have more than enough money to
mount a challenge against this guy's patent.
And if we win, we dissolve the patent
so that he can't do this
to anyone else ever again.
Because in the end, shouldn't it be
Mr. Stewart Burke, the patent troll,
who's forced to eat the biscuit?
I'm pretty sure that's sexual assault.
Yeah, no one deserves that.
I know. That's not what I'm saying.
Look, I'm pretty sure it's even made up.
Like a donkey punch. You know?
Again, what is a donkey punch?
- It's when guys...
- Just don't.
Don't.
G-man.
You busy at the moment?
Very.
I'm about to set Anton loose on that
talking chrome beer coozy.
So, care to take a breather and help a pal
throw a basketball hoop on the old garage?
Why would you need help from a scrawny
code jockey such as myself?
Fine.
I'm perfectly capable of
figuring it out myself.
All I need is... Ah!
May I borrow this hammer to pound in these
flamboyant little nails?
Those are screws.
Yeah, no, I...
Jared Dunn.
Yep, just a moment, please.
I'll transfer you.
(IN LOW VOICE) Go for Chambers.
(LAUGHING)
Ned! I knew it was you.
Hey, did that pussy Jared
keep you on hold long?
I eat that motherfucker's lunch every day.
(LAUGHS) No, man. I literally eat his food.
What do you want? Uh-uh.
Ain't gonna happen.
That's as high as we go, homo.
Till next time, rook.
(PHONE BEEPS)
(IN NORMAL VOICE) I mean, did you see that?
He's amazing.
- Who?
- Ed Chambers.
He got Pied Piper a great cloud
storage rate from Azure.
And he's got the hookup on a couple of
pallets of Pamplemousse LaCroix
at, his words, "an amaze-balls price."
Wow. Good job, Jared.
Well, I mean, don't congratulate me.
Congratulate Ed Chambers.
- Ed Chambers is you.
- Well, lwish. But...
Gentlemen.
You all said that it couldn't be done,
but it appears as if Sir Richard the
Not-Short hath now slain the slimy troll.
Stu Burke? R. Hendricks.
I got word that you called.
I assume you spoke with my attorney,
Monsieur Ron Laflamme?
STEWART: Yes, I did speak to Ron Laflamme.
What, pray tell, did he tell you
when he called you?
STEWART: Well, I called him actually,
to tell him
that the eight companies you apparently
tried to organize against me
have reached out to me
preemptively to settle.
And because I appreciated that, I offered
them a very, very reasonable rate.
So, Richard Hendricks, fuck...
Okay. Uh, yeah.
Uh-huh.
I understand.
So, you're firm on that?
Well, bye, then.
- So, your coalition fucked us?
- Yes.
So, now we have to pay the $20,000.
Uh, not exactly.
Because he... Stu is saying
that since all eight companies
have now licensed the patent,
he has a stronger case against us.
So, um, he'd actually like more money.
- How much?
- $300,000.
- So, we just ate the Wheat Thin, didn't we?
- (FRIDGE CHIMES)
MALE VOICE: Oh, I'm sorry.
I didn't see any Wheat Thins.
Shall I add them to your shopping list?
- Eh, sure.
- (FRIDGE CHIMES)
DINESH: Well, let's hope that Melcher
doesn't hear about all this.
You guys don't need all these lights on,
do you?
Yes, we do.
Okay. Well, that should be fine.
We should be fine.
Um, fine from what?
That fridge is putting up a fight,
so I'm gonna have to try something
with Anton.
Might put a little strain on the wiring,
that's all.
I'll be in the garage.
Hey, Richard.
But you're not seriously gonna defend
yourself in court, right?
Well, Larry Flynt did it.
And Sir Walter Raleigh.
Although he lost and was publicly beheaded.
But you could argue that he eventually won
in the court of history.
' Qet it!
I should have settled. Okay? And I didn't.
And you're right, I will probably lose.
But I'm not going down without a fight.
And I've got all of Monahan's discovery
from the Hooli case right here,
so that's something.
(RICHARD SIGHS)
Oh, my God.
(RICHARD CHUCKLES)
This is from high school.
These are all my notes from the
original build of Pied Piper 1.0,
back when it was just some stupid
search app for music copyright...
It's...
Hold on, hold on.
(CIRCUIT BREAKERS CLICK)
What the fuck?
Sorry. Everybody okaY?
I don't know, you fucking maniac! Are we?
Probably.
JARED; Richard?
What are you up to?
- (KEYBOARD CLACKING)
- About 6'2", Jared.
Looks like I can slay
that troll, after all.
- (MARIACHl MUSIC PLAYING)
- STEWART: What am I looking at?
Well, you said that you used
Cancion de Amores to sue musicians.
You claimed that they
stole that song, right?
Bought two houses,
put Jeremy through four years of college.
Six. And he's still 20 credits short.
Okay. Well, he may want
to consider financial aid.
Um, because that little song there was
itself stolen from an old country song
called I'm Clyin', parentheses,
With My Eyes from 1967.
A full eight years before
Cancion de Amores.
And I'm pretty sure Katrina and the Waves
would want to know
that they gave you a piece of
Walking on Sunshine for nothing.
Mazda may want to pull that whole
Super Bowl spot.
- Bullshit.
- No, no. Not bullshit.
Computer science.
Yeah, and we can take it to court
if you like, see who they believe.
Perhaps the most advanced and sophisticated
pattern matching algorithm ever devised,
by a fucking genius.
Or some old asshole
who once sued Stevie Wonder.
All right.
What do you want, you little prick?
(CHUCKLES) Correction, sir.
I am a big prick.
Hello, my cold friend.
(CHIMES)
Hello?
MALE VOICE: Huh. Suck it, Jian-Yang. Mmm.
Ah. Huh. Huh.
You attack and destroy my refrigerator?
- And you misspell my name.
- GILFOYLE: ldid.
Had to overclock Anton,
but I was able to brute-force
the backdoor password
to that chrome piece of shit
in under 12 hours.
And I added a little visual flair.
MALE VOICE: Huh. Suck it, Jian-Yang.
Mmm. Ah. Huh.
(SIGHS)
- So?
- So, he bought it,
hook, line, and sinker.
Yeah, he thinks the
search results are real.
You trolled the troll.
(CHUCKLES) Yeah, yeah.
For a second there, he wasn't buying it,
and then ljust started babbling on
about tech specs,
and saw his eyes glaze over.
Well, as a result, we now have a perpetual,
royalty-free license for the patent.
Yés!
See? I stuck to my guns and as a result,
we now have 20 grand
we would have otherwise lost
if l'd have listened to you
delicate little snowflakes and settled.
Yeah? 20 grand.
Yeah? So, let me cum into a bucket
and have you all drink it.
Uh, Richard? Can I have a moment?
(SIGHS) Sorry about that. I regretted it
the second it came out of my mouth.
Richard.
Well, yes. But...
Here. (SIGHS)
What's this?
Um, that is a bill from Ron Laflamme
for the paperwork he had to do to put
your coalition of companies together.
- $22,000.
- Yeah.
It's at the high-end of standard.
So, it would have cost us slightly less
if we'd havejust...
Paid the troll?
Well, that's true,
but can you put a price on dignity?
Apparently, I just did.
Do me a favor and, uh, don't tell the guys.
Yeah. You have my utmost discretion.
- Thank you.
- Um, speaking of,
Richard, I need to tell you something.
I had to let Ed Chambers go.
Who?
My fictional supervisor.
He bragged to a sales rep at LaCroix
about doing it to Sonia Sotomayor.
So, Ed is no longer with us.
I'm sure we can manage.
He also was never actually with us.
- Right.
- 'Cause he was never real.
Out of sight, out of mind.
And out of reality.
Yeah, well...
Oh, Ed Chambers...
Don't hit... No, no, no, no! Oh!
({THUDS)
%GROANS)
Fuck!
- (WHISTLE BLOWING)
- (MEN SHOUTING)
Yeah, a lot of these guys aren't man enough
to work for an all-female-led VC firm,
but not me.
I believe that the future is female.
And anyone who says otherwise
can suck my fat dick.
YO, yo:
- Whoo!
- (MEN CHEERING)
Bachman, scoreboard.
Ah, scoreboard.
Fuck. Shit. Who made
that one through the...
It was a three-pointer, dumbass!
(CHUCKLES) Three-pointer.
What, are we in Europe?
Is he fucking with me?
(MARIACHI SONG PLAYING)