ERLICH: A little to the right.
The right, more, more.
More. Woof! Aces.
We did it.
- Busy?
- Hey, come on in.
I'm just putting the finishing touches
on Bachman's Operational Center.
Can you believe that I talked the ladies
into letting me keep
that little piece of genius in here?
Oh!
- Sweet.
- Sweet indeed. It's human hair.
Where have you been?
We've been trying to close your deal.
Monica and Laurie were really fighting me
on one final deal point
and lwas getting bummed,
so I turned my phone off,
went kitesurfing in Fiji.
When I got back, lwas chill again.
And I got a message that they agreed.
- So, you closed.
- Yep.
What was that one little pesky deal point?
I think you're gonna like it.
(SHOUTS) Fuck, yeah!
(THEME MUSIC PLAYING)
A keyman clause?
Yes. And said keyman
is none other than yours truly.
It's the highest honor
that you can bestow on a VC.
DINESHI WOW.
- So, you get shares in the company.
- No.
- So, you get a seat on the board?
- I do not.
A bonus.
There's no cash involved,
but if Monica or Laurie
tries to oust me from Bream-Hall,
Keenan Feldspar can void the deal and walk.
So, basically, this new title just means
that you for sure
get to keep your shitty desk job.
Congratulations, but, Erlich,
can you please turn on the heat?
It's freezing in here.
Tsk, tsk, Richard. Negativity.
Have you seen Keenan's demo?
Reddit is shitting itself over it.
Of course I've seen it. I'm his keyman.
He gave me one of the first opportunities
to shit myself over it.
- It's that good?
- Guys, come on.
How good can it be? VR is just a fad.
Oh, Richard, I've forgotten
what an envious little crone you can be.
Envious? Me, of who?
- Keenan Feldspar?
- Of course.
Keenan was born
with a golden horseshoe up his ass,
while you sit here toiling away
in an icebox you call your home office,
cursed with the Midas touch of shit.
I'm not cursed.
And the icebox you're referring to
is your house, okay?
(PULL-RING SNAPS)
What?
Uh, guys, ljust got a
billing alert from Azure.
Apparently, all of our
cold data has gone hot,
so we've already exceeded
our monthly server budget?
Monthly? Bullshit. It's been four days.
What the fuck?
We have to store Melcher's data there
until we have enough phones.
We can't afford this.
I'm gonna call Melcher.
Hey, Richard, how we doing?
Is there something going on with your data?
Because it was basically parked
until a few hours ago
when it started flying on and off
our network like crazy.
Well, aren't you watching
the Weather Channel?
No. Why, is there a hurricane or something?
Worse. It's cold outside.
Okay. SQ?
California loses its
mind when it gets cold.
Citrus trees start freezing.
Sometimes, there's actual
frost on the road,
you know, and people
start filing claims like crazy.
Our whole office is going nuts right now.
Well, that kind of data traffic
is costing us a fortune.
That's the beauty of
the deal we made, Richard.
You agreed to store our
data for a flat rate.
Everyone else in my division
is getting gouged on their
storage and bandwidth fees right now,
but thanks to you, I look like a genius.
- I'II tell Liz you say hi.
- Oh. Oh, no. No, no. That's okay.
- What did he say?
- He says, "Hi."
And that we are responsible
for the overages.
Fuck.
- Maybe you are cursed.
- L'm not.
That's ridiculous. There's no such thing.
Fucking what?
Richard, a bill of this size
is going to be problematic.
Problematic? Catastrophic.
We're not gonna be able to pay that bill
so our server's gonna get cut off.
Which means
we're gonna lose Melcher's data,
which means he's gonna sue us
and seize our assets and our patents,
and the entire future
of the fucking Internet
is gonna belong
to a fucking insurance company.
I can't take this shit anymore.
Admit it, we're fucked.
Okay, let's just think. Let's just think.
Dan Melcher runs
a very conservative insurance company,
but even he was willing to pay us up front
for data storage, right?
True.
- Although that was complicated.
- What?
(STAMMERS) It wasjust
such a "in the weeds" deal.
Point being, we could find another customer
and then use that upfront payment
to cover Melcher's fees.
That's like getting a new credit card
to pay off your old credit card.
Yeah, and as CFO, I should tell you
we've already done that seven times.
Look, I don't have any moral issue
with any of that,
but it was hard enough to get Melcher,
how the fuck are we gonna get
a second Melcher?
(SIGHS)
It's cold out here.
I can almost see my breath, huh?
What do you want?
Well, uh...
It's just that the guys
are a little agitated
because we seem to be having
minor money troubles.
I was thinking since you and Bream-Hall
signed such a big check
over to Keenan Feldspar,
and since you're his keyman,
maybe you could help set up
a data storage deal
like we had with Melcher.
Merely tens of minutes ago,
you were rubbing VR's face
in a pile of its own make.
That means shit.
And now VR is supposed to be your lifeboat?
Just to remind you, Erlich,
you are also an investor in Pied Piper.
It would be good for
everyone, including you.
Very well.
Fill me in on the details
of your little proposal.
Pitch.
What do you mean? You know the details.
You were there with me
for every single pitch meeting.
And I'm sorry that
I wasn't key in those meetings,
so I don't recall
all of the little nitty-gritty details.
Saving you 25% on your data storage,
which makes us pretty deserving
of the Weissman trophy.
(ALL LAUGHING)
You know, the Heisman
trophy from athletics.
Dude, this demo is insane.
Gentlemen, you're stepping on
Richard's laughs.
I'm sorry, but I walked up a hill, and on
the top of the hill there was a tavern,
and I walked into the tavern,
and I can just look everywhere
and there was a barmaid.
Guess what? I walked
right up to the barmaid,
and ljust looked at her
for a really long time.
This technology could change the world.
GILFOYLE: I'm not one to gush,
but the possibilities
of your consequence-free reality
are darkly promising.
So stoked you guys liked it.
I hacked it together last summer,
and ljust guessed right
on a lot of the details.
But if you think that was cool,
wait till you see our final hardware,
which is in en route from China.
It's gorgeous.
Well, enjoy it while it lasts just 'cause,
you know, this can be a tough business.
Is it?
So, Richard...
(CLAPS) You wanna try the demo?
No, thanks. No, I'm not a VR guy.
Richard doesn't like things that are cool
or fun or taste good.
Plus, it makes him queasy.
He has a sensitive constitution.
Ah, come on, you're gonna do it.
Look at him. He's gonna do it.
It's gonna be awesome. Come on.
- You're doing it. Come on, come on.
- Sure. lguess.
- After you.
- Okay.
(TOILET FLUSHES)
(G ROANS)
Wow. You really vomited a lot.
- And, like, immediately.
- Yeah. Yeah.
Bad luck, I guess.
Yeah, so, (CLEARS THROAT) look, anyway,
about that data storage deal...
Oh, yeah, if Erlich says it works,
that's good enough for me.
- Let's do it.
- Really?
- KEENAN: Yeah.
- Okay. Perfect. That's great.
Um, well, I guess we should
get back to the house,
- draw up some paperwork for that.
- JARED: Mmm-hmm.
We should be able to
pull everything together by Monday?
Is it cool if we hang out
just to, like, play around
with the VR some more?
Okay, but I'm sure Keenan's busy.
No, you guys should stay.
You want a beer? ljust put in a fresh keg.
He put in a fresh keg.
It's so warm in here.
That would be the subfloor heating.
(LAUGHS)
I didn't even know I had it.
It just came with the house.
GILFOYLEI That's nice.
What are you telling me?
Box Two is delayed?
We were already facing some design
and production challenges,
but then this cold snap happened.
Apparently, there was frost
on the loading dock
at our microprocessor plant in Acton.
So, it's cold outside.
Why does everyone in this state
have to be such a wimp about it?
Well, a semi-truck slid
right through the door
and hit the main breaker panel
and melted down the entire facility.
The driver was incinerated instantly.
I see. Well, thoughts
and prayers, obviously.
But we'll still be ready to roll
out in time for Hoolicon, right?
Guys, hey, I'm not Gavin Belson. (CHUCKLES)
You can be honest with me.
How many days will this set us back?
We're going to miss delivery of product
by two quarters.
You realize Hoolicon is in one week, right?
I mean, it's my first Hoolicon
as CEO of this company.
I'm supposed to get up on stage
in front of an audience of thousands
and deliver a keynote presentation built
entirely around the release of Box Two.
I was going to descend
onto the stage in a giant box.
Boom!
Jack in the box.
Then Mike Tyson and Floyd Mayweather
were gonna come out and box
over who was gonna get to take home
the first new Box.
These are world-class puns!
Now, I got nothing.
Hello?
(LAUGHS) Hey, guys-
I have something to show you.
- Have you been here all weekend?
- Ls that the sushi guy?
(CHUCKLES) Matching pajamas.
You guys look like you're in a cult.
Oh. Keenan gets these for free.
Yeah, we're not gonna wear the same thing
three days straight.
You gotta come check this out.
This way.
(SIGHS)
Wow.
I didn't feel sick at all. Not once.
- Not even going up the hill?
- No.
No nausea at all.
Yeah, I felt fine the entire time.
What did you do, did you
reduce the latency?
I didn't. You did.
Dinesh and Gilfoyle helped me integrate
your middle-out
compression algorithm into my codec.
- L'm sorry, what?
- Lt's off the charts now, man.
We were even able to push
the barmaid to the cloud.
These two guys are mad geniuses.
Hang on, I have something for you.
Mmm-hmm.
What the fuck?
You just gave our proprietary technology
to this asshole
without even running it by me first.
Are you serious?
Well, we were just hanging out,
and he was like, "We should try it,"
and he said we could delete it,
and then he started getting really excited.
And then he said, you know,
"You're doing it," a bunch of times,
and then we did it,
and then we started getting really excited.
- And it was so exciting.
- And it worked.
The VR is rad now.
Gilfoyle, "rad"?
You are wearing
the exact same pajamas as Dinesh
and you're saying "rad" now?
You have been sucked entirely
into his little Keenan vortex.
Okay.
I grant you with (CLEARS THROAT)
the benefit of even a second's distance,
this isn't a good look.
I don't know. I think we look rad.
- Just hear Keenan out, okay?
- On what?
Here you go, Richard.
- What's this?
- Lt's an offer.
Iwant to acquire Pied Piper.
- Oh.
- (CHUCKLES)
(KEENAN LAUGHS)
JACK: Bingo.
2009, the HooliPad touchscreen
was recalled five days before
Gavin Belson's Hoolicon keynote.
Now, if he can pull something together
that fast, certainly I can.
Well, sir, I really don't see the value
in you comparing yourself
so closely to Gavin Belson.
Meaning what, exactly?
Nothing. Just that
he's considered the greatest showman
the tech world has ever seen.
(KEYBOARD CLACKS)
I mean, just look at him.
We've blown away
the FIPS 140-2 standard for security,
and that's been certified by NIST/CSE,
as you can see.
- JAC K: Wow.
- There.
- (CROWD CHEERING)
- (SIGHS) Look at the confidence, the poise.
Look at the stage presence.
It is accessible,
here we go,
through the dropdown menu there.
- (CROWD CHEERING ON SPEAKERS)
- How could I top that?
(CHUCKLES)
Oh, I don't think anyone ever will.
HOOVER: When he looked at you,
you felt like you were
the only two people in the world.
Hoover?
Yes, sir?
- Get the fuck out of my office this instant.
- (CLEARS THROAT)
Sorry, sir.
Anyone here use our enterprise server?
We've taken secure authentication
to a whole other level.
Jack Barker, you're gonna need a miracle.
Anyone care to talk secure biometrics?
Well, considering our looming debts
and the embryonic state of our network,
this is a very generous offer.
But we're not for sale, guys.
Richard, listen, it's like we've been
lost at sea for a long time
in a tiny boat and there is no wind,
and now, through sheer luck,
we've just happened
to drift right up to Hawaii.
Now, we can continue
sailing into the unknown
and probably sink,
or die of starvation, or scurvy,
or we can get off in Hawaii.
Let's get off in Hawaii.
What's so good about Hawaii?
- Have you never been?
- No.
It's very nice.
I think we should take it.
Okay, everything
Keenan touches turns to gold
and you are different than that.
I want to go to Hawaii.
Fucking Keenan Feldspar.
How dare he put me in this position.
Everything just comes so easy to him.
He invents one little thing,
and then he's gonna make a billion dollars
and just, "Keenan Feldspar
gets whatever he wants,"
and now I have to be the ogre
that says no to him. Great.
Richard, you are my captain,
and I'm your mate,
and I will sleep in the bilge with
the vermin and lwill eat hardtack,
and I will say thank you.
And if duty requires,
I will stand on deck and I will salute you
as we sink beneath the waves.
But as poor as our odds are, I'm worried
that if we turn down this offer,
we will lose the rest of our crew,
and if that happens,
we will lose everything, Richard.
Your algorithm.
So, you're saying that if I say no to this,
I risk having a mutiny on my hands.
Aye, Captain.
Thanks.
(SCOFFS)
Fuck you, Keenan Feldspar.
Whoa.
Problem?
Your counteroffer here
is really, really high.
Yes, but after crunching
the old numbies, um,
there's no way we could make
an acquisition work
for even just a penny less
than that number right there.
You know, what with the patent and the IP.
And you said it yourself,
my guys are the best.
So, Keenan, as you know,
the best is expensive.
This is more than ljust took in funding
from Bream-Hall,
and you want all cash.
- I can't do that.
- Really?
Aw. Rats.
Rats, rats, rats.
(SIGHS)
Weird.
I wanted this to happen, but it didn't.
That sucks. lwanted it, too. Very badly.
But, you know what they say in life,
"You can't always get what you want."
This feeling sucks.
Trust me, you get used to it.
GILFOYLE: Wait, Keenan said no?
To us?
I guess you can never really know someone
until you ask them to put their money
where their mouth is.
Yeah, kind of a shitty thing to do.
Kind 0f a shitty little dude.
Anyway, lesson learned.
Anyhoo, as soon as Erlich comes in
and brings us our signed data storage
contract from Keenan, we'll be all set.
We'll be back in business.
Huh? Go team.
Let's celebrate. Let's, uh, put
on some music. We never do that.
What was the number?
- What number?
- Your counteroffer to Keenan,
what was the number
you went back to him with?
Gilfoyle, to be honest,
these deals are pretty complicated.
Richard, what was the number?
Twenty-five million fucking dollars.
- Wait, what?
- You heard the man-child right.
Richie had the quail eggs
to counter $25 million.
- Isn't that right, Richard?
- What?
That's fucking crazy.
Yeah, I thought so, too.
But you know what's even crazier than that?
You guys got yourself a fucking deal.
What?
(KEENAN LAUGHS)
Okay, so, this is $25 million?
This is real?
- As crystal.
- Yeah.
I'm not gonna lie,
when you first told me that number,
I had a feeling of mad.
But then I had lunch
and after that I was a little tired,
but I mostly felt pretty okay.
And that's when it hit me,
this is a guy who knows how valuable he is.
It got me to thinking that perhaps
I've undervalued my own company.
Especially because
now I have this baller algorithm
that's solving all my latency issues.
Well, my algorithm.
So, I called Big Cat here,
and we slid that new demo over to Raviga.
Ed Chen liked it so much he offered
to triple the Bream-Hall deal.
But the Bream-Hall deal is signed,
it's done, right?
Was done.
Enter the keyman, the Big Cat.
You see, if I quit Bream-Hall, then
Keenan is free to do whatever he wants.
You quit Bream-Hall?
Two hours ago.
Ten minutes later,
we were in a handshake deal at Raviga.
This adorable little wombat
made clear his intentions
that he wants me to be
the new COO of his company,
along with a 5% stake.
And now we can all work together
on this dope-ass shit
and make a fuck-ton of money
while we're doing it.
See, it always works out.
- It does. Who's drinking? To the palapa.
- Yeah.
Pour me one, Big Cat.
Jared, there's no pink glasses.
Richard, I know you think
I'm a bullshit artist.
It's okay. I totally am.
I have this gift where I can make people do
whatever I want them to do,
- and they don't even realize they're doing it.
- Right.
Richard, you have the greatest technology
that I've ever seen.
You could change the fucking world.
You just have to get
people excited about it.
That's where I come in.
You and me together, bro,
look how strong this is.
Fucking forget about it.
We're going to be fucking cutting class
and crushing ass.
You really think that you can
get people excited about Pied Piper?
Richard, that's what I do.
You know you're doing it. I can see it.
- He knows.
- Well...
- The wheels are already turning.
- Maybe.
Come on, you know you're fucking doing it.
Let's do it, buddy.
- Let's fucking do it. Come on.
- Okay. Yeah. Okay.
(ALL LAUGHING)
- All right, here you go.
- L'm just gonna wait.
- Okay. Here you are.
- Yeah.
KEENAN: Get out there.
(SIGHS)
- Richard...
- RICHARD: Yeah.
Are we okay?
Uh, no, Jared, we're not okay.
We're fucking rich.
(CHEERING)
Whoo!
Sorry, it's a bit nutty around here.
Yeah, (CLEARS THROAT)
well, ljust want to say
how sorry I am that Erlich
flaked on you guys.
Not your fault.
Also, and I know this might piss you off
to some degree...
I have decided to make a deal
with Keenan Feldspar.
What? Why?
He made a really good offer.
Lots of money.
And, look, he's got my back.
Right, well, it's not like him
to talk you into a deal
and then just totally fuck you over.
Yeah.
No, look, he's copped up to all that.
I mean, he was very honest
about the whole Keenan vortex thing, so...
Well, you don't think his
discussing the vortex
is just a way of pulling
you into the vortex?
No, why would he...
Son of a bitch.
Yeah.
Okay, look, Richard... (SIGHS)
What I'm about to tell you
is a huge breach of ethics,
but it's going to save you
from making a big mistake,
Keenan and Erlich's little keyman game
is the greatest thing
that happened to this firm.
I'd like to hear why.
A, no more Erlich.
And if that weren't enough,
we get our $20 million back.
But the biggest reason is that we realized
once we took a look under the hood,
Keenan's tech is dog shit.
No. No, it's not dog shit.
I thought so, too, but then I tried
the demo, and it's pretty amazing.
There's this point in the tavern
where you meet this barmaid
and you can look wherever you want
however long you want.
Yeah, well, um...
Look, the demo is amazing.
When you run it on a $10,000 rig.
But the future of VR is mobile,
and there's no phone on Earth
that could handle that demo,
let alone the full bloated platform.
Isn't that why Keenan has acquired us?
I mean, to help him figure that out?
No, he just wants you
to make the demo better
so he can take as much money
off the table as he can.
He'll walk away rich,
the company will crater,
and you will go down with it.
And that would be the end of Pied Piper.
Look, Richard, you have to tell Keenan
that you're not going to take this deal.
(SIGHS)
Fuck. What do I do?
How am I supposed to tell the guys
that I'm taking away their payday?
You don't understand.
Keenan had us pouring champagne
all over each other
like a bunch of fucking douchebags.
I honestly don't think they even care
that the tech is shit.
Theyjust wanna go to Hawaii.
- Hawaii?
- Lt's a metaphor we've been using.
Um, we are pirates and our ship is sinking,
and Keenan is Hawaii.
This is what you talk about all day?
Look, (CLEARS THROAT)
this deal was our only hope.
And with all due respect, uh,
you run your own firm and you're not exactly
jumping at the chance to fund us, are you?
Because you're still theoretical.
Look, I'll make you a promise.
If you can get all of Melcher's data
onto a stable network of mobile devices
and prove that this works,
- I will fund your A-round.
- Really?
You have my word.
But you have to tell Keenan, "No deal."
Uh, guys?
Oh, he came in the front this time.
(GILFOYLE CLEARS THROAT)
So, we need to talk to you.
You need to talk to me?
You may want to have a seat.
Okay.
(CLEARS TH ROAT)
ls that a new sweater?
Hey, Richard, there's some bad news.
Richard, right before
Keenan signed the Raviga deal,
somebody else swooped in and offered him
an absurd amount of money for his company.
And he took it.
Really?
So, Keenan sold his company?
Deal's off the table.
We're not going to Hawaii.
Oh.
No.
No. (SIGHS)
Listen, Richard, we know you fought
really hard for this deal.
We will never forget that.
Yeah, I did. And lwould gladly fight for it
and you guys again.
Gosh. Damn.
Argh.
You don't seem that mad.
Iam. lam, Gilfoyle. I'm pissed.
If you need to kick another hole
in the door, we'd understand.
Yeah. No, I might have to.
Really. I just...
If I don't calm down, I will...
I will take you up on that.
Who, uh...
Who did he sell to?
The only other company that could
guarantee viable middle-out compression.
- Hooli.
- GILFOYLE: Yep.
Hooli? He sold to Hooli.
(CLICKS TONGUE)
- What a dick move.
- GILFOYLE: Yeah.
I mean, that's not the half of it.
And once he figured out what
Erlich's 5% would be worth,
he left him out in the cold.
What, he got Erlich to quit his job,
and then cut him out of the deal?
- GILFOYLE: Mmm-hmm.
- Jesus.
We thought you were cursed, but maybe
it was just your proximity to Erlich.
I mean, that dude must have driven a van
over a bunch of gypsies in a previous life.
Where is he?
I saw him grab his lighter and bong
and head out to the palapa
to sulk a few minutes ago.
Isn't that his bong right there?
Well, shit.
(FIRE CRACKLING)
Guys, there's a fire.
We need the fire guys.
Someone call the fire guys.
Erlich?
Hey, buddy.
Still not talking?
You've been out here all night.
It's freezing.
Sure you don't want to come back inside?
(SIGHS)
Yeah, it was a nice palapa.
Well, the concrete's still pretty warm
from the fire.
He should be okay for at least
a few more hours.
Well, that's probably longer
than we'll be in business.
Yeah, we got our first
past due notice from Azure.
They said we have five business days
till they cut us off.
If you guys want to feel
worse, check this out.
JACK: (ON SPEAKERS)
Come join us for an epic gathering
where we come together as one people,
as visionaries.
MAN: Is this not the most exciting time
to be in technology?
- (CROWD CHEERING)
- The whole thing is just, like, wow.
JACK: The most transformative
technology event in the world, Hoolicon.
See you all at Hoolicon.
I hope you're excited.
- / know "VR."
- Yeah, "VR. "
Fucking Keenan Feldspar.
Jared, how many people attend Hoolicon?
About a quarter of a million
over the whole weekend.
And, Gilfoyle, um, how many more phones
do we need to get us off Azure?
123,000, give or take.
Dinesh, how much are tickets to Hoolicon?
Why would I have that information?
(ROCK MUSIC PLAYING)