(KEYBOARDS CLACKING)
- You know what, should we...
- Fuck, yeah.
Uh, yeah, I guess, just
put it in the garage.
Oh. Uh, where I sleep?
Yeah, it's just, it's the
only place with room.
Okay, uh, well, it's
good to face your fears.
I was scared of intruders
until I had one of those in my room,
and then I realized if they're gonna
kill me, they're gonna kill me.
(CHUCKLES) 'Cause he kept whispering that.
All right.
(VEHICLE APPROACHING)
- (TIRES SCREECHING)
- (ENGINE REVVING)
(ROCK MUSIC PLAYING ON SPEAKERS)
(MUSIC STOPS)
- Hey, Russ.
- "Hey, Russ?"
Fuck you, Richard Hendricks!
"Fuck me," regarding...
It's all over the blogs,
you took our idea to Gavin Belson?
- Whoa. I'm sorry, "Our idea"?
- Yeah.
The new Internet,
we came up with that together
standing outside of my kid's school,
former school.
Uh, no. Um, you told me to name an idea,
and so I named one.
That was my idea,
you were just standing there.
Yeah, pulling it out of you
like a newborn baby.
Okay, but, uh, well, if a doctor
pulls a baby out of a pregnant woman
the doctor doesn't get
to then keep the baby.
Okay, first of all, my ex-wife is fucking
the doctor that delivered my son
and they're suing for full custody,
so you're wrong.
Second of all, this isn't a baby.
Stop trying to change the subject, Richard!
Okay, well, uh, I had to go to Gavin
because he owned the patent,
which, as it turns out,
he just signed over to me,
so, um, it's actually good that you're here
because you want in and we need funding.
Especially since no VC in town will
touch us, not even Monica's new firm.
So, Gavin pulls out and you want me
to be your sloppy seconds?
(SCOFFS) It's always about my money,
isn't it?
Uh, well, you are an investor,
so what else would it be about?
- My idea!
- It was my idea!
Well, then fund it yourself.
Fuck you, Richard Hendricks.
Fuck you right in your little asshole
and not in a beautiful way
like Grandpa and Pedro.
Uh, what the hell was that?
That was the last wealthy guy in Silicon
Valley that would even fucking talk to us.
Maybe I'll give him a day to cool off,
try him again tomorrow, something...
Not so sure about that.
(TRICKLING)
- RICHARD: Ugh. Come on.
- Payback's a bitch, isn't it, Richard?
Whoo-hoo!
I don't think he knows that's not your car.
(THEME MUSIC PLAYING)
Real estate listings?
What, are you looking to move out?
No, I'm just taking a
little Redfin holiday.
I find there's a certain
escapist allure to real estate listings.
I like that one.
Too bad it's 10 times what I can afford,
'cause you know, I quit Periscope to go
work for a company with zero prospects,
'cause fuck me.
Well, with preconstruction pricing
this one's actually
only six times more than you could afford
so, now, let's go onto Amazon
and see what we could buy
with all those imaginary savings.
RICHARD: Wait a minute.
What if we don't need an investor at all?
Fuck all these VCs.
What if all we need is a customer?
Customer for what?
We haven't built a product yet.
Well, uh, neither have all
those condo builders, right?
I mean, they're offering a discount
to people who buy before they build.
We can do the same thing,
but with data storage.
That sounds like a scam.
Well, no, it's actually common practice.
It's how I bought my condo.
The scam came after when I rented
to a squatter who wouldn't leave.
Granted, there's no shortage
of huge corporations
with vast amounts of data,
but it's highly risky.
I mean, Richard, we'd be
offering to store data
on a network of cell phones
before we built the app or the network.
Yeah, but, look, it's no more risky than
working with all these crazy billionaires.
I mean, Jack and his boxes,
Gavin just fucked off to go find himself,
who knows where, Peter died.
Yeah, I guess that makes him crazy.
The point is, if you don't draw the line in
the sand when some guy pisses in your car,
where do you, you know?
Someone pissed in someone's car?
(CLEARS THROAT) Not literally, no.
It's a, uh, figure of speech, an old one.
Ah. An adage.
Anyway, uh, Jared,
let's get a deck together on this.
Aye, aye, captain.
And, uh, just word to the wise,
often the first customer
is the hardest one to land.
Wait, "customer"? Are we pitching?
Yeah, looks like it.
God damn, Richie. Let's hit the road!
We're gonna piss in everyone's car.
(LAUGHS) Am I using that right?
RICHARD: Medical groups, sales groups,
insurance companies.
Jared, yeah. Good work here, really.
Well, Gavin was right.
His name certainly opened a lot of doors.
Ever since your announcement,
everyone has heard of us.
Jared, you didn't tell all these people
that Gavin was still working
with the company, did you?
Well, no, but I never explicitly said
that he wasn't.
Was that wrong?
RICHARD: No, Jared. That's fine.
The tech will speak for itself.
It certainly will.
Now, Richard, when we get into that room,
let me do all of the talking.
And also the tech will talk.
Wait, so Gavin's not coming?
- No, but we are. We've already come.
- (CHUCKLES)
Huh.
Gavin left the company?
Yes, um, but what's important,
at least we think, uh,
is not whether Gavin is gone, but what
brought him to us in the first place,
and that's the tech.
Uh-huh.
Gentlemen, sorry to keep you waiting.
I'm George Mandechian, CEO.
I'm very excited to...
(WHISPERING)
He did? Huh.
Okay.
(RICHARD INHALES SHARPLY)
God damn it. I mean, if peoplejust look at
what we're offering,
I think they'd be blown away.
Perhaps we need a new angle.
I'll fake a seizure.
- What?
- Pied Piper.
Hi, I'm Liz Tinsdale,
Head of Compliance
here at Fiduciated General.
Erlich Bachman.
And I'm, uh, Richard Hendricks.
Are we all here?
Yes, yeah, we are.
Uh, sorry, full disclosure, uh,
Gavin Belson has left the company.
- Oh! Oh, I see.
- His loss.
He won't be sitting across from someone
as charming as yourself this afternoon,
will he?
Okay, well, I mean,
you did come all the way here,
so, why don't you follow me?
I'd follow you to the end of the Earth.
Shall we?
- (WHISPERS) What are you doing?
- What?
RICHARD: So, as you can see,
your data will be even more secure
because it will be stored on multiple devices
and we can offer you a very competitive rate.
You can expect to see
storage savings annually of 25%.
Wow. That's very impressive, all of it,
but you guys have to understand
that companies like ours
are particularly risk averse.
Is it a slight Idaho accent, Liz?
Oh. It's Montana, actually.
- Even better.
- Yeah.
The big blue sky state.
Well, I knew
you had to have come from above.
RICHARD: Well, uh, speaking of heaven,
that's probably where you'll think you are
when you start saving 25%
on your data storage.
- (LAUGHING)
- You have a gate from there?
Liz, you have beautiful skin.
Um, well, thank you, both of you.
Listen, I think I know what he's gonna say,
but let me see if I can pull my CTO in here.
Can you reel it in a little?
We're trying to make a business deal,
not get you laid.
I'm not trying to get laid, Richard.
Clearly she has a lot of
pent up sexual energy,
likely from working in this worm farm,
so that's the angle I'm taking
since I'm not allowed to have a seizure.
Besides, she's going to bat for us.
You should be thanking me.
The CTO's on the way in.
Yes, because of the technology
and because of our business proposal.
Look, can you just, please, for once,
keep your dick out of the equation?
I really wish I could,
but my dick is the abacus
upon which this equation
- will be...
- Guys.
This is our CTO.
ERLICH: Oh, great.
Oh. Oh.
Hello.
I'm Dan Melcher, nice to meet you.
Yeah. Hello.
Hi, Dan.
- Do you guys know each other?
- No.
Ijust said my name was Dan.
That's how he knows.
Uh, I don't need to waste
any more of your time with this.
Why don't I... I'll take
this one from here.
- Okay.
- Oh. Yeah.
What the fuck are you doing here?
Very rude, Daniel.
Although, what can we expect
after TechCrunch Disrupt
when you sucker punched me
in the goddamn face.
You fucked my wife.
I fucked your wives. Plural.
- Both of them.
- Erlich.
The customer's always right,
so let's just leave it at "wife," singular,
- and be done with it.
- Okay.
I need you to listen to me very carefully.
It took me a very long, long time
to get back on my feet
after I got fired from Oracle
and tech firms wouldn't touch me,
but I've managed to find
a home here, a life.
Okay, it's insurance.
It's not ideal, but it's something,
and I don't care, whatever it is
that you're selling here,
I'm not buying it.
Well, it's a pretty
groundbreaking technology.
- Oh. Shut the fuck up.
- Okay. Yeah.
Look at me, never gonna happen. Okay?
Never going to...
Dan, did you give the dogs
their medicine this morning?
Uh, no, was I supposed to?
Yeah, because remember, I had to go back
to the restaurant
to get your card that you forgot.
Uh, yep. Sorry.
Um, I mean, I guess I could run home.
- You two married?
- Oh. No, not yet. We're engaged. (CHUCKLES)
Well, it was nice to meet you both.
- Bye now, Liz.
- All right, bye, honey.
Okay.
ERLICHI Oh, Dan.
(INHALES DEEPLY)
Dan, Dan, Dan.
Dan Melcher,
the guy who beat the piss out of you?
The very same.
I looked him dead in the eyes and I said,
"Daniel, I fucked every
wife you've ever had.
"Care to go three for three?"
Needless to say, he did not.
You don't come off in that story
as well as you think you do.
So, to avoid being thrice made a cuckold,
he agreed to a deal?
Well, uh, not yet.
Melcher actually signed off on it,
but his fiancée wanted to certify
that what we're trying to build
complies with their data handling
and security protocols.
We're reviewing it all tomorrow, actually.
Ah, I can't wait.
Tomorrow, the real fun begins.
Uh, no. No, you're not coming.
- Why not?
- "Why not?" Uh... Geez.
Well, you fucked Dan's last wife
the night before he was ourjudge
on the TechCrunch panel
with absolutely no regard
for what that meant to the company.
What it meant for the company is that
we went to the finals and we won.
Because of the tech.
We won because of the tech, remember?
We're getting this deal
because of the tech.
I'm not letting you fuck this up, okay?
I know you're looking for something to do,
but this is not it.
What do you mean,
I'm looking for something to do?
You're lucky that you've garnished
this much of my time.
I have plenty to do.
Tons of lots of things.
I have a thriving incubator.
It is thriving.
Isn't it?
Fuck yOU, 9W5-
(CLEARS THROAT) Okay, so how soon
can we test our app on a phone?
Look, uh, about all this Erlich stuff...
Oh, no, no, no, I don't want to
talk about him or think about him
ever again. (CHUCKLES)
- Okay.
- Look, I've signed off.
But, Richard, I need you to look me in the
eye and tell me that this is gonna work,
'cause if it doesn't,
I'm completely fucked.
It's gonna work, I promise.
All right. Well, I'm gonna step out,
you're in good hands.
_0kay-
_Okay,
should we start with adjuster records?
Sure.
You guys said you were proficient
in video files, right?
We were a video chat company for a while.
Oh, that's exciting.
Uh, yeah, I guess.
It wasn't really for me.
Um, in fact, actually, just as
we were taking off, I walked away.
Commitment issues?
Uh, I don't know, it's just...
I never really thought that video chat
was the best use of our compression.
Kinda felt like I was settling, you know?
Ooh.
Settling.
RICHARD: Yeah, our company can grow in
ways that we haven't even thought of yet.
I mean, I was gonna spend the rest of my life
just wondering if there was something better.
That's not really a way to live. (CHUCKLES)
And what, I'm gonna say to all my friends,
like, "Oh, this is how I'm
spending my time," you know?
Every morning I get up and it's vidchat
and then I go to bed, it's vidchat,
then I get up again, it's vidchat,
and it's... lwanna kill myself, you know?
Yeah. Yeah, I think I know what you mean.
RICHARD: (CHUCKLES) Yeah.
MONICA: So, what do you think, Erlich?
You're the first person to see the place.
I love the smell of fresh spackle and hope.
Yeah? Two more weeks
and Bream-Hall's in business.
Even better, that donkey Ed Chen and Raviga
were so blindsided
they're running around
with their hair on fire.
Yeah, it's a beautiful world, Erlich.
And after years of busting my ass,
I'm finally doing it.
Oh! And check it out,
we even have swag with my name on it.
- Look, Monica Hall...
- Laufle.
Hello. Well, good. Now that you're both here,
we can dispense with the mindless chitchat.
I'd like to be the first
to offer you, both,
the opportunity to take me off the market.
I don't understand.
I'm saying that I very much respect
what you're doing here, almost revere it,
and I wanted to offer my services
as an associate
and I will not phone it in.
I'll be the first one here at 10:30 a.m.
And the last one to leave
a smidge after 4:00.
I'll, of course, need an office,
an attractive personal assistant,
paternity leave if that goes well,
and an umbrella insurance policy
if that does not go well.
What do you say?
I'd like ajob, dears.
The singular function of this firm
is to ensure that our investors' money
is in wise hands.
If you are known for anything,
it is quite the opposite.
Therefore, no.
(PHONE CLICKING)
I'm sorry, Erlich.
Look, I know you're looking
for something to do, but...
Who is pushing this false narrative
that I'm looking for something to do?
But... What?
But Laurie is my partner and if she doesn't
think you add any real value,
then there's no future for you here.
I gave you weed. A lot of it.
(SIGHS)
You want a fleece?
God, there's something beautiful about
testing your first alpha.
It's like watching a child
take its first steps.
Well, let's see if our space-saver app
actually saves us any space.
(SIGHS)
- All right. Done.
- (BEEPS)
Yeah?
Can I mark this deliverable as complete?
Is our child a dancer? (LAUGHS)
(CLICKING)
Wait, I was only using 32.2 gigs of data
before the test
and now it says I'm using 47.8.
Fuck! Mine expanded also. What the fuck?
Why do I have a photo folder
entitled "Cool hairstyles"?
Why do I have an e-mail for
the "Anton LaVey Fun Run"?
Fuck. We got a merge error.
All of our information is on both phones.
I wonder what kind of
weird shit you get into.
Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa!
What are you doing?
I'm just looking at your very embarrassing
personal information.
Fuck you. If you look at my shit,
I'm gonna look at your shit.
All right. Whoa, whoa. Easy now.
I'll go balls deep on your inbox.
If you've taken one fucking
selfie, I will find it.
Okay. Guys, we've got to calm down. Okay?
Look at this. This is
not where we wanna be.
Let's take a deep breath and let's
just be cool and put our phones down.
Go ahead.
- L'll put it down once he stops touching.
- Okay.
Great. Good.
That wasn't so hard, was it?
- If he can do...
- No, no, no... Okay.
Gotcha.
No, you didn't. Fuck you.
(SIGHS)
Are those almond poppy seed muffins
or lemon poppy seed muffins?
No matter, I'll take both.
And the, uh, whole first floor.
It's been a pretty bad...
Uh, you know what?
Do you have any day-olds?
(INDISTINCT CHATTER)
(CLEARS TH ROAT)
Hey, are you sitting here?
What the fuck does it look like?
Sorry, he didn't tell us
who he was inviting to the meeting.
He just said it was a bunch of us.
How many are we?
I think a few other firms are coming.
Sequoia and Greylock,
maybe a few more for this round.
Jeff from Index Ventures.
You brought swag to a pitch meeting?
Yikes, that's so three years ago.
Have you seen Keenan yet?
I don't know who that is.
(ALL LAUGHING)
Seriously though, I don't know
who you're talking about.
(ALL LAUGHING)
Bream-Hall?
Hey, man.
I don't know who you think you are,
but you're not supposed
to be at this table.
I don't know who you think you are,
but men aren't supposed to grow tits
and yet there they are
atop your little paunch.
Who the fuck are you?
I'm fucking Erlich Bachman.
I'm Keenan Feldspar.
And I like the balls on you.
(LAUGHS)
Get out of there. I want
to sit next to this guy.
(LAUGHS)
Oh, man, nice swag.
I tell ya, it is, um, warm in here.
Oh. (SIGHS) Yeah, they, uh,
shut the AC off after midnight.
Oh.
The things this company goes through
to save a dime.
Well, classic Melcher.
(BOTH CHUCKLE)
Okay, should we cover this section
on intrusion detection intervention?
- Liz?
"Huh?
Okay, uh, I don't wanna pry,
but did I do something wrong?
It's just, for the past few hours,
you've been a little, um, checked out.
(STAMMERS) I'm just thinking.
So you're getting cold feet?
What?
It's okay, I know what you're dealing with.
- I don't think you do.
- I do.
Trust me. I do.
Okay, I bet someone in your position
has been told many times to
look before you leap,
but, Liz, what about right now you just
leap before you look?
Huh.
Look, I'm gonna go out on a limb here,
but I'm gonna go ahead and say that I'll bet
there's a piece of you deep down inside
that knows this is a good idea.
It's new, it's exciting.
I mean, by God, Liz,
this is the most durable sophisticated,
decentralized storage infrastructure
the world has...
(BOTH MOAN)
- Whoa.
- Uh...
(BOTH MOANING)
(RICHARD YELPS, GRUNTS)
And then itjust happened.
On the floor?
We were like two wild animals.
(CHUCKLES) I'm sure it was magnificent.
I get pissed at Erlich for not keeping
it in his pants,
and then I go ahead and do this?
Shit! I mean, Dan's gonna find out.
I mean, he punched Erlich in the face
for when he did it to him
and now, what do you think
he's gonna do to me, huh?
He's gonna fucking kill me
and then the deal's gonna fall through.
I can't believe ljeopardized
the entire company with my dick.
- Hey, hey, we can get through this.
- Yeah.
All right? First I need some details.
Are you in love?
What? No, no. I barely know her.
Okay. Okay, that's good.
Then we just need to extricate you
from this situation.
Now it's not gonna be easy because
she's very probably in love with you.
(SCOFFS) Jared, I don't
think that that's...
Richard, this is no time
for false humility.
You're a catch. Just deal with it.
Now, you need to break this thing off
clean and clear,
so you just walk into that office
and you look her in the eyes
and you say, "Listen, baby,
"you're getting hitched
and I was born to roam."
"Born to roam"?
Hey, Jared, did I miss any calls?
Not a good time, my man.
Jared?
(SIGHS) Sorry.
Nope, no calls.
What a shocker.
I need to call Tara.
Okay, but I need to hold your phone.
It might be sexual in nature.
Well, l think I can handle that. (CHUCKLES)
All right.
No.
Um, something else in here, please?
- Monica...
- Mmm.
The salient...
(ERLICH CLEARS THROAT LOUDLY)
Ladies.
What are you doing here?
I believe the answer to that question
is currently sitting in your unfinished
waiting area.
- Holy shit, is that...
- Keenan Feldspar? Yes.
Why? Have you heard of him?
Of course. Every competent VC has.
His VR headset is reputed to be
the new standard.
Oh, it is.
I tested the prototype last night
at his house. We got quite drunk.
What exactly is he doing
in our waiting area?
Well, Laurie, he's waiting.
Upon my instruction...
(BOTH LAUGH)
Imagine landing the biggest whale
in the valley
two weeks before you launch your firm.
Or should I say, before
"we" launch your firm.
All right. The new build is done.
Ugh. I'm so glad this is over.
I felt like Gibraltar in World War ll,
where he was both crucial and inert.
All right. One press of the button
and we are back to normal.
What's the problem?
I don't know.
What don't you know?
You seem a bit eager to
resolve the situation.
You're almost anxious.
It's a new color on you.
A new color on you would be...
Bah, bah, bah. Even as you're trying
to make a boring, racist comment,
you can't keep your eyes off my phone.
See?
Now, I know all my embarrassing shit
is on your phone,
and if you look at it, you will mock me
endlessly and without mercy.
But what's also true is that you already
mock me endlessly and without mercy,
so I have nothing to lose and potentially
a huge amount to gain.
Guys, this is madness.
I have nothing to hide.
I hear you, and yet...
I'd like to look at my phone.
Sure. Suit yourself.
- Swipe.
- Mmm-hmm.
Unlock.
Mmm.
You sure you don't care?
Does it look like I care?
Okay.
(CHUCKLES)
(SIGHS)
(G ROANS)
Fuck!
What the fuck!
(FLUSHES)
You dick!
- Give me the phone.
- Dinesh...
- Give it to me.
- You are not thinking clearly.
- Ow!
- (PHONE CLATTERS)
Sorry.
Looks like we both lose.
I don't think so.
How do you figure?
'Cause now I know you had some
embarrassing shit to hide.
I don't even need to know what it is.
My phone may be in the toilet, but I win.
No, you don't.
'Cause you'll never know what was on there.
And that will slowly drive you down
a dark path and torment you
so that every fiber...
Nuh-uh! lwin. lwin. lwin. lwin.
Iwin!
(DOOR SLAMS)
Shut up, Jared.
(SIGHS)
- Last night.
- (BOTH CHUCKLE)
Yeah.
- Last night was...
- Bad.
- Bad. Bad. Yeah.
- Yeah, it was bad.
Bad. Yeah. It was such a bad thing
to have done.
Worst sex I think I've ever had by far.
Oh! So it was bad for you, too.
Yeah. I mean it wasjust all elbows.
I mean, how many times did our teeth clink?
Uh, too many. Too many.
- You know?
- Too many.
And you move your head a lot.
- Well, passion.
- None, right?
I know, and, like, right out of the gate.
When I took my top off
and you actually said the word "gulp."
- I said it? Out loud?
- Yeah. Mmm-hmm.
Okay, well, mistake on my part.
As bad as it was, you
know, and it was bad...
- Um...
- Okay.
Really awful.
- I get it.
- I just...
If there's an upside to any of this,
it would be that I realize now
what I have in Dan.
Silver lining. So that's nice.
Listen, I can't do this anymore.
This, what we...
So ljust wanna, if we could just
close the deal, be done with it,
and if it's okay with Dan,
it's fine with me. So...
Good. Okay.
Okay. So I will come back and get my stuff
when you're gone.
- No, I'm just gonna...
- So...
The door.
- I was born to roam anyways, so...
- Yeah.
- Richard!
- (ELEVATOR DINGS)
(ELEVATOR DINGS)
Lizjust told me.
- She did.
- Yup.
And if it's fine with her,
then I guess the deal's fine with me.
So, it's approved.
- Good.
- L'll ride down with you.
Oh, you don't have to. Okay.
(ELEVATOR DINGS)
(ELEVATOR MUSIC PLAYING)
Listen,
it goes without saying,
but Liz can never find out about that
whole thing between us.
Okay. Yup.
(HIP-HOP MUSIC PLAYING)