♪ God rest you,
merry gentlemen ♪
♪ Let nothing you dismay ♪
♪ For Jesus Christ, our savior ♪
♪ Was born upon this day ♪
♪ To save us all
from Satan's power ♪
♪ When we were gone astray ♪
♪ Oh, tidings
of comfort and joy ♪
♪ Comfort and joy ♪
♪ It is tidings
of comfort and joy ♪
- Happy holidays, Mrs. Johnson.
Or are you more of
a "Merry Christmas" gal?
I need to make sure
you're getting
the right blend of tequila.
My name is Dr. Randall Kirby.
I'm here because your doctor
with the warm and fuzzy bedside
manner couldn't make it.
Your husband, Tom, tells me
that you're a fighter, so...
if it's okay with you,
I'm just gonna let her rip.
You came in for a cervical
surgery with Dr. Duntsch
a few days ago to remove a disc.
Do you remember that?
Do you remember going home,
telling your husband
that you couldn't swallow,
and then you got a fever?
Well, you called Dr. Duntsch,
who told you
that everything was normal
and that your fever
was from the flu.
Then he stopped
taking your calls.
Your fever wasn't from the flu.
It was from an infection
moving towards your heart.
Now, we've had that
PICC line pumping antibiotics
into your superior vena cava
since you got here.
You've turned a corner,
but now we need to deal
with the other issues
from Dr. Duntsch's surgery.
That crazy straw
coming out of your nose
is draining stomach acid
from a hole Duntsch cut
in your esophagus.
That's why you couldn't swallow.
As for the surgery Duntsch
was supposed to perform,
he failed to remove the disc.
He left it lodged in your spine.
The hardware he was supposed
to attach
scattered in there like a bag
of leftover screws
from an IKEA bookshelf.
He sliced through a nerve
to your vocal cord.
We can't fix that.
This never should have happened.
I apologize to you
and to your family.
I promise I will make sure this
never happens to anyone else.
Um, om wanted me to discuss
a family matter with you.
Your children are in town
for the holidays,
and you don't want
them to visit.
He's hoping that you would
change your mind about that.
I'll fend them off
if you provide the stick.
I'm so sorry.
Hey, thanks for coming.
It's, uh, nice to show a united
front with these jackasses.
Ah...
- Dr. Kirby.
- Dr. Lockett.
He's the CEO here.
This is Dr. Robert Henderson.
He's my crime-fighting
partner in crime.
- Yeah, uh...
would you follow me, please?
Duntsch never operates
here again.
- Well, I guess we can call it
a night, then.
No harm, no foul.
- How did you come to hire him?
- We needed a neurosurgeon
on staff
and performed all due diligence.
- You just missed
that teeny-tiny detail
about the two dead bodies
at Dallas Medical
and Baylor-Plano,
but who's counting?
- We inquired with
the Texas Medical Board.
We checked the National
Practitioners Data Bank...
- Continue.
- To see if he was ever
suspended.
He wasn't, no complaints.
- So neither Baylor-Plano nor
Dallas Medical reported him?
- No.
Look, had we known,
we never would have hired him,
plain and simple.
He even came with
a clean letter from Baylor.
- "All investigations
with respect to any areas
"of concern regarding
Christopher D. Duntsch, M.D.
"have been closed.
"As of this date,
there have been no summary
"or administrative restrictions
or suspensions
"of Dr. Duntsch's
medical staff membership
"or clinical privileges
"during the time
he has practiced
at Baylor Medical Center
at Plano."
- Dr. Henderson, tell me...
you're in my position.
What would you have done?
- They warned 'em...
this nurse, Preston's her name,
she and some other somebody.
- Who?
- I don't know.
A scrub tech. It doesn't matter.
They warned the administration
about Duntsch.
They looked him up
on the Internet.
They found a ton of crap
about him.
I'm not talking good crap.
I'm talking he's
a crappy surgeon.
- I get it.
- Here's the kicker.
When they went to show them
what was on the Internet,
it was all gone.
Everything negative about him,
completely wiped way.
- Well, how does
somebody do that?
- I don't know... hacking's not
really my area of expertise.
The point is they warned them,
and they blew it off.
Due diligence.
We're up against
a citadel of bullshit here.
Most ass-covering...
In fact, I should use this
to wipe my ass.
Definitely...
- Written by lawyers.
- Yeah.
- Are we completing
each other's sentences now?
- Ah...
I'm going to see Amy Piel
over at Baylor.
- You give me a ride?
- Jag's right this way.
- So?
- They're gonna grant me
privileges to operate.
- They're gonna grant,
or they have granted?
They are going
to grant me privileges
when they see
my roster of patients.
Don't... It's...
It's not a big deal, Wendy.
I have a ton of patients.
All I got to do
is make a couple calls.
- Well, that place looks like
a Port-a-Potty.
Not like Baylor.
- Fuck Baylor.
- Yeah, fuck Baylor.
Fuck Dallas Medical.
Fuck whatever that last one was,
that Legacy Frisco place you
were at for, like, two weeks.
It's been quite
the fucking year.
- Can you just drive me
to my clinic, please?
- Where does it end, Chris?
- Oh, my God.
Wendy, I'm handling it, okay?
You left me, remember that?
- I don't feel sorry for you.
Why don't you go
fuck your nurse again?
Maybe she'll make you
feel better.
- I'm driving
your sorry ass around,
not because I trust you
or because I'm here for you...
but because I can't let you
mess things up for him.
- Can I come by this weekend?
- Why don't you make a call
to your roster of patients?
Then we'll talk.
- It's from my dad.
- Mrs. Demmings.
How's that Scheuermann's
kyphosis coming along?
Is the tingling in your legs
pretty consistent?
- I can't stand long enough
to hold my grandbabies now.
- And it started in your teens?
- Had no pain
until two years ago.
- The problem is these
two vertebrae right here...
T7 and T8.
- The ones sticking out.
- Exactly right.
It's actually the discs
in between them.
Spinal discs are like
natural shock absorbers,
and when they're healthy,
they kind of have
the consistency of rubber.
But when they get diseased,
they harden,
and these two are pushing
those vertebrae
right into your spinal cord.
- Every doctor I see said
there's nothing they can do.
- Well, you haven't seen me yet.
- What are you saying?
- Well, your preexisting
kyphosis is an issue,
- but there are new ways...
- Surgery.
- It's minimally invasive.
A thoracoscopic anterior
spinal fusion.
We make a small incision,
about the size of a dime.
We go in there
and pull out the bad discs,
and then we fuse the vertebrae
together with a plate.
And that's it.
- One surgery?
- In and out in about two hours.
You wake up... no pain,
no tingling,
and you're about
a good inch taller.
It... it straightens out
the curvature of the spine.
So the bad news is, you're
gonna have to bend down
a little bit lower
to pick up those grandbabies.
- Can I have a word with you?
I get that you're
the golden boy around here,
but you're a resident.
These are not
your patients, yet.
- I'm just presenting her
her options.
- You gave her a fantasy.
With her kyphosis,
she's not a candidate.
Raising her hopes
is unethical and cruel.
- I spent all night
researching this.
- You diagnosed her off
of Google?
- Just look at it.
It's a case from NYU...
worse than hers.
I can show you how to do it.
Just look.
Look, all anterior
decompressing arthrodesis.
- See the end plate?
- Mm-hmm.
- See the retractor?
- You see the angle?
- When the presenting symptoms
are pain,
decreased mobility, headaches,
and speech dysphasia,
what would your differential
diagnosis include?
- Cervical stenosis?
- Are you asking or stating?
Either way, it's incorrect.
Eventually...
you'll want to decide
if you're Semmes-Murphey fellows
or Semmes-Murphey dropouts.
- Dr. Skadden? Excuse me.
- Christopher, yes.
- Uh, um, I was...
- Wondering if I'd read
your proposal on obtaining
and culturing disc stem cells?
- Yes.
- Eliminates the need
for extraction.
Tons of potential.
I'd love to read more,
once you've fleshed out
the research you cited.
- Of course. Yes, sir.
- Thank you, Dr. Skadden.
Chiari malformation.
Speech dysphasia.
It's likely related to pressure
on the cerebellum.
That would be my diagnosis.
I'd really like to be considered
for your
fellowship program, sir.
If and when the time is
right, Christopher.
- Kayla, Kayla,
hey, I got great news.
Skadden read my proposal.
- Where are you going?
- Don't worry about it.
- Wait, are you leaving?
- Don't play fucking dumb
with me, Christopher.
Oxy, Adderall... it's like
a C-V-fucking-S in there,
and your name's all over it.
- The scrips?
- Scrips.
- They're for friends.
They're all friends in there.
It's no big deal.
- Okay, well enjoy your friends.
And whatever's left
of your career,
you stupid son of a bitch.
- Oh, this man's a hero.
Partied us under the table
last night,
then did his rounds,
saving lives
like Mother-fucking-Theresa.
- What the fuck happened
with Kayla?
- Kayla's cool.
Give her the night,
she'll calm down.
And if she does dump your
dumb face, I'll talk to her,
take care of everything,
like always.
You'd lose your big, ugly head
if I didn't tighten the screws
every morning, wouldn't you?
- I'm the one
with the big, ugly head?
- Yeah.
Oh!
Duntsch on the offensive.
Trying to reverse Summers
with a Granby roll.
But Summers dominates.
Oh, he dominates.
He dominates so hard.
Uncle! Uncle, uncle!
Shit.
Hey, Skadden said
he'd take a look at that.
You just got to come on down,
and we'll do some imaging.
Get you fixed up.
Whew.
I got to work.
Have you seen my LSD blotter?
How many hits did you take?
Oh, I must be
tripping hard, bro.
The letters
are all squiggly and shit.
- No, it's Cyrillic.
- It's psychedelic.
Oh, stem cells.
Is this for your PhD,
Dr. Doctor?
"Glioblastoma's
the most prevalent
malignant brain tumor."
That's harsh.
- The glioblastoma stem
is so dominant
that it takes normal cells,
and it changes them
into cancer cells.
- It dominates.
- It dominates hard.
- And everybody's trying
to figure out
how to stop glioblastoma.
But what if...
you could just program it
to make healthy cells?
- Then it... it wouldn't be
cancer anymore.
- Right.
Exactly right.
It can be whatever you want.
A cell that takes over
another cell
to make something good.
- A molecular biological
Granby roll.
- Yes. Yes. Yes.
Stem cells you inject
directly into a diseased disc,
making a brand-new
healthy baby spine.
- Preach.
- 50% of all spinal surgeries
are to repair diseased discs.
- We're talking about a startup.
- You're Dock Ellis.
You're pitching a no-hitter.
You're crushing it.
I can be your guinea pig.
- What?
- Inject that shit into my neck,
so I can grow a new baby neck
with no pain.
Pain's a pain, bro.
That could be your slogan.
Fuck.
Fuck!
Shit.
- Bob.
- Hello.
- What a surprise.
- Hey, Amy.
- Afternoon, Randy.
So how can I help you?
- Christopher Duntsch.
- Oh, boy.
Well, that about sums it up.
- He operated on a patient
at Legacy Frisco a few days ago.
- He left a hole
in her esophagus,
sliced through her vocal cord.
- We parted ways with
Dr. Duntsch almost a year ago.
- Well, what can you tell us
about this reference
that you wrote for Dr. Duntsch?
- I didn't write anything.
- Well, whatever law firm
you paid to write...
- And it isn't
a reference letter.
It's a letter stating there
were no restrictions
or suspensions
of his privileges.
- But it implies that there's
nothing in this record
to preclude him from working
at other hospitals.
He... he maimed people here.
He killed Shelley Brennan
by drilling
through her vertebral artery.
- He also did that to another
patient at Dallas Medical.
- Shouldn't that have
precluded him
from employment
at other hospitals?
- I have to be careful
about what I say right now.
Whoa.
I feel like I'm in the fucking
Twilight Zone here,
like I'm staring
at the face of a coverup.
- That's offensive.
- Oh, well,
I'll make sure to pass on
how offended you are
to his other victims.
- Facts were disputed
in some of his surgeries here.
- Surgeries?
Yeah, I saw one of his
"surgeries" here firsthand.
- And yet somehow, Dr. Kirby,
I didn't receive your complaint.
Our letter for Dr. Duntsch
is our fair and honest
appraisal of his standing
at this institution.
- Was Duntsch ever suspended?
Your letter indicates that
he was under investigation,
and since it's your policy
to suspend any doctor
under investigation,
I assume that you followed
through with your policy.
- Yes, you're correct. We did.
As I recall, it was 21 days.
Well, that's convenient.
- Excuse me?
- National Practitioner
Data Bank.
- That thing established
by Congress...
- I know.
- To warn the public
and other hospitals
about bad doctors.
- I know.
- You only have to report
the ones that are suspended
for 30 days or more.
- How come
you didn't report Duntsch
to the Texas Medical Board?
- I think we're done here.
- Can I ask you
a personal question?
Would you let Duntsch
operate on you?
- Lies of omission
do not make this institution
any less complicit, Ms. Piel.
- Nobody here is gonna help us.
- I'm not sure what kind
of help we're looking for.
- Come on, we can be sitting
in Skadden's office
in a few hours.
- We spoke to him already.
- I know.
- He says he
doesn't know anything.
- I know!
Come on, waste some time
with me.
Maybe we'll find out U.T.
turned out a fraud.
- Hi, everybody.
So sorry I'm late.
Katya, Dr. Duntsch.
Ilya, Dr. Duntsch.
Welcome to DiscGenics.
Thank you all so much
for coming.
That's for you. That's for you.
For you, sir.
And do you mind
passing those around?
I just need some vitamin C.
Be right back.
Okay.
Sorry about that.
Now, let me tell you
why you're all here.
I'm hoping that you will
continue to be interested
in what it is that I'm trying
to accomplish,
maybe financially interested.
- We already know.
- Our work
with osteosarcoma stem cells...
it's a simple deduction.
You wish to research
spinal cancer.
Nyet.
Nothing so basic.
I brought you here because
of your cancer research.
I practically memorized
your paper
on phenotypical heterogeneity
of neural cells.
But, look, we can all cure
cancer another day.
Right now your research
can be exploited
to create stem cells
to grow new spinal discs.
Eliminate the need for surgery.
That's what we're doing here
at DiscGenics.
- I question if you understand
the most basic science.
- Um...
may I see that for one second?
Thank you.
Um, if you'll all turn
to page...
13.
This is your work
in spherical clone generation.
You were able to demonstrate
stem cell markers OCT 3/4,
NANOG, and STAT3,
unless I misunderstood.
- That is correct.
- Right, but unlike with STAT3,
where there was robust
expression in both spheres
and adherent cultures,
NANOG and OCT 3/4
had more variable patterns
of expression.
Ergo, the key determinant in
self-renewal and pluripotency
for stem cells in embryonic
settings are variable.
Am I right?
I'm right. So all I'm asking
is that we take your work
into stem cell
self-renewal markers,
and we use it to create
a new cell therapy.
We build stem cells
to repair diseased spinal discs.
Will you help me out?
Well, what do you think?
Definitely intrigued.
- Outside the obvious,
how can I help?
- Honestly...
My surgical reps are killing me.
You know, there's only
so many hours in the day.
- You are an M.D./PhD.
You have to be able
to balance both.
You look tired.
Yeah.
I'm burning the candle
at both ends and the middle.
- A little friendly word...
if I had a future ahead of me
as bright as yours,
I would never want to be a
minute late showing up for it.
- Okay?
- Yes, sir.
- I'm gonna go press some flesh.
- Today I will be performing
an anterior cervical
discectomy and fusion.
The vertebral bodies are
exposed, and so is the disc.
Chris, I'm thinking DiscGenics
is gonna need some more money.
- What do you mean?
- You should meet
with some investment bankers.
I am drilling directly
into the disc
until I encounter the posterior
longitudinal ligament.
Beyond that is the spinal cord.
- Before I get the patent?
- The PLL is pierced.
Inside the diseased disc
resembles crabmeat.
I use a nerve hook
to remove the disc
and decompress the spinal cord.
It's classic
chicken-and-the-egg.
Private equity
is a lusty courtship.
The spinal cord is the white,
glossy structure with a juicy
blood vessel on top,
and that is the dura.
Now, we tease out...
We now tease out the disc.
Dr. Duntsch has successfully
removed the disc.
Well done.
Don't worry.
You'll get your patent, Chris.
And you and your company
will make us obsolete.
- We now drill holes
for the twin screws
in the vertebra.
You ready?
The only useful thing
you learned at Harvard
was how to name-drop
the word Harvard
into any given conversation.
Oh, here are
our two esteemed visitors
I was telling you about...
Dr. Robert Henderson
and Dr. Randall Kirby.
It's a pleasure to make
your acquaintance
in the flesh, gentlemen.
Dr. Kirby went
to Rice University
and Baylor College of Medicine.
And Dr. Henderson...
I'm so sorry.
I-I'm completely forgetting.
Uh, where did you get your M.D.?
- University of Nebraska.
- Yes.
Right, right.
Um, go, Corn Huskers.
- Duntsch's friend, if you can
believe he actually had one.
- Turned him
into a quadriplegic.
As of today, he's closing in
on two dozen
botched surgeries...
holes that drilled
through muscle,
nerves severed, arteries.
I mean, the guy can't define
basic regional anatomy.
- He approaches spinal surgery
like a child
playing with Tinkertoys.
- This is not
the Christopher Duntsch I knew.
These things here, I...
I never saw.
I just can't explain it.
- Well, perhaps
you could help us unpack
the reference you provided
for Duntsch?
- Of course.
- He met all
of his training hours?
- Yes, though I-I can't speak
to his... his residency.
You'd have to check
with them for that.
- I'm sure you wouldn't have
included him in your fellowship
if you didn't think he was
properly trained, correct?
- Correct.
- You oversaw his
surgical reps here?
- Yes.
And if you were one
of my fellows
and I was watching
and you did
what you've shown me here,
that would be the end
of your fellowship.
- Any drugs?
- I never saw anything
that would lead me
to that conclusion.
- Psychiatric issues?
- He may have sought counseling.
A lot of students do.
I'm afraid that's really all
I can help you with.
- With all due respect, I have
to disagree with you there.
- His references are
the bedrock to his bullshit.
He can get credentialed
anywhere.
- You're in a unique position
to tell them
what you know about Dallas.
- I did,
on the form for Forest Park.
I mentioned poor outcomes
at Baylor.
- But not Dallas Medical?
- No, no.
They wanted the form back
immediately.
So I checked the boxes
as requested,
stated that he was...
satisfactory, which he was.
- If it had been me,
I would have done everything
in my power to say,
"No, I cannot recommend him."
- I can read you the form
for privileges,
but it only relates
to his time here.
You're only allowed to attest
to what you directly observe,
that period of time
the observation is made,
and your role as observer...
what happened
during his training.
- What about the images
we've provided you with?
Yeah.
Yeah, I'm sorry.
I-I'm afraid I'd have to throw
the ball back to Dallas.
What happened, he did in Texas.
Makes you think
the hospitals there
will take any surgeon
with a pulse.
I see why you're so upset...
these hospitals
not reporting him,
Not vetting him properly.
But this is a Texas problem...
not a Tennessee problem.
Hi, it's Christopher Duntsch.
Dr. Christopher Duntsch calling.
Uh, just following up
on that exam you had
a couple of months ago.
I just wanted to see if you're
still interested in surgery
to correct all that pain.
I'm still working
out of Baylor-Plano,
but I did actually start
working at another hospital.
I'm just following up.
How's that neck pain?
A tingling foot?
The exam is free.
You are interested.
Oh, you moved.
Out of state.
You know, January is
Spinal Health Awareness Month.
Hello?
Mrs. Bloom?
He passed.
I will say hi to Jerry for you.
Kim is great.
Yeah.
No, she's great.
Well, Jerry...
moved on.
That's a hairline fracture.
You... you could be paralyzed
if you don't correct it.
Kim is great.
Yes.
Yes, yes.
I promise I'll never call back.
- Dr. Duntsch?
The Dr. Duntsch?
- Can I help you?
- We're kind of closing up.
- Uh, I'm Stan Novak.
I, uh, found 'em in your door.
- Oh, it's that
damn office manager...
so scatterbrained.
When did you hurt your neck?
- Motorcycle crash
six years ago.
I've had five back surgeries.
How'd you know it was my neck?
It's kind of what I do
for a living.
Let me guess...
when the spasms happen,
it feels like an electric shock?
- Oh, any little thing
sets 'em off.
Sometimes hits me
when I'm driving.
I almost go off the road.
- Yeah, that's Lhermitte's sign.
We're looking
at a cervical fusion.
You got severe compression
of the spinal cord,
but if we decompress that,
you'll have a full recovery.
I've seen so many doctors,
but I wanted you.
Saw your award video.
Best Docs.
- Two reasons why patients
normally present
to their doctors for pain
related to the spine...
the first is related to
the peripheral nervous system.
That's called radiculopathy.
Now, that's normally
associated with compression
or degenerative changes
to the spinal structure
irritating the nerve, or...
- Award for best doctor
in Texas, huh?
You caught me in the middle
of an expansion.
I'm a little short-staffed
right now.
- You can still do it, right?
- I'm all booked up at Baylor,
but I did just start
at University General.
I can squeeze you in there.
- We get the process, Duntsch.
- And we do
like disruptive tech.
- Then you're gonna
love DiscGenics.
- Oh, it's just that
I was forced to take
the "D to a C" program,
in high-school biology, so...
- I put the fucking
A in AP chem,
and I still don't get
what it does.
- Okay, brass tacks...
I'm inventing
an injectable fountain
of youth for the spine.
- Work for his wanker?
- That's phase two.
- Hey, there's hope.
- Look, simply put, stem cells
take over diseased cells
in spinal discs and repair them.
- How far along is it?
- We're looking for partners
right now to raise capital
based on lead assets
that we've already generated.
I mean, look, I am developing
a key process
in the manipulation
of stem cells,
but, equally important,
our competitors are going
to need to use this step
if they want to play
in our space.
We'll own it,
and they'll have to pay.
- And how'd you come up
with the concept?
LSD.
- I knew it.
- ♪ Bass down low,
bass, bass, bass down low ♪
♪ B-bass, bass down low ♪
♪ I-I-I like my beats fast... ♪
- Whoa, whoa, whoa, hey,
Make way for the king.
Yo, what the fuck's a MISI?
- Minimally Invasive
Spine Institute...
M-I-S-I, MISI.
- Minimally invasive spines
are your jam, man.
Too many choices.
What are you gonna do?
- What are we gonna do?
I don't think you should
sell anymore, you know?
- Come on, man.
- It's no big deal.
- No, no.
Come with me.
- Where?
- I got job offers in Dallas,
California, wherever.
- What am I gonna do?
- You already live with me.
You drive me.
We're best friends, right?
- Goddamn right we are.
Wherever you go,
I'll work for you.
Hey, how about director
of marketing?
Preach the empire of Duntsch.
- ♪ I like my beats fast
and my bass down low ♪
♪ Drop it to the floor ♪
♪ Bass down low,
bass, bass, bass down low ♪
♪ I-I-I like my beats fast
and my bass down low ♪
♪ It's like one, two,
three, okay ♪
- Wait a second.
- ♪ Every day feel like
my birthday ♪
♪ And we sip champagne
when we thirsty ♪
- Evening.
Just wanted to introduce myself.
- Get out of here.
- My name's Chris.
- What's yours?
- I paid for this, Chris.
Back the fuck off.
- Touch my friend again,
I'll break your spine,
and you'll have to pay him
to fix it.
- So, what's your name?
- Crystale.
It's a little early
for Halloween.
- I like your costume better.
- You gonna pay for it?
- No, 'cause you are priceless.
- Oh, if only I hadn't heard
that line seven times tonight.
- I bet you break a heart
every time you say that.
- If you're really a doctor,
what kind are you.
Aside from being
a cheap-ass one?
Well, Crystale,
unless you're board certified
in neurosurgery
and molecular biology,
I don't think I could
explain it to you.
- I'm board certified
in knowing you're an asshole.
- Hey!
- My name's not "hey."
- Well, it's not
Crystale either.
Look, I've had a crazy day.
A bunch of dreams
just came true all at once.
Has that ever happened to you?
- Dancing here is my trifecta
of dreams come true.
- Okay, so I'm an asshole,
and I'm sorry
for what I said earlier.
- Pardon the interruption.
Listen, bro, I don't need
to be marketing director.
Only title I want in your life
is friend,
and you can never fire me.
I go where you go,
but you do need
a slogan for DiscGenics.
- A slogan?
- I'll give it a whirl.
- You don't know what it is.
- Do you know what it is?
- I don't need to. I'm good.
- Holy shit. Done fucking deal.
Fuck, yeah.
Chris, you got to hear it.
She's rock and roll.
- ♪ La, la, la, la-la, la-la ♪
- Yes.
♪ If you want to get with me ♪
♪ There's some things
you got to know ♪
- ♪ Drop it to the floor ♪
- ♪ Bass down low ♪
♪ Bass, bass, bass,
bass down low ♪
♪ I-I-I like my beats fast
and my bass down low ♪
♪ B-b-bass down low ♪
♪ Bass, bass, bass,
bass down low ♪
♪ I like my beats fast
and my bass down low ♪
Bob!
Hey! Come on!
- No, no, no... oh.
I came at a bad time, I'm sorry.
- No, no, no! Come on.
- It's opera night, come on in.
- Come on.
- Hey, look at this.
He got another job.
University General Hospital.
You know what?
I went to med school
with the owner
of this place... Dr. Sasani.
We should go there.
- And do what exactly?
- I don't know.
We'll figure it out.
We'll, uh, denounce him
publicly.
No more half measures, right?
- Okay.
- Come on.
Jacqueline, look who's here!
This is Dr. Bob Henderson.