I can't move.
Why can't I move?
Chris?
Where's Chris?
- Try to relax.
- Where's Chris...
- Doctor's going to come in...
- Duntsch? He's my doctor.
- Take a look and see
what's going on.
- Nothing's going on. I can't...
Nothing works.
I can't feel shit.
Chris!
- And move your shoulders.
Shrug up...
and down.
That's it.
Some mobility.
That's a good sign.
- Fuck some mobility.
- I want it all.
Jesus Christ!
- Jerry...
do you remember me?
I'm Dr. Ivers.
I was the anesthesiologist
in your case.
- What's happening to me, Doc?
- We're not sure.
I'm here to ascertain whether
your partial paralysis...
- Paralysis?
- Is being caused
by the anesthesia.
- Dr. Ivers...
I need Chris...
Duntsch...
my doctor.
Please, call his ass.
Page his ass. Hunt his ass down.
Excuse me?
Where are you taking me?
- Dr. Rosario
ordered some images.
- Who the fuck is Dr. Rosario?
- Worst part's over.
Now, remember to lay very still,
or else we'll have to
start all over again.
- Hi, there, my name
is Michelle Shughart.
I'm the
Assistant District Attorney
overseeing
the Christopher Duntsch case.
- Uh-uh.
We don't want to have nothing
to do with that asshole.
- I just need a few minutes
of your time...
- Our family has been
through enough.
- Yes, ma'am.
- It feels like there's
an ice pick in my back.
- He always talked
about being the best.
My experience...
you got to preach it,
probably isn't true.
But I didn't feel
that way about him.
I liked him.
- We tried.
No lawyer would take up the case
'cause of the reform
down there in Austin.
- Tort reform. House Bill 4.
- Politicians.
I can't believe that I voted
for that dipshit Rick Perry.
I can't even bring
a malpractice claim.
Well, I mean, I suppose I could,
but no matter what happens...
no matter what somebody does
to you or the people you love,
all you're gonna get
is $250,000.
Now, what's the lawyer's cut
of that?
- Not a whole heck of a lot.
- Who wants to get all tied up
and twisted
for "not a whole heck of a lot"?
Meanwhile, Slick Rick
and his cohorts
and his lobbyists line
their war chests with donations
from insurance companies
and hospitals...
like Baylor.
- My husband made me go
to Duntsch.
He wanted me to be able
to get back to work
and help more with the kids,
but now he's gone,
and I'm alone
and worse than I was before.
- I looked into the operating
lights, said a prayer...
"Protect me from all danger.
Keep me safe."
- He spun a good tale.
- For every one
of his victims...
I've spoken
to too many of them...
and he made them all feel
comfortable until it was over.
- You want my help, hmm?
- If you can testify...
it'll go a long way
to putting him in prison.
- Will it make me whole again?
- No.
But it could bring justice.
- I'm too old to go looking
for justice.
I'd settle for a peaceful heart.
- So you want murder?
- How are we going
to prove intent?
- He killed two people.
- Any good defense lawyer
would bar other victims
from testifying.
With no other victims,
we have no pattern of behavior.
It's just
a medical misadventure.
- What about manslaughter?
- Second-degree felony.
- Carries 2 to 20.
And since this is a doctor,
I'm taking the under, at best.
I mean, honestly, Steph,
if you heard these people...
their stories,
saw what he did to them...
and they have no recourse.
Can't sue anybody.
The state of Texas took
that option away from them.
I feel bad.
- About what?
- I want Duntsch to die in jail.
- You know you're a prosecutor?
Dying in jail is an oft-pursued
avenue of justice.
- I don't know.
Let's focus
on aggravated assault.
Jury might buy he purposely
caused serious bodily harm.
- How could they not?
- Well, "purposely"
is the keyword there, Steph.
Hi, there, Dr. Henderson.
It's Paul Racconti
with "Dr. Phil."
I heard about your involvement
in the Dr. Duntsch story
down there in Texas...
- Dr. Henderson,
my name's Liz Geller.
I'm with "The New York Times."
We're planning on doing a piece
on Dr. Christopher Duntsch...
- Hi, Dr. Henderson,
this is Maya Comici
of The Blaze.
Please call me back at
your earliest convenience at...
- What is The Blaze?
- Yeah, I thought
about looking it up,
but then I decided life
is too short.
- And incredibly irritating.
- You could have
your 14 minutes of fame.
Now, there was a story I
thought you'd find interesting.
A journalist in town
did a piece,
and Duntsch commented on it.
- Where?
- In the comments section, Bob.
It's a bunch
of rambling nonsense
about how this is all
a witch hunt, a scam, a hoax.
He says he can't wait
to get back and clear his name,
"My patients need me."
- Are you commenting back?
- I am now.
"Dear Dr. Death"...
"I wish you knew
how satisfying it felt
"to rip your medical license
"out of your grubby paws
this past summer.
"I sleep better at night
"knowing you'll never practice
in Dallas
or the state of Texas again."
- You're gloating.
Don't complicate
Michelle's case.
And you shouldn't be out there
harassing the defendant.
- Gloating feels so good.
- Heavenly Father, we thank You
for blessing us with this meal
and for our health.
We thank You
for this opportunity
to break bread with our son.
Thank You for leading him home.
And we pray, with Your wisdom,
that You will guide him
back to the light.
Amen.
- Amen.
Lovely.
You know, Dad,
this is only temporary.
I mean...
I'm sure it's awkward
having me in your home.
- If it were up to me,
all my boys
would be under one roof.
- Well, look, I'll be gone soon.
I'm planning
on heading back to Dallas.
I'm gonna start practicing
just as soon as this bullshit
with the Medical Board
is cleared up.
I'm gonna have
my medical license back
before you know it.
- What about your son
and your girlfriend?
Do they factor into your plans?
- Well, yeah.
- I mean, of course, they do.
You know, I-I've got, uh,
visitation with Mason
once a month, and...
it does piss me off
that I have to spend
all this money
flying back and forth
and pay her child support,
but, you know,
once things are back to normal,
money won't matter.
This is an attempt
to collect an outstanding
debt, Mr. Duntsch.
Give us a call back,
as your American Express card
is in danger...
This is Bank of America.
Concerning your loan payment...
Chris, you keep
ignoring my calls,
I'm gonna have to sue.
Call me.
- Stay out of my business.
- Your business keeps coming
to me, Chris.
- Why can't you just support me?
- All I do is support you...
and your family.
Now, this is simple...
if you're gonna stay here,
you will do as you're told.
You're gonna declare bankruptcy.
I can't have these pe...
I will not have these people
coming after your mother and me.
Just wipe
the slate clean, Chris.
You start over...
not just for you,
but for your son.
You'll still have a chance
at a future if...
- Hi.
I know normally people
mail these in,
but I always like
to give a personal touch.
- You're certainly taking
the initiative.
- Carpal tunnel?
- All the typing.
- Do you mind
if I take this off?
If you approve
my medical license,
with my stem cell research,
we'd be able to relieve
the pain on the median nerve...
Eradicate the problem.
Free up all those little nerves,
and your pain'd be gone.
- Wow.
- Wow's right.
And just like those nerves,
I believe that we are all
connected to a greater purpose.
And I'm really hoping that
you can help me achieve mine.
- Oh...
well, you got my vote.
Not sure it'll help much,
but I'll be sure
to put your application
at the top
of my supervisor's pile.
- Great.
I hear you're having
some muscle weakness
in your extremities.
- Where you been, Dump Face?
- I had an L4-L5 lumbar
procedure right after yours.
Look, Jerry,
once you're out of my OR,
your case and care
are transferred
to other hospital staff.
It wouldn't be appropriate
for me to leave another patient
to come see you.
- Well, they really sucked
at taking over my care.
But fuck it. You're here now.
What's going on with me, man?
- The anesthesiologist
administered
an incorrect dosage.
This led to swelling
in your spinal cord
and the quadriplegia,
but you give it a week,
a course of steroids,
you'll be better than before,
as promised.
- Okay, Chrissy.
You say it's temporary...
I'll believe you.
- I'll chill out.
- Good.
- Hey, Chrissy...
thanks.
- Why did you tell him that?
It's clear
from the images that...
- The swelling is not
going down... I am aware.
We need to alleviate
the pressure on his spine.
I want you to prep an OR.
We're going back in...
posterior this time.
- Are you going to tell him?
- No. He'll just freak out
more than he already is.
- But he needs to sign
the consent forms.
- I spoke to his grandma.
- She signed off.
- Are you sure
you want to do this?
Maybe Dr. O'Connor
could take over the case?
- We were doing eight balls.
- Excuse me?
- Christopher Duntsch and me...
Cocaine.
You hear me?
All night long.
The night before my surgery...
We were blowing coke
all night long.
Chris Duntsch and me.
All fucking night!
- Cocaine?
Amy, seriously?
- Given the seriousness of what
he's claiming, I have to ask.
- Well, now you have,
and it's ridiculous.
I mean, maybe he was.
I don't know.
Honestly, I think he's
suffering from ICU psychosis.
His nurse told me
that he hasn't slept
since the night
of the second surgery.
That would make anybody crazy
and hallucinate.
He just needs to sleep.
- He's hallucinating that
you did cocaine together
the night before surgery?
- Well, I-I don't have
another explanation.
- I d... I don't know what
Mr. Summers is talking about.
- I have an OR to grace...
- Please sit back down,
Dr. Duntsch.
In light
of the poor surgical outcomes
- of Mr. Summers surgeries...
- Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa.
Whatever poor surgical outcomes,
while unfortunate,
they're not my fault.
Mr. Summers should've had
that surgery done years ago.
- Our internal investigation
will hopefully confirm that.
In the meantime, Baylor
is suspending your privileges.
- This is bullshit!
- You'll have to undergo
a psych evaluation
with Baylor's
board psychiatrist,
and both of you will have
to take a drug test.
- Give me the cup.
- I'll do it right now.
- This is totally
and completely baseless!
I mean, yes, of course,
so will I.
I mean, if that's
what we got to do,
that's what we got to do.
- I'm sorry, Chrissy.
I didn't know what to do.
I feel like
I ain't getting the truth.
Like...
after my first surgery...
I could move a little...
but now I can't move at all.
So what the fuck's going on?
Am I gonna be able
to walk again?
I mean...
"swelling and steroids,
and I'll feel better
than I did before"?
How do I know
you're not lying to me?
Don't you have anything to say
about all this?
- You ruined everything for me.
Good luck.
- No. I-I'm...
- I'm driving around
looking for the lab right now...
I can't find it anywhere.
No, I'm standing outside
right now.
They're telling me
they're closed.
Of course I know
they close at 4:30.
They're just saying
there's not enough time today.
Yeah, Preston Road...
I'm on it now.
What's that?
It's traffic.
You're not going to believe
this, but I forgot my ID.
They won't let me take it.
Yes, of course, absolutely...
loud and clear.
I will be there
first thing Monday morning.
Okay, thank you.
Monday, Monday, Monday, Monday,
Hey.
- Fucking pathetic.
I warned you...
no drugs around Mason, ever.
He was napping.
- I told you,
I got this all under control.
- Was all this part of your big
Dallas plans?
- What?
- Wind up a junkie...
- You can't take Mason.
- Without a job?
I got a job!
- This isn't right!
- No, it isn't right.
But you know who is right?
Your Dad, about you.
Mason and I do deserve better.
- I have a relationship
with Dr. O'Connor.
I talked to him.
He wants to take over
your case...
See if he can help make this
as normal as possible for you.
I know it won't ever be
the same, Jerry.
We're here to help.
I'm here to help.
- Kill me.
- I can't.
- Get the fuck out.
- I'd like to start
our time together
by offering my condolences.
Your friend, Jerry.
- We went to the same
high school.
- Well, at any rate,
you surgeons have so much
pressure on you to perform.
Drugs and alcohol
can become a crutch.
Look...
I drink as much
as the next person.
Glass of Malbec here,
Glenlivet there.
Never within 12 hours
of operating.
These allegations against me
are completely baseless.
- And what about drugs?
- I mean, sure.
I have tried cocaine
back in college.
It wasn't for me.
- What about Summers's surgery?
I understand
you're just doing your job.
They told you
I needed a psych eval.
I was just doing my job, too,
to the best of my ability,
which is pretty goddamn good.
- Do you regret the outcome?
- Of course I do. I'm human.
But you have to get back
on the horse.
I just need to get back
- You don't feel the need
to take time off?
- I already have, too much.
- I'm talking
about personal time
not ordered by
the administration.
- I read somewhere once
that if, from time to time,
you don't have
negative surgical outcomes
in your practice,
you're not operating.
My patients
mean everything to me,
and the longer
I'm here on this couch,
the longer they're out there
in crippling pain.
- Okay, I hear you.
I'll let Piel know
I've determined
you're fine to operate.
- Thank you for your time,
Dr. Roman.
- Let me know
if you ever need anything...
ever need to talk.
- You know, there is something
I've been having
trouble with lately.
- What kind of trouble?
- Ah, with...
concentration,
since the suspension.
- Ever during surgery?
- No, no, no, no, never.
I was just wondering
if maybe you could...
just give me something
to bridge the gap
between suspension and surgery.
All right. There's that.
And...
I remembered this time.
Thank you.
Um, hey, I'm taking Ritalin
prescribed by my doctor.
I just want to make sure
it's not going to cause
a positive test.
- Dr. Roman already called,
told us all about it.
- Great.
- I'm not after you.
So he first shows up
here in Dallas
with a job at the Minimally
Invasive Spine Institute?
- MISI. Yes.
- But he wasn't there
for very long.
- Do you know why?
- Baylor recruited him, hard.
- Why?
- Neurosurgeons make big bucks.
- What about drugs?
You ever witness any of that?
- I flushed it.
- Was it cocaine?
- I don't know.
- What were you doing
in his bathroom late at night?
- What are you getting at?
- The defense
will ask you, too...
under oath.
- Briefly, and I ended it.
- May I ask why?
- What's next?
- Jerry Summers...
his surgery.
Any truth to those
eight ball allegations?
- I don't know.
- Did Jerry do drugs
the night before?
- I couldn't know.
- I don't live there.
- Is there anything that
you can think of
that would point
to how all of this happened?
- He sent me an email.
But I want to be clear here.
I didn't think
a damn thing of it.
Duntsch was always spouting,
self-aggrandizing
nonsensical bullshit.
- May I see it?
The email?
- I didn't second-guess
the email
until after Jerry's surgery.
Duntsch refused to see him.
He was so...
He was so dismissive of him...
of his fear and his pain.
And then Shelley Brennan
comes in.
And she's dead.
20 minutes into her surgery,
she's dead.
And I start thinking...
about that email.
- What were you thinking?
- Was he...
Was he doing it on purpose?
- Like banging your head
on a cupboard...
- Mm.
- Or grabbing a hot pot.
One little missed step.
Didn't even fall,
just slipped a little bit
off the ladder
hanging Christmas lights.
Work's been near impossible
ever since.
I'm an elementary-school
teacher.
The kids keep me on my feet.
Surgery is a big decision,
Mrs. Brennan.
- I hear you.
PT, steroids, none of it worked.
Surgery seems all that's left.
Going on a cruise
with my husband,
another couple.
- That right?
- Yeah, Antigua...
in a couple months.
I haven't been
on a vacation in...
I don't know...
whoo, a long time.
- How did you hear
about Dr. Duntsch?
- He came recommended
by my family doctor... highly.
I checked
all his reviews online.
Everyone loves him.
- Are you sure you don't want
to find a doctor
closer to where you live?
Mrs. Brennan.
- You're the man who's gonna
make everything better.
- Dr. Duntsch.
I've been speaking with your
GP about this spine of yours.
- Mm-hmm.
- It sounds like we need
to relieve some pressure
on that nerve right here.
But it's a simple micro lami.
We should have you in and out
in 20 minutes.
- 20?
- Yeah.
It takes longer to boil a pot
of pasta at a high altitude.
What's the schedule
looking like?
- Um, I'm not sure, Dr. Duntsch.
Did Baylor clear some of their
operating rooms for our use?
- Why don't you give them
a call and find out?
We'll get you
in first available.
Now...
- Do you have a drug
and alcohol problem, sir?
- No, sir, never have.
- We caught up with
Dr. Duntsch outside Denver
where he now lives.
I talked to a doctor
who said you're a sociopath
and a killer.
Do you have a response?
- Yeah, I'm gonna deal with that
in the context of libel later
when I'm defending myself.
- His patients all say there's
a more fitting punishment.
- Ms. Shughart, this is amazing.
- You know, I may have
bitten off a mouthful.
- We get it.
- How can we help?
- I need to prove that Duntsch
assaulted these people,
that he should've known what
he was doing to his patients.
- Mm-hmm.
- The only way to do that
is to differentiate
between a normal medical
procedure and what he did.
And the only way to do that
is to be able to teach
a stripped-down version
of neurosurgery to the jury.
So...
I need you to teach me
neurosurgery.
- "Pain.
"Pain is the most common reason
patients seek medical care.
"Pain has sensory
and emotional components
"and is often classified
as acute or chronic.
Acute pain is frequently
associated with anxiety,"
and that's how
my mother slept with my father.
Uh-oh, Bob, looks like
we've lost the class.
- No, no, no.
Um, maybe. Yes.
- Well, maybe you're more
experiential learners, huh?
All right, you, Come on up here,
lose the shirt,
and bend over the table.
I'm a doctor.
You are all lawyers.
Come on.
Okay, pay attention.
Here we have
the prominent vertebra
in the lower neck, the C7.
Okay, I'm just going to mark it
out here... C7.
- No, no, no.
- Doctor, Doctor, Doctor, Doctor.
You're marking it too big
because it's going to overlap
with the T1.
- How am I supposed to see that
if I'm not actually
inside of his body?
- Well, if you don't operate
as fast as you talk...
- Eh, Randall Kirby
is the preeminent surgeon...
- I'm calling it.
- Time of death is right now.
Uh, let's try again tomorrow?
- Anybody want to grab a bite?
There's a neat little place
around the corner
with an early-bird special.
- You are nothing
if not consistent.
- Short rib sliders, $3.
- Why don't you
throw your AARP card down
and maybe you can get it
for $2.75.
- Well, that's not exactly
how it works, but...
- Let's hop on your Rascal
and find out.
- Elder abuse.
- Thank you.
- He's not that old.
- No, no.
Madeline Beyer's over
65 years old.
She qualifies.
Injury to an elderly person
or a minor.
- With that charge,
there's no limit
to the scope of the complaint.
- We can introduce
all of our victims,
even the ones
outside our jurisdiction.
Show intent,
and the maximum sentence
is life in prison.
- Hmm.
- Shit.
- She doesn't want to testify.
- Why don't you let me
talk to her?
- We may need a lighter touch,
Dr. Kirby.
No... no offense.
- No, we had an agreement.
- We said once a month.
- This would be twice a month.
- Wendy, please.
- No, fly away.
- No.
- Hey!
- Hi.
- Hey, buddy.
- I brought you something.
- Thanks.
- That's for you.
Hey, what is with
this little dinky ball?
We got to get you
a regulation ball
if you're ever going to play
for the Broncos.
- Okay, I'm calling the cops
for trespassing and kidnapping.
- He's my son, too, Wendy,
and I pay for this apartment.
- No, your dad pays
for this place.
- Get the fuck
out of here, fat boy.
- Ow. Shit.
- Who the fuck is... Ow!
- Stop it! Both of you!
- Shawn! Shawn, stop!
- Shawn, stop!
Stop, Shawn!
- Dad?
Dad, I need help. I was...
I was robbed.
I need some... I need you
to send me money.
I was robbed.
I need some help, please.
Please, just send me
some money, to Dallas.
Please, Dad.
- I sent you money, Chris.
- I'm not in the mood, Dad.
- You asked me,
and I sent you money.
- I know.
- Shoplifting? Shoplifting.
First, it was a DUI,
and now it's shoplifting.
- I told you I'd pay you back.
- How are you going to do that?
You gonna borrow
some more money from me
to pay me back
the money you owe me?
- It's Wendy.
- It's not.
- It is.
- Stop it, Chris.
- It's Wendy.
- You know, you keep playing
to the edges, and you wonder
why you're falling off.
- She won't let me see Mason.
- Well, good for her.
You deserve what you get.
Want?
- Texas is never gonna
reinstate my medical license.
- Well, maybe that's
a good thing.
- Nobody'll even hire me
to do research.
After everything I've done,
everything I've achieved...
I got nothing left.
- It's not nothing, Chris.
It's just going to be different.
- Nobody robbed me...
in Dallas last year.
Um...
I lied to you.
- Luke 15, verses 3 through 7.
"The shepherd that left
his flock
to find the one lost sheep."
I doubt the sheep got beaten
with a plastic bat
by a meth-head shepherd,
but all right.
- I know it's not going
to be easy, Chris,
but go back to Dallas
with a pure heart
and make things right
with Wendy.
The first step to atonement,
and the hardest, is confession.
And you've already taken it.
- Oh.
It's nice to see that you're
back out in your garden.
- Mm-hmm.
I had to hire someone to help,
and they're trying their best.
But...
If you want it done right...
- Ms. Shughart sent you?
- Yes.
- She's young.
Yes.
But no one else would help us
until she came along.
I'm gonna cross a line here,
but I'm asking you to testify.
I consider myself
a fairly intelligent person,
a decent doctor.
I can open and fix
and close a living being.
And I can't get my brain
around the case
that Ms. Shughart is building.
But I do know this...
without you, there's a chance
that Duntsch may walk away
with just a slap on the wrist.
You're asking me
to relive something
I'd much rather forget.
- I don't see
how you can do that.
You live with the reality
of this wheelchair every day.
Duntsch belongs in prison
for the rest of his life.
Now, I came in too late
to save you.
I can't give you anything back.
But your testimony will ensure
that Duntsch never does this
to another patient ever again.
- What would I have to say?
- The truth.
Just tell your truth,
and everything will be okay.
- You're old enough to know
truth in our world
rarely works out for the teller.
- Mm.
What choice do we have?
- Morning, fellas.
- You're on my to-do list.
We got eyes on
Florence Nightingale's motel.
- Booked to be here in 72 hours.
- Great. Thanks.
- Duntsch's trips are getting
a little few and far between.
If he ever stops coming,
Denver police are slow as fuck
when it comes to extradition.
- I'm on it.
Trying to slip into
an already convened grand jury.
We've got one chance
to get this indictment.
- You know, I can't believe
this is for a doctor.
You should arrest
my elementary-school nurse.
She diagnosed me with measles.
I had the chicken pox.
- I'll see you back
at the office.
- Did we win?
- It's gonna be a few hours.
- Well, we cleared
our schedules.
- Thank you.
- I had a tee time.
I booked it months ago.
- Thank you.
Thank you.
When the gods wish to punish us,
they answer our prayers.
- What does that mean?
She got the indictment.
Ahh.