Previously on "You"...
Everyone just calls me Beck.
And you are Joe?
Goldberg.
A guy needs to protect himself,
and your name was
a glorious place to start.
The next thing our little
friend the Internet gave me
was your address.
Professor Leahy.
Professor Obvious
wants to sleep with you.
Your friends are disloyal,
and that Peach is the queen bee.
How broke are you?
Benjamin J. Ashby, Greenwich
born, boarding school bred.
God, you make me insane.
Oh!
I think I know you.
Oh, right. Of course.
You're smart, except in
the ways you are really not,
like not locking your phone.
Maybe we could get
a drink sometime.
Sure.
What you really need is
someone to save you.
Man, I'm thinking maybe--
Whatever you think I did...
I can help, Beck.
...you got the wrong guy.
Let me help you.
Tonight's the night, Beck.
Our first date.
It just feels right, right?
I'm looking forward to it,
and I think,
obvious hangover aside,
you are, too.
But I've read people wrong
in the past.
One day, I'll tell you
about Candace,
every red flag I was blind to,
how destroyed I was.
What can I say?
We all have baggage.
But I feel like I'm dealing
with it the right way.
Not bothering you,
just checking it.
Hanging with you like this is
admittedly honing skills
I never knew I'd need,
but hey, handy.
You can't afford new clothes,
but let's be real.
You'd look perfect
in a potato sack.
Not a criticism,
God knows I am, too,
but you seem distracted.
Of course, a new phone.
Not sure how you went
24 hours without one.
As you activate
your new friend there,
I know you think you're also
deactivating your old one.
But here's where you're wrong.
Your old phone, which I have,
is still logged into the cloud.
And that means
I'm still logged into you.
Sci-fi movies are so wrong.
Technology is our friend.
You've reached Benji.
Leave some love. Namaste.
Hey, look,
you haven't texted back.
Just let me know
you're okay, okay?
That's all I ask.
This is really annoying, Benji.
It is annoying.
You're not thinking about us,
you're thinking about him.
I kind of thought I took care
of that for you, Beck.
Want to start off the class
this morning?
- Sure.
- Good.
My last T.A. was like
a little mouse,
- afraid of public speaking.
- Oh, that's my job.
Well, lucky us,
you're good at it.
We're still on for tomorrow,
drinks, poetry?
Nothing if not up
for both of those.
Hey, they came for the big day.
Want me move them down
to the basement?
No, I'll do that. Just get
started on the window display.
Oh, hey, I was thinking about
making cookies for #ReleaseDay.
Amanda Chantal Bacon has a dope
recipe in "Moon Juice Cookbook:
Cook Cosmically for Body,
Beauty, and Consciousness".
Kill me.
Sounds great, Ethan.
Oh, and that kid is back.
Paco?
Hey, speed reader.
Hi, Joe.
What are you reading?
This book about werewolves
the girls in my class
won't stop talking about.
It's more about love stuff
than werewolf stuff.
There should be right up here...
Yeah, it's right here.
Here, try this.
"Frankenstein"?
Yeah, the monster is
really cool and scary
but also not really the monster.
What does that mean?
Just read it. You can tell me.
Ethan's got snacks. Set 'em up.
Let me the hell outta here!
Now!
Settle down, Benji.
Let's talk.
Okay, granted I didn't think
too far ahead
when I swung that mallet.
I just knew Benji was
the worst kind of poison,
the kind you know is bad
but can't stop taking.
So I did what I had to do
to help you, Beck.
And now, there's
an adult human male
in the basement
of this bookstore.
Somebody!
The basement's soundproof.
Aah!
The owner loved to
read in peace down here.
I'm sorry.
I told you,
I don't know who you are,
I don't know why I'm here.
I swear.
Confession, I have no idea
what to do with him now.
I'm gonna give you
my family lawyer's number.
He'll get you paid.
Of course he thinks
I want money.
You know who my father is?
Benjamin Ashby II,
hedge fund manager.
We have a jet. We'll send
you anywhere in the world.
Best case, that's somewhere
far away from you, Beck.
Worst case,
that ends with prison time.
Not an option.
It's a poppy seed bagel,
extra schmear.
Go to hell.
I don't eat gluten.
It's an allergy, okay?
That shit is real.
Gluten, dairy, if I ate
a peanut, I could die.
Well, gosh,
whatever can I get you?
I'd just like a bare burger
wrapped in chard.
Or I could do sushi.
Sushi?
My diet is limited. Please?
Whoever you are,
you're not a killer.
Oh, how I wish I was.
This would be
much less complicated.
Let me out of here.
I won't say anything to anyone.
He doesn't even know my name.
I can figure this out.
I'm claustrophobic.
My blood sugar's low.
Is this sugar?
I found it in your wallet along
with three bars of Xanax,
Adderall, half a sheet of,
I think, acid, is it?
Whatever. It's not even for me.
I network. I own a business.
That's right, Home Soda.
It's artisanal.
It's gonna blow up.
Is it?
Do your investors know
you do heroin?
Or your--your father?
How about your girlfriend?
I don't have a girlfriend.
Oh, shit!
That's where I know you from.
You were in the cab!
Beck's cab!
She--she said your name.
It's Jimmy. No.
This is Joe.
He literally saved my life.
It's Joe!
Now, that's a complication.
Do not tell me that you're
doing this because of Beck.
She's not my girlfriend.
You can have her!
Take her!
Careful, Benji.
Not winning any points.
If you knew her,
you would not be
putting me in a cage
and ruining your life over
Guinevere Goddamn Beck!
If you want out,
you'll do what I want.
The days of being with a man
who doesn't value you,
those are over.
If we can get over
the first date hump.
Can't help it,
worried about Benji.
That's why it's so crucial
Benji's out of your picture.
Please, he's off
getting shit-faced.
Or he's in some kind of trouble.
What we have right now is
just a little spark.
Every choice is a message.
With Candace, I always felt
like I was pushing.
But now I realize,
can't force it,
the timing, the spark.
So you tell me if
you're too distracted, Beck.
You decide.
Sure. Looking forward.
Free at six.
So it was just one of those
cheesy diaries with a lock,
but I couldn't stop writing.
I just--I felt better having it
all down on paper, you know?
And then I did this little
creative writing assignment
and it just blew
my teacher's mind.
She acted like it was the best
thing she'd...
Honestly, part of me thought
this date would never come,
and now it feels so easy,
so right.
This is how our story goes,
Beck.
And here I am.
Sometimes you just,
you do things on instinct
because you have to, and
then you scramble, you know.
Yeah, I kinda know.
I totally didn't Google
you, but if I did,
I might discover you
aren't on social media.
Fact, it renders you insanely
vulnerable with zero upside.
I'm an old-fashioned guy.
I like real life.
What about your job?
Bookstore manager or--
or international
super spy, which is--
I mean, is that your goal or--
I know I'm in a city
full of people
with--with--with big, fat
neon sign aspirations.
And I know it's not cool to say
and it's not big and flashy...
but I love books,
and I want my life to be about
what I actually love.
Yeah, I get that.
Sorry, just a second, okay?
Yeah, go ahead.
Hey.
Yeah, I know it's serious,
Peach.
I'm the one who told you
I was worried.
Okay. Yes, I'm coming.
I'm sorry, I have to go.
This friend, he just--apparently
he had to go meet someone
and never came back.
It's worrying.
We can pick it up some other
time if you have to.
All right, thank you.
I hope your friend is okay.
I thought I'd done it,
gotten Benji out of our way.
Looks like I have to
finish the job.
To figure out what to do
with the poster boy
for white male privilege
in the cage,
I need to understand
who he truly is.
And to do that, I need to know
what he cares about.
This is totally unfair.
If I knew you were
gonna quiz me,
I'd have put more recent
books on the list.
So bottom line, you've never
even read "On the Road".
It's very possible to
read a book
without having to read it
in the traditional manner.
You can read about a book.
Yeah, I get it.
You're a fraud.
Here, give me the stupid book.
I'll read it right now,
you sadistic prick.
Anything to get me out of here.
I do understand something
about you now, Beck.
You somehow think this guy
is all you deserve.
You're looking a little gray
and mealy in there.
Yeah, no shit.
You stole my stash!
I thought it wasn't for you.
Fine.
You happy? It's mine.
I'm a chipper.
I never do it more than
three days in a row.
And I'm quitting.
Okay, only if you're quitting.
Doesn't work that way.
It's only one way.
Thank you. Thank you.
Just one more thing.
Password.
Leanna.
L-E-A-N-N-A.
His phone lock is
another girl's name, Beck.
Jesus Christ.
Oh, yeah.
Well, he's been living
a frankly off-brand life
for a guy who markets
health soda.
Based on the evidence,
he's not missing you
when you're gone.
You don't mean anything to him.
Say cheese.
I was worried.
I called his mother.
We were about to call
the police, and he's high
in some random shitburg
in Massachusetts
according to his geolocation.
Don't say geolocation.
You're not a stalker.
At least we know he's fine,
just being the worst.
So we're all gonna go try
that new bar tonight, right?
In SoHo.
You are such a lush.
Shit, I can't go. I'm sorry.
I'm supposed to have drinks
with my thesis adviser.
Oh.
Ugh, scale of one
to ten, how pervy?
He won an award
for a book of poems
that probably has 35 references
to, like, vagina lips.
Well, banging your professor
is like a grad school
- rite of passage.
- Is it?
Annika's like the Wikipedia
page for slut, so...
Whatever. I banged
my bio professor.
It was fine.
Notably, I passed the class.
You know, eyes on the prize.
Ovary up, girl.
Beck doesn't want to ovary up.
He controls my status as a T.A.
He could knock me
out of my housing.
Or you could not figure
it out and report him.
I think it only works
that way in the movies.
Whatever.
We're seeing you tomorrow.
My party.
Tomorrow is the anniversary
of my parents' divorce.
The party I always have
to distract myself.
Of course. Sorry. I'm coming.
One more line, man, come on.
Just tell me your plan
and I will help you.
Where is she right now?
She's partying her face off
with Lynn and Annika, right?
Actually, she's about
to meet her thesis adviser,
but glad to hear
you take her seriously.
See, this is
what I'm telling you.
You see this hardworking
writer chick.
How could you not?
She's branded the living shit
out of herself
across the Internet.
I want you to know,
if I wasn't about
to be late to see you,
I would beat this guy bloody
for the way he talks about you.
I'm telling you,
this is her thing.
Right now, she's got on
red lipstick
and she's getting ready to
work her professor hard
for that "A".
I'll see you later, Benji.
Hey, come back.
I'm hungry!
There's a directness.
That's what's special
about your work.
So if it's not direct
to the bone, cut it.
Thanks. That's really helpful.
And coming from you,
it means a lot.
A lot of people find
a direct woman irresistible.
You should lean into that
in your life as well.
Yeah, easier said than done.
Well, you can always
practice on me.
I'm safe.
You really have nothing
to be nervous about.
The world is your
bright red apple.
You think he writes these
lines in advance like a poem?
I wish I had your... confidence.
Putting your work out
into the world is a service.
I'll try and remember that.
I wouldn't tell you
if you weren't talented.
I'm happy to share
all my secrets.
So, Beck, maybe it's time to
acknowledge what there is here.
Don't touch me.
It's not sexy, it's repulsive.
Sorry, but this is--
You invited me to.
No, I didn't.
You flirt brazenly.
You wear clothes so sheer
I can see your nipples.
What do you call that?
- It's crazy.
- If you're gonna stay
on the safe side of the
plausible deniability zone,
cover your tits,
stop the blow-job eyes,
and write... better.
I like you,
but clearly you're overworked.
It's only right to release you
from the T.A. position.
No. No, please.
Get some rest.
You're right to be angry.
Some things can't
just be allowed to be.
Something has to be done
about someone like him.
Hello.
Hey, where are you?
I'm in the Village.
Maybe we can finish our talk.
Yeah, I'll be there in 15.
Are you staring at my lipstick?
No, no. No, I'm not.
I'm not.
No, it's just different.
No, I just--I wanted
to try something new,
but you're right,
it's not really me.
So why did you call me?
I don't know.
Spontaneous impulse.
That's okay. You'll learn
you can tell me anything.
We cut it short last time
because a friend of yours,
he was missing, right?
Oh, God, he's fine.
He's just an idiot.
Agree with you there,
but you want to keep it light.
I can do that.
Okay, this couple here
coming in the door,
what do you think, first date?
Third. She's not sure
she wants to seal the deal.
Hmm.
And those two.
Where?
Brink of divorce.
Ooh, that's cold.
Okay.
Oh, that's easy.
It's us in 30 years.
And that was way too much.
I love that.
Wow, you're in super good
shape for an old guy.
Thank you, and you,
if I may say,
are hot as ever.
But in a dignified,
age-appropriate away.
It's all the yoga.
It keeps me young.
To be honest, Joe, I'm so happy
that you could come tonight.
It's been the worst day.
My thesis adviser,
he made a pass at me.
Oh, you're kidding.
The most embarrassing part is
I actually thought he
believed in me and my work.
This isn't your fault.
Yeah, but dumb shit
like this happens all the time.
I'm starting to think
I'm some kind of magnet
for, like, dudes
with serious issues.
So what are you gonna do
about your thesis adviser?
I don't know. Get through it.
I believe in you.
Hey, do you want to come to
a party with me tomorrow?
Already booking our next date.
It's at a friend,
Peach Salinger's.
Like J.D. Salinger?
I mean, yes.
Whoa! Wow.
But she doesn't like
to talk about it.
And she's a sweetheart.
Her family's just
a little, you know?
Yeah, whose isn't?
Mm. I like yours better.
Well, let's give thanks to
our lord Stephen King,
who bestoweth books
so that our bookstores
in third dimensional
locations may live.
It's cool how you
get in the monster's POV.
You understand
why he does stuff.
Almost like it's...
Justified?
Yeah, but then it's weird,
'cause he's bad but not all bad.
Quick Twitter break for Benj.
Maybe Dr. Frankenstein's
the bad one
for even making him, right?
Well, I think it's open
to your interpretation.
You ready?
Let's do it then.
Release the kraken!
Hey, come on in.
Hey, good morning.
Cookies, homemade,
not just for me.
Get a book.
Thank you so much.
Your receipt is in the book.
Whoa, we need another
box already.
Ethan, can you watch
the register for a second?
Kid ran down to
the basement to get it.
I'm an idiot. What? No.
Yeah, I saw him grab the key.
Paco!
What did I say?
I'm sorry.
I told you not
to come down here.
I just wanted to grab a book.
Don't be an idiot!
Why would you do that?
- I'm sorry.
- Why?
So what happened with you
and Professor Vaj Lips?
Let's just say I better
find a better job
or some kind of housing or--
I don't know.
Okay, enough of this shit.
Peach, no. I can't--
I can't accept it.
Stop.
It's just first, last,
and a deposit, okay.
Don't be so noble, okay.
Just take the check
and stop stressing.
Here.
Jesus Christ.
If you want to kill me, what
the hell are you waiting for?
Why would I want to kill him?
Who wants to kill people?
Three cups,
one is your brand, Home Soda.
It's the best, right?
So prove it.
Tell me which one it is.
If I get this right,
I get a fix?
If you get this right,
I'll let you out.
I need a palate cleanser.
Cup two.
Three.
One, two, or three?
I don't know.
Wait! None of them, okay!
They all taste like stale,
cheap drugstore soda.
They're not mine.
They're all yours.
That's bullshit!
Home Soda is, obviously.
Let me out of here!
You psychopath!
Fine!
You win! I lose!
We all lose.
What am I gonna do with
this lying sack of shit, Beck?
You want Beck, right?
Let's--let's be clear.
She does not want to be
with a guy like you.
I can help you.
No. Actually, she invited me
to a party tonight.
To Peach Salinger's.
A Salinger party, oh, Joe.
She--she's taking you
to add texture.
She wants to seem interesting,
like she hangs out
with real folk.
She's deep, she's an artist.
Truth?
Beck will always
leave someone like you
for someone who can
take her places.
We never made it
to a single party
'cause she couldn't
jump on me fast enough.
She's playing you for a chump,
my friend.
So yeah, it was really bad.
Basically, food poisoning
is the reason why
Peach and I are friends.
Puke does bond you.
She show you her ladle?
She's got this red
kitchen ladle.
It's a whole call-you-daddy,
spank me thing.
She's kinky as shit with me
because I'm loaded.
Not you 'cause--
'cause who are you?
So hopefully nothing
gastrointestinal happens,
but I do hope you guys
like each other.
You want to change that.
You need me.
Shit.
One look and I can tell you,
not my crowd.
What they are is everything
Benji claims you want to be.
Beckalish.
Hi.
Hey.
Mwah, mwah.
- Here you go.
- Thank you.
Is this Joseph?
Joe.
Am I just texture here, Beck?
Now, Joseph...
Just--just Joe.
I'm gonna have to borrow
our friend here.
So make yourself at home.
Everyone here is friendly.
Brown people don't bite.
Alumni.
Where'd you go?
I didn't.
Hmm.
Come on.
I blacked out.
Annika Atwater,
rich and #carefree,
building a brand as
a body positive influencer,
which seems to involve
wearing a lot of free stuff
on Instagram.
Lynn Lieser, publicist,
#cocktaillover.
Daughter of a surgeon
and tech CEO, adopted,
and has all the smugness,
none of the angst.
If you have a full set,
each one of them is worth
three times as much
for a collector.
You've read that one?
Just the first one.
Typical.
You think I need some
illiterate working in my shop?
No, hey.
If you want to work
in this shop,
you learn the value
of these books.
Mr. Mooney, please.
Everything you need is in there.
- Please!
- Joseph.
There you are.
It's Joe, just Joe.
This is a lovely
collection, Peaches.
It's Peach, and, I mean, you've
probably read more of these
books than I have.
A good salesman has to
know his product, right?
So you met Beck
at a book shop, right?
That's right.
Only in New York.
And then you just
happened to meet again.
Casual tone, detective eyes.
Well, it's lucky we did.
She was on the tracks
at the time.
So I heard.
Oh, God, thank goodness for you.
I mean, being in Greenpoint
of all places
at the very right moment.
Oh, it's time for the toast.
So in the time I was in there,
you attract Benji 2.0.
Peach looks thrilled.
Are you thrilled?
What do you want?
So which Beck are you?
The one I see
or the one Benji does?
Hey, stranger.
How are you holding up?
Having fun?
Beck.
Why did you bring me here?
I don't know.
I thought it could be fun?
I don't think I have
a lot in common
with your other friends.
I like that about you.
I always think I'm
gonna love these things,
yet somehow never do.
Then why did we come?
It's been this way since Brown.
Just feels like
I'm getting sucked in
and I could just be me,
yet that somehow never feels
quite good enough.
You know, I stole
this dress to fit in,
which is pathetic.
I don't know about that.
Yeah, not as pathetic
as the fact that Peach
wrote me a check
to keep me afloat,
which I don't want to cash
but now I have to.
Look, if you're not one of them,
it's just 'cause stuff didn't
just get handed to you.
It didn't.
Right, and when it's like that,
sometimes, to survive...
you have to show some teeth.
And I'm guessing that
yours are pretty sharp.
I'm glad we met,
glad we're friends.
For the love of Christ.
Joe? I know that voice.
Joe Goldberg?
Maddie Johnson.
I'm Candace's friend.
Great, a little soon
for you to hear this, Beck,
but here we go.
Wow, Maddie, that's crazy.
It's so good to see you.
This is Beck.
Hey.
So I heard about
you and Candace.
You know, I thought
we were pretty happy,
but she thought she could be
happier with some guy in Rome.
So you know, I get it.
She's following her bliss.
It's just how she left
so suddenly.
I mean, we were all
kind of hurt.
Would you excuse us?
My Uber is here.
It was nice to meet you.
Sorry. It was good
to see you, Maddie.
I just felt like that
needed to be over.
Let's get you home.
Be here for Paco.
What could he possibly
need from me?
He needs someone who isn't
drunk, Ron, how about that?
What the hell is wrong
with you, punching a wall?
Solve our problems.
I'm sorry.
It's okay.
It's not okay to yell.
Grown-ups do it all the time.
Grown-ups are assholes.
Some people used to
yell at me, too, you know.
And I don't want to
be like them.
I got you something.
I can't take this in the house.
Ron.
So all the bathrooms
in the building
have the same kind of ceiling.
So go in the bathroom.
The ceiling tiles around
the vent move if you push them.
So you push one...
pop the book in there,
slide it closed.
Like a secret hiding place.
Cool.
Thank you.
Mm-hmm.
Have a good night, Paco.
If you want it, it's here.
You are not responsible
for my feelings,
I am, but for the record,
I feel like congealed, day-old
egg rolls right about now.
What was the point of
taking me to that party?
Benji was right.
Benji!
Honestly, I get how he feels.
You left me here to die!
Enough of this, just kill me!
Hi.
I--
I just--I want to ask you
to please reconsider.
I need the T.A. job.
I need housing.
Can we maybe discuss placing
me with another adviser?
It's the middle of the term.
I know.
Inconvenient, but it's--
it's really important.
I wish you the best.
But I really can't,
in good conscience, do that.
I understand.
So I--
I guess I'm realizing
I have no choice...
but to share this.
And that is?
Well, it can fit in one tweet.
A list of six women who
have a story about you.
Not hard to find,
didn't take much asking around.
What's the term again,
harassment or misconduct?
Anyway, they were too scared
to come forward,
but then we realized it's
harder to dismiss seven women
with the same story.
That's not possible.
I've done nothing inappropriate.
You want to make yourself
a public liar?
That actually would
sink your career.
Blackmail is not something
you live down.
You're trying to call my bluff,
but I'm not bluffing.
So your call.
I've had a lot of time
to think in here.
You're right.
I am a fraud.
I've done things worse than you.
And that's how I know, Joe,
you're not a killer.
I want to tell you something.
And once I tell you,
I'll know your worst secret.
You'll know mine.
Then you can let me go.
Yeah! We thought
this group was strong.
A lot of interesting stuff
in Benji's nightstand.
But he was right.
The thumb drive is by far
the most interesting.
It started out your standard
issue frat hazing,
but a certain intensity
kicked in.
Then the coke or the homophobia.
Teach this bitch a lesson.
Teach him a lesson!
They all stood there,
laughing.
- And Benji...
- Whoo!
...was the worst
because he stood there
holding the camera.
Dumbass, wake up, dumb-ass!
Oh, shit!
Their parents made it go away,
but Benji kept
a copy of the video,
I assume, to hold over
friends' heads.
Instead, I get to hold it
over Benji's.
And he doesn't deserve it,
but he's right.
It is enough to buy his freedom.
Should I have changed
the subject on that balcony,
tried to kiss you sooner?
It's not fair how easy it is
to kill a spark.
It's a miracle
love ever happens.
If it's not a myth.
Hi.
Thanks to you, I showed
that professor some teeth.
And?
What's that?
A thank-you doughnut.
It worked.
Hmm.
That's good. I'm glad.
I mean, I was worried.
You were right
and I have housing
and can rip Peach's check up
and generally live
to fight another day.
And I wouldn't have
had the guts if you hadn't--
so really, thank you.
All I want to do is help, Beck.
I mean, you saw something in me
and, God, not everyone
gets why I'm here
and what being a writer means.
It's the most--I mean, it's
the only important thing.
And--and you helped me
to not lose it.
Aren't you gonna look, see if
I guessed the right flavor?
No bullshit, classic,
even old-school,
and secretly better than
all those crazy,
trying-too-hard ones.
It is nice to be seen.
It's a good guess.
It's good.
Come back here.
So plain glazed, yes.
Noted.
I have to go to class.
Have a good class, Beck.
Did you get it? The video?
Maple latte, almond milk,
two Stevia,
did I get that right?
Yeah, yeah, I saw the video.
Yes! Yes!
Yes!
Oh, mutually assured
destruction.
Let's talk about something
first, though.
What you said about Beck
basically being a gold digger...
I was just being honest,
that's--that's all.
What you are is wrong.
I'd go so far as to say
you create the problem
when you assume this stuff,
when you treat her like trash.
You cast her in a role
that isn't her and--
and you trap her in it.
Bro, I'm--I'm--
I'm done with her.
Say I can trust you.
I've got the video, right?
I mean, solid maybe.
The thing is that doesn't make
up for the damage you've done.
I'm sorry.
If it was between
me and you, Benji,
honestly, I would roll the dice.
I would.
Like you said, I'm not a killer.
But this...
is about her.
I'm telling... you--
I'm scared.
I'm very scared of what
you would do to her.
Maple almond latte.
Two Stevia,
two tablespoons of peanut oil.
Could have gone either way.
He's lied about so many things.
Who knew the peanut allergy
was real?
Guess Benji's gonna die
an honest man.