He's got a good pulse.
Maintain head stabilization
and flip him over.
On my count, guys. Ready? Go.
Sir, we're paramedics.
The mailman saw you
having a seizure.
We had to break down your door.
You know what your name is?
On my count,
one, two, three, up.
We're taking you
to the hospital.
I can't. No, I can't.
No, I can't...
Hey, buddy, buddy,
we're trying to help.
Sir.
Stay out of my house.
You just had a seizure, you could have
a stroke, a bleed in your brain.
Leave me alone.
35-year-old male, crushing headache,
and three seizures in the last two days.
So it's a bleed, a clot,
a tumor, metabolic or infection.
- Stick him in the CT and...
- Can't.
I'm assuming he has
a giant head.
Severe agoraphobe.
The world scares the hell out of him.
So we can only test him
with whatever we can take to him.
- Fun.
- The agoraphobia a symptom?
Only of being shot.
He and his girlfriend were mugged
seven years ago. It's when it started.
Anybody can hate humanity
after getting shot.
It takes a big man
to hate it beforehand.
How did you get this case,
if he didn't come to the ER?
I talked to him through his door
when he had flu last year.
I run the Community
Outreach Program now.
See?
Perfectly reasonable explanation.
She's definitely not here
trying to work her way back on the team
and steal your job or anything.
- It's a legitimate question.
- He agreed to meet with us.
But even if I can get
inside his house,
his brain is a black box.
We can pick this up
in a minute.
- What's this?
- Takeout menus.
But I'm hoping
you'll come up with a better answer
when everyone asks
what we're talking about.
- Last night...
- Forget it.
I know this is awkward,
but we need to talk.
There's a reason that we've evolved
the feeling of awkwardness.
It tells us
not to talk about things.
I was emotional
because of the adoption falling through,
and you actually
let your human side show for a moment.
That is why we kissed.
I just want to say thank you
for not taking advantage.
You're welcome. Any time you
want to stop kissing, I'm there for you.
Portable equipment can't distinguish a
bleed or a tumor, can't see vasculitis.
What did Cuddy want?
I kind of hit that last night,
so now she's all on my jock.
Wow. She looks pretty good
for someone on roofies.
The only equipment we have
is a sonogram and a portable x-ray.
What part of "olivine, pyroxene
and amphibole" don't you understand?
Pyroxene? "Pyro" means "fire."
They're indicator minerals.
You can't see diamonds,
so you look for the indicator minerals.
I assume the diamond
is the tumor or bleed or whatever it is.
Provoke a seizure.
The indicator
is the increased electrical activity
focused around the abnormality.
We do an EEG, see the focus,
see where the problem is,
which tells us what the problem is.
The Formster and the Camster,
kicking it old school.
Thank God she's not
trying to steal your job.
Go do it,
and search the home for toxins.
I agreed to talk,
not to let you in.
You could be very sick.
- We need access.
- I'm just not ready.
Why does he have
two locked doors?
He must use this room
as an airlock.
Deliveries in, garbage out,
he never has to go outside.
Just tell us when you are.
We're not going away.
Seriously?
You want her to admit
that all he has to do is ignore us
for a few minutes and we'll take off?
He was shot, girlfriend killed.
He probably has
post-traumatic stress disorder.
He doesn't believe in a just universe,
he doesn't trust anyone.
Give him some honesty.
I shouldn't have implied
we'd wait forever.
We've got a whole hospital full of
patients. We can give you a few minutes,
but eventually, if you don't let us in
we're going to have to leave.
Just one person comes in.
No, we've got to search
the whole house for toxins.
How about I examine you in one room,
and my colleagues will do the search?
I'm going to try
to provoke a seizure.
I need you to look
straight ahead, okay?
Yeah.
- Are you all right?
- Yeah, I just...
I haven't been in a room
with anyone for a while.
- Okay, can you just give me a second?
- Sure.
Okay-
You're the person I talked to
through the door last year, right?
- Yeah.
- You were nice.
And smart. Kind of made me
expect someone older.
I'm not that young.
- Must have been scary being shot.
- Don't do that. Okay.
You don't know me.
I've got everything
I want here.
I make a lot of money
writing tech manuals.
I get stuff delivered.
I work out.
I see anything I want over the Web.
I'm happy here.
- You don't seem very happy.
- Right now I'm not.
Go away.
- Did you speak to Cuddy last night?
- She's fine.
Why would it take anyone more than a
few hours to get over misplacing a baby?
You spoke to her?
Kind of hit that,
so she's all on my jock.
What?
Huh!
Everyone else thought
I was kidding.
You "hit"?
Like making out or full-on sex or...
I've got a chart laid out with all
the bases, I'll take you through it.
- What are you going to do?
- What can I do?
I'm gonna ignore her
for the rest of my life.
This mosquito bite
kept me awake...
Don't care about the bug bite.
She's your boss.
So now I have two reasons
to ignore her.
It was just a kiss.
- There's a reason...
- Yes, those large things in her bra.
You were hiding it from me.
Means it meant something to you.
Yeah, I fiendishly concealed it
within the phrase "I hit that."
Stop scratching,
you'll draw blood.
Finally,
you said something useful.
I'm just gonna break the skin
and let the poison out.
If you dated Cuddy,
there would...
Sorry, I get better reception
when you're not here.
What do you got?
His place is totally clean.
No animals. No hidden drugs or alcohol.
No lead in the paint.
And since
you're not breathing hard,
I assume you're not holding
Cameron aloft in triumph,
which means no seizures.
Hey, speaking of breathing hard...
Cameron, you engaged to Chase yet?
Sorry, we should have clarified.
We're calling about the patient,
not Dr. Cameron's love life.
We aren't engaged.
Moves things along much faster
if you just give him the answers.
Seizures can also
be induced through...
- After six years?
- A year-and-a-half.
Through sleep deprivation or...
Sleep deprivation
would take too long.
- You living together?
- We spend most nights together.
There's a bunch of drugs
that can lower a seizure threshold.
And cloud the diagnosis
with side effects.
- His place or yours?
- His, usually.
- Interesting.
- You would have said "interesting"
no matter what the answer.
And no matter what the answer,
it would have been interesting.
No engagement,
commitment issues.
His place, control issues.
Not sure whose, but, interesting.
Yeah, moves
much faster this way.
Where was the patient
when he had his first seizure?
In his entry hallway,
getting his mail.
And getting close
to the outdoors.
It spooked him, raised his BP.
Now use that fear.
Bring him outside.
He punched out a fireman.
We're doctors, not bouncers.
Okay.
So bring the outside to him.
Floor's genuine wood.
Why are they here?
They overheard me announce
the half-price bank foreclosure
in the ER waiting room.
Where is everybody?
Cameron's with the patient,
everybody else went home.
Because they don't need to be here.
Neither do you, and yet you are.
This way.
Moldings original?
Original?
They were here before the house.
The shut-in is also original.
- Come on, don't be shy.
- House, get them out of here.
Easy for you to say, you're not going
to be making some serious capital gains.
This is cruel.
And leaving him undiagnosed
is what, altruistic?
Procedure worked. He's seizing.
What do you see?
Normal theta, normal delta.
This isn't a seizure.
It's something.
Mr. Nozick, are you okay?
My stomach. It's killing me.
See? It's something.
Partial small bowel obstruction.
Blockage explains the pain. What
explains the blockage plus seizures?
Atrial fibrillation
throwing emboli.
Crohn's causing an abscess.
It could be a million things.
There's no way to know unless we get him
in for an MRI on his head,
or exploratory surgery
so we can biopsy his bowels,
- which he won't let us do.
- Wouldn't.
Pain changes things.
House.
He told you
to stay out of here.
He can chase me out
once he's done doubling up in agony.
Whatever your big problem is has caused
a complication we call "colon FOS."
"F-0", "full of," since we're
in mixed company, "S" is "stool."
Nothing is coming out,
so the pain's gonna get worse and worse.
So we need to stick
a pooper scooper in you.
We also need to take
a look at your bowel.
I made my wishes clear.
Uh-huh. And, see,
if the Crazy Fairy were here,
she could grant them.
I'm not insane.
I feel pain when I go outside,
so it's rational
to avoid that pain.
Except now you're
feeling pain inside.
Well, not as bad. Nowhere near.
We can give him drugs
for the blockage.
If it doesn't work
that blockage
will rupture your intestines
and spew sewage
throughout your body.
Whatever you're scared of out there,
aren't you more scared of death?
You, obviously,
can't stand people.
But for me, it's worse.
All right?
I'd rather die in here
than live out there.
If you don't mind floppy hair
and an annoying accent,
I know a surgeon who will
operate in your home.
Thank you.
With the risk of infection,
Chase won't actually...
He's not gonna do surgery
in some crazy dude's house.
- You just said...
- What I said was
that Chase would put him under
at the house.
We take him to the hospital,
open him up, do our thing,
then slip him back into his room
for the post-op,
without him ever finding out
that we tricked him.
So, that was implied.
- It's unethical.
- He'll be asleep.
He gets to make his own calls,
even if he's asleep.
Why are you siding with him?
Oh, yeah, you're that girl who likes
broken people because her husband died,
and since Chase
isn't all that broken...
Hey, why don't we operate
on his infarcted leg while we're at it?
Who cares if he said no?
I was risking my life
to avoid becoming a cripple,
he's doing it to avoid
sunlight and fresh air.
We've got to make it look good.
I know I'm a pain in the ass.
I know it would have been easy
just to walk away,
but you're a good person.
Count down from 10.
Ten, nine,
eight...
Let's go.
- How you doing?
- Better.
Great.
Everything else good?
Everything involving me
kissing House is good.
Oh, God, you dragged it out of me,
you're a genius.
It's no big deal.
I was feeling vulnerable,
he's a friend, and I leaned on him.
It's funny.
I've leaned on friends in the past.
Never leaned so far
my tongue fell into their mouths.
I don't think of House that way.
I never have.
Why not?
You know exactly
how it would go.
It would start off exciting,
we'd get caught up in the novelty
and the hostility and the forbiddenness,
and then we'd realize that
the flirty hostility is just hostility,
his inability to open up
is no longer exciting,
it's just frustrating,
and then it's the inevitable blow up
and the recriminations,
and we don't talk for two months.
Yeah. Well, it certainly proves you've
never thought about House that way.
I get your point.
I will be more careful with my tongue
in the future.
That's not my point.
Maybe novelty and hostility and
forbiddenness doesn't have to end bad.
Got to go.
What time you done?
Thought we could try
that new sushi place next to my house.
Why don't we stay
at my house tonight?
But we always stay at mine.
That's what I mean.
We used to split, what happened?
- I don't know, I'm closer to work.
- By five minutes.
And my house doesn't look like it
was decorated by a drunk rugby player.
Well, we can discuss it.
I hadn't really...
Why does it have to be a discussion?
Can't you just stay over?
You do know they page me when that much
surgical equipment is signed out.
He didn't consent.
He consented to the surgery.
You think he's going
to sue over where?
He won't even know where.
He'll wake up in his house,
he won't know a thing
about what happened.
Until he catches a post surgical
infection in his dirty apartment
and finds out we tricked him
and winds up owning the hospital.
Why aren't you
arguing with her?
Because she's right.
I don't care where he gets the post-op,
just that he gets it.
Keep him here.
House?
You Okay?
Yes, we don't need to talk.
Your hand.
That's weird. I usually
don't get the stigmata until Easter.
Please tell Dr. Chase
the patient's ready for him now.
Stewart, wake up.
It's Dr. Cameron.
If you can hear me, blink.
We were concerned for your safety,
so we brought you to the hospital.
No, it's okay.
- No, it's okay.
- Why'd you...
I just wanted
to keep you informed.
I didn't want you to have a bad shock
while you're recovering from surgery.
- I got to get out of here.
- It's okay, Stewart.
Calm down. Calm down. Stewart.
- Stewart, I'm going to sedate you.
- I got to get out of here.
I'm gonna sedate you.
No!
Calm down. I need some help in here.
Damn it, somebody get in here.
What did you do?
Well done. Your patient
called his lawyer, threatened to sue us,
is now heading home
completely undiagnosed.
He'll soon be on his way back.
He's sick. He'll crash,
he'll lose consciousness,
and I'll declare an emergency,
bring him back in.
Not any more you won't. His lawyer
now holds his health care proxy.
The next time
we have an emergency,
Larry Ruseckas, Esquire,
will be calling the shots.
I made the right call. If he
had flipped out after major surgery,
it would have been worse.
The benefit of being boss
is that I don't have to argue.
You're all off the case.
What's going on
between you and Cuddy?
Bad loving gone bad.
Seriously, why didn't you argue with
her? She just threw us off the case.
Because ignoring her
is a lot easier.
Convince the patient
to let us back in again.
See if you can clear
his blockage with lactulose.
If this thing kills him before we
can diagnose, it won't be fun anymore.
Okay-
You're going to
keep working on this?
Yeah. I brought in the case.
There is no case. He's gone, you've been
tossed. This is totally nuts.
He's incredibly sick.
We don't know...
Fine, forget about the patient.
What is going on with you?
This is why we left
House's team.
To avoid this constant flood
of pure craziness.
That's why I left House.
You got fired.
I'm sorry.
I know I let you down.
But you know
who else I let down?
Pretty much everyone
who's important to me.
My boss, my old boss,
my boyfriend.
I did that for you.
I'm not gonna
let you down again.
It's like
the red badge of idiocy.
If the Confederacy
had mosquitoes,
we'd all have Southern accents,
and I'd be paying Foreman less.
She kicked you off the case.
This is what happens
when you don't address it.
She acts weird,
things get different.
You understand that
different implies difference?
She's tossed me
a million times before.
No, she always chastises you,
and you'd always
come running to me to complain,
so you're acting different, too.
You're scared.
You are scared to get involved.
How is that scared?
It's rational.
Emotionally mature people
who work together should not date.
Guaranteed break-up,
guaranteed ugliness.
Any relationship that doesn't end
in a break-up, ends in death.
Everything falls
apart in the end.
That's your worldview.
The corollary,
which you keep forgetting,
is that you have to grab
any chance for happiness.
Why does this matter
so much to you?
Cuddy and I are fine.
The only person getting
worked up here is you.
I don't want you to be fine,
I want you to be happy.
I think if you dated her...
Are you familiar
with the adverb "vicariously"?
- If I wanted to ask her out...
- You did ask her out.
Last year.
Whatever happened there?
I don't know,
I wasn't interested.
Wrong.
You were interested,
but Amber grabbed your genitals first.
And now you're single,
and it makes you miserable,
but you think it's too soon
for another relationship,
so you're gonna
make me miserable.
Please.
Get a girlfriend or a life or something.
For me.
Better or worse?
Worse. Drugs aren't working.
I think we should do the surgery
in his house, like we planned.
Well, then one of us
wasn't paying attention
because I thought that surgery thing
was just a trick.
We prepared the room.
We hung the drapes.
It's probably 10 times as sterile
as any mobile operating theater
you'd find in a battlefield.
We still need Trapper John.
Chase doesn't want
anywhere near this surgery.
Maybe you could talk to him.
I can't understand
a word he says.
Taub, you doing anything later?
Blood in the field.
Not where I'm looking.
How am I supposed to know
where you're looking?
Here's a hint.
It's the bloody part.
The whole thing's bloody.
It's a guy with a hole in his body.
It's like you've never done this before.
Use the suction.
I will. And, in fact,
I've never done this before
because I went to med school,
not nurse school.
Hey, wanna see
if your client's actually made of money?
Cutting out
the last piece of bowel.
Suture.
Mucosa's pink. Flattened villi.
Intestinal atrophy.
It's Whipple's Disease.
Explains the seizure
and the stomach pain.
Little bleeder here. Cautery.
Hey, wait, the gas...
That always happens
during surgery.
It's the gas build-up in the blockage,
nothing to sue about.
Treat him for the burns, put him
on antibiotics for the Whipple's.
He'll be fine.
Hey. That's nice of you.
- Hi.
He doing good?
Burns are healing fine.
He's stable otherwise.
Good. So, I could stay
at your place tonight, if you like.
I can't.
Well, you're not gonna
sleep here again?
You might have noticed
the lack of nurses.
Because you're not on the case.
You can't really use that
as an excuse for...
Dr. Cameron.
Wait here.
- Your stomach?
- My legs are numb.
I can't feel them at all.
New symptom, peripheral neuropathy.
Got worse on antibiotics.
It's not Whipple's.
Porphyria.
Liver's fine.
Amyloidosis.
We'd have seen it
on the intestines.
What did we see
on the intestines?
Pink mucosa, flattened villi. If it's
not Whipple's, it's gotta be celiac.
Wheat allergy
means he's not absorbing nutrients.
Explains the seizures,
the stomach and now the nerves.
We should run
a blood test for celiac.
Not fast enough, not accurate enough.
Force feed him wheat.
Then do an endoscopy
as it hits his duodenum.
See if there's
an allergic reaction.
His guts just exploded. It might be
a tad painful to make him eat.
That's House's point.
There's nothing diagnostic about it.
He's trying to put the patient in pain,
force him to come in.
It is a valid test.
So is the blood test,
which is painless.
Foreman, listen to
that little voice in your head
that's coming from the telephone.
Force feed him.
Don't. You know House.
You know I'm right.
We'll do both tests.
I'm not here to
play matchmaker.
Okay-
House basically...
Well, he accused me
of being interested in you.
He's just trying
to change the subject.
I know. But I do have...
I've always had
some feelings for you.
Are you saying
you want to date me?
No, I...
It wouldn't be fair to House,
and it's too soon after Amber.
But you thought
you should just say it?
Yeah, I thought
you should know.
Let's have dinner
tomorrow night.
Okay-
Or maybe it'd be better
if we just had sex.
Pardon me?
In front of House's office.
I mean, I don't want to
take any chances.
I assume the point of this
is to make him jealous,
to make him realize that
he does want a relationship with me.
Yes.
You think it'll work?
You're an idiot.
Trust me, everybody will be happier
if House and I aren't dating.
You sure this is the best test?
No. But you've kind of
tied our hands.
As soon as this hits your intestines,
I'll look at it through an endoscope.
Stewart, I know you don't want
to talk about this,
but people who get shot
often get PTSD.
It's nothing to be ashamed of.
It's very treatable
with drugs and therapy.
It's not PTSD.
My girlfriend was with me
when I got shot, and she died.
I'm sorry.
But that's what I mean.
I lost someone myself.
I know it's traumatic.
No. What I'm trying
to say is that
I was like this before the shooting,
since I was a kid.
Everything was hard for me.
I didn't go out that much,
and when I did,
I had panic attacks,
like, physical pain.
You know, it was, like, worse,
it was like I was dying.
When I met Angela,
she was the only reason
that I ever wanted to go out.
But then she died, and...
Blood test will be done soon.
I'm guessing
that's a new technique.
Hey, do you remember
that idea that Cameron had
about trying to torture the patient
into admitting himself?
Pretty sure it was your idea.
You want me
to slow down the test?
Wow, everyone's got
all these great ideas today.
So you're thinking, "Patient won't leave
because leaving causes pain",
"so we gotta make
staying more painful."
That actually makes sense.
You'll increase his pain,
but not enough to make a difference.
He's on morphine.
He's on morphine now,
pretty soon,
he'll be on lessphine.
'Cause when you restock, you'll actually
be giving Cameron IV bags of saline.
And why do you think
I'll be doing this?
Same reason
you did the surgery.
That was because
it was an emergency.
No, it was because
your marriage is falling apart.
When you confess adultery,
things tend to go bad.
When one part of your life
does a Titanic,
you make a life raft
out of whatever's left,
which makes your job more significant,
which is why you did the surgery,
why you pulled an all-nighter,
and why you'll do this.
She's having me
sleep on the couch,
just for a few nights.
I'm not doing this to save my job.
I'm doing this to save his life.
Right.
That's what we'll tell everyone.
Oh...
Have you considered
that it's not my place
you really wanna be walking into
right now?
Ric Ocasek will kill me if I...
Oh, you mean Cuddy.
Yeah, she's a little nuts,
but she's beautiful, smart, funny.
And most important,
she can stand you.
Yeah. I came here
to have you lecture me on Cuddy,
not because there's a killer mosquito
chasing me around my apartment.
House, there is no mosquito.
This is all about Cuddy.
She's "bugging" me. Poetic.
Have you seen this bug?
Have you seen this bite?
No, what I've seen
is a suppurating wound
that you've scratched and mutilated
into a gangrenous state.
Delusional parasitosis.
I am not imagining things.
House, you're a drug addict,
you're always imagining things.
You got bitten
the night you kissed her.
Your itching always gets worse
when you think about her.
You need to address this.
She's my boss.
No, you're not afraid of authority,
you're afraid
she actually is right for you.
You're afraid to take a chance
because ifs too big a chance.
If it doesn't work with her,
then maybe there's no one out there.
I am not rationalizing.
I'm better off alone.
Also, have you seen
her ass recently?
You're not staying here.
Oh, come on.
No. You can go home, or...
You're going to Cuddy's,
you're gonna ring her doorbell,
and you're gonna ask her out on a date,
like regular people do.
At 3:00 in the morning?
When do regular people sleep?
Bye-bye.
Is he in enough pain
to come in yet?
No.
Antibody tests back?
Inconclusive.
- Then why are you here?
- I missed you.
- Endoscopy?
- Inconclusive.
Well, then do it again.
I know it sucks,
but I need to test your stomach again.
It's really hurting.
I know, I'm sorry.
I'm gonna try to get you on your back
and have you open your mouth.
He's out.
- Anything?
- No pulse.
Start CPR.
Get the paddles.
Who are you calling?
Pizza. You like anchovies?
I'm calling the lawyer.
Genuine emergency, he'll okay admission.
He's dying-
Exactly.
Hi, sorry to wake you.
Your introvert is having a heart attack.
House, if we don't restart his heart...
He can survive 15 minutes
on oxygen and CPR.
We can get him to the hospital in five.
Lawyer says yes. Continue CPR.
2123, Holden Green,
patient with PEA.
- Clear.
- Wait.
I got a pulse.
Cancel the ambulance.
He's stable enough to stay here.
His heart's back
to sinus rhythm, but it's bradycardic.
Taub's putting in
a temporary pacemaker.
It'll keep
his heart beating for now.
Hey, Cameron, how would you like
your old job back?
I'm asking 'cause it's the only way
I can fire you.
Sorry, in ER we like
to actually resuscitate dying people,
- not just let them flop around.
- Could be lymphoma.
No, we'd have seen it on the abdomen.
It has to be a poison.
Organophosphates.
We checked the place over and over.
It's completely clean.
There were rose petals
in the front entry.
Unless he's eating
a bouquet a day,
- he couldn't...
- How clean?
Very, he probably
has a little OCD.
How often do you wash your tub?
Every couple of days.
- Bleach and ammonia?
- Yeah.
You know how kids
play toy soldiers in the bath?
He likes to re-enact the Battle of Ypres
three times a week with real gas.
Ammonia and bleach
makes chlorine gas.
Highly fat soluble.
He lost weight after the stomach pain,
explains why his symptoms
kept getting worse.
Put him on parenteral steroids
and sodium bicarbonate.
Even if you're right, that external
pacemaker's gonna fail eventually,
and I don't have the skills
to put in a permanent one.
Well, maybe the poison
hasn't completely shot his heart,
and you won't have to feel guilty
for the rest of your life.
How am I going to place the leads
in the exact spot on the right ventricle
without fluoroscopy? The Force?
Taub put in a temporary one.
You can do that playing
Pin the Tail on the Donkey.
Permanent pacemakers
need precision.
So we can use
the portable x-ray.
- It's not real time.
- Sonogram.
And what happens
when I put him into V-tach
because the sonogram
isn't precise enough?
He's dying-
Exactly why I don't want to be
the one to kill him.
Thanks.
You knew I'd have to say no,
but you came anyway.
You just wanted a reason
to be angry at me.
If there's something wrong between us,
then let's...
Forget it.
You know why we spend nights
at my house?
Because when we
spent them at yours,
I could tell you
didn't want me there.
Why would I keep inviting you over
if I didn't want you there?
You always kicked me
out every morning.
You never offered me a drawer, you
never cleared out your closet for me.
I was just a visitor.
How long have you
felt like this?
From the start.
I know it's hard for you
because you lost your husband,
but I can't keep
chasing you forever.
I just tried your house,
where are you?
Clubbing. Good or bad?
Bad. Vitals are dropping,
the abdominal pain keeps getting worse.
Means we were too late
with the treatment.
Tell the lawyer he's off the clock,
we're done.
You're giving up?
Call Taub.
Tell him to pick up some morphine.
No need for the patient to be in pain.
- He's on morphine.
- No, he's on saline.
I figured you'd put him on saline,
so I switched him back to morphine.
I love you.
When you reach puberty, give me a...
His abdominal pain,
that was on morphine?
Yes.
Is there something
that causes abdominal pain
that doesn't respond to morphine?
I was right.
He is being poisoned.
What's this density on his hip?
- Just bone.
- Think less boney.
You think
he's got lead poisoning?
Explains the constipation,
the nerves, seizures. Hold him down.
You're not gonna feel a thing,
except excruciating pain.
Your mugger used hollow points,
which exploded and left fragments.
Your doctors missed a couple
hiding behind your hipbone.
It's no biggie, except years later,
they started to dissolve,
and then, biggie,
you started to dissolve.
I'll start him on chelation.
The agoraphobia, could it...
Nope. The lead wouldn't have started
to disintegrate till years after.
But it could have
exacerbated the fear.
I don't need to change.
I know you think that but your life
could be better, you'd have choices.
- He's lying.
- About what?
About everything.
About his life.
He doesn't even think he's happy here.
He's miserable.
- I've got everything I need.
- Yeah?
Well, then why did Taub find
rose petals in your entry hallway?
Struck me as a little weird,
thought it might be medically relevant.
But it actually just told me
that you were pathetic.
The day you crashed in your entryway
was your girlfriend's birthday.
You weren't there for the mail, you were
trying to go lay flowers on her grave.
Yeah, he's got PTSD,
yeah, he's agoraphobic.
But he's also a coward.
If you want to change your life,
do something.
Don't believe
your own rationalizations.
Don't just lock yourself up
and pretend you're happy.
- Hi.
You were right.
About my husband.
It affected me.
It still affects me.
If you're saying
you'll never be able to...
I cleaned out a drawer for you.
Like, a big one.