What can I do you for? Ds Harris.
You heard anything about
an art theft in Sussex?
Tyres screech
we've gotta get rid of that painting.
Can't sell it now, can we?
Just Chuck it in the river.
I can't fight Kelly's adoption
with the police sniffing around.
What do you suggest,
Joan? We go straight.
Do you know him well
enough? I do, yeah.
We can say anything to one
another. There's no secrets.
Can you think of any unusual suspects?
The Irish. They've always
got money to spend.
I've found a buyer for the stubbs.
We agreed that you'd
Chuck it in the river.
A work of art is not going in the river.
That's the woman involved.
That robbery in Sussex.
All you've gotta do is work
for me. I'm not a grass, Tom.
You've organised a sale with
the ira, and you didn't tell me?
Jessica Cunningham
to see Hugo saxton.
When Jessica confirms she's
happy with what she sees,
I'll call Michael, he'll give you the cash.
We had a deal.
Leave, while you still can. I really do...
Police! Get down! Urgh, argh!
Have you been following
me the whole time?
I'm sorry. I tried to offer you a way out.
Pigs. You're all the same.
Shouting I'm truly sorry,
but I think it's better if
you don't speak to Kelly
while you're in your current environment.
There's nothing left.
Everything I've worked for...
The Irish have destroyed it all.
You know, how'd they
even find the warehouse?
You tell me.
You're gonna need to warn Joan.
When's that ever stopped the ira?
Don't let her do a deal, boisie.
Shit.
When? Two nights ago.
Bloody hell. Everything?
Everything. Art, books.
My stones?
It's all ash.
Fucking hell.
I've got less than what I started
with. I've got nothing. Snap.
So, what you gonna do?
I'll start again. I've done it before.
But... you need to watch your back
in case they try and send
you a message as well.
What? In here?
Just lay low, hide. How?
There's nowhere to fucking go!
It's just a couple of days,
until your bail hearing.
So, what is it? A punishment
for bringing the pigs to their door?
Or a warning. You
know, not to make a deal.
What? With the law? Been done before.
But it would open a whole can
of worms for me and albie as well.
You're not worried that
I'd do that? Course not.
Buzzer
I need to see my brief,
all right? Joan... get him in.
I left photos for you.
Do you know her?
No. She seems to know you.
Ira.
So, your bail hearing's on Monday.
All being well, you'll be
released until your trial.
And then?
I'll contact you when
we get a date for court,
should be in about four to six months.
The most important thing you
can do between now and then
is to stay out of trouble.
But you think I'll get off, yeah?
I mean, my husband
said that it'll probably be
I'll try my best, mrs
hannington, that's all I can do.
What if your best isn't good enough?
You're looking at a long stretch.
Worst-case scenario.
Ten years.
You wouldn't necessarily serve it all,
but you do have multiple
juvenile convictions.
And I see you stole a car... In... April.
They have strong evidence - a witness
that links you to the armed robbery
where the painting was stolen,
so it's not simply the
fraud at the London hotel,
it goes much further
than... No, no, no, no, no.
I can't do ten years. I can't.
You'll adapt. People do.
I'll lose everything. Everything
that I've ever fought for.
My daughter. She's only six.
Then might I make a suggestion?
Make a deal?
If you help them to land a bigger
fish, one of your associates...
No. No. Not a chance, no. Then
you'd get to see your daughter grow up.
Shouting outside.
Chatter.
I'm Joan.
We've mutual friends.
Tell 'em I had no idea
the law was following me.
I don't know what you're talking about.
What I'm saying is I'm
not your enemy. Ok?
I don't want any trouble.
How about you crack on and
let me get on with my dinner?
Sit down.
Trying to rip off the ra?
You'd better be tougher than you look.
If you touch me, I'll get you
put in seg so fucking fast.
What?
I just had a right moment
with that girl from the ira.
Yeah.
Door locks, clattering.
Can I get you something? Water?
She winces, sighs shit.
That looks bad. Yeah.
At least she didn't smash up my face.
I know a lass can get you codeine.
No, I don't want anything from anyone.
Joan sighs
I need a clear head for my
bail hearing in the morning.
Hope you get out.
Not safe for you in here.
See you at the trial. Be good.
All right?
What happened?
Did something happen?
You'll feel better after a bath.
Wash the smell of prison off you.
It's ok. You're home now. Ok?
Yeah. I can look after you. When
have you ever looked after me?
We go to Spain, I carry the gear
through customs. That's not fair.
You agree to go straight,
you send me to the ira.
I didn't force you. I was
in the room with them.
And I was right next door. She sighs
you're always next door.
We'll work something out. We always do.
What?
Boisie, what?
Well, I don't know yet.
If I make a deal, the ira kill me.
If I don't, I'll get ten years.
I have to get away. Away, away?
Yeah, we have to run.
Start a new life abroad.
Look, I get where you're
coming from... all right.
Right, but it's not that simple.
You're facing a serious charge.
Thanks, I forgot
and I've got everything here.
You've lost all your stock.
Still, I can't... What?
Pack up your fucking shop?
How do we even pay for it?
I'll do a job.
Nicking a ring ain't gonna be
enough for a whole new life.
Then I'll do a bigger job.
Like what? I don't know yet.
No, I really think we need to
take our chances with the courts.
"We"? How many times?
There is no fucking "we".
It's me facing the stretch.
Me the ira came after.
They came after me an' all!
Destroyed everything I had.
You're telling me we got the same?
Joan.
I'm sorry.
If I did come up with a job.
Would you at least think about it?
He sighs
he sighs you can spend
a lifetime on your own
and tell yourself you're happy, but
I'll do whatever you need, Joan.
This is all very mysterious.
I can't go to jail. I
wanna relocate to Spain.
No extradition treaty yet, so
the cops won't come. Exactly.
Can you set us up? Well,
is that you or you and Boise?
Does it make a difference?
Anything's possible.
But it won't be cheap.
You got the Irish in. You owe me.
Look, I... I can't just magic
up cash for a new life.
Right? There's papers, tickets, a motor,
and that's before you get to the villa.
You need capital to live off.
Spain's all corrupt as hell.
It's all backhanders. I can get money.
You know Boise lost
everything in the fire?
I'm gonna do another job. What, on bail?
She scoffs I've got nothing left to lose.
Gonna need to Nick a bloody big rock.
Yeah.
You better get thinking,
then. Come up with a plan.
I'll be on it my end.
Door opens, Joan clears throat
door closes, footsteps approach.
Joan?
Mr Jones.
Now, now. You know it's Bernard.
How lovely to see you.
How's your father?
I am so sorry, lovey.
Hi.
My usual, please, but, er, I'll eat in.
Yeah, ok.
Egg and cress on brown,
no salt, lightly peppered.
You remember. I'm
touched. Joan chuckles
well, you were always so good to me.
Took a chance on me
when no-one else would.
What are you doing back here?
Just moved to the area.
I suppose I do get a bit lonely,
but... I haven't really felt up
to trying for a new position.
No. Working for a boss
I don't know, a stranger.
I, er... She laughs
I must admit, I was
trying to bump into you.
Hoping that you'd be good
on your word and take me back.
Joan, I'm sorry, but I
replaced you straight away.
Kirsty. Fine young lass.
God.
Sorry, how silly of me. Sorry.
But.
Round about the time you left,
we had a bit of an issue
with another member of staff
miss foley.
Issue?
Remember you told me she
had, er, money problems?
Dimly, yeah, yeah.
Well, she only went and
stole five stones from the safe.
I know. Can't prove it's her,
but I had to give her the boot.
Did you get the police in?
Didn't want anyone digging in the books.
Here you are.
Can I buy you lunch?
No, thanks, I'm not hungry.
No, you don't wanna
ruin that lovely figure.
So, in fact, we are a little short-staffed.
And, er... He chuckles ..i miss that smile.
What is it?
Bernard's, where I used to work.
What do you mean?
I mean go for quantity, not quality.
I mean clear the place out.
All the stones from the safe,
every gold and platinum wedding
band, necklaces, bracelets,
earrings for mum, cuff links for dad,
christening mugs, Valentine's gifts.
I mean every single piece
of that fucked-up, fucking
"premier collection".
Now, that would buy us a new life.
You're bloody brilliant, Joan.
So, you think we can pull it off?
I think you can do.
Anything.
I was thinking we should
bring albie into the job
as well as sorting the flit.
We're gonna need a driver, right?
And he's done jobs to
this kind of scale before.
This is gonna take some planning.
But this job, I mean,
it's just for us, yeah?
Joan, we're moving to Spain
together and never coming back.
Does it get more "us" than that? Ok.
Can we get a villa with a pool? Yeah.
And a view of the sea?
And a view of the sea.
She gasps and a terrace?
And a terrace. And a lemon
tree in a little, fucking pot?
Lemon tree in a little, fucking...
You know what I've always wanted?
Diamond tiara?
She laughs what?
It's a pet. Yeah.
She giggles a baby tiger. For god's sake.
I mean, we can give it
back when it gets big.
Joan hannington, I'm sorry, I
draw the line at a baby tiger.
All right, just a cat,
then. You don't like cats.
Yeah, but Kelly will love it.
What? Kelly.
We've never stayed
anywhere you can have pets.
But Kelly's not coming.
Of course she is.
That's the whole bloody point.
You never said...
You... you just assumed that...
That you knew me? Yeah.
That you'd know that
she was the reason.
That I'd never leave her behind.
Joan. Jesus Christ. What?
It makes no difference.
Are you serious? We
can't take a kid on the run.
We have to. I have to. You know I do.
No, no, no. It's far too
risky. It's not fair on her.
I'm doing it for her. For you.
For both of us. We have to be together.
Boisie, please, it has
to work. No. I'm sorry.
If Kelly comes, you're on your own.
What's fucking new? Joan, wait.
I'm not going without her.
I had an idea.
We go on our own, and
I'll come back for her.
When?
Once we're settled in a safe area.
Nice villa, swimming
pool and a lemon tree
and a school nearby.
Like a proper family home.
You'd come back for Kelly?
Risk that for me?
Yeah, once we're sorted.
Well, how long's that gonna be?
Couple of months. Year, Max.
It'll probably be less.
Look, you'll be together in
the end. Isn't that what matters?
It's the only way.
Surely you can see that?
Well?
Ok.
Sure?
With you in a tick.
He groans
welcome, Joan.
Welcome back. Glad to be back.
And you're sure you're
ready? Yes. Raring to go.
I just hope I haven't forgotten anything.
All the days of the deliveries,
all the locks and whatnot.
It's been a bit of a tough time. Of course.
And I've had to up the
security since the Linda issue.
More cameras?
And a panic button...
Straight through to the police.
When were you thinking? During
the stock-take next Thursday.
He likes to close for half a day now,
so one o'clock.
You wanna plan a heist
during broad daylight?
Are you bloody crazy?
Well, you can't see inside
the shop from the street.
The doors'll be bolted.
As long as we're quiet,
proper quiet, no-one'll know.
What about security?
There's cameras everywhere, so
you will need to wear balaclavas.
And false plates for a Van.
There is a panic button
that goes straight to the pigs.
It's connected under a cabinet.
So, I'll cut the wires, and
then once we've closed up,
I'll lead Bernard into the safe room.
Well, how? Believe
me, I can arrange that.
You ok with that, mate?
It's me that needs to be ok with it.
And I am.
You know the first people
the police are gonna suspect
are gonna be employees,
Joan, husbands of employees.
We'll be on our way to Heathrow
before the police even arrive.
As soon as they do, they'll
fax an alert to all the airports.
You'll never leave the country.
And you're on bail, so you're
looking at 15 years, not ten.
Ok, then we'll get a ferry.
Can't we find a quiet
port, slip through the net?
I've got a mate who works
at newhaven. It'll cost, though.
I'll look into it.
Right, it's agreed. We'll leave by boat.
Back to Bernard's. Access
through the alley here.
There's three windows, one in
the toilet, two in the back room.
Or the window on the
back door. We'll recce.
You'll need to play the innocent victim.
Yeah, act brave,
like you don't wanna give me
the safe code straight away.
Of course.
After we've cleared the safe,
we'll start on the shop front.
Where's Bernard?
He has to stay in the back
while Joan and I strip the place.
We'll need another man to watch him.
Why can't you do it? I'm driving.
You must know someone.
Well, what about Paul mills? Who's he?
Best there is. Total pro.
You think he'll be interested?
Well, maybe. Ask him. Door unlocks
door shuts, albie clears throat
hi! Guess who won
slimmer of the week?
Hello.
Hi. All right, hiya, val.
I thought you were going
for a drink after slimmers' club.
Er, yeah, I decided it
wasn't worth the calories.
Jonny all right? Yeah,
watching TV in his room.
Maybe check on him? Why?
What are you lot plotting?
Talking shop.
Poor you.
It's all right. I enjoy it.
Come and say hi to jonny.
Joan?
We won't make any
decisions without you.
Bloody better not.
I'll call him. See what he says.
Paul? I'm Joan. Sorry I'm late.
Been shopping? Get
anything nice? Mind your own.
Ooh, calm down, love.
I've never worked with a bird before.
Yeah?
I've never worked with an
ugly bastard like you before.
Joan.
You two married, yeah?
And that's cool with
you? Yeah. Joan's sound.
And it's my job.
Right, what do you think?
Have they filled you in?
I've done eight post
offices and ten banks,
and it's always been sweet.
Nice one. But I was in and out.
This is slow.
Stripping cabinets, opening
cases with tiny, little keys.
Makes it risky. Given
we're in the high street,
middle of the afternoon...
We're gonna recce tomorrow, time it out.
And I know the gaff back to front.
I'll be directing the job once we're in.
Yeah. Can you handle that?
What weapon you taking, love?
I'm the victim, aren't I?
I'm not carrying anything.
Colt 1911.
Fit it with a silencer. Why?
Are we doing this properly?
Yeah. Then we need to be prepared.
The boss, Bernard, he's
like putty in my hands.
We are not going with loaded guns. No.
I'll need a sawn-off, double barrel led.
Scare the shit out of him.
You don't seem sure about this.
I've never been more
sure of anything in my life.
Are you in?
I'll let you know.
She sighs that went well.
He's got to trust us. All of us.
Music box plays
you shouldn't have been late.
You spooked him.
The social said I can
visit Kelly on her birthday.
I had to get her something.
I'm glad you can see her before we go.
Do you trust me, boisie?
I'm giving up my whole life for you, Joan.
Seven years ago, Nance.
Feels like yesterday.
Yeah, in that cab off to hospital.
You screaming blue murder.
Should have gone hours before.
Yeah, you wanted to wait for Gary.
Yeah, what a mug. Nancy chuckles
you had bad taste in men.
Yeah, with dad as a fucking role model.
What? He's really poorly, Joan.
Good.
Don't you think you should visit,
Bury the hatchet before he...?
I'm sure he'd love to see you.
God. The social worker's here.
Yeah, course she is. That's all right.
Can you hold this? Yeah, course.
Mummy!
Happy birthday, kel!
You look... seven.
I am seven! Seven today! Joan laughs
I know you are. Say
hello to auntie Nancy.
Hello, auntie Nancy. Do
you like my school uniform?
I do. Happy birthday, Kelly!
Here, this is for you.
I thought we'd do presents after tea.
Aw. Aw.
Can I sit on your lap for tea, mummy?
Course you can. Yay!
Give me a minute,
ok? Sit there. Good girl.
So, I want to know all
about your new school.
Did they sing you happy
birthday today? Yeah.
Joan exhales heavily
that's so brilliant. Have
you got lots of new friends?
Yeah. Everyone in my
class wants to be my friend.
You're so popular!
I'll check access at the back.
You keep him busy round the front.
Thank you very much. Goodbye.
Thank you, sir.
Can I help you, sir?
After a ring for my wife.
Go ahead. Take your time.
Can I help you, sir? He's
after a ring for his wife.
Absolutely.
You go get your lunch, sweetheart.
How long have you been married, sir?
A few months. How
about an eternity ring?
An expression of everlasting love.
Absolutely. Can I see
that one at the back?
Course.
There we are. Nine-carat
diamond in platinum.
Boisie exhales
or there is the option of the half eternity,
meaning the diamonds only
cover the front of the ring.
I wouldn't wanna do it by halves.
Quite right, sir.
I'll take it.
Just not right now.
I'll be back.
Here we go. Presents! I want presents!
Course you do. Here you go. Open it up.
I'll take the paper. There we go.
Here. That's it.
Music box plays
you can put all your treasures inside.
Did you have one when you were seven?
No, but I always wanted
one. I used to ask every year.
That's from me.
Wow! Pens, glue, stickers!
It's a making box! She
loves making things.
Do you like it, mummy?
Mummy? I love it.
She's very creative.
Yeah, she's always beavering away
on a project. She's got real talent.
Yeah, excellent. All right.
He places phone in receiver
that was albie. Paul's just called. He's in.
He groans
are you still thinking about Kelly?
Yeah. And my dad.
You think we should go and see him?
Maybe.
I mean.
What if he wants to say sorry?
He hates slap.
I thought you didn't
care what he thought.
I don't.
She exhales.
I won't be long.
Thought I'd better come.
He wheezes.
Nancy told me that
you're not doing too good.
She told me that you're
in trouble with the law.
You never did know
how to obey the rules.
It's complicated. It's not my fault.
And how many times did we hear that?
It's true. Ask Nancy.
Just grow up, Joan.
Stop fighting.
Make life easier on yourself.
God, you know nothing
about my life now.
I know you've put Kelly in care.
You lost her.
No. No, I haven't.
It's all right. She'll
thank you for it one day.
Joan huffs and you know it.
I have tried to be nice, but I can't...
Here we go. Poor little Joan.
No. You did this to me,
dad. You made me like this.
Always blaming someone else.
You think you can raise a kid
by beating the shit out of them?
Belting them across
the... back till they bleed?
You know, I will get my daughter back,
because I love her.
Something that you'll never understand.
Thanks for coming.
What's the emergency?
I need you to add Kelly to my
passport so I can take her with us.
And boisie's ok with that?
He tuts I mean, you
hold stuff back from val.
Yeah, no, to protect her. That's different.
No, you have to tell him.
Yeah. I will, I will. I just
I need to find the right time.
I know how deep your debts run.
There'll be ten grand more
after the job, once we've sold on.
Promise me you'll tell him.
Before the job. Promise.
How you gonna get her?
Got an idea, I just need to research it.
Children chatter.
Phone rings 'hello, king's morten.'
'hello, it's Simone highsmith
'from the New York herald.
'I'm over here writing an article
about British children at play,
'and I'd love to visit the school.'
Subtitles by accessibility@itv.Com