DT John Luther,
DS Justin Ripley.
I've lobbied to be
stationed with you.
I put in a request nine months ago.
Chased it up
three times a week in writing.
My mate, Justin. I love him.
I don't think you're gonna shoot me.
Don't you... Don't you...
Hey! Get up!
John, I don't know what to say.
Wotcher.
- I wanted something.
- What?
You.
I assumed you'd need it eventually.
So.
Now what?
So, now what?
Your phone's off. You're wanted.
That's why my phone's off.
Fair enough.
Nice view.
Yeah.
So never do this.
Never come up to a really high place
and wonder what it'd be like to fall.
Why would I do that?
Got enough to worry about.
Why do you do it? Come up here?
You ever have that dream
when you're falling?
Yeah.
Did you ever wake up in it?
No.
You?
Nah.
What do you think would happen?
Don't know.
No. Me neither.
Oh!
Hello, love.
One of us left the bathroom window
open this morning.
And a bloody pigeon got in.
Scared the crap out of me.
Flapping about.
Who are you?
♪ Love is like a sin, my love
♪ For the ones
that feel it the most
♪ Look at her
with her eyes like a flame
♪ She will love you like a fly
♪ Will never love you again ♪
Guv...
How goes it?
Fair to middling.
John Luther, this is, uh, DS Lane.
- Emma.
- Wotcher.
Guyv.
- Fancy a cuppa?
- Always.
Crikey. Pretty close to the edge.
Closer and closer every day.
That's why the place comes cheap.
How are you filling your days?
Days seem to fill themselves, really.
So...
So, Alice Morgan...
Yeah. They gave you that, did they?
Yeah. What can you do?
What can you do?
Has she been in contact at all?
Alice?
- Since when?
- Well, since you last saw her.
On Southwark bridge. Was it?
No.
No emails, no phone calls?
She didn't say where she was going?
- Nope.
- And you didn't ask?
Has something happened?
- Interpol caught her scent in Berlin.
- Okay.
- Well, pick her up.
- No.
No, trail went cold in Madrid.
And then this happened, in Antwerp,
three days ago.
- Blimey.
- Hmm.
The dead man at the wheel here,
Akram El Majadi,
small time hoodlum
from the 18th Arrondissement, Paris.
Did he have her back?
Who can say?
What was she doing?
Well, we were hoping you might
shine a light on that.
No.
I can't be of any help.
Hmm. Okay.
I don't suppose we thought you could...
Not really.
So, what are we all doing here?
Well, I'm afraid she's dead, John.
No she's not.
We found her in the Schelde.
I mean, yeah, it does look like her,
but it's not her.
The autopsy confirms it.
- Dental records.
- They could be faked.
Prints too.
I'm sorry, John. It's her.
Just give me a sec.
- How?
- Um...
She drowned.
Alice?
Toxicology is clean.
No signs of trauma. Water on the lungs.
The theory seems to be
that she was concussed
after the car crash, possibly confused.
You're saying she fell.
John, you understand that we need to
have a look around the place.
Yeah. I mean, yeah.
Okay, DS Lane, if you'd like to
keep John company.
Yes.
May I?
- Can I get you that cup of tea?
- Yeah.
Yeah? Tea.
Okay.
Boss.
I need you back in London.
Uh, how so?
Mmm-hmm.
Understood. Okay.
Okay.
So, now what?
You're gonna arrest me?
Why, you've done something wrong?
- You know I haven't.
- Then, why arrest you?
You have to leave the tea though,
I'm afraid. Duty calls.
Vivid misdeeds in Hackney Wick.
Give me a sec.
You and Alice Morgan...
I'm aware that, um,
there was a fondness between you.
- Yeah, there was.
- Hmm.
A fondness. Yeah.
So, maybe you shouldn't be
alone right now.
Hmm? Is there someone I can call?
No.
No, no, I'll, um...
Be fine. And give them all my love.
Hey...
You're okay? Really?
Yeah.
Everything's tickety-boo. Totally disco.
Thank you, Guv.
- You've been with Luther?
- We have. Yes.
And did he know? About Alice Morgan.
Well, it's difficult to be certain.
And that's what we'll tell
the Lokale Politie Antwerpen, is it?
- "It's difficult to be certain."
- He didn't know, boss.
He was, um, crushed.
The victim is Chloe Morley.
Looks like her husband's the killer.
Alistair Morley.
Dentist. Picture's in the file.
Hmm.
- SOCO's left?
- Yep.
And her husband did this?
Apparently so.
God help us.
What did he do with the heart?
He ate it.
Forensics found what was left of it.
- Guv?
- One sec.
Emma, Guv?
These CCTV images...
He's letting himself out
of Alistair Morley's work place,
driving Alistair Morley's car,
texting on Alistair Morley's phone...
He's killing Alistair Morley's wife
and eating her heart. But...
Whoever this is,
it's not Alistair Morley.
Alistair Morley.
Guyv.
Belongs to a Julian Lewis.
Is he our man? On the CCTV?
Definitely not.
DS Silver.
Wotcher.
Wotcher, boss.
Benny, what's going on
with this Alice Morgan thing?
Hang on a minute.
I'll give you the bones of it.
Morning, sir.
Okay, so, truth is,
we don't know much.
The Belgians are looking after it
and you know what they're like
with sharing stuff.
Do they like anyone for it?
Honestly, I don't know.
I don't know if they're even looking
for anybody because,
as far as I'm aware
they're treating it as an accident.
Yeah, but it wasn't an accident.
Did Theo Bloom take something
from my house today?
- Something like what?
- Like a phone.
A burner.
Well, if he did he would've logged it
for chain of evidence.
Yeah, ‘cause he's squeaky clean,
isn't he?
Eh? Benny?
No cleaner man. No cleaner man.
Not since that chap in the manger.
So, he wouldn't take a phone, would he?
Look, why would he?
He had a warrant didn't he?
And if he didn't, who did?
Boss, what's going on?
Nothing, Benny. Nothing.
I'll let you crack on.
:::::: www.hiqve.com ::::::
Julian Lewis? Police. Open up.
- Armed police!
- Down! Searching! Clear!
- Bathroom clear!
Medic says he ate the tongue.
Boss, what do we do
with something like this?
We keep going.
Trace it back,
to a point of origin.
First cause,
and there we will find our man.
Belongs to a Bruno Dressler.
How are you?
Well, let's be honest, boss.
I don't know how I am.
- She was...
- Yeah, she was.
Any idea how it happened?
- Do you?
- No.
In that case, let me offer
some friendly counsel.
Such as?
Step back and let the Belgians
do their job.
Yeah, of course.
I mean, what else am I gonna do?
- How is your thing?
- Not great.
I'm playing catch-up
with some bedlamite.
Following his spoor back to source.
Now you know what I'm doing now.
Animal like that,
he's always moving forward.
You should be too.
You know, John, we can't
discuss this any further.
Not unless you walk away
from this leave-of-absence thing.
Gotta go, boss. Sorry.
All right, mate?
Looking a bit militant there.
It's the police.
Well, can I see a badge then?
No.
Errol...
Is he having a laugh?
You having a laugh?
Let's have a talk in my office, then.
Shall we?
Yeah.
- Recognise her?
- Nope.
Wouldn't mind though. Chung, innit?
Chung?
That's very funny, ‘cause I think
one of your boys just killed her.
Callum Green,
Shaunie Mashman, ain't he?
I wonder how many
of those boys out there
know that you've been
a snitch since before
Cool Britannia was all a thing.
I mean, we know what they'll think
about that now, don't we?
They'd end your days on earth, Errol.
- Let's have a word.
- Hey, hey, hey...
This woman... I don't know who she was.
So what's Callum Green
doing with her in Antwerp?
AlLI know is that
it was contracted out.
Oh, yeah? By who?
Come on, man...
- Doesn't matter.
- Hey, hey, hey...
George Cornelius.
Come on, man.
The old-school geezer from Islington?
That's him, yeah.
You are a snitch.
What're you...
Good afternoon. I'd like to speak
to George Cornelius please.
No, I'm sorry, he's not in.
Yes, he is.
Hurry up.
You rang, My Lord?
George Cornelius?
You know I am.
Come with me, please.
Sorry, mate, who are you again?
Police.
Which police?
"The" police.
I don't care if you're fuckin' Sting,
you lot do not come around here,
not for any reason.
This is my house.
You all know this.
Yeah, well, sorry about that but
I'm here now so
we might as well crack on.
No. Straight-up, no.
What's going on? Who's your guv'nor?
I've got this, Dad.
Look...
Come along with me.
There we go.
Down the steps, let's go.
Are you really a copper?
Sort of.
This is your gaff, is it?
Don't spend a lot of time here though.
Not by the look of it.
No, not really.
Actually, I was thinking of
leaving the country.
Well, I was until you put a crimp on it.
Oh, yeah? How'd I do that?
By killing Alice Morgan.
Or having her killed.
Same difference, really.
I did what to who, now?
Don't tell me you don't know
who she is, George.
Mate...
I didn't put her down
or have her put down.
- Why would I?
- I don't know.
But there's one way to find out.
Before I end it for you.
You do know they saw you.
My boy, my daughter-in-law.
They clocked your face,
they clocked your car.
How long do you think you've got
before my firm
are popping your eyeballs out
with their thumbs?
Yeah.
I don't care, George.
You don't scare me.
Fair enough.
All right, what it is,
she comes to me, your girl...
Different name.
She's got these uncut diamonds,
blue ribbon merchandise,
worth a lot of money
but difficult to shift
unless you've got the right connections,
which I've got, she doesn't.
We agree a 70/30 split.
She doesn't like it
but she needs the money, sharpish.
- Did she say why?
- Her and some
geezer are running away to...
Sao Paulo.
So, that'll be you then. The geezer.
Yeah, that'll be me.
Right.
So, I give her the name of
a contact in the trade,
bent as a bottle of chips,
she's supposed to meet him in Antwerp.
Except, she meets your boys instead
and you rob her.
Well, what can I say?
It's a lot of money.
And at the end of the day, I'm a thief.
The thing is, she doesn't like
being ripped off
and she knows how to put up a fight.
She stabs the driver
in the back of the skull
with a hat-pin.
And what about Callum Green?
Callum?
He stumbles out of the car,
gets himself straight to hospital.
Turns out, she's
kicked him in the nuts so hard
they've blown up like footballs.
He's in no condition to hurt anybody.
And the burner?
Why'd you steal the burner?
- What burner?
- George.
The phone I used to call Alice Morgan.
Mate, until today,
I had no idea you existed.
You didn't do it, did you?
I really didn't.
Bruno Dressler's 35.
Owns and runs Body By Dressler,
a small chain of gymnasiums,
a clean record, more or less.
His name was connected
to a trial in America
of a man called Donald Guthrie.
Dressler and Guthrie exchanged emails
on a fetish website
devoted to, and I quote,
"Cannibal erotica."
He and Guthrie exchanged
intensely detailed fantasies
about how they wanted to kidnap, rape,
cook and eat young women
and teenagers.
I'm on my way.
Roger.
Got a body in the bath.
Dissolved in lye, apparently.
Very old-school.
Could be Dressler.
Hard to tell.
The head and hands are missing.
Okay. With you in five.
- Yeah.
- John.
It's Theo.
Can you talk? Sorry to impose. I, uh,
need a disinterested ear.
Yeah, of course. Go on.
You ever had your nose
pressed up too close to something?
Uh, yeah. Once too often.
Can't see it, John.
I can't see past it or something.
I'm, uh...
At one of those drawings.
I'm looking at the profile
of an old hag.
You know there's a portrait of a
young girl in there somewhere,
you just have to re-focus somehow.
Okay.
What are we looking at?
You find a body dissolved in lye.
The head and hands are missing.
What's the first assumption?
Your boy's working hard to
prevent you making an ID.
But that's not what this boy does.
Not what he needs.
So, why does he need it now?
Why remove the head and hands?
Because they're important to him?
Yeah, but in what way?
Seems to me there's one of two options.
Option one, they're important
to him personally, so...
He wants to keep ‘em.
Option two...
For some practical reason,
they're important so he wants
to make sure they're never,
ever found.
I'm thinking it's option one.
He's keeping them.
Hang on.
Theo?
Just give me a sec.
A police officer,
reported dead
following a large explosion in a
Central London block flat.
Police and emergency service personnel
attending the site
have yet to comment on the...
You stay there.
They've taken Theo away.
They look after him now.
Yeah...
EMTs took me out.
I'm fine.
Of course you're not fine.
Once they've signed me off...
I can come back.
I'm fine.
Where do I sit?
By jump.
Alice Morgan.
There's not a lot to see, boss.
I still need to see it.
Guy...
Boss.
You got a minute?
I'm sorry you lost him like that.
I loved him.
Uh, I don't mean, uh,
"loved him," loved him...
I know what you mean.
I just wanna say...
Whatever it takes...
You know...
I'm in.
Anything?
Anything.
Hmm.
You got a family?
- Yeah.
- Your girlfriend's expecting a baby?
Six weeks.
You love her?
More than anything.
That's good.
There are some things that you might
have heard about me
that quite possibly, could be true.
I know what you're
going through right now.
I sincerely do.
But there's something I need you
to hear from me.
Never cut corners. Never.
Not even if you know
no one else will know,
no one else will find out.
That it is exactly the right thing to do
because it never, ever is.
Ever.
We do this the right way.
All right? Straight down the line.
You do it that way,
or I get you kicked off
for being unfit for duty.
Lab reports confirm
that it's Dressler in the bath.
And we got into
Dressler's laptop.
He spent a lot of time
online over the last
couple of months, boss.
Exchanging fantasies about
cooking and eating human flesh.
And detailed fantasies at that.
There's a lot in there about brides,
wedding dresses, pregnant mothers.
And all of that's in there, is it?
- Yup.
- So, if we can find all that,
our boy can find it too.
He leads us to Dressler, right?
The fridge, the laptop.
All that time spent
running around in circles.
Also, he's got the time to...
To what?
To finish up what he started.
I don't know.
Let's see who's been poking around
Dressler's private life, shall we?
Last year
then we thought... Yeah, I know.
We thought you were gonna
come to us this year.
I know. Why not, right?
- Hello?
- Hello.
Is this Alistair's mum?
Who, who is this?
I was with him when he died.
Who are you?
He was asking for you
at the end
when he couldn't fight any more.
"Mum."
He was so scared
of dying.
Why would you do this?
Ahh!
What do you got?
Well, you were right.
We find spyware deep
in Dressler's laptop.
How closely
was he being watched?
Close enough to know everything
there is to know.
It's not just passwords and
bank account log-ins.
Whoever's been watching him
knows every sentence he's composed,
every website he's visited.
He knows his thoughts.
Used to be that we could never know
the truth about each other.
Not really.
Those days are gone.
More's the pity.
And how confident can we be
that the killer
and the fellow who loaded the spyware
is the same guy?
Well, we can't, to be fair.
Um, we can't be certain.
It could be anyone
who had access to that laptop.
You say "anyone" but I mean...
Well, how many people
can that be, realistically?
I mean, someone like Dressler,
a man with that kind of fantasy life,
those kind of secrets.
How many people are you gonna let
near your computer?
How many people do any of us
let near our computer?
So, if he was watching Dressler
that closely,
what are the chances,
he was watching all of them?
In order to plant the spyware,
our subject had to have direct
physical access to everyone's computer,
so, we pulled credit card records
from all the victims,
and cross-referenced.
Now, over the past two, three years,
each of them made at least one payment
to a company called
Geek Patrol.
They come round your house,
fix your computer,
set up your Wi-Fi network,
whatever.
And all the computers were
fixed by one man.
A Steven Rose.
That's him.
Have we got an address?
What are we waiting for?
Bomb squad.
All right, you've got your perimeter.
The area's cleared.
We need to get in there, Guv.
He's not gonna booby-trap
his own place, come on.
- And you're sure of that, are you?
- Yeah,
Iam.
Easy for you to say, John.
You weren't here
when I had to watch them
scrape Theo Bloom off the wall.
Guy, Steven Rose could be on his way
to his next victim.
And we won't know who that is
unless we're in there.
The answer is no!
You want to discuss it further,
we can do it back at the factory.
I think I hear someone in there.
In fact I can!
I can hear someone screaming for help!
DCI Luther...
Exigent circumstances, sir!
DCI Luther!
Benny!
Ben, come on!
Come in.
Benny, can you, uh, stop this.
Whatever, turn it off, whatever.
I'll give it a go.
You okay?
- Boss?
- Yeah.
It's all right.
Steven.
You've gotta stop.
It's US law?
No, this one's
according to English law.
When can I see it?
I'm sending it over right now.
Why don't we talk tomorrow morning?
9:30 your time?
Okay.
Sorry, Guy,
she's asked for you by name.
Can I help?
Are you DCI Luther?
Yeah.
I have a message for you.
A message from who?
Alice Morgan.
:::::: www.hiqve.com ::::::