What the fuck do you want?
You want to tell me how
you got those bruises?
Not really.
You afraid if you do,
you won't get your kids back?
I'm starting to
wonder if I should
be more afraid of
getting them back.
I don't deserve
to be their mother.
Maybe I don't deserve anything
more than exactly what I got.
I'm gonna give you a free pass.
Nothing you say now will affect
my custody recommendation.
You have my word.
This is off the record.
Why would you do that?
Because believe it or not,
I'm trying to help you...
And I can't without the truth.
I put her in danger again.
Who, Deva? She was home?
What happened?
They came for me.
Who came for you, Carrie?
You want the truth?
I'm a liar.
I lied to my family.
I lied to my husband.
Gordon, he never lied.
And his truth is the
only one I have left.
He dedicated his whole life
to fighting corruption
in this town.
And you feel you
have to see it through
because he died saving you.
- It's not so simple.
- Then help me.
Help me out with it.
Help me understand, Carrie.
What's the truth?
Carrie, help me...
That I never stopped
loving somebody else.
I know,
I have to stop this fighting.
No.
You have to finish
what you started.
What kind of shrink are you?
This is not the shrink talking.
This is the father in me.
And I know that until
you make peace with this,
you can't be the parent
that your children need.
So go finish it.
Where's my drugs?
They took everything.
Who did?
I... I don't...
You let Calvin Bunker take my drugs?
Huh?
You let Bunker take my drugs?
Hey, it's Veronica.
You, uh,
disappeared on me this morning.
But anyway,
I tracked down our statutory rape victim.
She said all the right things,
but my bullshit
meter is ringing.
Anyway, I'm going back to the hotel,
so call me
and I can fill you in on the...
Okay,
hotel surveillance shows Dawson
leaving the property a
little before noon yesterday.
I've got every available
deputy out searching for her.
FBI is mobilizing a task force.
She won't live that long.
We have to find her now.
How?
Hood, I have been hunting for
this son of a bitch for months,
and all I got is dead ends.
What about the girl?
The one that burned herself.
Gail Westcott.
We searched her
apartment three times.
We can't find a single
connection to Bode.
I did request an expedited
subpoena for her cell phone records,
but that's still gonna
take a few days.
You still got the phone?
Well, yeah, I mean,
what's left of it.
Let's go.
I've seen that look before.
I need your help.
Some things never change,
do they?
Just like old times.
You're the expert on old.
Wait a minute. I know you.
Excuse me?
You and I were in
a gunfight together
with the, uh,
the Ukrainian gangsters at the metalworks.
Correction, I was in a gunfight.
You were lying on the floor
crying about your motherfucking leg.
- What's in the bag?
- Cell phone.
I need the call history.
Last few days.
Look, I'm afraid there's
not much to work with there.
Maybe for your police techs.
This got something to
do with the Bowman girl?
Yeah.
Give me 15 minutes.
Sugar, where's my computer?
Exactly where you left it.
Well,
it ain't gonna fetch itself.
Fuck!
I'm in.
The heat scrambled most
of the internal memory,
but there was still
enough raw data
for me to recover the
ESN and hack the log.
I have no idea
what you're saying,
but I sure as hell
missed hearing you say it.
What time did that
girl set herself on fire?
7:00 AM.
She make any calls that morning?
Five in the two hours
before she grilled herself.
All to the same number.
Bode.
Give me the number.
I'll have my people do a trace.
I already traced it.
You best keep up, cop.
Belongs to a Kim Newton.
You know her?
No, but I'm guessing
she's connected to Bode.
Address.
Thanks.
Who the fuck let you in here?
I'm looking for Calvin.
You must also be looking
to get your ass kicked.
Mr. Bunker took something
that didn't belong to him.
My employer would like it back.
Yeah? Well, you can tell Proctor
to go fuck himself.
We're putting him
out of business.
Oh.
I see.
- Easy!
- You, you!
You're an FBI agent.
Yeah.
And you're a serial killer.
I don't kill them
because I like to, you know.
I know.
You kill them
because you're insane.
It's all relative, right?
Not really, no.
You think Satan speaks to you.
There is no Satan.
Ergo, you're insane.
You're not afraid of me,
are you?
Oh, don't take it personally.
I've just seen behind the
curtain one too many times.
The curtain?
Yeah, you know,
like The Wizard of Oz.
Turns out the big
powerful wizard
is just smoke and mirrors,
a delusional old fart
with a few magic tricks.
You know what I think?
What's that?
I think you've taken
down enough wizards
to wonder if maybe,
they know something that you don't.
That maybe there are truths
other than the ones
you tell yourself.
And those truths
have fucked you up so badly
that you don't even
know when to be afraid.
It bothers you I'm not afraid.
Makes you feel impotent,
less powerful.
You can't profile me.
I don't have to.
I already caught you.
I like you, Veronica.
But you're still gonna
cut my heart out.
Yes, I am.
See what I mean?
Fucking insane.
What's wrong?
I just got a call
about a handful of Calvin's
guys dead at the clubhouse.
- Do you think Calvin did it?
- No, they're his guys.
But I think the
Brotherhood's going to war.
And I don't want to
have to worry about you
while I'm dealing with Calvin.
You're not safe here at
Brook's house anymore.
I spoke to a friend
in Dade County.
He's a retired cop.
He's got a place
in Turnberry Isle.
You and Hank will be safe
there for the time being.
- It won't be for long.
- You don't get it.
No matter where we run,
as long as Calvin's breathing,
he's not gonna let me go.
Yeah, it's me.
I'm talking to your
fucking voicemail again.
This is your last chance,
Maggie.
Tell me where the fuck you are
or I swear to God
I will destroy...
Call me back.
Oh, shit.
You really think
I'll let this stand?
You stupid bitch.
This will not fucking stand.
I will fucking end you.
I will rip your
fucking lungs out
and I will strangle
you with them.
Calvin?
- Hello, Martin.
- What the hell are you doing?
Jesus Christ.
Stupid gook motherfucker!
Oh, my God.
Senator Mitchum,
thank you for seeing me.
I figure if it wasn't important,
you would have just called me.
So, what is it?
We had some complications.
We can't afford
any complications,
not with these people.
Or we both wake up
strangled by our own tongues.
I know that.
That's why I'm here.
You're having
production problems?
No, production is on schedule.
I'm having, uh,
personnel issues.
Sheriff's Department.
Hello.
Check around back?
It's open.
We having company?
Later.
I'm not really dressed for it.
I could use a drink
if you're pouring.
What would you like?
Whiskey, please.
You're really gonna make me
drink my last drink
through a straw?
We both know if I untie you,
you'll try to run.
Then I'll have to rough you up
again to get you
back on the table.
And what would
the neighbors think?
Nothing. I'll check upstairs.
Okay.
- So who's coming over?
- Just some friends.
You have a ritual.
Yeah.
Upstairs is clear.
She was here.
Oh, shit.
Well, she's not here now.
I wonder if this place
has a basement.
Satan didn't tell you to kill me.
I just showed up.
I can't let you live.
Maybe I could just join you
and worship with
you and your buddies.
- No.
- Why not?
Because Satan doesn't exist,
remember?
I'm pretty sure you said that.
Nothing more annoying
than a psychopath
who engages in Socratic debate.
Shh.
Now what?
You okay? What's wrong?
Hey.
You look beautiful.
Sorry, Kim. I'm not into girls.
My name is Lilith.
No, it's not.
You asked me how the sex was
when I met Declan.
It was transcendent.
Like he was occupying my soul.
- It was rape.
- No.
You were a child.
And he made me a woman.
- Hey, her car.
- What?
Her car is in there.
Give me a hand.
- This her car?
- Yeah.
There's blood here.
Shit.
Hey, Hood.
- What?
- Diprivan.
Brand name for Propofol.
Same shit that killed
Michael Jackson.
- What's it used for?
- General anesthesia.
So what the fuck is
it doing in a garage?
Brock?
Hey.
Killers, rapists,
drug dealers
all walking the
streets because of you.
No, it's Proctor. It's Proctor.
He threatened me.
I swear to God...
You are the goddamn
District Attorney.
He...
He threatened my family.
I have three kids. Please.
Please don't do this.
I want to know about everything
Proctor has his hands in.
I only know what he
wants me to know.
- Are you lying to me?
- No.
No, wait. Wait, wait, wait.
Wait.
Last week...
Last week he made my office
seize all the tower records
from the old municipal airport.
Why? Who's flying in?
Emilio Loera.
Loera?
He's a major player in
the Colombian cartel.
Proctor's selling to the cartel?
I don't know. I swear to God,
I'd tell you if I did.
- Go home.
- What?
You just quit.
Get your kids and get
the hell out of Banshee.
Hey, Hood.
The dizziness comes in waves.
They must have drugged us.
You got any give on your cuffs?
No.
Yeah, me neither.
What is this?
I don't know.
Some sort of basement.
Of course.
Did you get a look at him?
He came to visit
me the other night.
- Who did?
- Bode.
You saw him?
Why the fuck didn't
you say anything?
I don't know. Maybe I was, uh...
Spooked.
He knocked me out.
And when I came to,
he had a knife to my throat.
He could have
killed me right there,
but he didn't.
Said he wanted
me to bear witness.
- To what?
- I don't know.
But I'm guessing
we're about to find out.
So Dawson probably showed
up and got the same treatment.
She might still be here.
If she's not already dead.
Hey, I applaud your effort,
but, uh,
you're not gonna break out
of stainless steel cuffs, okay?
You don't break the cuffs.
You work the links.
If you're lucky,
there's a defect.
Why don't you try yours again?
All right.
Ah, fuck.
My right hand's a little loose.
If I can just get a
little more leverage.
They're solid. Stop it.
Hood. Hood. Stop!
Hey, hey, look at me.
Give it up, all right?
We're not getting out of here.
You know what sucks about this?
I mean,
besides the fact that we're gonna die.
I never got to be the
sheriff I wanted to be.
I waited so long for this.
I waited for one sheriff to die.
And then I had to
wait for you to burn out,
which you did in such a big way.
- No offense.
- None taken.
I mean, okay,
so I'm not the most charming guy.
I rub some people the wrong way
and, you know, I can't kiss ass.
It's just not in my nature,
you know?
But I've never been afraid
to stand up to anybody
who threatened the
well-being of my town.
I wanted to be that guy,
you know?
The guy that made
people feel safe.
And I haven't done that.
Hey.
Can I ask you something?
- Be the last time.
- What?
Who the fuck are you?
Really.
Who are you?
Look, I know you got a lot of secrets,
Hood.
I'd be an idiot not
to acknowledge that.
No, we're not gonna do
that condemned men
confess their sins shit,
all right?
Yeah,
I think that's exactly what we're gonna...
No, we're not.
Any minute now,
that door is gonna open
and something very bad
is gonna walk through it.
Now, don't you want to meet
this with a clean conscience?
- No, shut the fuck up.
- Come on, Hood, please.
Then just answer the
fucking question for me.
- I said drop it, Brock!
- No, I'm not gonna drop it!
I want to know! Why are you here?
Why did you become a cop?
I am not a cop!
I never was a fucking cop!
What are you...
- What does that mean?
- I'm not Lucas Hood!
I saw him die.
I picked up his wallet
and I became him.
That's not even possible.
I don't... What are you...
I'm a lie, Brock. I'm a fake.
I was a thief.
Not just a thief,
I'm a fucking
infiltration specialist.
Diamonds, gold, art,
anything, I could get it.
The places no one could get into,
I got in.
I had a good run,
but I got caught
and I did 15 years.
No, no. You're fucking with me.
Come on.
You're an ex-con? No.
- That's right.
- No.
Who else knows about it?
Siobhan know?
In the end, yeah.
Why would you do that? Why?
Why would you come to this
town and pretend to be a cop?
I don't know. I...
When I got out...
I had nothing.
Whoever I was before
was gone.
I was no one.
All I knew is
I needed to be close
to the one person who...
Who really knew me.
- Carrie Hopewell?
- Ana.
She was all I had.
So when I got out,
I tracked her down
and I came for her.
But she had Gordon
and the kids and a life.
That's right.
Oh, my God.
I became...
Sheriff.
But you're not. You weren't.
Well, I was getting up every day,
putting on the uniform.
Eventually, the lie took over.
I believed it.
I was the Sheriff.
I was a cop and I... I liked it.
I fucking loved it.
Somehow it just...
Somehow it just felt right.
There's nothing fucking
right about what you did.
It is the opposite of right.
You son of a bitch.
I believed you.
I trusted you. I followed you.
- I killed for you.
- No.
No, you killed for you.
Not me.
I just showed you the way.
A criminal.
That's rich.
I was deputy to a criminal.
Oh, God.
It all makes sense now.
All of it.
I'm so stupid.
If you're not Lucas Hood,
what's your name?
Sheriff Lotus.
It's good to see you again.
And you.
Dr. Quick tells me you're
friends with Agent Dawson.
That's right.
And if you've hurt
her in any way...
I'm gonna fucking kill you.
You fellas are in
for a treat tonight.
Yeah? You gonna con another
poor girl into burning
herself to a crisp?
Gail was a true believer.
No, she was a confused
and vulnerable young girl
who you manipulated
for your own sick pleasure.
It looks like you're going
to be my guests tonight.
Thing is, we have a dress code,
so Dr. Quick is going
to work his magic
and make you look a
little more like family.
You bust into my office.
You steal my camera.
I gotta say,
I was hoping we
would meet again.
Gather round, everybody.
It's almost time to begin.
We have an unexpected
offering tonight.
I think he will be pleased.
Don't worry, Sheriff.
This won't hurt a bit.
Well, maybe a little bit.
Here we go.
No, no.
Stay the fuck away from me.
Stay away.
Amen, evil from us deliver but
temptation into not us lead and
us against trespass
who those forgive we as
trespasses our us forgive and...
bread daily our day this us give
heaven in is it as earth on...
done be will thy
come kingdom thy
name thy be hallowed
heaven in art who Father our.
Hey, hey.
You don't have to do this.
But I really want to.
Hey.
You can't hurt me.
He won't allow it.
Oh, yeah?
Then he won't mind if I do this.
What's so funny?
You have no idea how
insignificant you really are.
That makes two of us, pal.
Declan!
Hood!
Is that the man
that killed my niece?
Yeah.
Thank you.
Don't bother.
Job.
You remembered.
I have money, Job.
Lots of it.
You have no idea.
$23.62 million.
Not counting the $5.2
million in Swiss francs
you have stashed
away in the Caymans.
Or rather I should say, you had.
What did you do with my money?
Oh, honey,
that ain't your money no more.
What do you want?
What do I want?
I want...
20 months of my
motherfucking life back.
It wasn't personal.
But you're right.
I fucked you.
We can put the past behind us.
Imagine what you
and I could do...
Twenty months!
Twenty months
of planning all the things
I was going to
do when I got out.
All the things I was going to do
to the motherfucker
who put me there.
But I have since seen the light.
Erasing your worthless ass
ain't gonna give me
back the time you took.
You're not going to kill me?
No.
I'm going to kill me.
You wanted to
fuck with the best.
Well, now you are the best.
Now you are Job.
From now on,
anytime anybody comes looking for me,
they're gonna find you.
Every security
system I ever cracked,
every organization
I ever compromised,
every dollar I ever stole,
they all got your
fingerprints on 'em now.
Mossad, People's Republic,
Uncle Sam, and a who's
who of unsavory terrorist types,
they all got serious
beef with you now.
Bitch,
I just made your punk ass famous.
And something tells me...
You gonna be a hell of a lot
easier to find than I ever was.
Have a nice short life,
motherfucker.
Job, wait.
You can't do this to me.
Job!