Oh, my God.
Help me.
No, please.
Please don't.
Please.
Please don't. No.
No.
No, please.
Please! Please! Please! Please!
Stop. No.
Cut!
Moving on, people.
- Let's reset for close-up.
- Sheriff's Department.
- What the fuck are you doing?
- You're all under arrest.
The fuck are you talking about?
This is a licensed production.
There's no license for what
you're doing here, asshole.
Jesus Christ, son,
pull your pants up.
You all right?
Look at me.
How old are you?
Don't answer that.
You're making a big mistake.
Don't fucking touch me.
Bunker,
I want you to arrest all these people.
- Don't fucking say anything.
- Shit, fuck!
Go ahead, resist.
Give me a reason, huh?
Run!
Fuck you, bitch!
Pony Joe.
Motherfucker.
Fuck.
Have I mentioned
you're under arrest?
Fuck you, traitor.
Split 'em up.
I need individual statements.
Where do you want the director?
Put him in the
interrogation room.
Turn up the heat.
- I want to talk to my lawyer.
- Yeah, yeah.
Good morning, Sheriff.
Mr. Mayor, you're in my chair.
I heard you and your
deputies had a busy morning.
Well, arrests don't mean shit if
your DA can't get a conviction.
That won't be a problem.
Yeah, I guess it won't.
I'm not an idiot.
You think I don't know
that every time your girl Cruz
gets an anonymous tip,
we're doing your dirty work?
I don't need to remind you
who put you in charge here
and kept you in charge, do I?
What can I do for you,
Mr. Mayor?
What progress have you made
on my niece's murder investigation?
We have a few leads.
Yeah, I read through the files.
These files are confidential.
And in case you've forgotten,
you're still a person
of interest in this case.
And if I wasn't out there wasting my
time shutting down fuck films for you,
I'd have arrested a suspect
in all three murders by now.
I expect daily
updates from now on.
Really?
I thought that was Deputy Cruz's job.
I want them from you, Brock.
Then I will make it a top priority,
Mr. Mayor.
Thank you for your time.
You're welcome.
Hi.
You look good.
Fuck you.
So what do you have here,
10 acres?
Twenty-five.
The woods are mine, too.
It's peaceful.
It's private.
Thanks.
New place is great.
A work in progress.
Mmm.
Where have you been?
I guess I needed some time.
Yeah,
I could have used some, too.
I shouldn't have
turned my back on you.
You didn't turn your
back on just me.
- Job's dead.
- Why, because Dalton said so?
No, because that's what
they do with people like Job.
You didn't know.
There was nowhere left to look.
You kept looking for him.
Yes.
Still nothing.
No.
What about Deva?
Didn't you at least
want to see her?
I have seen her.
She didn't tell me.
She knew if she did,
you'd want to come.
And Deva going behind
your back feels like a betrayal?
I just... I need to protect her.
- From him?
- From everything.
- That's not possible, Carrie.
- It used to be.
Ana.
Before he showed up in Banshee
and forced himself back into your life?
- I didn't say that.
- But that's what you feel, isn't it?
I'm sorry.
For what?
Everything.
The losses you've suffered,
the pain you've endured,
all the result of a choice
made by someone else.
And now he's back again,
showing up like he did two years before.
If you're so concerned
about my losses and pain,
why don't you let my
kids come home to me?
- We've already discussed this, Carrie.
- Let's discuss it again.
All I can do is make
a recommendation.
Beyond that, my hands are tied.
Then what the fuck
am I doing here?
Tell me who gets to make that
choice and let me go talk to them.
This is bullshit.
Let's talk about Gordon.
What about him?
Have you started sorting
through his belongings?
No.
The longer you wait, Carrie...
What?
The harder it gets?
Trust me,
it can't get any fucking harder.
Hey,
get those last three pallets loaded.
That truck should have
been on the road hours ago.
Motherfucker.
Mr. Proctor,
I was not expecting you today.
My condolences on your loss...
Don't.
I'd say our terms of
agreement were pretty clear.
You and your brotherhood
manage my operations
and I permit you to maintain
yours for a bit of your profits.
And that's what you've been getting.
I check the accounting myself.
Which is why I hold you
responsible for any errors.
Or omissions for that matter.
- You've been running a side business.
- Mr. Proctor...
What happened this morning
was your one and only warning,
Mr. Bunker.
From now on,
my cut goes up by 10%.
Do you want me to talk to
Mr. Watts about our new terms?
That won't be necessary.
I didn't think so.
What are you going to
do about the arraignment?
Why should I do anything?
My men are solid. I can vouch for them,
but the director's a freelancer.
There's no telling who he'd
rat out to save his own ass.
Mr. Bunker, you seem
determined to prove your ineptitude.
I'll deal with it.
Somebody pick this shit up.
Hey.
You don't seem happy to see me.
How are you?
Never better.
Good, 'cause I need your help.
With what?
You ever heard of
Aaron Boedicker?
Yeah, a meth dealer.
He and his clan used to
just cook up in the foothills,
but now they've
started selling it in town.
Sounds like a
problem for Proctor.
No,
it's actually a problem for me.
They were experienced
cooks and I was looking
to branch out on
my own a little bit.
I warned Boedicker that
Banshee was off-limits.
Let me guess, the inbred drug dealer
didn't listen to the 24-year-old girl.
I'm asking you
to help me fix this.
My uncle finds out what I've done,
I'm dead.
- Please?
- It's not my problem.
You drinking yourself to
death in a shithole motel room
wasn't my problem either.
I'm going after Boedicker
with or without you.
I just thought that with you
I'd have an actual chance.
Stop!
Drop the gun, bitch.
You drop yours, asshole.
Why the hell would he do that?
'Cause if he doesn't,
I'm gonna blow your fucking head off.
Well,
since you asked so nicely...
It's okay, son, I got this.
Get him out of here.
So, is this a social call?
'Cause my memory could be failing me,
but
I don't remember
inviting you to visit.
- You didn't.
- Then you're trespassing on my land.
- We had a deal.
- You've been getting your cut.
The deal was you wouldn't
sell meth in Banshee.
Do you have any idea what my
uncle would do to you if he found out?
I never much liked
being told what to do.
Then you're really gonna
hate it when I shut you down.
Shit, girl,
that there just ain't
never gonna happen.
Lem, get the girl inside.
She and I need to
have a little chin-wag.
Hey.
I don't think you appreciate how
much trouble you're in, little girl.
He'd better not touch me again.
And I don't know what I was
thinking getting into business with you.
You're the one who
broke the agreement.
The problem with being a pretty
girl is that over time you get the idea
that you can do or say
whatever the fuck you want.
I'm gonna do you a favor.
I'm gonna remove
the burden of beauty.
Hesher here chased down
a rabid possum a while back.
He ain't been the same since.
Jesus.
You fucking bitch.
Oh... Jesus Christ!
You okay? Look at me.
Look at me.
Come on.
Rebecca! Rebecca!
Hey, Rebecca.
We don't have time for this.
Rebecca.
Get down!
Yeah!
I know, I know, I know...
Bunker.
Not the kind of bar I would
think you'd hang out in.
There's a lot you
don't know about me.
I'm sure that's true, sir.
Is there a law against
drinking in this bar?
The sheriff asked
me to ask you to wait.
Wait for what?
I'll let him tell you.
- Nice car.
- Thanks.
What are you doing here, Hood?
I was thirsty.
Thought I might get a beer.
You're not here investigating
the Bowman murder?
No, sir.
I told you, I'm retired.
Yeah, yeah, listen.
Someone's out there killing young
girls and I'm a little under the gun here,
so I'm gonna ask you again,
what are you doing here?
One of the guys in the band
had a thing with Rebecca.
I figured I'll watch the show,
introduce myself.
No, you wait here.
Bunker and I will go talk to him.
Kid's a hillbilly drug dealer.
He's gonna run as soon
as he sees the uniforms.
Then we'll know
which one to grab.
Let's go, Bunker.
Sorry.
Your thoughts are
being read out loud
So everyone can hear
We know your insecurities
We know your biggest fear
Your thoughts are
getting worse and worse
You picture your
mother dead in a hearse
You plague your friends
with the worst curse
You can think of...
Everybody knows,
knows what you're thinking...
- Get out of the way!
- What the hell, man!
Get out of the way. Hey!
- Bunker!
- Look!
Here!
Shut up.
Hood!
God damn it.
Come in.
Mr. Franklin.
Do you wanna sit down?
- You wanted to see me?
- Yes.
I've been going through the case
file from the pornography arrests.
The evidence is overwhelming.
I'll have no problem getting
convictions for all five defendants.
- Withdraw the charges.
- What?
- Why?
- I have my reasons.
Sir, with all due respect,
you told
me to throw the
book at these guys.
And now I'm telling
you to let them go.
Mr. Proctor,
there's only so many times we can do this
before people start
asking questions.
- I'll worry about that.
- Sir, frankly, I don't understand...
And you worry about me.
- Was there anything else?
- No, sir.
Thank you for your time.
He won't be a problem.
Take a seat.
What the fuck am I doing here?
I said take a fucking seat.
What happened to Rebecca Bowman?
How the fuck should I know?
Why am I even sitting here?
You're not even a cop anymore.
That's right.
That means I can kick your
fucking head in and not get fired.
You dragged me here.
You know, why don't you go fuck yourself...
Or...
All right. All right.
I liked Rebecca.
We had a good thing going.
Till she dumped you?
She didn't dump me.
Things just got complicated.
Complicated how?
- Can I get a beer or something?
- No.
Complicated how?
I should have never told
her about my fucking uncle.
Aaron Boedicker?
- They did some business, right?
- She was his business.
He was cooking that junk up in
his bathtub before she got involved.
She's the one that gave him cash
as long as he didn't deal in Banshee.
That was the deal.
- I told her he wouldn't stick with it.
- And he didn't.
That's when she started acting
all crazy paranoid about everything.
I thought that she was
scared of my family,
but she said they were nothing.
It was Proctor that
scared the shit out of her.
The twisted shit she
told me about him.
Man, you have no idea how
fucked up that guy really is.
You wanna know what
happened to Rebecca?
Ask that motherfucker.
All right, go.
Get the fuck out of here.
Seems this girl's ghost
has got you all out of sorts.
Yeah, I owed her one.
Must have been a real big one.
You got something to say,
just say it.
Seems like you owe Job a
lot more than you owe this girl.
There, now I've said it.
Senor Proctor.
Welcome to Pennsylvania,
Mr. Loera.
About your niece.
You should take time to mourn.
Business can wait.
On the contrary.
A life can stop,
but business must go on.
My operation's been growing
exponentially since we last talked.
Expanding my distribution
network is of high priority.
- How does that benefit me?
- Market dominance.
It's no secret that the
Sinaloa's partnership
with the Chinese has
hurt your bottom line.
Once the cartels got
into the pill industry,
you could no longer
control the market pricing
like you did with the
cocaine and the heroin.
They're moving product
across the border,
twice your rate,
just a fraction of the price.
The increased traffic is just causing
you even more border headaches.
I can offer a local pipeline
without any of the risk
or expense of having to import
the product itself from Colombia.
No disrespect,
but I deal in a very different volume
than you do here
in Pennsylvania.
Your ambition impresses me,
but I'm not convinced that
you can play in my league.
Then allow me to convince you.
Very well. I expect three tons
ready for pickup in 14 days.
Done.
When this transaction
is completed,
I expect to be your
exclusive East Coast supplier.
Do we have a deal?
Senor Proctor,
I've heard the stories.
You're a dangerous man.
But a dangerous man in Banshee,
to the cartel...
is still nothing but a mosquito.
Failure to deliver
is not an option.
I'll see you in two weeks.
I reviewed the complaint.
All seems to be in order.
Are you prepared to make a bond
recommendation, Mr. Franklin?
At... At this time, Your Honor,
the People would like
to withdraw their complaint
against all five defendants.
Are we discussing the same case here,
Counselor?
There seems to be more than
sufficient cause here to proceed.
Yes, Your Honor, however,
the people have recently discovered
new evidentiary inconsistencies
and possible Miranda violations
on the part of the Banshee
Sheriff's Department.
In light of these unfortunate developments,
we have no choice
but to vacate the charges
and decline prosecution.
Very well.
I take it there are no
objections from the defense?
- No, Your Honor.
- Motion granted.
All charges are dismissed.
These men are to be released
from custody immediately.
I am free. Home and free.
Mr. Prosecutor,
I'd like a word in my chambers.
Hey, Bunker. How you doing?
I can't believe this
guy's back on the street.
Most of his actresses
are underage.
He doesn't just shoot them,
he drugs them and rapes them.
Nice to see you again,
Mrs. Hopewell.
What happened?
I'm having my things removed.
I thought you'd want to
redecorate your new office.
Thank you, Uncle.
You're welcome.
Aaron Boedicker
didn't kill Rebecca.
- Are you sure?
- I'm sure.
She was fucking his nephew.
Did you know that?
Who she fucked is
none of my business.
I trust you'll keep me informed
of anything else you find out.
What if I find out it was you?
I got nothing to hide.
Yeah?
Forensics report
came back from the lab.
There was a positive match
to the blood sample we found
in Rebecca Bowman's SUV.
Help me.
Hood.
- Son of a bitch.
- It doesn't make him a killer.
Yeah, well,
it sure as shit makes him a liar.
You're safe now, sweetie.
Everything's gonna be okay.
I'll be right back.
You don't really think he did it,
do you?
I don't want to, but he and Proctor
have never been best buddies.
You know,
maybe Rebecca got caught up between them.
That's not a motive for murder.
- Without that, we don't have a case.
- Yeah, I know.
And we don't have anything
connecting him to the other girls.
No, I know. I know.
And also you know Hood.
I know Hood just well enough to
know that I don't know him at all.
Do you want me to bring him in?
No, let's wait.
Let's see where
this trail leads us.
Yeah.
Thanks.
Right this way, girls.
Welcome to Dick
Webster Productions.
This is where the magic happens.
I want you to sit down.
Sit down on the couch.
Get comfortable.
You want to check out some of the
posters or, you know, some of the DVDs?
I'm gonna get us some cocktails
and then we're gonna start the audition,
okay?
We're gonna make it vodka.
Yeah, buddy.
You got me.
You got me, lady.
Who the fuck are you?
A concerned citizen.
I don't think you
want to mess with me.
I do.
How can Watts
be so fucking blind?
Proctor's got us running
around like niggers in the field
doing all the hard work while that
motherfucker just keeps getting richer.
Maybe all that time in the cage
and Watts doesn't mind taking
it up the ass, but I fucking do.
I'm done being
everybody's bitch.
Yeah, what are you gonna do?
I'm going to wait
for the right moment
and then I'm going
to fucking seize it.
I'm going to remind the
Brotherhood who the fuck we are.
Sometimes I wonder if
I'm the only one who sees
how batshit crazy
this world has become.
Please don't kill me.
Watts has lost his vision.
Fuck Watts.
He doesn't care that
our families are in danger,
that our future is on the brink,
but I do.
Fortune favors the bold.
Power comes from being
willing to do whatever it takes.
Killing you would
be much too easy.
Justice at any cost.
I'll be watching you.
Hello?
Who's there?
I don't want any trouble,
Proctor.
I didn't kill Rebecca.
I swear to God.
You can tell him that yourself.
Please. Please.
Good morning, Job.