Everything was delicious,
sweetie.
Thanks, baby.
So, how was work?
Slow and painful.
Same as always.
Except for when I got
promoted to shift supervisor.
I knew it.
We need to celebrate.
Do you have anything in mind?
As a matter of fact.
Go on, get things started.
I'll clean up in here.
- You sure?
- Of course, baby.
She's a beauty, isn't she?
All right, one second.
Don't want to make a mess.
Please.
Please. Please.
Please, don't.
No!
Easy.
You're welcome
for saving your life.
Only after I saved yours.
What?
What are you doing here?
I'm trying to help you.
No, that's not what I mean.
What are you doing?
What I have to.
No. That's bullshit.
- You don't have to live like this.
- What am I supposed to do?
Hide away from
the world like you?
No, you don't do what I do.
You can leave.
There's a whole world out there.
The life that you're choosing,
it ends one way.
Maybe.
But at least it's my choice.
Jesus Christ.
I need you to leave.
I need you to go.
- No.
- Get out of...
Don't.
Did you know that Rebecca
Bowman was pregnant?
You've asked me that
three times already.
And I'm gonna keep
asking it till I'm satisfied.
Did you know?
No.
Tell me about your
relationship with Rebecca.
It wasn't a relationship.
Then what was it?
Like just friends with benefits,
or something, until you killed her?
- Fuck you, Brock.
- No, fuck you.
Look, I don't think you're
killing young girls.
But I don't know that you're not.
The only thing I know is you've been
lying to me since you got to Banshee.
And the lies end here.
- When was the last time you saw her alive?
- I don't know. A while ago.
- I need you to be more specific than that.
- I don't keep a fucking diary.
Her car's GPS proves she was at
your cabin the night she was killed.
- Like I told you, I didn't see her.
- Really?
How do you know?
I mean, you don't keep a fucking diary.
I think you did
see her that night.
I think she told you
she was pregnant.
Knowing you, you probably
didn't take that news too well,
so, you argued.
Maybe it turned violent, physical.
No.
Why is your blood in her car?
I don't know.
Why don't you ask Proctor?
- I'm asking you.
- Well, I don't remember.
Well, do you remember cutting
the hearts out of these two girls?
Jesus Christ.
Come on, you know me, Brock.
No, see, I don't.
I don't know you.
The only thing I
know is that you went
off the deep end when
Siobhan was killed.
You snapped and maybe
you're reenacting her death
over and over and over
again like some psychotic...
Jesus,
open your fucking eyes, Brock!
This didn't happen
in the moment!
Whoever did this shit
took time to plan it!
Think!
What,
you think I got them pregnant as well?
Huh?
- You fucking know it wasn't me!
- I don't know anything!
Yeah, well,
that about sums it up.
Ted, Sheryl and Martin.
How y'all doing this morning?
Have a seat, Mr. Watts.
State your name for the record.
Randall Cody Watts.
Good morning, Mr. Watts.
I'm Commissioner Ted Smith.
I'm joined today by
Commissioner Sheryl Golden
and Commissioner Martin Davis.
Yeah, we've all met.
Today is your sixth appearance
before this board of parole.
If you say so, Teddy.
I've lost count.
Sheryl,
I see you finally had that baby.
I did.
I hope you and Mr. Golden
picked out a nice Anglo name.
Mr. Watts,
I suggest you take this hearing seriously.
What about the kike sitting next to you?
You think she's taking this seriously?
- Mr. Watts!
- Shut the fuck up, Martin.
- Mr. Watts.
- We all know the drill.
You're going to deny my parole,
then go home congratulating yourselves
on making the world a safer place.
But what you minimum wage
pencil dicks can't possibly understand,
is that however repulsive
you seem to think I am,
that the darkness
swallowing this country whole
and coming for you and
your half-breed families
is a million fucking
times worse.
- We're done here, Mr. Watts.
- Go fuck yourself, Ted.
Oh, and, Sheryl,
you be sure to give little Shoshanna
Golden a big kiss from her Aryan uncle
'cause you know I'm
gonna be thinking about her.
The pain is only psychological.
Sheriff's giving
you five minutes.
You finally got to visit me in jail,
huh?
Better late than never.
- I didn't do this.
- I know.
Do you have any idea who did?
Not yet.
I don't know if you'll make bail,
but I can use my house
as collateral if you do.
Thanks.
How's Job?
They did a real number on him.
He'll be okay.
How about you?
I really need to get
the fuck out of here.
Hello, Ted.
- How is he?
- Innocent and Brock knows it.
Well, the evidence says otherwise
and the sheriff has to follow up.
You got something for me?
I did. It can wait.
No, I need the distraction.
It's the details of a drug
processing and distribution facility.
Proctor's?
Mmm-hmm.
Thank you, Bunker.
Be careful, Mrs. Hopewell.
You just made bail.
I didn't kill her.
Maybe you did, maybe you didn't.
Either way.
What the hell is this?
Get away from there! Proctor!
What the hell are you doing?
I posted the prisoner's bail.
- Bail? This is bullshit.
- Hood is coming with me.
- The hell he is.
- Let him in.
- No.
- Get out of my way, Brock!
- Not gonna happen.
- I'm the fucking mayor!
- And I'm the fucking sheriff!
- Get out of the fucking way.
You give me those keys,
or I will shoot you.
Wow.
Everybody is so angry.
- Ma'am, you cannot be back here.
- Why not? Everybody else is.
- Bunker, take this woman up front, please.
- Stay put, Bunker.
Special Agent Veronica Dawson.
Violent Crimes.
Yeah, that always seems to
suck the air right out of the room.
I take it you're Sheriff Lotus.
- And you are?
- Kai Proctor.
Mr. Proctor,
I am truly sorry for your loss.
Let's go, Proctor.
- I got this.
- Get your fucking hands off me!
I got this, Sheriff.
Mr. Proctor, I can only imagine
how frustrated you must be with
how things have been handled.
But this is my
investigation now.
And while I've got a little
bit of lost time to make up for,
I can assure you I'm a quick study
and I plan to get to the bottom of things.
Do me a favor,
give me some time to sort things through,
and as soon as I do,
you'll be the first to know.
You have 24 hours.
Then what happens?
What a fun group.
Shh.
Do you think she's pretty?
I think he'll be happy.
Lucas Hood.
Onetime sheriff.
Part-time mountain man.
And now the primary
suspect in three homicides.
It's a hell of a résumé.
Sheriff Lotus told me
you don't talk much.
Well,
maybe I just don't talk to him much.
He also told me
about Deputy Kelly.
You two were a couple
at the time of her death?
God, losing a deputy and
a lover in one fell swoop.
That must have been tough.
I've been there.
My husband Paul.
He was leading a
tactical operation.
Some low-level terrorist we could
lean on to get us some bigger fish.
By the book, breach and arrest.
He had the perp
facedown and zip-tied
when in walks the guy's 13-year-old
nephew holding a GLOCK 9.
Paul could have dropped
him in a heartbeat.
I mean,
who can't outshoot a kid, right?
But instead,
he tried to talk him down.
I guess that kid
didn't feel like talking.
He shot Paul in the neck.
Killed him instantly.
You've been doing this a while.
Long enough.
Long enough to know
that the fake husband story
is not gonna work
on someone like me.
So, either you think I'm an idiot,
or you wanted me to call you on it.
What, so,
that I would feel like I'm in control?
Seeing as we both
know that's not true,
why don't you cut the bullshit
and ask me what you want to ask?
Okay.
Did you kill Rebecca Bowman?
No.
Well, that was easy.
I so appreciate your cooperation,
Mr. Hood.
You're welcome.
I'm sure we'll meet again.
I'm guessing you don't have a
lot of pals down at the Bureau.
- You know a lot about the FBI, do you?
- No, not really.
But I know a little
something about burnouts.
Yeah, I'll bet you do.
- He didn't do it.
- Really? You decided that in five minutes?
No, I decided that in about two.
- The evidence...
- The evidence is shit and you know it.
The evidence isn't shit.
It's circumstantial.
I'll cut him loose.
- Not yet.
- Why?
Because the minute
we release him,
Hood's gonna try to find
Bowman's killer on his own.
And I'd like a little
bit of a head start.
For the record, I also knew that
your husband story was bullshit.
Hmm.
Did you know that Proctor was in
the drug business with your old crew?
What are you talking about?
There are neo-Nazis
crawling all over his warehouse.
- How do you know that?
- I'm looking at them right now.
Kurt, did you know?
If I knew,
I would have said something to you.
Look, we need to take a
step back and figure things out.
This changes things.
- Not for me, it doesn't.
- Carrie...
Carr...
Why didn't you tell me?
I wanted the new
facility to be a surprise.
When will it be operational?
The end of this week,
maybe a little sooner.
We can run double shifts,
triple the output in the first month.
I'll hire a new
foreman to oversee...
Rebecca, the Brotherhood
will be managing this operation.
What?
- Yeah.
- Why?
They can provide the distance
and the insulation I require as mayor.
This should be mine.
No, I know.
But you have to trust me on this.
I have something much
bigger planned for you.
Yes, your big plan.
Meanwhile, nothing is happening
and you're handing over
our business to Nazis?
I know that's how it looks to you,
but I promise this is what's best for us.
No, this is what's best for you.
And that's all you've
ever really cared about.
I wish you'd stop
treating me like a child.
I will when you
stop acting like one.
When you were my age,
you were already running things.
- There was no one holding you back.
- There was no one protecting me either.
- I don't need your protection.
- Yes, you do!
This is a dangerous business.
I'm fucking dangerous!
You have no idea
how dangerous I am.
Oh. Grandma means well, honey.
I think she's just worried about you.
You're just gonna have
to give her a chance.
Well,
could you at least pretend for Max?
'Cause I need you to set a good example,
that's why.
Honey, hold on.
Job?
Deva,
I'm gonna call you right back.
- Fuck, Job!
- Fuck!
I almost shot you.
- Imagine my fucking relief.
- You shouldn't even be out of bed.
And you shouldn't be storing
your AKs next to your Ann Taylor.
- How'd you get in there?
- It's a motherfucking tumbler.
You have enough firepower
in here to start a war.
Not start one.
Just finish it.
Amen.
Evil from us deliver but...
Us against trespass.
Who those forgive we as...
Heaven in is it as Earth on...
Name Thy be hallowed.
Heaven in art Who,
Father our...
Hot date?
- You should really get some sleep.
- That would require me closing my eyes.
It's gonna take time, Job.
Fuck this. I'm coming with you.
That's a bad idea.
No, it's the worst
motherfucking idea ever.
You're not coming.
Not you or nobody get to
tell me what to do anymore.
You are not leaving me in
this motherfucking house alone.
Just don't...
Don't leave me.
You're staying in the car.
You're gonna need
someone to watch your back.
- You're gonna need somebody...
- I'm serious.
Fine.
Got your message. What happened?
- Have a drink.
- Come on, man.
I dropped everything 'cause I
thought you were in trouble here.
Shit,
I need to get back to Proctor's...
Fuck Proctor.
Now, sit down,
and show me some goddamn respect.
No, no, don't be a fucking pussy.
Okay?
There you go.
Drink.
You all right, man?
Watts should have never
made a deal with Proctor.
He's so busy chasing
his own retirement plan,
that he's abandoned
everything that we've been
fighting for all these years.
Hmm.
He may be blinded
by Proctor's money,
but I'm not.
And I'm not gonna keep
my mouth shut anymore.
Calvin, you're drunk, buddy.
- Whatever you're thinking...
- No. No.
I'm done thinking, Joe.
I'm done being Watts' bitch.
It's time for me to
man the fuck up.
Watts has to fucking go.
We've been at this for months,
Job.
You must be getting tired.
Let's change the mood, shall we?
Job.
Job. Job.
- You okay?
- I'm fine.
How about you?
I'm fine.
Yeah, you look fucking fine.
Not now.
Just in case I do have
to drive home alone,
you want to tell me
what this is really about?
Why are you doing this?
Hmm?
Do you think all this
Catwoman bullshit
is what he would have wanted?
Stay in the car.
- Hey, what did he say?
- He said you're gonna die.
Oh, what the hell is this?
Hey, this is private property.
Who the fuck are you?
I asked you a question.
Are you deaf, you stupid bitch?
No, I hear you loud and clear,
bitch.
Shit!
Come on back, bitch. Come on.
Come on.
Bitch. Bitch, move. Move!
Run!
So, how'd that go?
Like clockwork.
Unlock gate 13.
See you again real soon there,
convict.
And you fuck your mama, Larry.
You my ride?
Nice car.
Them Krauts always done it best.
We headed to Banshee?
Mr. Proctor would like to see
you at your earliest convenience.
Well, then what the hell
are we waiting for?
- Fuck.
- FBI, skeezy fuckers.
Put the pipe down.
What are you doing?
Get the fuck out of here. Go.
Dawson.
On my way.
({CAMERA SHUTTER CLICKING)
Raven,
this is Agent Dawson from the FBI.
Yeah, what do we got?
Coroner estimated she was killed
Nine or 10 hours ago based
on body temp and lividity.
- MO is the same?
- Yeah.
Attractive female, 18 to 24.
Son of a bitch cut her heart out,
too.
Cut isn't surgical,
but it is precise.
He's in a safe place
when he does this.
Takes his time.
Defensive wounds?
Ligature marks,
just like the other victims.
She was tied up.
Some kind of rope, heavy braiding.
Enough to bruise like this?
She was bound for a while.
He doesn't kill them right away.
No signs of sexual abuse.
No,
he doesn't see them sexually.
Right here. He drugged her.
Just like the others.
Butchered her alive.
Got an ID?
No, nothing yet.
What'd the witness say?
Caught a glimpse of
someone dragging the body
into the woods
just after 5:00 a.m.
And why the hell did they
wait four hours to call it in?
Because his mommy
thought he was making it up.
What's the kid's name?
- Tocho.
Let's cover her up.
Make sure the coroner gets all those notes,
yeah?
Are you Tocho?
Is that you?
Can you tell me what you saw?
Huh?
Was it a man or a woman, huh?
- Young or old?
- Come on, that's enough.
No more questions, huh?
Come on, Tocho.
Okay,
I'm gonna finish cutting this
for you and you're
gonna eat all of it.
- And then treats.
- Okay.
But the vegetables, too.
- Okay?
- Okay.
- Promise?
- Yeah.
How are the potatoes?
Dry.
I'm sorry.
I must have overcooked them.
Stay here.
- What the fuck?
- It's nice to see you, too, Calvin.
And, yes,
I'd love to come inside.
Do I smell Magpie's cooking?
- How did you get out?
- It's a hell of a story.
Maybe I'll tell it
to you sometime.
Daddy.
- You're out?
- Good news, baby.
I've been rehabilitated.
And who might you be?
Uh...
Hank, this is your grandfather.
You just call me Papa,
sweetheart.
Uh, okay,
we're gonna go up and take a bath now.
You know what?
Fuck a man's heart.
You want love,
go right to his stomach.
Congratulations.
You're not a serial killer.
I'll need you to fill
out some paperwork.
Need a ride?
You don't seem like
the type to hold a grudge.
You kept me locked up.
I just got here.
Had to get my bearings.
I'm glad I could help.
You knew I was innocent.
I think innocent might be
a bit of a stretch, don't you?
Yeah, fuck you.
Hey, you're welcome for that alibi,
by the way.
Look, Hood, I know where you live.
It's a long walk to that cabin of yours.
I need a drink.
You definitely need a drink.