So, where's your place?
About a mile through the woods.
This is rustic.
Some backyard you got here.
Yeah, I like the quiet.
Ugh. I fucking hate it.
What,
too many voices in your head?
You have no idea.
You should talk to
someone about that.
Oh, why the hell do you
think I gave you a ride?
Well, you're just so honest.
I'm honest. You're silent.
We both got our things.
So, um, what's your real damage?
I mean, you're obviously
punishing yourself for something.
Hey, we've all got shit we
wish we hadn't done, right?
And what shit do you
wish you hadn't done?
Oh, we definitely haven't
drank enough for all that.
So is this the part where you tell me
to just forgive myself and move on?
Well, I don't know what you did.
Maybe it's not forgivable.
Did you forgive yourself?
No.
But I don't punish
myself either.
I mean, I figure the world's gonna do
that to me one way or another anyway.
You want to talk about
Rebecca Bowman?
- I'm not judging...
- Don't.
- Sooner or later...
- I said don't.
What do you want?
I'm just trying to figure out if I'm
gonna keep running into you on this.
And we both know I can't
stop you from poking around,
but it would make my life easier if
you could just keep me in the loop.
Of course.
Thanks for the ride.
Don't be a stranger.
Listen,
I've had a really bad few days.
I thought we had a deal.
Rebecca was off-limits to you.
You knew I was living here?
I thought you were
keeping her safe.
That wasn't my responsibility.
Fucking her was?
I should kill you right now.
Well, get the fuck on with it.
You find whoever
did this to her.
FBI has it covered.
FBI is gonna arrest him,
most likely kill him.
You bring him to me.
And you'll need to find
another place to live.
Let's go.
Ms. Bowman,
I really think we should wait...
Take out the goddamn box.
Felix...
Where's my money?
- Ms. Bowman...
- Where the fuck is my money?
Your uncle.
He came and took it.
What?
That's my box. You can't just...
There are rules.
Rebecca, put that gun away.
Put that gun away.
It's okay, Felix.
- Just give us two minutes.
- Yes.
Have you lost your mind?
You took my money?
Skimming cash from my strip club,
and locking it in a box
doesn't make it yours.
You may not have
paid me that money,
but I earned it.
Every fucking penny.
If you want to point that at me,
you had better be ready to shoot it.
Shoot it!
We'll talk about this later.
Watts, come on, man.
This is bullshit.
You shut the fuck up
and do as you're told.
Beautiful morning, isn't it?
Reminds me of how
blessed I am to be a free man.
You said you had something
you wanted to show me.
That I do.
Right this way, gentlemen.
My son-in-law's epic fuckup
may have given you the unfortunate
and grossly inaccurate idea
that the Brotherhood might not be
able to deliver the muscle you need.
But I'm here now,
and I wanted to show you firsthand,
I'll be running a
much tighter ship.
Pony Joe here was in charge
the night your factory got torched.
- Watts...
- Do it.
Now.
Come on.
You know it wasn't my fault!
Hey!
Calvin!
Hey, don't you do this.
Don't do this!
Come on!
Calvin! Calvin!
Don't do this! Calvin!
Let's go, Calvin.
- Hit it, boy!
- Don't do this.
I will have zero
tolerance for fuckups.
- What about the production delays?
- Already started outfitting...
I need three tons in eight days.
That kind of volume
usually means beaners.
Attract a lot of unfriendly attention
on both sides of the borders.
You got one hell of a pair of balls on you,
I'll give you that.
Banshee will become the distribution
hub for the entire East Coast pipeline.
As long as I can count on you,
the Brotherhood will be well compensated.
Employed is fine and good,
but you're talking
about the cartels now.
And for that kind of risk,
I don't want to be compensated.
I want a piece.
Mr. Watts,
you make this delivery on time,
I'm sure you and I will come to
an agreement about your piece.
Glad to hear it.
You hear that, bow tie?
You and me is gonna be buddies.
Well...
That went better than expected.
We just killed one of our
own for that fucking Dutchie.
Yeah, well, it was him or you.
Don't think I
didn't consider it.
Go clean this shit up.
Congratulations, Job.
Twenty-eight hours.
That's a new record.
Now, your over-under with
the guards wasn't too good,
but I never doubted you.
Why?
Why ain't you
just killed me yet?
I could do that.
I could.
But honestly,
I'd miss these little
sessions of ours.
I'll see you tomorrow.
That's one way to get down.
Well played, Job.
Hey.
- You okay?
- I'm fine.
More nightmares?
- If you ever want to talk about it...
- No.
Okay.
You can still make
yourself useful.
What the fuck is this?
That is a list of your
chores for the day.
No free lunches.
This is bullshit.
I'm convalescing.
I'm going into town,
I'll see you later.
I do not do windows!
So they let you out.
Yeah, you sound surprised.
No.
Nothing surprises me
anymore when it comes to you.
But for what it's worth,
I was pretty sure
you didn't kill the girl.
Thanks very much.
I mean, come on.
How well do you ever know a man?
How's Job?
Why don't you pay him a
visit and find out for yourself?
I will.
You smell like an ashtray.
Yeah, I had a fire.
Proctor.
Yeah, he was pretty angry
about your relations with his niece.
That still doesn't
make me a murderer.
Doesn't make him one either,
in this particular case.
You mind if I go next door,
take a shower?
No. You have to use mine.
Your place belongs
to the termites.
Exterminators say we
got to burn the place down
else they'll be over here.
That's probably for the best,
huh?
You got a place to stay?
You should go.
This is a bad idea.
You think we are who we are?
Or you think we can change?
What, you mean people like you?
Tell me about your father.
Seriously?
I know it's a cliché,
but I think in this case we can
both agree your father was influential.
What's there to tell?
My father was a monster
that got what he deserved.
Do you really believe that?
I had a dream about
him the other night.
We were at Coney
Island at the Boardwalk.
He used to take me
there every Sunday
in the summertime
when I was a little girl.
After the rides,
we would have popcorn and saltwater taffy.
And we would sit on
the same bench and
he would tell me
stories about my mother.
Then we'd take our shoes
off and put our feet in the surf.
And what happened in the dream?
Nothing.
I mean, I don't know.
We were just there.
You miss him.
How fucked up is that?
Well, look who got out of jail,
again.
So how you doing?
You look better.
Yeah, I'm a real fashion plate.
How about you?
What about me?
I hear you went native
while I was away.
Yeah.
That's one way of putting it.
You got another way?
Listen, Job,
I tried to find you.
We all did.
After Dalton was dead...
You mean after you killed him.
I thought you were dead.
I believed it.
And then something, uh...
Something inside me,
it just, uh...
I gave up.
And I'm sorry.
Well, it could have been worse.
Could have been 15 years.
You never put that shit on me.
- Rabbit fucked us.
- Yes, he did.
On my watch.
Baby, all our bullshit...
That's all in the past.
You and me,
we ain't ever getting
that time back.
So...
What you really
need to worry about is
what's happening
in the here and now.
What do you mean?
Our little friend is building a fortress,
and she is armed to the teeth.
For what?
Seems she feels the only
way to honor her dead husband
is to finish his war
on Proctor herself.
Mr. Watts has made
provisions to keep all
five facilities running
around the clock.
I'll need you to keep
an eye on things.
I don't trust him.
If I don't deliver on my
promise to the Colombians,
Watts is gonna be the
least of our problems.
Stop the car. Stop the car.
Excuse me, Mr. Mayor?
Mr. Mayor, is it true that your office
is withholding Rebecca
Bowman's body?
- Do you have any comment...
- Sir, what do you expect...
What the hell are you doing,
Miriam?
We want her back, Kai.
You can't keep her like this.
- I'm not keeping her.
- You can fix it.
Rebecca wasn't the
only girl who was killed.
She's the only one
we need to bury.
It's not right keeping her body like this.
It's disrespectful.
I'm gonna give you two minutes
to get these men out of here.
We will not leave
without Rebecca.
You lost all right to Rebecca
when you shunned her!
If you don't leave right now,
I'm gonna have you dragged away,
and put into jail.
We are not scared of you anymore,
Kai.
There's nothing
else you can do to us.
I wouldn't be so
sure about that.
- Mr. Mayor?
- Mayor Proctor...
Go home!
All of you!
Get out, now...
Or you will all go to jail!
Go away!
Sir, sir.
We should go inside.
I want these steps cleared right now.
You understand?
- They have a permit.
- I don't give a shit.
Hey.
- Jesus Christ, Hood.
- Afternoon, Sheriff.
You have any idea how
many laws you just broke?
You gonna arrest me again?
If you came looking for an apology,
you're not gonna get one.
No,
I would have done the same thing.
You would have shot me.
Yeah, maybe.
- What do you want?
- Heard there was another girl.
Yeah,
20-year-old college student.
Any leads?
Other than a six-year-old witness
who can barely speak English, no.
Nothing.
You're not gonna stay out of this,
are you?
You know, I got to ask,
you really didn't know
she was pregnant?
No.
Must have been quite a shock.
I'm sorry, Hood.
- Ms. Francis?
- Yes.
I'm Sheriff Brock
Lotus from the BSD.
We spoke after
your sister was found.
Yeah, I remember.
I already answered all your questions.
The FBI, too.
No, I know. I...
We appreciate it.
These are, um,
Jill's personal belongings.
I just wanted to
return them to you.
Look, I can only imagine
how hard this must be for you.
This guy killed three women,
and he was still out there free
walking around to kill Jill?
I mean, you're the Sheriff.
It was your job to protect her.
I know.
Howdy, Kurt.
- You're out.
- They let me go.
And it got me thinking.
Everybody deserves
a second chance.
Come back to the family, Kurt.
We need you.
Now more than ever.
Calvin, he talks a big game,
but he ain't made of the
same steel you and I are.
You want me to
rejoin the Brotherhood?
With your knowledge
of BSD procedure,
you'd be more
valuable than before.
Come on.
What do you say?
Randall...
I don't know how you got out.
But you made a mistake
coming back here.
How's that?
Because now that I
know that you're out,
I'm gonna dedicate myself
to putting you back in.
Yeah.
I didn't expect you
to bite right away.
I mean, hell,
you got to be you, right?
Well, look,
tonight I'm gonna party.
Celebrate my emancipation.
Tomorrow I'm gonna get to work.
If you haven't accepted
my offer by then,
you're gonna be the
first order of business.
Sheriff's office.
I know, I'm sorry...
Helen,
call everybody and tell them...
I'm holding a press
conference in one hour.
- What are you gonna do?
- What I should have done a while ago.
What is the meaning of this?
You won't be selling your
produce in Banshee anymore.
You won't be selling
your produce anywhere.
Oh...
Kai!
Why, Kai?! Why?!
These are sad and dangerous
times for the town of Banshee.
Four young women have been
brutally and senselessly murdered
by a twisted coward
who preys on those smaller
and weaker than himself.
You Tocho?
Can I draw, too?
My entire department
along with the FBI
have been working
around the clock
to identify and
apprehend this killer.
But obviously we haven't yet.
And for that,
I take full responsibility.
You know,
I used to be a policeman.
And even though I
don't do it anymore,
sometimes I still help them
chase the bad guys away.
I would like to make a pledge,
a promise, that I will not stop
until Jill Francis, Meredith Coble,
Amanda Crowley
and Rebecca Bowman receive the
justice they so desperately deserve.
Is that the man you saw the other night,
in the woods?
See these things
you drew on his head?
Was he wearing a hat?
Are they horns?
And now,
I would like to talk directly to you,
you sad, pathetic coward.
I don't know what you have
convinced yourself that you are,
but you will never be anything
more than a sad little freak.
I am gonna find you. I am.
And I'm gonna take you down,
and I'm gonna make sure that you
never hurt anyone else ever again.
- You drinking?
- Whiskey, rocks.
I've heard good
things about this place.
But where's the real action?
I don't know what the
hell you're talking about.
I think you do.
Go home, little girl.
Not until I find
what I'm looking for.
Thank you for the tip.
That's just nasty.
What the fuck?
You shouldn't be here.
Yeah?
Well, bad choices are sort of my thing.
But you must know
something about that.
I don't know who you are,
but the rules here
are very simple.
No one walks out the
same way they walk in.
Yeah, I'm gonna pass on that.
See, I'm pretty kinky,
but you guys, you're fucked up.
No!
You come here, too?
- How'd you know I was here?
- I didn't.
The Kinaho kid drew this.
This is the only place in town
where the freaks have horns.
How'd you get here?
Our murders are consistent
with other ritualistic murders
in the FBI database.
Pointed to Satanism.
Hey, shitneck,
where'd you get your work done?
Where did you get
your work done?
Get fucked.
Wrong answer.
Okay! Okay!
Guy named Quick. Dr. Quick.
- He's a surgeon?
- Yeah. No, he used to be.
Where do we find him?
Works out of the back of a
dry cleaner over on Swanson.
You kids need to
find a new hobby.
It's you.
Hey, Gail.
You seem nervous.
No, I just...
I just didn't expect
you to be here.
I'm sorry.
I didn't mean to startle you.
I've been watching you, Gail.
You're quiet,
less flashy than some
of the other acolytes.
But your commitment
is very pure.
I find that exciting.
Thank you.
We're a lot alike, Gail.
You're a true believer,
aren't you?
I am. I am.
That's good,
because I have chosen you
for a very special honor.
Will you serve him with me?
I will. I will.
Thanks. Thank you.
Is there a problem, Deputy?
Just answering
your prowler call.
We didn't call no police.
- Must have been your neighbors.
- Must have been.
'Course,
we ain't got none of those.
No. No, you don't.
Why'd you leave your car all
the way at the end of the road?
It's a long walk
to this here gate.
Do you live here?
Just visiting.
It's a lot of
surveillance equipment.
Well, you know what they say,
just 'cause you're paranoid don't
mean they ain't all out to get you.
Words to live by.
Mmm-hmm.
Have a safe night.
I'll do my best.
I just want to say a
few things real quick.
I gotta thank you all
for this celebration.
It's great to see all of you.
Now,
I look around and I see, man,
a lot of changes since I went in.
A lot of changes.
But after eight years in a cage,
there's one thing that
hasn't changed at all.
That's my commitment
to all of you.
Yeah!
Like it or not,
you degenerates are my family.
- Family sticks together.
- Yeah!
No matter what.
And on a personal note,
I've done my time.
Paid my dues.
And I'm tired of living in the
gutter in the name of the cause.
We sacrifice a
lot for our beliefs.
But we's also allowed to
enjoy some of the spoils of war.
Yeah!
So I have laid plans.
Plans that will put some of
those spoils into our own pockets.
And with that money
comes security.
And with that, power.
- Tonight we drink.
- Yeah!
- Tonight we fuck.
And tomorrow,
the new Aryan revolution begins.
Yeah!
What the fuck was that?
That was a new beginning,
Calvin.
Money?
That's your fucking pitch?
Money? Since when has the
Brotherhood been about money?
Grow the fuck up, Calvin.
I take care of my own.
Ideas don't pay the rent.
We can't all put on ties
and suck dick for some
shit ass conglomerate.
You're selling out
the Brotherhood.
Everything that we worked for,
everything you went to fucking jail for.
I went to jail for my brothers,
for my family, for you...
You ungrateful shit.
And I come out and I see you shitting...
all over the deals I made,
looking at me like I'm in your fucking way.
Now, Maggie,
she married the wrong brother.
Kurt might be confused,
but at least he got balls.
Okay.
Let's fucking party!
Bunker. Really?
What are you doing?
You know you have a
GPS tracker on your cruiser.
What the hell are you doing?
Brock, leave me alone.
That's Randall Watts, the top dog.
He just got out of jail.
One shot in his head and this is over...
One shot and you're gonna have
the entire Brotherhood up here.
Get up. God damn it, Bunker.
Be smart.
We've gotta be
smarter than them.
We cannot beat them at their game.
We gotta beat them at ours.
You're in uniform
using one of our vehicles.
What the hell are you thinking?
- I'm sorry.
- No, fuck sorry.
This town's going off the rails.
We got a serial killer on the prowl,
we got a mayor who's a gangster,
and you want to start a
war with the neo-Nazis.
Look at me.
I don't have much in my life
that I care about anymore, Bunker.
Just Banshee. That's it.
And I'll be damned if I'm gonna
give up this town without a fight.
Now you gotta decide right now
whether you want to
fight with me the right way
or you're just gonna be
another headache I gotta handle.
Okay.
- Okay?
Let's get the hell out of here.
That was a...
Good speech.
Ugh.
Damn.
I took a couple
shots back there.
But you gave some, too.
Hey, don't worry.
I already checked under the bed.
You should get some rest.
I should.
But I can't drink all
this scotch by myself.
Yeah,
I think we both know that's not true.
Try and tell me you
don't need a drink
after that madness we
just witnessed back there.
Yeah, you have a point.
Jeez.
So,
we gonna track down that surgeon?
Well, I'm not a cop anymore.
Even when I was,
I wasn't much of a team player.
Yeah, me neither.
But we're both out there
looking for the same guy.
Might as well have
each other's backs.
I know you can go it alone.
Me, too.
That's why they sent me.
But this guy is
a different kind of bad news.
And this is your town.
You know the lay of the land.
And I could really
use the backup.
Okay.
Maggie.
Oh, I've been trying to reach you.
They let my dad out.
I know.
He came to see me earlier.
You've gotta do something, okay?
You can't wait any longer.
I'm working on it, Maggie,
but this is a lot bigger than
just your father and Calvin.
You're talking about the drugs.
How do you know about that?
I found these on Calvin's desk.
Jesus Christ, Maggie,
if he caught you...
I'm just trying to give you
what you need, okay?
This is some kind of
a production schedule.
There's some big delivery coming up,
I think.
This was on Calvin's desk?
Yeah, why?
These are very large quantities.
This isn't just
local drug dealing.
This is...
These numbers...
I swear to you,
this is almost over.
But I need you to go home and
pretend like everything's okay.
Kurt, I can't do this much longer,
okay?
I'm scared all the time.
I know.
I will get you out of there.
I promise.
So, did you make me one?
I want you out of here.
This is my house and
you are not welcome.
That's cute, Calvin,
but it's a little
late to grow a pair.
How about you just shut the
fuck up and pour me a drink?
Fuck it. I'll do it myself.