Morning.
How are you today, Mr. Proctor?
That depends.
You brought me another head?
No.
Thinking I might leave with one,
though.
You killed my men.
You stole my drugs.
You know,
there's nothing more annoying
than an old guy thinking
he's still running things.
Bunker, you little shit.
I believe you know our
mutual friend Senator Mitchum.
Put that knife away before
I cut out your fucking eyes with it.
Mr. Mitchum,
what are you doing here, sir?
What am I doing here?
You murdered my fucking
lieutenant is what I'm doing here.
Sir, he was selling us out.
He was acting on orders.
You and Proctor?
Sir, I don't understand.
That's 'cause
you're a fucking idiot.
This little insurrection
stops here.
Do you hear me?
Yes, sir!
You have been
misled by this imbecile.
The minute he
killed one of our own,
you should have
torn him to pieces.
But maybe it's time to remind
you that the Brotherhood
goes way beyond Banshee,
Pennsylvania.
You're part of a
national movement,
one that not only
shares your beliefs,
but is willing to do
something about it.
This is Monty.
He's gonna be running
things from now on.
Make sure things go
smoothly from here on out.
You cannot come here...
Smartest thing for you to do
right now is shut the fuck up.
Do you hear me?
Your first and only priority
is Mr. Proctor's delivery.
Once that happens,
Monty will evaluate the chapter,
choose a new captain.
Any questions?
Okay, go on.
Get out of here.
Is he gonna be a problem?
You have my permission
to shoot him if he is.
I didn't think you'd come.
I wanted to make
sure I said good-bye.
Feels like that's pretty much what we do,
right?
Yeah,
it's kind of a bad habit, huh?
So, college.
Yeah.
I give it about three months.
With everything that's happened,
I just don't know how I can
possibly fit into someplace
as normal as college.
Ah, you're gonna do great.
I don't know.
I think normal might not
be in my repertoire anymore.
Hey,
you know what's great about being your age?
You got all the time in the
world to figure things out.
You do.
And you will.
You're strong, Deva.
You're a fighter.
Like your mother.
And your father.
You're gonna do great.
And now I'll always
know where to find you.
And will you? Find me?
Promise.
Good.
You might be a shitty father,
but you're the only one I got left.
So Declan believed that
the Devil spoke to him.
Satan did speak to him.
Okay. So you believed it, too.
Something that's true
doesn't require your belief.
Well,
I guess I can't argue with you there.
You need to understand
he didn't choose this.
He was chosen.
So how did he pick 'em?
He chose girls that
seemed to him to be pure.
He called them blessed.
Blessed girls.
Well, he did want to offer me
and I don't think he
thought I was blessed.
You were a surprise.
But I wasn't the only surprise,
was I?
What do you mean?
Well,
Declan was killing on a lunar cycle.
Not every month,
but always on a new moon.
- When the night is darkest.
- Right.
Except for...
Her.
She was killed on the 21st.
Not a new moon. Not a full moon.
Just an unremarkable night.
We had our reasons.
So you were in on it?
Of course I was.
We were in it together.
So, then, tell me,
why did you choose her?
Rebecca Bowman.
What was it about her
that made you and Declan
decide to break out
of the lunar cycle?
Was she a surprise, too?
I don't want to talk anymore.
- You did the final count?
- Yes.
- It's all there.
- Good.
Bring the truck to the designated
point and wait for my call.
We'll be ready.
Close the door.
We're set.
That is a lot of dead skinheads.
Looks like a bomb
went off in here.
Any idea where your brother is?
No.
Still looking.
You get the feeling
there's something
going on that we
don't know about?
- Excuse me.
- Yeah.
This is Bunker.
Proctor's deal of the
century is going down now.
This is a really bad time.
I'm sorry.
Should I try and stall the Colombian men
who just flew in
on a private jet?
Cartel?
That would be my
guess if I cared.
Jesus. Where are you?
I'm at the old
Municipal Airport.
All right, I'll meet you there.
Can I see that for a sec?
Mrs. Hopewell, I presume.
Brock?
Hey.
How's the interrogation going?
It's going.
You okay?
Uh, yeah. I'm just kind of
rolling through it, you know?
You made pretty good backup,
by the way.
Guess I always thought
you were my backup.
Yeah, no.
Well,
I just came to say good-bye.
Hey.
Declan Bode didn't kill Rebecca.
What?
Bode was killing
on a lunar cycle.
Now, Rebecca's killing stood out
because it wasn't on a new moon.
Now, I pressed Lilith about it,
and she made a bunch of noise,
but behind it all,
I don't think she
knew anything about it.
Well,
maybe Bode didn't tell her.
No, it doesn't make sense that
Bode would break his routine.
So, what, you're saying
there's someone else out there
killing girls and then
cutting out their hearts?
I'm telling you
that someone killed
Rebecca and made it
look like it was Bode.
They'd have to know details
about the other murders, right?
Mmm-hmm.
They haven't been released.
Right, so we're looking for
someone who had access to BSD files
and who's capable of a sadistic,
ritualistic murder like that.
- Oh, fuck.
- Can you think of anyone?
Hey,
maybe you should let me do the talking.
Sure.
They're not home.
Let's take a look around.
- Mr. Proctor.
- Senor Loera.
Good to see you again.
I must admit,
I'm a little surprised that
you were able to pull this off.
I don't promise
what I can't deliver.
Bring it up.
Show me.
Hi.
As long as we all
whipping our shit out...
Emilio Loera, I take it?
Who the fuck are you?
I'm nobody.
You know my name,
so you know who I am.
Which means you know what
kind of a mistake it would be
to try to steal from me, right?
I wouldn't dream
of stealing from you.
No, I came here to provide
you with a valuable service.
Oh, yeah?
Which is what?
I came to show you that
Mr. Proctor was mistaken
when he told you that
Banshee was a safe place
for you to set up
your manufacturing.
Very mistaken.
I mean,
if he had it so locked down,
how did I steal this truck
full of all these drugs?
- I'm gonna fucking slit your throat.
- Stop.
I suppose you have some
fee in mind for this service.
No. Sometimes a service
is its own reward.
Just let my friend and
me walk away right now,
and we'll call it even.
Start walking.
You're not just gonna
let her walk out of here?
Shut up.
Hey, Miss Nobody.
Did you really think that
I was gonna let you leave?
No, actually, I didn't.
That's right.
Someone just blew
up your fucking drugs.
Nice shot.
Thanks.
You know,
you really need to stop doing this shit.
- You invited yourself.
- I'm serious.
It's become like a
bad habit with you.
This was the last time.
I've heard that shit before.
This is a very nice car.
Son of a bitch!
Oh, come on.
No one really knows how to do that.
It's just a matter of
applying the right torque
and then a little
bit of scrubbing.
Toolshed.
Look at you.
If there's one thing
I've learned lately,
it's that there's
always a basement.
Right over here.
We got blood.
Yeah.
What do you think?
I think nothing good
happens in basements.
Jesus.
You find anything
else over there?
No.
No, nothing.
All right, well,
I say we head up.
I can get Forensics down
here in a couple hours.
I want to find out
whose blood that is.
Sure.
You mind if I don't
stick around for that?
I got to check in on someone.
You got to check in on someone?
Yeah.
Hey, you want or need company?
Not this time.
The cartel will come after you.
I know.
And what then?
There'll be time to negotiate.
But before then...
You.
That looks broken.
What the hell are you doing?
Ahh! What the fuck? Hey!
That's Rebecca's necklace.
Yes, it is.
I don't understand.
Bode didn't kill Rebecca.
You? You killed her?
I found this in your shed.
- You think I killed her?
- That's right.
Are you out of
your fucking mind?
I loved her.
I would have died for her.
Maybe you loved
her a little too much.
- What?
- And when you found out she was pregnant,
you realized you
couldn't control her again,
so you took her down in that
weird little dungeon of yours
and you butchered her.
What the hell are you talking about,
"dungeon"?
- You killed her.
- What the fuck are you talking about?
You found out she was
pregnant and you killed her!
No! No, I didn't!
I didn't kill her.
Shit.
What the fuck?
You son of a bitch.
He'll kill you for this.
And will you? Find me?
Promise.
Everything I did...
I did for you.
Untie me!
Untie me, you son of a bitch!
You're ruining him.
I can't let that happen anymore.
He loves me.
You don't understand.
Don't do this.
He doesn't see you,
but I do.
- I see you.
- Burton, please.
I see you!
Please.
I'm sorry.
I'm... I'm sorry.
I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
I'm sorry.
I'm... I'm...
It's okay.
- It's all right, Burton.
- I'm sorry.
It's all right.
Did you hear anything?
Nothing yet.
- Kurt.
- I know.
- Kurt!
- Oh, my God, Calvin.
Maggie, go inside.
So you and Maggie, huh?
I guess I should have
seen that coming.
She was always a
sucker for wounded birds.
Just walk away, Calvin.
No, I'm not going to walk away,
Kurt.
I can't.
I mean, a man can only take so much,
can only swallow so much shit
before the time comes to address it,
right?
I'm sorry.
I didn't expect this to happen.
You're sorry? You're sorry you
ever joined the Brotherhood?
You're sorry you
brought me into it?
You're sorry you fucked my wife?
You're just one sorry piece of shit,
aren't you?
I will shoot you.
Go ahead, Kurt.
Shoot me.
Then you get
Maggie free and clear.
You can move into my house,
raise my son.
Come on, Kurt.
Why build your own life
when you can just steal mine?
- Shut up.
- Shoot me.
- Shoot me!
Please just walk away.
Do it. Go ahead.
Ahh!
Motherfucker.
Give me that fucking gun.
God damn it.
Oh, shit.
Maggie!
There's nowhere you can go,
either of you.
I will find you and
I will make you pay!
Even if you lock me up,
the Brotherhood will hunt you down.
You know it.
They will slit your
throat in front of her
and then tear her ass to pieces.
There's nowhere you can
go that we won't find you.
I will kill my own son
before I let you raise him.
I'm gonna kill you, you bitch.
As long as I'm alive, I will...
Well, I should have known better
than to let you go off like that.
How'd your Forensics team do?
They found some skin samples.
Probably gonna match Proctor's.
It turns out it
wasn't actually him.
It was Burton.
Burton?
Yeah.
Guy with the glasses.
His butler or whatever.
The butler did it?
Seriously?
Well, I should probably go
arrest this butler Burton, no?
Right.
Should have guessed.
Then I guess my
job here is done.
Yeah, me, too.
Me, too.
It's about time I moved on.
It's been time a couple of times,
actually.
Well, if you're ever in D.C...
Look me up.
I will.
- Morning.
- Oh, thank God.
Real coffee.
Yes.
- How's Maggie doing?
- She's okay.
They'll be out of
your place by tonight.
No rush.
Let me see if
I got this straight.
Calvin got the jump on you,
beat the shit out of you,
then somewhere along the way,
you remember you got a gun
and you shoot him
from 20 feet away.
Is that it?
- Yeah.
- Bullshit.
Sir, I'm not sure what
you're trying to imply, but...
No, I'm not implying anything.
I'm saying it.
You beat the shit
out of Calvin,
and then you killed him
for good measure.
Hey, Bunker, relax.
It's just you and me talking here,
okay?
Come on, sit down.
I don't know what it is about this town,
Bunker.
What geographic phenomenon
makes us a magnet
for every scumbag and
criminal east of the Mississippi.
But what I do know
is that to do this job,
Sometimes, you've got to take
off these badges and get bloody.
It's happened before,
and it'll happen again.
And I got to know
that I can trust you.
And you can trust me.
You understand?
Yes, sir.
Good.
A little trust would
be nice around here.
Kurt Bunker,
that's your real name, right?
Just...
So what about Proctor?
You can place him at
the scene of the drug deal.
Yeah, we could arrest Proctor.
But I got a feeling
that the cartel's
gonna want a few words with him
about their dead men,
and when they come,
I'd just as soon
he's as far away
from the police
station as possible.
- If you take my meaning.
- That makes sense.
Time and experience, son.
Time and experience.
So, you go write up that
bullshit report so I can sign it.
Yes, sir.
Thank you, sir.
Thanks for the coffee.
Look at your face.
You just can't help yourself,
can you?
I gotta be me.
I know.
Max comes back tomorrow.
That's great.
Yes.
Job tells me you're
heading out to New York.
Yeah. Well, he is.
I'm gonna take the scenic route,
catch up with him.
Where are you headed?
I don't know. I'm gonna...
Hit the road and
see what happens.
You want to come?
Yeah.
You be careful.
I Will.
You know, the whole...
All those years in my cell,
you were always there with me.
I'm still there with you.
And I'll always be here.
No one else...
Nobody ever really knew me.
I know.
Please don't forget about me.
Never.
Good-bye, Ana.
It's Carrie.
This was a hard car to find.
Yeah, sorry.
I should have figured
that once I loaned it to you,
odds were that I wouldn't
be getting it back in one piece.
How you plan on
getting out of here?
Same way I came in.
It's gonna be mighty
quiet around here.
Don't even pretend like
you're gonna miss me.
I was talking to Hood.
You know,
I think I'm actually gonna miss this place.
I know I'm not.
Sugar,
it's been a thin slice of heaven.
I know you don't mean that.
It's true, I don't.
- You in a rush?
- Damn right.
Every time I try to get out
of this motherfucking place,
some shit goes down,
and I get stuck in it.
I'm getting while
the getting's good.
But before I do...
Figured I'd pay my tab.
Where the hell did you get this?
Now,
you know better than to ask.
Point is, you spent your
retirement fund getting me out.
Well, you're too old to be
slinging drinks, so...
Thank you.
You know how to reach me?
No one knows how to reach you.
- He does.
- Yeah, I do.
This is where I leave you.
Banshee, Pennsylvania.
Suck my tit.
What?
I was just remembering the
first time you walked in here.
I never could have imagined.
You know,
some might say you weren't all that bad
at that whole sheriff thing.
Yeah, and other people might say
I was the worst fucking thing
that ever happened to this town.
You got a place to stay?
Putting that badge
on the way you did,
I never thought you'd
be walking out of here
on your own two feet.
Neither did I.
You know,
I probably wouldn't if it wasn't for you.
You know you hid
up on that mountain
because you felt the need
to atone for something.
And for all we know,
you'd still be there
if Brock hadn't come
and pulled you down.
We are cons.
We're made to believe
that you pay for your sins
by getting locked up.
But maybe the way to redemption
isn't hiding on the mountain.
Maybe it's about
choosing another road
down here with the rest of us.
Maybe.
The past has kept you
locked up long enough.
Today, there's really only one
question left to ask yourself.
What are you going to do now?