Is the sheriff in?
Sheriff Lotus is in a meeting.
Can I help you?
I have information
he needs to hear.
Can I help you, ma'am?
He wants you to
know he won't stop.
Taking those girls
was just the beginning.
- What is this?
- He wants you to see.
You will all see.
What the hell are you doing?
Don't! No!
Don't do it!
Calvin.
Where have you been?
What happened to you?
Is that blood?
- Calvin...
- Quiet.
Stop, please. Stop.
What the fuck is wrong with you?
Nothing, just not so rough.
- Please.
- Jesus.
Wait a second.
Are you screwing somebody else?
What? No.
Of course not.
We haven't fucked in months.
What is it?
You just...
You scared me.
What happened to you?
What's going on?
Oh, God, Calvin.
Calvin!
Shower's all yours.
Help yourself.
Not really my thing.
You know,
I started out an undercover.
Pretty white chicks have to go a
little bit further to
prove themselves.
So it was either fuck
'em or smoke their shit.
Sometimes it was both.
You don't have to
explain yourself to me.
I've been meaning to kick it.
But when you spend your
days up to your neck in this shit,
sometimes I got to
get out of my own head.
Do I need to worry about you?
No.
Might be nice if you did.
Wow, you, my friend,
have some intimacy issues.
Thanks for letting me crash.
Could have shared the bed.
Just saying.
Who the fuck are you?
Maggie.
Kurt.
What's wrong?
- It's...
- You want to sit for a second?
No, I don't want to sit.
Helen,
you think you could get Hank here
one of those snacks
that you keep upstairs?
Sure.
Hi, Hank.
Want to come with me?
Thank you.
Come here.
What happened?
Did he hurt you'?
That motherfucker.
I left.
I couldn't be in that
house another second.
- He let you leave?
- He doesn't know.
I just grabbed Hank
and packed things and...
I don't even know where I'm going,
Kurt.
- You'll stay with me.
- I can't.
That's the first place
he's gonna come look.
Not if I find him first.
No.
No, I have to think about Hank.
Kurt,
I think he killed my father.
Randall's dead?
I don't know.
They left together and then Calvin...
And he was covered in blood.
And then he...
It was terrifying.
Okay. Shh.
It's okay.
That's my mother's sweater?
It is.
She never wears it.
- Looks good on you.
- Most things do.
You best clean that glass up
before your mother gets home.
Yeah, I'll get right on that.
So how do you fit into
this whole shit show'?
Your mother and your
father and I go way back.
Yeah? Which father?
The one that gave
you that smart mouth.
Got it.
So is she Carrie or Ana to you?
There weren't no Carrie
before I invented her.
Well,
I can use a shiny new life myself.
You wanna hook me up?
I figure you owe me.
Ain't you the fucked-up
little delinquent?
Hey, I'm just trying to play
the shitty hand I was dealt.
Girl, what you were dealt
were two parents who
would kill or die for you.
That's a hell of a lot
more than most people got.
Deva.
What are you doing here?
Missed you, too, Mom.
I'm just surprised to see you.
You changed the
locks on the door again.
Sorry, I should have told you.
- Does Grandma know you're here'?
- I left her a note.
I really don't think
they'll miss me.
- Deva.
- I'm not going back, Mom.
There's no Wi-Fi and
it smells like ass there.
- Honey, if the court finds out...
- They won't.
- I know I can keep a secret.
- You stay out of this.
If it makes it any easier,
you really don't have a choice.
All right,
so why don't we just arrest Calvin?
She'll never
testify against him.
She's terrified.
She thinks Calvin
killed her father.
Does Calvin know'?
- Does Calvin know what?
- About you two.
- No.
- You sure?
- Yeah.
- 'Cause you didn't think I could tell,
and it took me all of
about 10 seconds to see it.
Now, granted,
I'm a smarter-than-average cop
And he's a
hatemongering asshole...
Calvin doesn't know.
They can stay at my place.
- Really?
- Yeah.
Just until you find a way
to take your brother down.
- Thank you.
- You're welcome.
Hey, you okay, by the way?
This morning, the burning.
Must have hit
pretty close to home.
Yeah, I'm fine.
Can't get that smell
out of my head.
It takes a while.
- Can I help you?
- I highly doubt it.
You can't go back there.
- You can't go back there.
- I know.
That's the swelling, babe.
They'll soften up...
- Sweet Jesus.
- Hey, hey, hey, you can't be in here.
And yet I am. FBI.
Honey, get out of here.
Dr. David Quick.
I have been looking for you.
What's up, Doc?
Why don't you take a seat?
Should we try that again?
Performing breast
augmentation after
being stripped of
your medical license,
now, that's a felony.
We don't perform
any procedures here.
Tiffany is a friend of mine.
She asked me to look at her boob job,
that's all.
- Mmm, so, Why'd you run?
- I don't like cops.
Hey, you can't go in there,
buddy.
You got a warrant?
I don't need one.
I'm not a cop.
Yeah, look,
we can go clown that road,
but ifs tangled and boring and,
in the end, you'll still lose.
Or you can answer a few
questions and I'll forget we ever met.
Over here.
Okay.
- What do you wanna know?
- Body modifications.
What about it?
- You do it?
- Now and then. It's a growing field.
So,
you must do some pretty fucked-up shit.
Not as fucked up as
the shit I turn down.
You wouldn't believe the
kind of things people want.
Hey, Jesus, man!
Shit's expensive.
I'm looking for a guy
with horn implants.
- You ever do anything like that?
- Yeah.
Well,
then whip out your files, Doc.
We don't keep files
on that kind of stuff.
I can't imagine devil
horns is a common request.
They're more
common than you think.
It's Satan's country out here.
Yeah, but still it's pretty unique,
even for a guy like you.
Who was the last guy you did?
I'm sure you remember something.
The kind of people
who want this shit,
they're not exactly
model citizens.
I take cash in advance.
I don't even ask their names.
How convenient for you.
This is bullshit.
I'm gonna call my lawyer.
Let's go.
He doesn't know anything.
This has not been a satisfying
conversation for me, Dr. Quick.
If I were you, I'd call me.
Thank you.
Hey,
I barely started working that guy.
He wasn't gonna talk.
This might help.
- That was on his desk.
- Mmm-hmm.
You, my friend,
have some serious skills.
He was watching you the whole time,
so was I.
- How'd you do it?
- That's the trick, isn't it'?
Just when I thought
I'd seen it all.
Wow, amazing what low
self-esteem can do to a sociopath.
Mmm.
I've been trying to reach you.
I've been busy.
Do we have a problem,
Deputy Cruz?
Not at all.
But speaking of problems,
remember that matter
you asked me to look into?
- Yeah.
- I looked into it.
You found him?
No, I found her.
Exhibit number four was also
turned in to our hearing officer
five days before
this trial began.
Now, if it pleases the court,
you'll note that the photograph
shows the remnants of
a crushed back side door.
This photograph was
taken at the scene...
Mrs. Hopewell.
Of a hit-and-run
five months back
at the intersection
of Highway 6...
I'm seeing you around the
courthouse quite often these days.
Taking an interest in the law?
You could say that.
You know, I never really had the
chance to offer my condolences
for the loss of your husband.
You hated Gordon.
No, I didn't hate him.
I respected him.
Never took it personally.
I'd like to think he didn't either.
He did.
Ah.
Well, either way,
I was very sorry to hear about it.
I'm sorry about your niece.
We both suffered a great loss.
You know, sometimes a loss
like that clouds the judgment.
Makes us do things impulsively.
Things we might regret.
Do you know what I mean?
No, not really.
No? Well, I'd watch out for it.
You still have so much to lose.
I guess we all do.
I suppose we both
should be more careful.
Remember me, sunshine?
Yeah, the bitch who didn't know
when to stop asking questions.
Ah, you remembered.
I'm so flattered.
I'm also the bitch
with the badge.
Did I not mention
that the other day?
- I don't want any trouble, all right?
- Now, that's the spirit.
We're looking for a
guy with devil horns.
- You got people like that in here?
- Yeah, body mods.
Right, well,
this guy is killing girls.
Why don't you scroll through here,
see if you recognize anyone?
Look, most of the so-called
Satanists that come
in here are tourists.
They're assholes
looking to be more
edgier and badass
than they really are.
With the exception of this guy.
Who's this?
That's Bode. Declan Bode.
He's a hardcore ritualist.
- Does he come here often?
- No, he used to a while back.
Feeling people out.
Maybe looking for followers. I don't know.
Nobody took to the guy,
'cause he was a little too committed.
So, you're talking about a guy
who was so twisted he
creeped out other Satanists?
- Got it.
- Where do we find him?
Fuck if I know.
You knew his name.
Yeah,
and that's all I'm telling you, cop.
- Where do we fucking find him?
- I don't fucking know, man.
- Where?
- I don't fucking know!
The fucking guy thinks the
devil works through him, all right'?
One night the
freak comes in here,
starts spouting off about
how he's talking to Lucifer.
I tell him he's full of shit.
Guy takes the paring
knife out of my hand,
starts peeling back his
fingernails one by one,
smiling the whole time.
Then he orders a drink.
Who the fuck does that?
Someone we should meet.
See?
When we're helping, we're happy.
Yeah? Well, that's interesting.
Okay.
All right, thanks.
I'll call you back.
Our boy Declan Bode doesn't
have much of a footprint.
No known address. No relatives.
But he does have a prior.
He was convicted of statutory
rape 15 years ago next county over.
- Girl's name is sealed.
- Can we get it unsealed?
Yes,
but I will need a court order,
which won't happen
until tomorrow.
Oh, Jesus Christ.
Don't you have any
judges you can wake up?
It might surprise you to learn
I'm not very popular
among the federal judges.
All right,
so what do we do now?
Now we wait.
Just wait?
Yeah.
Great.
You're not built for downtime,
are you?
The way you move,
the way you pace,
the way you want
to push through every
wall without even
looking for the door
or the key to that door.
You have a point?
That's not the
temperament of a man who
worked his way up
through law enforcement.
Put my feet to the fire,
I'd say you're more criminal than cop.
You don't know me.
I know you can't sit still.
I'm guessing you
were once made to
for a very long time
and you didn't like it.
You check the comers
every time you enter a room.
That's not police training.
That's survival.
Your demeanor towards
me is complicated.
You have trouble
making eye contact.
It's not lack of confidence.
You've got a secret.
Or secrets.
Maybe I just don't like you.
But you do.
Don't you?
Wow.
You think you know me?
Let me tell you something.
You have no fucking idea.
Yeah, I check the corners,
because for as long as I can remember,
there's always been someone
waiting there to get the jump on me.
And I don't stay still,
'cause every time
I do,
someone close to me fucking dies!
I'm sorry.
No, you're not.
No, I'm not.
It's nothing.
Hey.
What is it?
I'm sorry.
There is a serial
killer out there...
- It's terrifying.
- I know, baby. I know.
- I'll take patrol.
- It's my shift.
No, I'm pulling rank.
I've got to get out of this zoo.
Okay.
Someone there?
Shit.
Burning the midnight oil, I see.
This is not the place to talk business,
Calvin.
That's fine because we no longer
have any business to discuss.
The Brotherhood no
longer works for you.
- Is that so?
- Yes, that is so.
Well, that's unfortunate.
Not from where I'm sitting.
I can't help but wonder what
Watts will think about this.
Well, why don't we ask him?
What do you think, Randall?
Seems the cat got Watts' tongue.
That's a bold choice.
Yeah.
I thought you'd like that.
So here's how it's gonna work.
Everything that's
yours is now ours.
Warehouses, shipments,
buyers, I fucking want all of it.
You can go quietly
or you can go bloody,
but either way, you are gone.
You can keep the
head as a souvenir.
Hi.
I saw you on TV.
I didn't ask for this.
He chose me.
Do you understand?
You can't stop me.
I've been delivered.
To feed the beast,
I've become something different,
something more.
And you... You're a bug.
A tiny worthless insect
in the face of his power.
Fuck you.
Close your eyes, cop.
Close your eyes.
Cherish the darkness,
for soon you will bear
witness to his plan.
And only then will I take
your miserable little life.
Where are they, Kurt?
Get the fuck off my property.
Where's my wife?
She's somewhere safe.
She'll call you when she's ready.
You are fucking with my family,
Kurt.
My wife, my son.
Do you have any idea what I
will fucking do to you for that?
Where's Watts?
Watts is dead.
Where's Maggie?
She doesn't want to see you.
Fuck you.
You don't get to fucking tell me that.
I just did.
I'm going into my house.
In two minutes,
if you're still here,
I'll come back out.
Trust me,
you don't want me to come back out.
Kurt.
Do you remember,
Dad used to take us to
the dogfights when
we were in Vandergrift?
Yeah.
Remember, I'd once asked him
if the matches
ever ended in a tie.
And he laughed at me
and he said,
"There's only ever one
way that a dogfight ends."
You remember that?
I remember.
There's only one way, Kurt.
I know.
Deva!
- Are you hurt?
- No.
Come on, Come on.
Get out there, Get on the roof.
- What?
- Go, go, go!
Here, take this. Safety's off.
Two hands. Point and squeeze.
Find a place to hide, wait.
You stay safe.
Go.
Now!
No.
I am sick and tired...
of fighting for my
motherfucking life.
Ah!
Damn.
Where's Deva?
Are you hurt?
Give me this.
I'm sorry.
Deva.
Whoa, whoa, whoa.
Slow down. Slow down.
You okay? You hurt?
Okay.
I just wanna go home.
I know.
The thing is,
I don't know where that is.
Come here.
Underwood,
tell me you have something.
The judge unsealed the file.
The victim on that statutory
rape is a Kim Newton.
She still lives in the area.
- You got an address?
- Just emailed it to you.
You're the best. I owe you.
You owe me many.
What is it with
this fucking town?
Can't we go one
week without some
motherfucking
army shooting at us?
Seems like you handled it fine.
That's because it's already
become a motherfucking habit.
Thank you.
Baby,
there's a whole world out there.
So they tell me.
What the fuck happened here?
Proctor.
What are you doing
messing with him?
Are you kidding me?
You don't get to
walk into my life
every few years and question me.
Hey, hey,
Deva could have been fucking killed.
Get out of here.
- Come on, Ana.
- Get the fuck out of here!
Who the fuck do you think
you are saying that shit to me?
You don't think I don't know
what could have happened to her?
I don't know what...
Shh. Hey, hey, stop.
It's okay.
Hello. Can I help you?
Kim Newton?
Yes.
My parents were the
ones that called the police.
I was 15, Declan, he was 25.
I was a quiet girl.
I didn't have many friends in school.
Always the kid in the back row.
Nobody really paid
any attention to me.
And then I met Declan.
He told me I was beautiful
and I could tell he meant it.
I had never even
been kissed before,
and here was this
handsome older guy
falling head over
heels in love with me.
And I understand now that I
was young and impressionable
and he manipulated me,
but, you know...
I still think he loved me
and I know I loved him. Mmm.
So what happened?
My dad found out.
He wanted to go after
Declan with a tire iron,
but my mother convinced
him to call the police instead.
Oh, I cried for days.
And the sex?
Was it perverse in any way?
It was intense, but, no,
I wouldn't say it was perverse.
Is Declan in some
kind of trouble?
He's a person of interest.
When was the last
time you spoke to him?
The night he was arrested.
After that,
I never saw him again.
It's a nice piece of
property you have.
Oh, thanks.
My parents left it to me.
Well, if you think of anything else,
give me a call.
- Thanks for your time.
- Yeah.
Hey, it's Veronica.
You disappeared
on me this morning.
But, anyway,
I tracked down our statutory rape victim.
She said all the right things,
but my bullshit meter is ringing.
Anyway,
I'm going back to the hotel,
so call me and I'll
fill you in on my...
Oh, shit.
I heard you were looking for me.