Hello, my name is Oscar. I'm an
accountant in Scranton, Pennsylvania
and I am gay.
And I'm here to tell you
that, yes, it does get better.
When I was younger...
What? What's he doing?
He's searching out
younger gays.
No, it's just a way
to tell young people
no matter how hard
it gets for them
there's a brighter
future ahead.
With you.
No matter how hard it gets
for you... Kelly, seriously, I...
Just keep chatting. I'm just
checking my makeup in your webcam.
Do you not own a mirror?
Webcams make me look
the way I look in my fantasies.
I know, right? What is it? You
always look so good in those things.
I'm throwing out
all my mirrors.
Okay, as you can see,
I now have a cool job
at a dynamic workplace.
Being gay is a celebration
of life. It's a simple...
I'm sorry. I just
can't sit idly by
and have
the gay youth of America
misled by
some reductionist...
I'm not misleading.
...pep talk.
Sexuality is a spectrum.
It's a paradox to think of
any sexual activity as normal.
It gets better, but it also
gets vastly more complicated.
Hey, Robert? That guy,
he looks just like you.
Damn it! Kevin. God!
You okay, Robert?
I'm fine.
Put some ice on it.
In any case,
it gets better.
Maybe not much better,
but better.
It hurts.
One, two, three.
I wanted to give a nice
gift to the tenants in the building.
At first I thought,
"Muffin basket.”
Then I thought, "What's even more
precious to people than muffins?”
Can you just
smile, please?
I don't want to!
Their own children.
Hey, everybody.
Just a few hours left for
the free family portrait studio.
Darryl, we'd love to see
little Jada come by.
Angela, why don't you
bring by your little angel?
No, thank you.
Jim, you've got
those two cute kids.
We sure would
love to see them.
I know why you're
doing this, Dwight.
Last week, I may
have gone too far.
I'll explain it quickly.
Basically I found out where
he gets his clothes dry-cleaned,
custom-ordered the same
suit made with tear-away Velcro
and you can
fill in the rest.
What?
Damn it, Jim!
Now he's trying to get me to
bring my children into work.
I think it's fair
to be cautious.
Let me get this straight,
you lost all of it?
All your winnings,
$150,0007
You mean to tell me
no one wanted
an energy drink
for Asian homosexuals?
They did not.
You've got
half-a-million of these?
Well, I've got to try it.
I wouldn't.
Oh, come on.
What's the harm?
Hmm.
What flavor is that?
The coconut's pretty subtle.
Come on, man. Can you
just give us a yes or a no?
I don't know, man. You all
quit with a lot of confidence.
I mean, you all came up in here
dancing and everybody was...
Ooh! Hold on a second.
If I were Val, I would
break up with Brandon.
Then I would date
the hell out of me.
I wouldn't give in
to me too fast,
let me buy myself some
nice dinners and such.
When I finally did give in,
I would go crazy on myself.
Hi, guys.
How's it going, man?
I'm... I'm good.
Thank you. How are you?
Great, yeah. Good.
Oh, how the mediocre
have fallen.
Oh, God.
Look, I'm not here
to get my old job back.
I had my opportunity,
I blew it.
I'm moving on.
Just wanted to come in here
and literally beg you
for something, anything.
I will sweep the floors,
water the plants.
No, you don't...
Clean the toilets.
I don't need anyone... Pull
the poop out of the toilets.
Not even a thing.
Just please...
Andy. Andy.
Please give me something.
Why don't you clean
the carpets for today?
Thank you.
Well, you're...
Up you get, then.
Pick yourself up.
There it is.
Thank you.
You don't need to.
I have a delicious secret.
Good, good. This carpet's
overdue for a good mopping.
Is a mop the most efficient
tool to use on a carpet?
Yeah, it is, actually.
I can't hold
it in any longer.
I am faking this, okay?
Because I convinced
David Wallace
to buy Dunder Mifflin
back from Sabre
and at 3.00 today he's
going to walk in here
and reinstate me
as manager.
Family picture.
Pam. No.
What? Honey, we talked
about this.
No, we talked about
not bringing them
into Dwight's photo
studio/trap.
Yes, and then we decided
that was crazy.
No, we decided it was
crazy not to worry about it.
No, we settled in a
much more rational place,
remember?
No.
We decided that there's no
way Dwight would harm a child.
But are you 100% sure?
I don't think any of us are.
No, no.
Nope.
But it's free and we'll
keep our eye on them.
Yes.
Yes, that's...
And we will make sure that
Dwight doesn't do anything...
Okay.
...C-R-A-Z-Y.
Wait. C-R-A-Z...
Great, right up there.
Yeah.
You sit right here,
one time.
There you go.
Okay.
All right, why don't you
just give him to me?
Oh, great. Thank you.
Perfect.
This is great, excuse me.
You ready? There you go.
Okay.
All right, let's do it.
I'll just stand here then.
Yeah, just keep your eye
on Dwight. Okay, yeah.
Sir, could you
look into the camera?
Let's do it.
Shoot it. Great.
Sir.
Up here.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Jim, right here, right
here. Okay. Good.
Oh, so that's it?
That's it.
See, that wasn't so hard.
Cute kids.
Thanks for coming.
Hello, Erin.
Hello, everybody.
What, why? Hi, honey.
What... How are you doing?
You know,
my office got a call
that they were shooting
family portraits right here.
And if there's one thing every
politician instinctively understands,
it's a good photo op.
Okay, you're going to go
through the hallway.
Here's a map. And if you get
lost just follow the blue line.
Thanks.
Well, well, well,
Senator Lipton. Welcome.
Angela.
Dwight.
Nice to see you.
May I hold him?
Sure.
No. I am going to hold him
because I haven't seen him all day.
I think that Dwight
is doing this whole thing
to get a sample
of my baby's DNA
to prove he's the father.
Which is impossible.
Because the Senator is the
only man I've ever been with.
Did you see that?
What do you think
about that? See?
See that ducky?
Okay, hold on
a second, folks.
A few of the baby's hairs
are out of place.
Oh, thank you.
No, no, no.
I like the baby's hair
the way it is.
Really?
This is getting more and
more delicious by the minute.
It's go time.
Hey, Nellie.
I made... I made you...
I made you some soup.
Well, I don't
want any soup.
But it's really good.
Oh! Come on, Andy.
Ah.
I know this is going
to be a great payoff.
A delicious moment.
But after you're manager,
some of these images are
going to be hard to shake.
Well, but it's...
Just calibrate.
Okay? Calibrate.
Okay, here we go.
Oh, you know what? I don't want
to throw a wrench into the works,
but I want everything
to be perfect
and the baby's fingernails
are just bothering me.
Uh-uh. Leave us alone.
I guess we're okay
with the fingernails.
Okay, great.
Suit yourself.
Although,
aren't those
excess skin cells
in the baby's cheek
distracting to you as well?
Dwight! We're fine.
Oopsie! Did somebody
make a poopsie?
I'm just going to take
him out and change him
just for a second here.
He defecated.
Ooh!
Oh!
Stinky.
A lot has changed
since you all left, okay?
You're going to have to
jump through some hoops.
And the new foreman is here.
Now, she's one of the best
we've ever known, okay?
So I need you to show her
your utmost respect.
Make sure that
she feels welcome
and at home, okay?
Can you do that?
That's some pretty blatant
complimenting you're doing there, man.
I don't even talk to her
like that. - Uh, Brandon.
I would.
You would?
Yeah.
Sounds like you're trying
to hit on my girlfriend.
Calm down. He's not.
Yes, I am.
Just so everyone's
on the same page.
So you really
think she's going to
leave a guy who owns
his own restaurant
for a dude who ate his
own restaurant? Brandon.
Good slam.
Thank you, Biggie.
Good luck to you.
Oh, and have
a burger for me.
Okay, shall we
take a few more?
I think we have all the shots
we need. Thank you, Dwight.
Okay, here we go.
Yes, here we go.
No, Dwight! Give
me the diaper! Dwight!
Is this what
you were looking for?
Huh? Huh?
Andy, we wanted
to talk to you.
A lot of us are very
concerned about you.
You're dirty, you stink of
booze, you're limping inexplicably.
I just want you guys
not to worry
because old Andy's
going to be just fine.
No, no, no, see, this is
what we're talking about.
I mean, what was
that accent?
And last time I checked you were
drunk and now you're not drunk.
No, unfortunately,
it's true.
He's been a nightmare
and the worst part is he's
been taking it out on me.
- You hit her?
- What?
No, no!
That is not the deal.
Calibrate.
He's not hitting me, but he's
been verbally abusing me.
That is
not true, either!
That's also total... Everyone please relax.
I think you're going to
like this surprise guest.
Happy birthday to Gabe.
Oh, get out,
Skeleton Man.
I can refer you to
someone to talk to.
Huh?
I can give you a name.
Hold on.
I'm just going to... Hello?
Hey, what's the scoop?
Are you close?
What? No, no, no, no, no,
no, no. You have to come now.
Traffic clears.
No, next Friday.
That's not going to work.
Okay, yeah, okay.
Damn it.
Well, this is not going to be
quite as delicious as I wanted,
but I do have a very tasty
announcement for you guys.
Not only am I not
a lowly janitor,
I am the regional manager
once again.
Guys, I got
my old job back.
Oh, boy.
Oh, Andy.
I'm not crazy. I convinced David
Wallace to give me my job back.
David Wallace hasn't
worked here in years.
Okay, yes,
I see the confusion.
I saw David
at the fundraiser.
He is now
a multi-millionaire
because he sold
his toy vacuum "Suck It"
to the U.S. Military.
Andy, come on, man.
I... Okay, I get how
that sounds crazy.
Andy, nobody's calling
you crazy, Andy.
We're your friends, Andy.
Stop saying my name.
No, he's not making
this up. Thank you, Erin.
Andy tells me about seeing
David Wallace all the time.
But have you ever
actually seen him yourself?
Oh, my God. Wait.
Erin, come... Come on.
You know I've been
talking to David Wallace.
Do you see David Wallace
in the room right now?
Operation Phoenix is a go.
Just get the car ready.
Okay, you look at me
like you're adoring me
and I'm going to
look at the camera
like I don't even
know you're there.
But I do adore you.
Andrew, it's time
for you to go home.
You're better than this.
Yeah, I know.
Everyone is
better than this.
Because this is the worst
thing I have ever seen.
Why did they add coconut?
I miss original.
- Hey.
- Hey, guys.
- Hey!
Hey, guys, long time.
David, what are
you doing here?
Is it true you're
buying the company?
Okay, I guess
the word is out.
Please keep this a secret, but
yes, I've been talking with Andy.
What? I thought
I heard my name. What?
I'm the new manager?
I'll get to that
in a second, Andy.
But it's...
It is me? Right?
Yes,
as we discussed.
What?
Oh, my God!
It's very possible...
Probable.
Wow. From janitor
to manager?
Yep.
It's quite a Cinderella
story. From M-O-P to MVP.
There's an official
announcement. A few details...
From total loss
to total boss. I mean...
Can we expect
any payroll interruptions?
Now that is
a great question, Stanley.
Right now I think
all your operations,
or most of your operations
are pretty much down in Florida,
so the shift back...
I was so looking forward
to that and it did not go
as I thought it would.
So we're not going to be
a part of Sabre anymore?
Actually nothing is going to
be a part of Sabre anymore.
Jo Bennett's planning on
liquidating the rest of the company.
Oof!
Wouldn't want to be a Sabre
employee right about now.
I'm actually the CEO.
Ah!
I didn't realize
you were standing there.
Hey, my friend, trust me.
This is for the best. I never
understood that corporate mess.
Well, okay.
Well, great to meet you.
Likewise, I'm Bob,
Bob Kazamakis.
Pleasure.
I'd love to give you
a little rundown
on what I've learned
about this place.
That's very
gracious of you, Bob.
I would love that.
Please.
I guess I better
take off these dirty rags
and figure out how to be
a manager of this place.
Perhaps your
year of experience
managing this branch
will come in handy.
Gosh, I hope so.
No! God, Mose. God!
Hi, Angela.
Get out of the car!
Get out!
Where is he? Where is he?
I'm not supposed to say.
Yes, tell me!
Tell me where he is!
Mose! Damn it!
Where did he go?
Mose, get back here!
See that smile.
Jump in here.
Come on.
Looks like I might get my
delicious moment after all.
May I say one thing?
It would be rude of me not to let
you say whatever's on your mind.
"The quality of mercy
is not strained."
No.
"It dropeth as the gentle rain from
heaven upon the place beneath."
Do not bring Shakespeare
into this.
How dare you play
the "Bard Card."
"It blesseth he who gives
and he who takes.
"'Tis mightiest
in the mightiest."
I just want one mother
delicious moment.
Is that too much to ask?
If I were to
hire you back, if,
what do you think
you would do well?
Special projects manager.
That's my background.
I just go around
doing whatever I want.
All right, you sly bastard,
when can you start?
Okay, everyone.
I had a conversation
with Bob
and since I am going to be CEO
now, there'll be no need for him.
Ouch! That's got to hurt!
But he is going to make so
much money from the liquidation,
he's going to be
freed up to do
something much
more important. What?
David has generously offered to
donate $1,000,000 in matching funds
to a cause
that's very dear to me.
So for the next three years,
I'll be traveling overseas,
concentrating all of my
efforts on educating, mentoring,
some African, some Asian, but
mainly Eastern European women.
I had no idea
how pervasive
this problem was until
Bob explained it to me.
Oprah Winfrey's
Leadership Academy,
and other schools like it, while
wonderful, end with high school.
I want to see these girls
right through college.
Especially the gymnasts.
They've lost so many years
of crucial education
to perfecting their bodies.
Muscle groups the rest
of us can't even fathom.
Gymnasts? You're going to
seek out uneducated gymnasts?
Yeah. So I'm hoping to identify
some truly exceptional women
who show great promise.
Well, Andy, it's been fun.
Hmm.
It's been a great year.
Hello.
Where is it?
They're testing it now.
How long does it take
to get the results?
Seventy-two hours.
You're going to wait here?
Yes.
Dwight, I can't do this.
Dwight!
Senator Lipton.
Hey.
Hey, how are you?
You didn't call.
Um...
Well, the issue
that concerned me...
You know what
this is about.
Call.