No you'll not take her.
Emily is not here, okay.
He has her.
Legally, you can't be here.
You can't change the way things
are
what's winsford?
He never told you
about the second home.
I swear to god,
if this is a trick.
You forced me when you
said that you'd take Emily.
Dr. Morgan,
please come to the front desk.
Dr. Morgan to the front desk
please.
Three miscarriages,
three failed attempts at ivf,
countless clinics and all the
medication.
And I did that.
And no, no, no, I know
what you're gonna say,
it's not my fault,
so we thought about adoption.
It wouldn't be your child.
Exactly.
A lot of men feel that way.
I mean, women too.
Well, Jen would be fine with
adoption.
We did try a surrogate.
- Right.
- In america.
A hundred grand...
They disappeared.
I know we need to stop, but...
You can't let this go?
I don't know what to do,
Jack, can I offer you a
solution?
Yes, please.
So, from what you've told me,
Jen is at the end of
her fertility journey,
you can't have a family with
her.
But you do have choices.
You can choose to let this go,
this idea of what a family
should be.
It sounds as if you have
a wife who loves you very much.
She could be your family.
Or...
Do you want to start over...
With someone else?
Because if you need to do that,
then I want you to.
Okay?
It costs me saying that.
But we've been to hell
and back enough times now
to know that the truth
has to be faced eventually.
It's your life too, Jack,
you deserve to be happy.
You can't stay with me
just because you promised to.
I don't want that.
That's not love.
Love has to be selfish.
And if it's not, then...
It's something else entirely.
All I ever wanted was
just a family with you.
That's all.
Oh shit.
Are you okay?
Can you hear me?
Yeah.
It sounds as if you have a wife
she could be your family.
Or...
Or I start again, with someone
else.
Jack.
Jack. Jack.
What the hell are you doing?
- You can't go in there.
- Is she's bleeding?
- Does she need an ambulance?
- She'll hurt you.
She hates you, Jen.
She doesn't.
Do you really think
I'd do something like that
unless I absolutely had to.
Do you, Jen?
Why did you bring her here?
She wanted to see her daughter.
- See her, to just see her?
- Yeah.
Is that what she told you?
No, okay, she was gonna take
her Jack,
but she promised, she
promised me.
It's what she does, she lies
all the time.
If she takes Emily now,
I'll never see my daughter
again, do you understand?
Now I need you to take Emily
somewhere safe, all right,
somewhere she can't get to her.
Jack.
What are you gonna do?
Make her an offer.
Money?
She's not gonna take money.
She already has, Jen.
I paid off her debt,
I moved her into the house,
I married her.
And now she's weaponizing Emily
and...
So what, you've been giving her
money?
And now what,
you're just gonna pay her off?
And what if she won't go?
She'll go.
What the hell happened, Jack?
Where is she?
Jack, where's Tasha?
I don't know,
I don't know where she is.
She hit me and she ran, all
right.
What did you do?
What did I do?
What exactly do you think I
did, huh?
She hit me and she ran
and pushed me in
a six foot concrete hole, Jen.
And you're asking if she's okay.
Jesus f...
I don't think you understand
what happened.
She did this and she left me
for dead, all right.
Well then, you have to call the
police.
You have to call them.
No, no.
Fine, then I will.
No, Jen she'll twist this.
She'll twist it and then it'll
be her word
and even... even you don't
believe me.
So we have to leave first thing
in the morning, all right.
I'm sorry, but I have got
myself involved
yeah. This is your wife
you're talking about.
I'm well aware of that
and that's why we have to go.
What are you talking about?
You and me, go where?
It's always been about you and
me.
I don't understand.
I wanted this.
This is what I want.
I want you.
Tell me you want me too.
New contract's in Toronto,
what if Tasha goes to the
police?
She left me for dead, Jen,
she's not going to the police.
So if we go to Toronto,
custody stays with me,
okay, you get us on a flight
tomorrow night.
Right?
And then once we're there, the
new company
the accommodation,
our feet?
Yeah.
I mean, you've had time
to think about this, but...
I just can't help
but think that this is.
Reactive.
Yes.
It is.
Look, I don't want to stay here
and fight this out.
I don't want to put Emily
through that.
Tasha's made it perfectly clear
that she will stop at nothing
until she gets what she wants.
I need you with me.
I do, I need you.
You kept my name.
So tomorrow night,
to their new life.
We pretend she's mine.
And Tasha?
And throws herself from one
thing
So you never even loved her?
Your marriage, it was all
just...
I mean, how could you have been
so sure
that I would still be here
at the end of all of...?
Why do you think I kept you so
close?
I love you so much.
Right.
I'll be back tonight.
I need to get everything sorted.
Oh... hi.
Tasha, what the fuck, are you
all right?
I'm fine.
God no, it's just a cut.
I'm fine, I'm not in pain.
Okay well, we need to
at least go back to mine.
I need to go back to winsford.
- I left.
- No, no.
Listen, we're not going back to
winsford.
This is fucked up, look what
he's done to your neck.
It doesn't matter. If he's
alive, I'm never
he'll find a way,
and if he's dead...
Just... just get in the car.
We need to find Emily.
So he's not at home or at Jen's.
Have you had any luck finding
anything?
I've called all the hospitals.
- Yeah, and...?
- Nothing.
So now what?
If he hasn't reported me,
he's up to something else.
We have to find her soon, or...
Or what?
What can we do?
Jen...
You told me we can't
change the way things are
through sheer willpower...
But it's not true.
I don't know where Emily
and Jack are,
but you do
you have that choice.
He was manipulating everything.
I hope you can see that.
So please do the right thing
and bring her back to me.
I need my baby.
And I promise you,
when you do, I'll be gone.
I'll be packed and ready to
disappear
Oh my god.
So please do the right thing
I need my baby.
And I promise you, when you do
I'll be packed and ready to
disappear
So when were you gonna tell me?
- Never?
- Oh.
You're a piece of shit, I
trusted you.
- Out of everyone, you do this.
- It wasn't like that.
You showed up after two years
because you had this idea.
- You pretended to help me.
- No, no, I came back for you.
Bullshit, you came back for her.
You snuck into my house,
you followed my husband.
You spent time with my daughter
and then you stood back
and watched the whole thing
fall apart.
What do you want from me?
You wanted to be a dad?
Is that all I am to all of you,
a fucking uterus?
What? No.
No, I just, I needed to know.
I told you, Sam.
I told you she was Jack's.
The dates don't line up.
You thought I'd lied?
You know what?
I've had enough of this shit.
No, no, no, look, look,
look, look, look, look...
Look, I made a mistake all
right.
I'm here for you.
Look, you know how I feel about
you
and you never say anything
about it
because if you acknowledged it,
you'd have to do something.
Sam, you have a pick up.
All right, look, I've got...
I'm on a night shift.
I'm gonna be back at
7:00 A.M. in the morning
and we're gonna sort this out,
all right.
I promise.
I fucked up.
Why do you think
I kept you so close?
It's always been about you and
me.
- Hey you.
- Hi, just returning your call.
Look, I know it's late.
I'm pretty concerned about
this christening situation.
Why don't you come over
tomorrow?
Bring wine.
Oh, I haven't had this in ages.
So fancy, thank you.
Thank you so much.
This is what I want.
I want you.
Hi, it's me.
Sorry, I know you're at work.
I just need to get those old
tax boxes down from the loft.
Oh, well Tasha
should be in, is she not?
She's not answering.
Well you've got your old keys,
don't worry about it.
Are you sure?
Agh! What the hell are doing in
my kitchen?
- I think I'm gonna leave.
- Yeah, I think you should.
Tell me you want me too.
I want you.
You could pick her up
and have her..
An hour, no more than two,
I promise, no more.
I've just got a couple of things
Jack, I don't think
I should be the one to...
Two hours, I promise.
They've got your picture
in their desk thing.
I love you.
What does she look like,
Oh fuck.
Fuck.
Hey, sorry, I know this is crazy
and I just need to,
- oh okay.
- Yeah?
Yeah, yeah.
Agh! How do you turn your
fucking Bluetooth off?
I know where you're going.
Don't do it Tash, don't meet
them.
You don't know anything.
I'm 15 minutes away.
Heathrow terminal 2, right?
Yeah, look I'm on my way.
I need you to wait for me.
No, you don't get to do this,
Sam.
No, no, no.
This isn't about, I don't
want you to forgive me or...
For what I did.
You cannot go back to him again.
It's not safe.
I gotta go. I gotta go.
I think I see them.
No.
Jack.
Jack, Jack, Jack.
- Jack.
- Oh shit.
Grab his leg.
Emergency responders
at the scene of a crash on the
a4,
two miles east of Heathrow
airport.
Eyewitness reports suggest a
lorry
carrying flammable
liquids burst into flames
when an SUV traveling west,
drove across the central
colliding with the vehicle.
At least one man has lost his
life.
And five other people are
with at least two people
still unaccounted for.
They're setting her now.
I'm looking for my... child,
baby.
Brown hair, brown eyes, Emily.
Okay, whereabout did you lose
her?
She was in the car, in the
car with me.
Yes, she was in the car.
Did somebody pull her out?
I can't even see the car
anymore,
- okay, well, which car?
- The SUV, it's black.
Okay. This is Sierra 47.
Anyone got guys in an SUV,
color black, on site?
Okay madam, let's find you
somewhere to sit down.
No, no, no, no, no.
Mrs. Warrington.
No!
We know you're in shock...
And I understand
this is incredibly painful.
But as you know, we are looking
into
how this could have happened
we also need to know
how the incident began.
Your husband and
when they were pulled from the
vehicle,
no one knew to look for a car
seat.
The chemical fire burnt
at a thousand degrees.
As with the poor lorry driver
who died,
there was very little
anyone could have done.
Due to the severity of the fire,
however, enough evidence of
Emily's DNA
was found on the car seat
and within the vehicle
to confirm that
So we have Natasha warrington
dangerous driving.
Paramedics found contusions on
her neck,
they say wasn't caused by the
incident.
Your ex-husband, Jack warrington
as you previously suggested.
You see, we have a written
statement
from one of the motorists
but our records show
Natasha warrington wasn't
responsible
We've been gradually lifting
in order to give the swelling
a chance to dissipate.
But at this stage, we'd hoped
for that
we really are at the mercy
he could regain consciousness
within the next few days,
which we have every hope of
happening.
But if not, then we'll have to
start
All mighty god, the
father, the son
come down on you
Amen.
You're here.
Of course you are,
of course she'd bring you.
He might not wake up.
Do you know that?
You might have got to her
somehow
- but we all know you did it.
- Hayley, come on.
You did this. You killed her
but that's what you wanted
all along, isn't it?
You fucking bitch.
Okay, Hayley,
that's enough all right.
Tasha.
Come on,
I just wanna talk to her.
I just need to speak to her.
If I hadn't have texted her,
if I hadn't have gotten
involved...
She won't accept my calls,
you gotta give her some time.
Okay.
Sam, something's happened,
I need you to listen to me.
Tasha, what are you doing?
- Come on.
- This never happened.
I'm trusting you.
Don't go too far.
Thank you for trusting me.
Seeing past what you thought I
was.
Look, I'm sorry that you got
dragged into all of this...
Our mess.
Something good came out of it
though.
You have Emily.
It did.
It's not your fault, Jen.
You know that, right?
You weren't responsible for him.
And everything I've done,
the lies I've told,
it's not okay.
But I had to be sure.
He would've found a way to
blame me.
I just...
I wish I'd seen the truth
sooner.
We're sold a lie from birth,
the idea that there are
good people and bad people,
but there aren't.
We all think we're good people.
We all... have the best of
intentions.
You know, I have no doubt
that in his mind,
he did it for love.
He did it for us, for me.
Some misplaced sense of...
What that might look like.
Love can justify almost anything
it makes us all do terrible
things.
Oh there she is.