Look, it's daddy's ex-wife,
agh! What the hell!
Jen, I need you to go.
Ooh, it's a ducky.
She had pouches
You thought you saw Jen.
Jen! What the hell do you think
you're doing with my child?
It's not yours, Sam.
I saw Sam your Sam outside the
house
you followed Jack?
If he didn't think something
was going on between us before,
- I'd say he might now.
- I'll let you get back to Sam.
I'm gonna be gone for three
nights.
Emily's already
what did she look like?
The woman who took my child!?
Here.
Right. Here.
Jen! Who verified her?
Who verified her
as a carer for my child?
Let's have a look.
Jack did.
Okay. Okay...
Wait.
Mrs warrington, wait.
Last week?!
Last week, and you didn't think
to
That's not nursery
Jen! Jen, are you in there,
please?
I need to get hold of
Jack warrington.
No, no, no.
Someone has taken our child.
Tasha!
Lola!
Lola, I need to know
where Jack is.
A number for him in New York.
Where he is?
Oh, is everything all right?
No, it's Emily.
Something's... I just need to
get a hold of him.
His mobile isn't working and
I...
Sorry I don't have time
for this.
I understand, I just need to
tell you
it seems you aren't aware...
The situation?
Please sit down, Tasha,
seriously.
Jack isn't here.
I know he's not here.
He's in New York.
No, Jack isn't here anymore.
He isn't with the company.
He doesn't work here.
What?!
What are you talking about?
Of course he works here.
No, he quit two weeks ago.
It was a bit of a thing.
And he took quite a few clients
Okay.
He just quit?
- Left, yeah, resigned.
- Why?
And you don't know a phone in
New York, or a hotel anything?
No disrespect Tasha but...
Are you sure he's even in new
York?
Jen warrington.
- Through there.
- Thank you.
Where's Emily?
You can't just barge in here.
Where the fuck is she, you mad
bitch?
Is that him?
It's on mute
if you could stop
shouting in my face.
- This is my place of work.
- I really don't give a shit.
Where's my daughter?
Emily.
Emily?
Tasha, please stop! Okay!
Look, I know you're upset
and clearly this is very
difficult
okay?
Jack asked me to collect her
for him.
Oh, he has her?
Where is he?
He's quit his job, did you know
that?
I think he's in some kind of
trouble.
No, he's not in any kind of
Actually, I think he meant to
leave
oh, he told you that, did he?
He was planning on leaving?
What is going on? Where is he?
Jack collected Emily
about half an hour ago.
Okay, so he's not in New York?
Okay. It seems I am caught in
the middle of something here.
Jack told me that he discussed
the
and you agreed to...
Okay. That doesn't appear
to be the case.
I'm really sorry, I can't do
this.
Jen, you need to tell me
what the hell's going on here!
I'm going home
and you should too.
This is not at all appropriate,
okay?
I can't.
- He's changed his number.
- No he hasn't.
Yes, he has.
Why is he doing this?
I don't understand.
I'm sorry, Tasha, but I really
don't
oh my god!
This is because of whatever you
think you heard
between me and Sam
the other day.
This is exactly
you did this to get him back.
Oh my god.
Of course I ha...
You know, if Jack found out
something was going on
between you and Sam,
that's between the two of you.
Excuse me.
Come on, Jack! Let me in!
Jack?!
Emily?!
Hello?
Fuck!!
Hello, ma'am.
Is
can I ask if you're the house
owner?
Yes. Yes, this is my house.
Okay. We've been alerted
to a possible break in
via your home security company.
Is there a problem?
There's no problem, my husband
changed the code
and I'm just about to reset it,
but thank you.
Ma'am, would it be alright if
we took
yeah, sure.
Wait - is that normal?
All part of the service.
I smashed the door.
It's a long story
but my husband and I...
We're having problems and...
God this is really embarrassing
but...
He changed the locks and the
alarm.
Right. Have you got any ID
ma'am?
Driver's licence?
I don't have a driver's licence
but
can I?
My husband covers the bills.
I had a baby last year,
I haven't gone back to work.
If you've got a mortgage
statement,
yes. Yes, yes, I have that.
Is there a problem?
No. Um, I don't know.
I... I'm not on the mortgage
statement.
My name's not on it.
What does that mean?
I know that he put me on it last
I've just spoken to your
husband.
Yes, the security company
connected me to mr warrington.
The good news is he's not going
to be
for the criminal damage to the
door.
However, you are going to have
to
I'm sorry, what?
You can't stay here.
But I live here.
No, sorry. I live here.
I'm his wife. I know I'm not on
the
I have rights, don't I?
Seems he applied for
an occupation order yesterday.
Legally you can't be here.
No, no, no. No, sorry...
He's got my child.
He's got my daughter.
I... I don't know where they
are.
Is he the child's legal father?
He has parental responsibility
as much as you.
Do you have any concerns
over the baby's safety?
Could she be at risk from your
husband?
No, no, nothing like that. I
just...
Tah-dah. The spare room.
Thank you so much for this, Sam.
I appreciate it.
Honestly... it's the least I
can do.
I can't believe he's doing this.
Yeah.
What did they tell you?
- The police?
- Yeah.
That I'm screwed.
And what did they tell you to
do?
Go see his family tomorrow...
Okay. Are you gonna call first?
No. I'm not giving anyone else
the chance to hangup on me.
If I'm right in front of them,
they can't ignore me.
Right.
I can't let this go down
the legal route.
I don't have any savings or
money
what are you talking about?
- Jack's loaded.
- Yeah, he is.
And what, you don't have
a joint account?
No. I didn't want anyone to
think
you...
Okay.
Okay. No, okay.
How're you getting there?
Do you need me to drive you?
He thinks we're having an
affair,
because of the stalking thing...
Oh.
Okay.
Okay, okay.
Yes.
Um, did you mention anything to
him
us in the past?
No. Did you?
No.
Okay, good...
Because there was no us, Sam.
It was one time, when we were
drunk.
Yeah.
So, I didn't mention it.
The point is I can't show up
with you
oh god, I know, I'm sorry.
This is a lot to deal with.
No, it's fine.
Listen, I know this... is
really bad,
and I fucking hate that I have
to do
yes.
Yeah.
And I'll get one of the guys
from
thank you.
- I won't forget this.
- It's okay.
And I'll pay you back. Okay?
Sure.
Don't worry.
- Just here is fine.
- Okay.
Thank you.
- I'll be 30 minutes Max.
- No problem.
Ah. Okay.
Best get the boss.
Hayles! Incoming!
Right, I think you should leave,
he's not here and we'd said
we'd stay out of it so...
I just need to speak to him.
I'm sure he'll call when he's
ready.
As far as I can tell,
he's well within his rights...
You've made your bed.
- Sorry, my bed?
- Yeah.
He told us... about your
boyfriend.
Sam isn't my boyfriend.
Okay, not sure it's any of
my business, but sure.
Hayley, I need to see my
daughter.
You know how good Jack is with
her,
what will?
The divorce - mediation,
whatever.
The divorce?
Yeah.
Hayley, this is ridiculous.
I'm sorry but...
How can he? We haven't even...
I think we all know you've had
problems for a while now.
Jack said as much the other week
I'm sure someone will call
in the next few days.
In the meantime,
oh god, the water works...
Tasha, you'll forgive me
if I don't buy it.
You are a fucking bitch Hayley.
You think it's endearing but
it's
I hope something like this
happens
and when it does, I hope that
you
and when you do,
I hope they fucking ruin you!
Well...
That's some real mother of the
year
get off my property,
before I call the police.
How about that one?
Hard no.
That's a certified ten, mate.
Nah.
She's got the crazy eyes.
Fuck off.
Oh, feisty.
I'm serious lads, I am not in
the fucking mood, so fuck off.
Can I buy you a drink?
What? Fucking what?
You wanna fuck me,
show me the world,
whack me in a huge fucking
house,
and then break my legs
like fucking 'misery'.
No.
Yeah, didn't fucking think so.
Fuck off, you shit bag.
Hello?
Who is this?
It's me. I just need to talk to
you,
just five minutes of your life,
then you never have to see me
ever again. I promise.
Fucksake, Tasha.
Go home to your family.
I can't, I don't know where
they are.
You're all I've got right now.
Let me in, let me in, let me
in...
Jesus Christ.
Let me in, let me in, let me
in...
You can come up if you shut up.
How much have you had to drink?
I'll make coffee.
I'm sorry Jen, I am -
about everything.
About what I did to you.
Your husband. Your house. Your
life.
I just didn't think.
No, sorry, you're right.
That was a lie; I did think.
I knew exactly what I was doing,
I was okay with hurting you
because
you weren't a person with
feelings
and that's unforgivable.
But I came here to tell you that
but I came here to tell you that
if that's what this is,
then I want you to know,
that I will go so easily...
Really, I will.
I'll... leave you guys to it.
I just...
I need you to tell me
where he has her.
Please.
I need to see Emily.
You're drunk, Tasha, and I
don't want
I don't owe you anything.
I didn't even want Emily,
I didn't want a kid.
I'd booked an abortion.
I didn't plan for any of this.
I was so young,
no means to look after her,
but the point is I did
and she is the best thing
that ever happened to me.
You have everything I ever
wanted.
We wanted.
Three miscarriages.
The first was the worst.
She even had a name.
We had our whole lives mapped
out.
And then I kept losing them.
A dull ache,
blood, weeks and weeks of
waiting.
Hope and then trying not to hope
until honestly, you're not sure
I should hate you.
But, you want to know the truth?
I'm tired.
I'm just so fucking tired
of trying to make life happen.
I could fill an arena, Tasha,
I'm old enough and weathered
enough
you can't change the way things
are
I'm not a bad person.
But I'm not your friend either.
Look, I don't know
where they are Tasha...
But I will try to find out.
Okay.
Right now, I want you out of my
house. Okay?
Of course.
Thank you.
- Thank you.
- For what?
Changing my life, kiddo.
For fucksake.
Sam.
Hey.
Look, I've done some digging.
The thing is she thinks he's
at whitsford
which I know that can't be true
because that would've been
what? What's whitsford?
You don't know what whitsford
is?
I have no idea
what you're talking about.
He never told you about
the second home?
The holiday house...
The whole time you...
I suppose things did move
rather quickly, didn't they?
Well, whitsford is in surrey.
It's bigger than the London
place,
it's actually very beautiful.
- Sounds nice.
- It was.
It was going to be our forever
home.
Okay, so he's there, is he?
It would certainly seem so.
Excuse me, can I borrow your
pen?
Thank you.
Here's the address.
Do you have any way of getting
there?
I will figure it out.
Thank you Jen, so much.
Tasha, wait.
When you get there,
what are you going to do?
Do?
I mean are you going to see her
or take her?
If I see her,
she's coming home with me.
I'm sorry, that's the honest
truth.
I understand.
But then you'll leave the
marriage?
Yes.
Do you have a way of getting
there?
Thank you for doing this.
I really appreciate it.
You don't need to thank me.
There's not much point me
giving you
you didn't tell anyone
I was driving you, did you?
Oh no, of course not.
Good.
When we get there, I think we
should
what do you mean wait?
Until it's dark, until he's
asleep.
Tasha, I thought you wanted me
to talk to him.
I told you I'd help bring him
round,
I didn't say I'd help
break into his house.
He's not gonna just hand her
over.
You said yourself,
he's terrified of losing her.
I think we go in there, get her
and
reassure him that...
I'm on the level with this.
I'm not going to disappear.
And you are on the level with
this?
He'll still be able to see her?
Shit.
Hey, this is Tash.
Uh...
This is it.
We should probably leave the
car,
I've been thinking...
Maybe I should go in alone.
I mean, I'm the one who knows
where
I know the lay out of the house,
there's a nursery on the first
floor.
You can wait here.
I'll bring her to you.
I'm just not sure
how he's going to react
if he finds you
if it's me, it's different.
I swear to god if this is a
trick...
If you warn him...
I'll fucking fight this
to the bitter end.
I just don't want a situation,
Tasha.
Not if we can avoid one.
Okay. I'll wait outside.
I won't come in.
What if he's not here.
He's here.
Creature of habit.
Stay put.
I'll go in and find her, bring
her
don't go too far.
Oh, shit.
Emily! Emily!!
Fuck! Jack, open the fucking
door!
Fuck.
Jack, if you don't open the
door,
Emily!
She's gone.
Alright, she's gone.
Look, I never wanted to hurt
you,
She's magical, you know...
Emily
you've made a beautiful little
girl.
Perfect.
So, you see I can't let you
take her from me.
And honestly, Natasha...
All of this was for her.
Our marriage.
All of it was to ensure
that legally I'd be her father.
Jen and I should be together.
You're a wonderful young woman,
Natasha
but what I felt for you
was never love.
This wasn't the ending I'd
planned,
I'd hoped for a smoother
transition
you forced me...
When you said that you'd take
Emily.
There's a line, all right, I'm
not
and also, you've had been
lying to me
spying on me,
bringing another man into my
house.
Yeah.
Don't think I don't know history
I know you were together.
Right, so here is
what's going to happen.
You are going to walk away
from this marriage.
You're not gonna try and fight
it
my resources far outweigh yours
Besides, you're young.
You can walk away and start
again.
Here's what you will get in
exchange:
Nothing outrageous
but it'll be fair.
You will get to see Emily on
birthdays and special occasions
and holidays,
until she is old enough
to make her own choices.
And in return for this access,
you will have to give up any bid
do you understand@
She lives with me.
That's it, that's the offer.
I can hear the cogs turning.
All right, I'll make it simple,
if you try and fight me on this,
I will make sure you get
nothing.
Nothing.
You've had a very busy few days,
leaving Emily with strangers,
causing a scene at my place of
work,
you know my sister...
Had to call the police, don't
you?
You broke in here too.
I had to defend myself -
Jen will back me up.
No court will ever believe you.
They'll see you as
an unfit mother.
I'll drag you through the filth.
Do you understand?
I'll make sure you'll never
see Emily unsupervised again.
Okay.
What was that?
I'll... I'll do it,
I just honsetly need more.
More?
Yeah, I'll sign whatever, but...
I need half.
Half of everything?
Jack...
I've read up on this,
spouses get half by default
unless there's a pre-nup,
which there isn't.
I'd have to write a letter
to the judge, explaining why,
if I took any less than half.
I think it's there to protect
people
I see.
Good for you.
Well, I'm sorry to see you
boil our
but if you want to sell her for
half
she's worth much more to me
anyway.
I know.
Fuck!
You're not taking her!
You're not fucking taking her!
You're not gonna fucking take
her!
You don't take her!
- Jack!
- You don't win!
Do you hear me?!
Fuck!
Pick up you bitch, pick up.
You fucking bitch.
Fuck!