I'm so sorry, I didn't see you.
Is that your wife?
Yep that's Jen.
Jen's agreed to a trial
separation.
I'm pregnant
with a married man's child.
We all know what you did
to get here.
Jen's running around
like she's still your wife.
It's not yours Sam.
If there is something
Jack'll find out.
She was in my house, drunk.
She showed up at our
supermarket the other week.
Have you seen a woman?
I left my baby with her.
You left your baby?
Have you been to see her
since your chat?
- No.
- It needs to stop.
Shit.
Tasha.
Tasha, please.
Would you wait?
Tasha, wait. Tasha
- stop it Tasha, stop it.
- You fuck.
- Stop it.
- You fuck!
Fuck!
Stop it, stop it!
Tasha.
It's not what you think.
Okay?
Whatever you're thinking, don't,
I'll explain if you let me
alright?
Thank you so much.
You're welcome. Anytime.
- Is that her?
- No.
- Are you sleeping with her?
I said no.
I'm not sleeping with her.
You followed me tonight.
How long have you been doing
that?
I didn't follow you.
I used the phone finder app.
Okay, okay.
All right, here's the truth.
Do you wanna sit down or...
You can't spend that much of
your
then suddenly feel nothing.
I'm sorry, you can't.
Now you told me to speak to her
and I did.
But one phone call
after twenty years,
one phone call,
that's not good enough.
Now it appears as though
there's no way to prove to you
that I choose you over her
unless I never see her again.
And I needed to see her again.
So you forced me into
a pretty impossible situation.
Are you fucking with me right
now?
I don't want you going for
date nights with your ex-wife.
I don't think that's
unreasonable,
it was dinner.
It was dinner!
She's got a new contract,
she needed someone.
Tasha I didn't want to let her
down.
I didn't want to.
Cause it's fucking difficult
alright?
And it's different when you're
older.
- Fuck off!
- It is different!
She's got all of her friends,
but all of them have families.
All of them.
They're all doing their own
thing.
It used to be just me and her.
And now what?
I just abandon her.
Is that what you want?
I don't want anything.
You do what you want
and I'll do what I want.
Oh, for fuck sake.
Well, can I ask where you're
going?
I'm taking Emily
away from this shit show.
You're taking her?
No you're not taking...
Sorry. Sorry. I didn't mean
that.
I'm sorry. Okay, sorry.
Fuck, I haven't been listening,
but I am now.
I promise you I'm listening now.
All right? I'm listening.
So...
No more Jen.
Okay.
And your family have to be
nicer.
Yeah, I agree with that.
I will definitely talk to my
family.
And I promise you
that things will get better.
I promise.
You're my priority.
What?
Come on, tell me.
It's this house.
It's...
I'm here all the time.
And I miss my life, my job.
Okay, right.
Right, this is what we'll do,
Emily's old enough for nursery
now,
you get your space.
I can't lose you.
Go on...
Say it.
I've got nothing to say.
I told you how I felt
about this from the start.
So don't make out
like I'm holding back.
Yeah, but this is different.
This is new information.
Well, the point is,
do you believe him?
- I do.
- Okay.
Well you know how I feel,
but there's no way of knowing
I mean, they weren't going at it
- Sam.
- I'm just saying for balance.
I don't trust him but...
You didn't catch him doing
anything
- no.
- Right.
Now it's all over
okay.
So it is a good thing.
Yeah.
Great news about the nursery
though.
- Yeah.
- Get some time back.
Oh.
So it's mandatory for companies
to have a pumping room.
Lush.
But there is no universal
signage yet
so I thought I'd give it a go
for my portfolio.
There she is.
I love it.
I'm here for you.
You know... whenever you need.
Oi, seriously.
Last time I told you
how I felt about Jack,
we didn't speak for a year.
A year!
I'm not risking that again.
If you're happy, I'm happy.
- Yeah right.
- For real.
Can I use your bathroom
quickly before I go?
Yeah just be quiet
because Emily's sleeping.
All right, sweet.
Who's gonna go to bed?
Me?
You?
Ooh.
More?
Later, after our sleep.
Yeah.
- Yeah.
Gonna sleep long?
Yeah?
Who's that?
Who's there?
Is that daddy?
No.
It's not daddy.
I come in peace, bearing gifts.
I know I'm an awful witch
but I've driven three hours
and I'm gasping for a coffee.
And I promise I'm on
absolute best behavior.
Yeah, come in.
Hi.
I'm just putting her upstairs.
I'm not gonna sugarcoat it,
Jack really went to town on us.
Even mum and dad didn't come out
and we'd given up on them years
ago.
They probably need water.
It's a long drive
and I had the heating blasting.
He must really love you, Jack.
He's not done anything
god this is good.
This is the one he gets
from Guatemala, right?
He told us how unhappy you've
been.
It's hard that first year
with a new baby, isn't it?
Yeah it's bloody hard.
It's uncanny...
How much she looks like him.
You're in there, of course,
the chin maybe,
but his eyes, cheeks, dimples.
Yeah kids are hard.
Can't imagine what it's been
like
no support network.
Hadn't occurred to me
until Jack said it.
He said you'd been brilliant,
of course.
I've been awful to you.
Not a literal or a figurative
sister, but...
I'm here now and I'm sorry.
I really appreciate you saying
that.
It's been a little harder
than I expected
but worth it, of course.
I mean, I wouldn't change
it for the world, but...
It's funny how we can
create a person in our minds.
You're not who I thought you
were
I didn't think somebody like you
I didn't realize
you'd be quite so fragile.
Don't get me wrong, I could
do with a touch more fragility
or I could of course
completely change
but that might run the risk
of a full character implosion.
Well, please don't implode,
Come here.
- Okay?
- Yeah, good.
Is Jen... okay?
Jack really loves you.
Okay? He'd do anything to make
you happy.
But you said jump, he jumped.
No one's said a word to her.
Cold Turkey after twenty years.
I'm not blaming you...
No contact means no contact.
You asked.
The answer is no,
she's not really okay.
I have to go.
Sorry.
Take care. See you soon.
Right, well he said
specifically no purple.
He didn't say anything
about mauve, did he?
So let's get the swatches
and mail them across.
Okay, one second.
I'm sorry to barge in, it's just
she told me Jack had
stopped talking to you
and hadn't explained why.
That's my fault.
So I thought I should
come and explain.
Or... apologize, I don't know.
I don't know what I'm doing,
Jen.
And, up until now,
I've been behaving as though
I'm still this laid back,
easygoing gen z or whatever.
But the truth is, I'm not.
You're a lovely person
but the lovelier you are,
the more it
you should hate me.
I stole your husband.
I don't hate you Tasha.
I hate what happened to me...
And Jack.
But that happened
long before you arrived.
Jack needed a fresh start
and you were exactly that.
And, if I'm honest,
I'm not sure I would be doing
any
It's okay, I'm right here.
God, she's just hungry.
Oh, hi darling.
Hello. Hi.
How's my girl?
Beginner's luck.
Yeah?
I've actually forgotten her food
- so I have to go.
- Oh, in the kitchen.
The cupboard on the right?
Yes. Oh, it's a ducky.
Quack, quack.
Oh look, ba ba ba...
- Did you find it?
- Yep.
What's this?
Everything okay?
Yeah, everything's fine.
- Thank you.
- My pleasure.
Jack brought her here.
A few times actually.
Or I should say he dropped
by and she was with him.
Recently?
No, no.
When she was younger.
Come in for weekend days for a
coffee
or we'd all go for a walk,
wouldn't we?
And you thought you'd buy food
for her, just on the off chance
that Jack would pop by
with my daughter?
No, of course not.
Jack must have left them here
by accident.
No, I probably should have
binned them actually...
All right, here they are.
You should probably have them,
or it's just a waste.
I'm sorry Jen.
No, no don't be silly.
I understand.
Like I said...
If the tables were turned.
Tasha, finally.
Hey, sorry I missed
your calls, are you okay?
Yes. I've been trying
to get
I know, I know, I was busy.
What's up?
I did something.
What? What'd you do?
I needed to talk to you earlier
so I went to the house
and Jack was there.
- Jack was there?
- Yes.
- In the middle of the day?
- He was being weird.
He was making even less
of an effort
to disguise the fact
that he didn't want me there.
So he left and I...
Followed him.
You followed Jack?
Yes.
But I think he saw me.
Sam, you idiot.
He saw you?
Why the fuck were you following
Jack?
Because I could...
I wanted to get hold of you
and he was acting strange.
- I'm looking out for you.
- He was acting strange?
Sam, this isn't looking out for
me,
okay.
Okay.
Are you sure he saw you?
Yeah.
Yeah, I think so.
And?
I drove off.
Oh my god Sam,
if he didn't think that
something
I'd say he might now,
don't you think?
I think a certain someone
droppedthis.
I'll let you get back to Sam.
Shit.
Yeah?
Yeah.
Oh, I forgot to say,
I forgot to say I have to
go to New York again.
Oh.
- Oh right.
- Oh, that's a good one.
It is.
Yeah, I was gonna get you a
ticket
beautiful.
Look, we're nearly at the
front.
We're nearly at the front.
So lookout, fellow drivers,
brcause my dad's
got a previous for speeding.
It's fine, here.
- Who is it?
- It's Johnny.
Johnny?
Sorry, it's a work thing. I...
- Yeah, yeah you go.
- Have fun.
Sorry, what is it?
Up we go!
Where are we going?
Look at you!
Where's your dada?
I don't know where your dada is.
Would you mind watching her?
Thank you. Thank you.
Have you seen... there was
a little girl here, just there.
Just a second ago.
Tasha? Tash!
- What's happened?
- It's Emily.
She was there and then she's...
Okay.
Jen!
What the hell do you think
you are doing with my child?
Oh my god. Oh my god.
No. I'm so sorry.
I'm her mother, I'm her mother.
I'm so sorry.
You left her alone,
I was looking for you.
I know, there was an emergency.
Thank you so much looking after
her.
It's a busy place,
thank you, thank you.
- Thank you so much.
- I'm glad to help.
It's okay, come on.
I'm so sorry.
I'm so sorry,
I wasn't paying attention.
It's okay.
Oh, I won't leave you ever
again,
- never.
- It's okay. There's no harm.
I promise I won't ever do that
again.
It's okay. It's fine.
- It's okay.
- No, it's not okay.
It's not okay. You were arguing
with Johnny and then I...
I saw...
You thought you saw Jen?
- Yeah I heard.
- Yeah.
I think half of the soft play
heard.
Tash, you know she's not here
right?
- Tash.
- Of course.
I'm so sorry.
All right, okay.
- I'm so sorry.
- It's okay.
And she had
Emily's food in her house.
What do you mean?
Pouches of toddler food.
In her cupboard.
It was...
She claims that you left them
there,
accidentally, the last time
you went around.
- Did you?
- Well...
I guess I must have if she says
so.
I don't know.
It was weird.
What did you expect?
A broken woman?
Well, she's not like you.
Not like me how?
She doesn't express emotions
like this.
It's just not what she does.
No, that's not a criticism of
you.
It's just...
Her whole world could be
crumbling
you'd think she was fine or
joking?
Whereas I?
Tash I'm not starting anything.
She's just older and she's been
through lots of things.
Don't do that.
Do what?
I get it, I'm...
You're the wise elders
and I'm this footloose chancer
who's lucky to be here.
No
The thing is, Jack, I...
Know who I am.
I've been a grown up
since I turned 16
and started working
to fund my own education.
I supported my mother and then
so you're gonna have to
find another angle
if you wanna justify
all of this bullshit.
'Cause the truth is that...
The truth is...
You left your wife but you
didn't leave her, did you?
She's here right now.
She may as well be
having dinner with us.
That's a really unfair thing to
say.
Jack.
Jack, can we...
Can you come back so we can...
It's totally unfair
and you know it is.
This isn't gonna change, is it?
You said things would change
but...
I can't do this anymore.
If I don't leave...
I feel like I'm gonna disappear.
Tasha.
Tasha!
Are you not speaking to me now?
I'm gonna go check on Emily.
Jack.
Look, you're my wife.
There's no one else here,
it's just you and me.
We could renew our vows.
We'll move somewhere.
Let's move somewhere.
We might have to if the glass
bursts.
Oh yeah.
I'll get it fixed.
You know what you said earlier,
about me being a wise old elder
and you...
You know I don't think that,
don't you?
It's been such a weird day.
I saw Sam earlier, your Sam,
and then again at work.
It was...
It was really unsettling.
Something's definitely up with
him.
I dunno what it...
Do you think he has feelings
for you?
What?
He was at the house?
Mm.
No.
No he doesn't.
I don't know.
What happened?
Did you speak?
Do you want me to say something
to him?
We spoke briefly, it was weird.
But no, don't cause a problem
on my account.
I just don't trust him, that's
all.
It was probably a coincidence
him being in town.
He's a cabby, isn't he?
Yeah, weird.
You should be careful around
him.
Morning.
Good morning.
I love you.
Are you packed?
Have you got everything?
Except you.
I'm right here.
Now listen, I'm gonna
be gone for three nights
so that gives you
three glorious days to relax
and be creative, find a job.
Generally have a lovely time.
And I'll see you when I'm back.
Right. Driver's downstairs.
I've got Emily up
and dressed for nursery
so I'll drop her off on
the way to the airport.
- Oh, that's okay I can-
- no, it's fine, it's fine.
She'll be fine.
I packed her nursery bag
with all of her things.
A garrot, mace, cleaver, usual
stuff.
I am a pretty hands on dad,
I don't know if you've noticed.
I trust you.
Well at least someone does.
Thank you.
What for?
Changing my life kiddo.
You too old man.
Old, old, old.
Hello?
Oh hey, it's Natasha,
it's Johnny. We met at Jack's
hearing, the driving ban.
I'm sorry to bother you at home,
he's not there, is he?
Hi, yeah, Johnny, I remember.
He's actually just left for
New York on a business trip.
Really?
Oh, okay.
Right.
Has he?
My mistake then.
I'll just try him again later.
Thanks Natasha.
The number you have called
Hello stranger.
There she is.
Back in the game.
It's just an interview.
It's in the bag.
I've got a good feeling about
it.
But listen, I need to speak to
you
sorry hang on.
- Emily warrington.
- Great, I'll go get her.
Sorry, are you still there?
Always.
How's my Princess doing?
Well good, I think.
The algebra's coming along
nicely.
Oh, and she speaks Spanish now.
Well no one needs
to learn algebra ever.
But listen,
I really need to talk to you.
Is everything okay?
Sorry Sam, I'll call you back.
Hi. Sorry, just to clarify,
you're here for...?
Emily warrington.
- I'm her mum.
- Yes, yes.
Emily's already been collected.
What?
W... what do you mean
collected?
By who?
Who collected Emily earlier?
- Emily's mum.
- I'm her mum.
Who the hell
did you give my child to?
She was in the pickup book.
No, no, no, no, no
this can't be happening.
What did she look like?
The woman who took my child!