(SOPRANOS THEME SONG)
You have to be 110%
sure this is who you saw.
This is definitely him.
- Had you ever seen him before?
- No.
- And the other man?
- I didn't get a good look at him.
The light reflected off the car.
But he was heavyset.
It was really dark.
I didn't want to be seen.
I heard shots but I thought
they were firecrackers.
When the two men drove out,
I hid in the ragweed.
- Sure.
- What happened began to dawn on me.
But like I told the officers...
...I left the flat tire
and walked to a phone.
Thank you, Mr. Arthur.
I'm so goddamn fed up with crime.
I had to come forward
to help you find them.
Thanks to people like you,
we may just do that.
May I ask who the dead man was?
Just a poor kid in the wrong crowd.
- Crack?
- Something like that.
Uh-huh.
(CAROUSEL MUSIC PLAYING)
(CHILDREN LAUGHING)
Mommy!
Mommy! Mommy! No!
Hey...
- What's the matter, you lost?
- Uh-huh.
You scared me half to death!
I can't turn my back for a minute!
I know what that's like. My little
guy was a real cadet at his age.
- Tony!
- Yeah?
It's good you could meet me.
No problem. I went
to Brookstone and got a scale.
- What's it about?
- Fucking Dick Barone.
As long as the two of you are happy.
I'm in no mood.
This garbage business. I found out
that bow-tied motherfucker...
...is charging me double
to tip my trucks at his place.
So pay the tonnage, and charge your
townships extra for the pickups.
I got the smallest amount of routes
of anybody in the association.
You're like the old woman with ham
under her arm, crying for bread.
- What the fuck?
- Never mind. The point is...
...your brother, Jack, never
concentrated on sanitation...
...so what do you want Dick to do?
I want a rate.
I'll see what he says.
Yeah. You see. Since you own
part of the company.
(WATER RUNNING)
- Did you shut all the lights?
- Yeah.
- In the kitchen?
I want to spend more time with AJ.
It's the other one who's almost
out of the house.
I'm not worried about Meadow.
Meadow can take care of herself.
- Why the sudden burst of fatherhood?
- Can you say anything without sarcasm?
You're right. I'm sorry.
It's a good idea. He adores you.
He never spends enough time with you.
Yeah, well...
I was reading in Time,
this study at Harvard.
"A father's support is
absolutely linked...
...to a boy's later capacity
to manage frustrations...
...to explore new circumstances...
...and do well."
Kid needs to toughen up.
No, I'm talking about opening up.
He needs some street smarts.
Not to be a sucker, or get
involved with the wrong people.
I don't want another Christopher
on my hands. Look at him.
He's lucky to be alive.
That other poor prick they found dead.
Kid was 23 or something.
Hey, pal, with the Ramlösa...
...put three cases of that in my car.
You got it.
That's not a mistake.
I want another 14 gross
of model number 4784.
Plastic picnic coolers. Ship them,
I'll worry about selling them.
Red.
Fuck blue, red sells.
- Put it here.
- Put that on the store tab.
He says take three gross of the blue,
he'll give us a price on the red.
Fuck that. He's never
getting paid anyway.
They gotta be all red.
Just do it, please.
Thank you. Goodbye.
Who gets chicken and peppers?
- A lot of work to move picnic coolers.
- Coolers are like scissors...
...everybody wants one, nobody
has any idea how much they cost.
You put a Nigerian on the street,
have him sell these...
...for a couple bucks apiece, who's
not gonna say, "Fuck it, give me one"?
How we doing with them
airline tickets?
Won't it raise a flag
with the travel agency?
A sports store charges
tickets in bulk?
Say it's for promotion. Customer of
the Year, Salesman of the Month...
...that kind of thing.
Don't worry. You put it
on different credit lines.
Suddenly I'm ordering
all this shit.
I mean, picnic coolers,
Ramlösa water...
When do they realize
I'm not paying and call the cops?
When your fucking credit
runs out, Diamond Jim.
Until then, get on the horn
and order.
Unless you can pay us
the principal you owe.
Hey!
Put the heat up.
Today!
(EXHALES)
Oh, fuck! Fuck!
- What's the matter?
- Spider.
So kill it.
You do it.
Come here and kill the thing.
- Come here.
- No way.
Come on.
It was a leaf, you frigging idiot!
- Mister!
- Yeah.
- There's a man here to see you.
- Who?
A police.
Be right back.
Did you let them in the house?
Warrant, warrant.
How do you say it in fucking Polish?
Agent Harris!
Who's your friend?
I'm Detective Harold Giardina.
From the Essex County Task Force.
Pleased to meet you. But if you
don't have a warrant, get out.
- I'm busy.
- I can see that.
A comedian. Is that how you
broke your nose?
We could've phoned.
We paid the courtesy of a visit.
Let's talk at the station.
- Talk?
- About Matthew Bevilaqua.
Dad?
Take the backboard out.
I'll be down in a second.
Lawyer up, whatever, it's your call.
Just name the time.
On your way out, can you roll the
garbage down? Tomorrow's pickup day.
(SCOFFS)
Let's go, Harry.
(DOOR OPENS, CLOSES)
Those are the FBI guys from before.
What did they want?
Nothing.
Keep this between us.
You know how your mother gets.
(SEAGULLS SQUAWKING)
What do you got for me?
A partial list of the major
investors in Webistics.
I haven't seen Tony in a while.
Besides the night he capped Bevilaqua?
- What do you mean?
- Did you fuck me?!
- Take it easy.
How about I put a bullet in
your stupid boar's head?
He was spotted, Sal.
So don't go pulling my taffy.
As of this second,
if you lie to me...
...you will never see the streets
for 50 fucking years!
- Did you know about this?
- No.
If you knew Soprano
was planning something...
...and didn't wear a wire...
I told you no!
There was someone else
there that night.
A quote, unquote: "Husky accomplice."
- Yeah?
- Yeah.
- But the witness couldn't I.D. him.
- Oh.
- Were you the perp he couldn't I.D?
- What, are you fucking crazy?
What did I tell you, huh?
No fucking violence!
I ought to burn you and let
the judge throw away the key!
I'm deciding to believe you.
But here's what you're gonna do.
I want Tony's voice on tape, saying,
"I killed Matthew Bevilaqua."
No distortion. No throat
clearings. No nose-blowing.
I get it.
But let me ask you something.
If I did ride with Tony
on something like that...
...wouldn't that get me tighter
with him, raise my coinage?
- Make Tony forget all his suspicions?
- You're a cute prick, Puss.
Get me Tony on tape
talking about this murder.
Who's the witness?
No joke, Sal. You don't want
to see my darker side.
- Go.
- If they had enough to pinch you...
...there'd be bars
between us as we speak.
- Why do they want me to go there?
- Lock you into a story.
So later at trial, any contradiction
will sink you.
- We going?
- Did you say you'd go?
- Please.
- All right, procrastinate.
Let me get our ducks in a row.
Keep your cool and go the speed limit.
Don't give them an in.
What'd I just say?
- Don't give them an in.
- Are you all right, Tony?
This is some bad shit here.
What's up, Anthony?
How did this happen?
Midlife crisis?
You can talk to me.
The mothers last year said we should
end senior night at Long Beach Island.
They'll dance, scavenger hunt and
the liquor stores will be closed.
- And we count noses.
- Okay.
Is that the time? I'm gonna
barely get Natalie to tap.
- Chris, need a ride?
- No, my brother's coming.
- Eric took my car to a meet.
- Next week, my house.
We'll tie up the loose ends.
- Christine, I'm so glad you stayed.
- I kind of wanted to.
When I found out about Eric's car,
I told Tony to give it back...
I wish I could say this is
a first for David, but...
Eric is going to college,
and maybe it's better for his grades.
- So April 1, huh? How I dread it.
- So long as Eric gets into Georgetown.
- It's his first choice.
- Meadow wants to go to Berkeley.
- Hi. We just finished.
- Sorry I'm late. I was bidding a job.
My brother, the wallpaper artist.
The one you can trust...
...with your Brunswick & Fields.
Vic, Carmela Soprano. Victor Musto.
- Nice to meet you.
- You too.
- You have a beautiful house.
- Thank you.
- Could use a little freshening up.
- Vic does amazing border work too.
I was thinking of wallpapering
the dining room. Do you have a card?
Yeah, sure.
I'm bonded and state certified,
but I'm still dangerous.
(LAUGHS)
- Well, bye, Carmela. Thanks.
- Let's get together and have lunch.
- Have you tried the new Vesuvio?
- No.
- Okay, lunch. Promise.
- Yes.
- Nice meeting you.
- I'll call about the wallpaper.
(DOOR CLOSES)
Nice lady.
Don't even think about it.
She's married to Tony Soprano.
Married's good enough. The husband
doesn't matter, I respect the ring.
Especially that ring.
Probably came off a dead finger.
(CLICKS)
- David? Are you down there?
- Be right up!
- What are you doing?
- Fixing the fucking light bulb!
- It glares off the ball when I rack!
- Jesus, okay.
You're always worried
about ruining the felt.
(DOOR OPENS)
(DOOR CLOSES)
Richie, baby, you're the best one!
Oh, baby.
Oh, you're the best one ever.
(MOANING)
Oh, baby, you're the best!
Oh, baby, you're the best.
Oh, Richie. Oh, Richie.
Oh, you're the boss.
Oh, you're the boss!
Oh, baby! Oh, you're the best!
It should be you.
Oh, it should be you.
What?
- Where'd that come from?
- What?
"It should be you"?
What are you trying to say, Janice?
- What?
- Don't "what" me!
- Why'd you say that?
- I was making love to you, baby.
You know what you said.
I was in the heat of passion.
I'm doing it like you like.
"Boss" this, "boss" that...
"It should be you."
That's not part of it.
How can you think of that during sex?
You're not in the moment.
I find powerful men erotic.
- Was that another dig in me?
- Oh, Jesus, Richie.
I gotta be loyal.
Without that, we crumble.
Tell that to Paul Castallano.
I'm old school, Janice.
All I mean is, my brother needs help.
- Teaching him manners is one thing.
- My Uncle Junior still has friends...
...and he thinks the world of you.
"When your opponent
gives you an opening...
...be swift as a hare." Sun Tzu.
When I think of that jacket
I gave your brother...
...and he spit on it...
...I could slice an ear off his head.
Richie, wait.
(MOTOR HUMMING)
Ma, if you need something,
call. I'll bring it up.
Are you smoking marijuana?
I want to watch the TV.
- We should get one for your room.
- Listen to her.
Like Rose Kennedy, with all
her money to throw around.
(MOANING)
(PANTING)
(SIGHS)
It's giving me agita.
Want me to go downtown.
Lock you into a story.
Why the fuck ain't they
talking to you?
Give them time. They will.
- Murder in aid of racketeering.
- Twenty to life.
There they are.
The Flying Cafone Brothers.
Not good. Not good.
On my kids, I will fucking cut you!
Just tell me!
Take it easy, Ton. It's fixable.
- First off, it's not a rat.
- Thank God.
Don't thank Him yet.
There's an eyeball witness.
What are you talking about?
Jesus Christ! Shit!
- Did you see anybody, any living soul?
- Fuck, no!
Don't worry.
A bump in the road.
Oh, you're beautiful.
- Who? Do we know him?
- All we know is that he's a civilian.
A flag-saluting motherfucker.
Maybe you should lamb chop it
for a while.
- I keep a suitcase in my trunk.
- Tell us about it.
Fuck all youse.
Bygones are never bygones.
This is a nightmare.
I'm gonna have to move some cash.
If I go, I'm going with a package.
Not like Massucco.
He had five minutes to run...
...and ended up in a rat motel
down in Elvis country.
- What is that?
- Where there are no Jews or Italians.
- I don't get it.
- It's starting!
- Get back in your office, David!
I open my mail and it's a lawsuit!
It's a fucking lien on the building!
- Not fucking now, okay?
- They're gonna know it's fraud!
- I'm gonna go to jail for this!
- Get the fuck back in your hole!
Now!
Davey...
You're doing a good job.
Don't worry about this witness.
That's true. We'll find him.
Exactly.
- You don't know what he said.
- I did too.
- What, then?
- I understood.
What's it mean?
It means, "Sit on this, cocksucker!"
(LAUGHS)
Five minutes away from life
in prison and I'm fucking laughing.
You gotta, skip, you gotta.
Davey never takes me to dinner.
Yeah, when you're dating
it's all candles and wine and...
Dave's been even more preoccupied
than usual lately.
- Well, he's busy.
- Carmela, my husband has a disease.
- A serious gambling problem.
- I am so sorry.
Thank God the store's in my name.
He can't sell it without me, or
he would have gambled it all away.
But I'm gonna make sure
we get through this.
Give me those.
I'm gonna make you two beautiful
women a special-tasting menu.
I was hoping he'd say that.
I know you ordered the Pellegrino,
but I want you to try this.
I got such a deal on this Ramlösa.
It was nice to meet your brother.
He seems very interesting.
He's a doll. When his wife was
dying, he waited on her hand and foot.
- A widower? So young.
- Breast cancer.
Ugh.
I thought there was
a sadness about him.
- And the children?
- Childless. She had a hostile womb.
- I had a dream about him.
- You did?
- Christine.
- He asked me about you too.
He was wallpapering my dining room.
It was your subconscious telling you
you want him to wallpaper the room.
Hey, cucuzza!
- I got something for you.
- What?
A Fenwick Rod and a Penn
International Reel.
- Thanks.
- Wanted it for Christmas, remember?
But it was back-ordered?
Well, I got a great deal on it.
- We'll take the boat and go fishing.
- Okay.
- What are you doing now?
- You want to go fishing now?
No, I figured we'd see a movie
or something...
...get some pizza.
I can't.
- What do you mean?
- I'm going to the mall.
- You gotta go to the mall?
- Not just me.
- Brad, Allen, Heidi, her sister maybe.
- Like a double date.
No, Dad. We're just going
to the mall. We go there sometimes.
- And do what?
- Get something to eat. Mrs. Fields.
Anyway, I gotta go.
I'm meeting them there.
All right. Go ahead.
See you later.
(DOOR OPENING)
(DOOR CLOSING)
Yeah, my girl did the same thing...
...at his age. Boys and girls,
always in a group.
- What's that about?
- What's it about for you?
In my day, a boy and girl
went on a date.
Your father hoped you wouldn't get
too far or you'd knock her up...
...and her parents would
break your legs.
I don't think it's about him
going to the mall with a group...
...that bothered you.
Wasn't it that he went to the mall
instead of going with you?
- He's starting to get his own life.
- One that doesn't include you.
It was always, "We'll do this."
"We're gonna do that."
I've heard you talk many times
about being with your son.
Well, that's over now. Gone. Done.
It's bittersweet, this period.
You're glad that they're growing up,
but you're sad to lose them.
I could be going away.
For a very long time.
For something I didn't do.
How about, "That's too bad"?
Or, "What a shame, Tony"?
- We can't go into specifics on this.
- Here's something specific.
I didn't do anything wrong.
We can't talk about it?
I could be going to the can
for the rest of my life...
...and I'm not supposed to
discuss it with my psychiatrist?
What the fuck are you for anyway?
How does that feel?
The idea that you might
be sent to prison?
I gotta stay around a little
while longer for the kids.
Especially my boy.
Once he's out of the house,
the government can do what they want.
- Give me life, the chair, whatever.
- I've never seen you like this.
- Like what?
- Scared.
I wouldn't use that word.
But sometimes I feel...
I don't know, I don't know.
You motherfuckers!
I don't fucking deserve this!
How's your medication?
Maybe we should stop.
(DOOR OPENING)
- What?
- Don't have the witness yet.
- Nothing?
- This is the FBI, Ton.
Local cops, buy them a Christmas tree,
they'll give up their grandmother.
You know how tight these feds
can keep it.
Go home, get some sleep.
You don't want to stop by the Bing,
get something to eat?
Tell me, T, what do you want me to do?
Just let me think. Come on.
All right.
(DOOR CLOSES)
(SIGHS)
(SNORING)
Tony! What are you doing here?
- Could ask you the same question.
- It's my store.
Congratulations,
it's a fucking disaster.
The airline tickets came in. You want
me to split them with you guys?
They're mine. It was my idea.
- This is where you sleep?
- Yeah, sometimes.
It's easier than going home.
I know what you mean.
(CHUCKLES)
I remember when you transferred
into 10th grade from...
...Baden-Baden.
Fucking Army brat.
Remember when those Paterson Guidos
caught you up at Garret Mountain...
...and you were in your dad's car...
...and I threw a rock at that guy?
Don't reminisce on me.
You told me not to get in the game.
Why'd you let me do it?
I knew you had this business, Davey.
It's my nature.
Frog and the scorpion, you know?
Besides, if you would've won,
I'd be crying the blues.
- Right?
- What's the end?
The end? It's planned bankruptcy.
(SOBBING)
You're not the first guy
to get busted out.
This is how I make a living.
It's my bread and butter.
When this is over, you're free to go.
Oh, for chrissake.
(GUNSHOT POPS)
(CHEERING)
Anthony!
Dig!
Anthony! Anthony, dig!
Come on!
Anthony!
Oh, my God, that was so exciting!
I banged my foot.
I would've came in second.
You were like a fish out there.
- Where's Dad?
- He couldn't make it.
He had a meeting.
He'll be here next time.
- This is the last meet of the season.
- Next year, I mean.
Oh.
Okay.
- Got a safe?
- Yeah, why?
- You want to pay in advance?
- There's over 400K there.
I want you to hold it for me.
This goes down, I'm out of the area.
My wife will come
for a weekly allowance.
You don't ask her any questions
and you never, ever refuse her.
If she wants it all...
...you give it to her.
She won't do that.
She's smarter than that.
And if the money doesn't last?
Don't worry, you won't
go into your own kick.
This witness can't remain
nameless forever.
I didn't hear that!
- Don't you got school tomorrow?
- So?
So it's late. Go to bed.
Did you hear me?
- I hope you apologized to him.
- For what?
- You promised to be at his swim meet.
- Oh, shit, I forgot.
- How could you forget?
- There was something I had to do.
He almost came in second.
You should've seen his face.
I saw his face when
he went to the mall...
...and I wanted to go to the movies.
Are you 6 years old?
- I said I'd try to be there.
- What is with you, Tony?
This whole week...
...you're like an alien life form.
There's nothing wrong.
Thank you for sharing.
Know what, leave me the fuck alone.
I'll make up for the swim meet.
Where were you?
Did you see Chris at the hospital?
Yeah, I went to see
Christopher at the hospital.
Wherever you were, it's more important
to let your son know you care!
No, only you care. Fuck you.
No, fuck you!
Fuck you! You fucking...!
What's wrong with you?
(CRICKETS CHIRPING)
Hey.
(GASPS)
My God, you scared
the shit out of me.
No. Shut them off.
- Why are you sitting in the dark?
- I don't know.
I like the dark.
- Sit.
- I gotta go online.
Oh, come on. Sit for a minute.
Come on.
- What's going on?
- With what?
Whatever, I don't know.
What's going on?
I just told you. The chat room.
Is that it?
You know I love you, right, Med?
- Dad...
- No, don't "Dad" me, come on.
I want to know.
- Do you know that I love you?
- Yes.
I know that you love me.
Your mother doesn't think
I love you enough.
And you listen to her?
Everything I do...
...and everything I've done,
and everything I will do...
...it's all for you and your brother.
I think you should go to bed.
I tell people...
...you're like your mother, but...
...you're all me.
Nothing gets by you.
- I know you think I'm a hypocrite...
- I'm going to bed.
Yeah, all right. Go ahead.
Dad?
Why don't you go to bed?
No, I'm gonna finish my drink.
Okay.
- Good night.
- Good night, baby.
Sometimes...
...we're all hypocrites.
- Good night, baby.
- Good night.
(JOURNEY MUSIC PLAYING)
How are you guys doing?
Ready for another sandwich?
- You ought to go into business.
- Oh, stop it.
Thank you, no, Mrs. Carmela.
I thought you might want this.
You said Ramone backed over yours.
I lied.
I smelled those sausages
and I wanted you to make me lunch.
Guess I'm hungry
for a home-cooked meal.
My wife was a gourmet cook.
Christine told me about her.
I'm so sorry.
Thank you.
We were talking
about the powder room?
- Do you have a minute to look at it?
- Oh, yeah, sure.
The paper here now...
...I think it kind of
closes the room in.
I see what you mean.
It's the vertical striping.
Somebody even talked me into
papering the back of the door here.
I must have been out of my mind.
It's a lot for the eye to handle
in such a confined space.
So, what do you think? Should I
just paint or do something plain-ish?
Just grass cloth, maybe, or...
Oh, Jesus.
Jesus, Mary and Joseph.
I never did anything like this before.
- I couldn't help it.
- I never felt like this before.
- It won't happen again.
- Of course not.
- I apologize.
- Okay.
- You should, maybe, get back to work.
- Yeah.
What about little Eric?
He has been ripped from the arms
of the only mother he has ever known.
You know how that boy loves you.
We cannot let her do this.
Hey, Uncle Junior.
I thought you guys might like
some salami and eggs.
- Always thinking.
- My mother says to send her love.
Put that stuff in the bedroom.
Leave the sneakers.
You want to try them on?
I don't wear that shit.
They're for the black kid
who washes my car.
Poor prick wears a pair
that's wrapped with duct tape.
You're too good, Junior.
That's your problem.
- Did she say she was knocked up?
- Who?
Fuck, I turn my head one second
and they slip one in on you.
She's a puttana, this one. Fucked
an arson investigator last week.
- Thank my nephew for the stuff.
- Your nephew?
This shit comes from my end.
Wait a minute. I take it back.
- The sneakers are from Tony.
- Cock.
You know, Uncle Jun, it kills me
to sit back and watch...
Forget it.
- Finish what you were gonna say.
- I forgot already.
- Then un-forget.
- I notice that he's fucking you.
This bust-out is a license to steal.
What's he throwing your way?
This garbage thing?
He's already taking your townships.
- Now he's fucking with mine?
- What should I do?
- I'm under indictment.
- I don't want to open old wounds...
- You're in no shape for disharmony.
- You and I both know he's gotta go.
That's my nephew.
How dare you, in my home.
This fucking guy was supposed to be
laid out on Midland Avenue a year ago.
I know it and you know it.
Let me tell you who's not a good kid.
My niece. I left my brother's
house one night...
...and my wallet was light. I'm
talking a 10-year-old girl, Richie.
Word to the wise,
that's all I'm saying.
Now you can make homemade
sausage and homemade pasta...
- Hi, Grandma.
- Your aunt forgot to lock that door.
I told her, I don't trust
that new mailman.
Guess what? I got my answers
from colleges today.
Oh, yeah? How'd you do?
Accepted at Berkeley,
accepted at NYU...
...wait list, Columbia,
Penn I didn't make it...
...Bowdoin I didn't make it,
BU accepted.
What about that other place,
Georgetown?
Wait list.
You don't owe them anything.
Thanks, Grandma.
Lock that door, will you?
And for dessert, the kids
can make their own chocolate pasta.
(MUSIC PLAYING)
(PHONE RINGING)
- Hello?
- Carmela, Vic Musto.
Hi, how are you?
I'm good. I'm fine. I...
I was just thinking about you
and what happened this morning.
- I just wanted to say again...
- No, please, it was a crazy thing.
But if it's a problem,
I've got another job in Wyckoff.
Yours is far enough along
that Ramone can finish up.
There's no charge...
...except for materials.
No, I wouldn't think of it.
It's just that...
...since Jill, there hasn't been
anyone to talk to.
Oh, I know.
- In fact...
- What?
Maybe you could send Ramone
to the other job tomorrow.
That way you and I would have
a chance to talk, on your lunch break.
- That would be so great.
- And I could make a lunch for us.
Maybe a galantine de poulet...
...mesclun salad,
nice bottle of Barolo.
- That sounds incredible.
- Okay.
Okay, then, thanks for calling.
That's terrific.
- See you tomorrow.
- I will talk to you tomorrow, bye.
- Who was that?
- It was nobody, the wallpaper man.
(PIANO PLAYING MUSIC)
Oh, my God.
- Oh, my God. Please, no.
- What the hell is it?
"The victim has been identified
as Matthew Bevilaqua...
...a Soprano family associate."
Fuck, give me that.
"Officials are keeping tight-lipped...
...as it may involve
a high-ranking Mafia member."
- Where's that number?
- Fridge.
Those lying cocksuckers!
- Where is it?
- On the fridge!
- Where on the fucking fridge?
- I knew it!
But you had to be the big man!
Jesus Christ, David.
Where the hell have you been?
Thanks for coming.
I'm glad you called.
My sister's been worried sick.
Yeah, I know. I'm sorry.
I should've called her.
Why don't I say "sorry" to the
whole fucking world with a blimp.
Christine knows you're gambling again.
I'm not gambling anymore.
I'm broke.
Jesus Christ!
I screwed up, Vic.
- I screwed up really bad this time.
- It's gonna be all right.
You'll go to Gamblers Anonymous
and we'll get you on your feet.
- Gamblers Anonymous.
- No joke, you're going back there.
Is that right? Where were you when
I dropped out in the first place?
- I was twisting in the wind out there.
- What?
You and your broom-up-her-ass sister,
you didn't give a fuck!
- You looked the other way!
- It's our fault?
Don't ever talk about her like that.
Oh, fuck her! Fuck you!
How much did you lose? How much?
How much did you lose?
- Everything.
- What do you mean?
Everything. For chrissake,
Vic, everything.
The savings, the business, everything!
(SOBBING)
You disgust me.
I have to go Chapter 11...
...then the liquidators will come in.
This is it, David.
You have fucking had it. This is it.
As soon as Eric goes to college...
He got into Georgetown today...
When he's out, you're packing up...
...and you're keeping
the fuck away from my sister!
Don't tell me you blew
his college fund.
Jesus Christ!
You fucking asshole!
How could you do that?
Jesus!
- I'm paying for Eric's education.
- Thank you. Thank you.
You're a great man, Vic.
Wait a minute.
How could you lose the business?
It's in my sister's name.
- I didn't gamble it away, exactly.
- What happened?
I got involved with some bad people,
and I got in debt to them.
Fucking Tony Soprano, all right?
Yeah. Tony-fucking-Soprano.
It's a bust-out.
When you can't pay them...
...they become your partners and eat
through everything, like termites!
- What about the cops?
- They're animals, Vic!
They started a fire
in my dumpster and then...
...these two guys came
to see me one night.
You got no idea what "dead eyes"
means until you face them...
...in your fucking bathrobe
and your flip-flops.
(SNIFFLING)
God damn it.
France, 1944.
General George Patton leads
his Third Army into battle.
He knows that the controversies around
him have tarnished his reputation.
He desperately wants to vindicate
himself in the only way he knows how:
In battle.
(PHONE RINGING)
- Hello?
- It's over, skip.
- What?
- You know that other party...
...who said he saw something
that we know didn't happen?
- Yeah.
- He realizes now he didn't see...
...what didn't happen.
- Yeah.
- Sleep well, my friend.
Major strategy is the attack.
"The more Germans we kill, the fewer
of our men will be killed," he said.
His hatred for the enemy...
...is matched only by his fierce
concern for his men.
(CRICKETS CHIRPING)
(EXHALES)
(SNIFFLES)
- You seem relieved.
- Yeah.
Yeah.
So this person, the witness...
...simply changed his or her mind?
I don't know what happened.
- You don't?
- What's that supposed to mean?
You know, when I was in Italy...
...I met somebody like you.
A woman. And it's not what you think.
Like me in what way?
Smart.
- Know what she said to me?
- What did she say?
- That I'm my own worst enemy.
- Kind of a cliché, isn't it?
You had to be there.
She's one of them...
...witchy broads, you know?
- Not like a psychic, but...
- I didn't mean to sound disparaging.
Well, it's an ancient culture
over there.
They believe all this weird shit.
- Like sibyls.
- Sibyls?
Like I said, you had to be there.
Okay, so I wanted to fuck her.
But she was right, wasn't she?
I mean, I bring all this on myself.
That's what you tell me.
Yes, I suppose it is. At root.
The question is, how do you stop?
You know what?
I dodged a very big bullet. And I'm
feeling pretty fucking good about it.
So I don't need anymore
psychiatry today.
(DOOR CLOSES)
- License and registration, pal.
- Hey, Tony, what are you doing here?
I got something for you.
- What is that?
- Fifty grand.
Get the fuck out of here with that.
- Why, because I'm a paraplegic?
- My idea was for you to donate it...
...to the spinal injury foundation.
I'm gonna walk again, Tony.
I know you are, Beans.
In the meantime, you donate, get
your picture up, you inspire people.
You mean, be like a fucking
poster boy? Is that what you mean?
Take the money. You can whack
it up with the foundation.
Fuck you, Tony.
Take the money, Beans.
You gotta take it.
Beansie.
Thank you! Thank you!
Thank you, Beans.
(POP SONG PLAYING)
(DOORBELL RINGS)
Lilliana, can you get that?
- Ramone!
- Good morning, missus.
Mr. Musto no is come.
- Is he okay?
- He has to go to the other job.
Oh, okay.
(RATTLING)
- Want to steer?
- Yeah.
- No, you don't.
- I do.
I'd let you, but if the harbor
master sees, we'll get in trouble.
Nobody's gonna see.
I don't know.
- Come on.
- Go ahead.
A boat's not like a car. You've got
no breaks and can't make quick turns.
So you've gotta anticipate
your turns a lot sooner.
This is so cool.
Six hundred and twenty horsepower.
(MOTOR REVVING)
Look out, stop!
On your starboard! Look out!
(JOURNEY SONG PLAYING)