Previously on
"You"...
Everyone just calls me Beck.
And you're Joe...
Goldberg.
People find the one.
I believe that.
I was in love, once.
Candace, she broke my heart.
Beck, I should have
seen the signs.
But we never do.
Exhibit A.
Claudia, single parent.
You think she knew Ron was a
shitbag when she fell in love?
You're a freak,
so stay away from Paco.
Because if you don't,
I'm going to grab
a steak knife, and I'll
cut those freak eyes out.
A guy needs to protect himself.
I had to be sure you are safe.
I just need to know
who you really are.
- You're smart.
- Shit, my phone.
Must have
dropped it in the subway.
Except in the ways
you are really not,
like not locking your phone.
And that means
I'm still logged into you.
Maybe we could
get a drink sometime?
Sure.
Hell, maybe I'm just
a fool in love.
It just feels right.
I'm going to help you
get the life you deserve.
You have
questionable taste in friends.
Hey, man, I'm thinking, maybe...
You fall for the wrong men.
Get up on the fence!
Beck, were you ever
sleeping with your therapist?
Yes, I cheated,
but it's over now.
What he did to me,
one of these days,
he's going to do to you.
Maybe he'll do whatever
the hell he did to Candace.
I need you to tell me
what happened with Candace.
Why, why does that even matter?
Because there's no evidence
that she was in Italy at all.
No one's heard a single word
from her since she left.
I know you, you won't
stop asking questions
until I do something about this.
[whispering] What the hell?
[gasps]
I'll call you later.
This, Beck,
is between me and you.
[dramatic music]
Joe, Joe!
[soft music]
- Please, I'm sorry.
- Move, move!
I was just
organizing the shelves.
You think you know
my business better than I do?
Get in, and you'll stay in
until you understand!
Understand what?
Who I am to you.
[dramatic music]
[pounding]
Joe!
[ominous music]
I'm here.
[softly] Joe.
Why...
am I in here?
Well, that's good,
because we're talking.
We're getting it
out in the open.
- You hit me!
- I'm sorry.
Beck, I'm sorry.
I just... I didn't
want you to freak out.
Joe, I am locked
in a glass cage!
Temporarily.
- How long?
- What?
How long are you going
to keep me in here?
If this is just temporary.
Oh, honestly, I haven't
thought that far ahead.
I... I...
I just... I need to know
that I can trust you
- to see the truth.
- What truth is that?
Everything I have done,
I have done for you.
Even this?
Even this.
- Oh, God.
- [crying]
I wish I knew
what you were thinking.
Tell me.
[tense music]
What's in the box?
Tell me.
Tell me I'm crazy.
Tell me you didn't kill Benji.
Tell me you didn't kill Peach.
- If you knew what I knew.
- [sharp exhale]
[sobbing]
- Shit, Beck, that's right.
- You have no idea.
I promised you the truth,
and I'm going to give you that.
[sobs]
Wait, Joe.
Don't leave!
I'm not.
We're going to get through this.
Joe...
[pounds on glass]
Joe!
No, Joe!
Joe, Joe!
[high-pitched ringing]
[soft dramatic music]
That could have gone worse.
I knew you'd be scared.
That's why I tried
to protect you from the truth.
[phone dings]
And now, I need to
protect us from the world,
long enough to work this out.
So, business as usual.
They're the best cover.
As far as your friends
are concerned,
you're going off the grid.
[keys clacking]
And it wouldn't be
a true social media detox
without announcing it
to the world.
I'll be back soon.
The basement is off limits
until I finish
open heart surgery
on a first edition Sylvia Plath.
Nice, uh, what kind
of condition is she in?
- Fragile.
- She's very fragile.
Evidence, evidence is all I need
to prove to you
I'm not some sicko.
I'm your protector.
You'll see.
[sirens wailing]
Let's skip the
"nothing to see here."
- Get straight to moving along.
- No, this is my building.
- That's my neighbor, Claudia.
- Your neighbor, huh?
- Yeah.
- So then you know the piece
of shit who
gave her a concussion?
- Yeah, his name is Ron.
- Oh, I know who he is.
That's him.
Why is he not
in the back of your cruiser?
Victim insisted
it was an accident.
- She has a kid, Paco.
- Where is he?
I didn't see
any children in there.
Probably for the best.
[dramatic music]
Joe.
You can't leave me in here.
- I'm not... I'm not.
- I'm sorry.
Look, it's pointless to try
to explain anything to you
without evidence,
so no more secrets.
Ask me anything.
So we both knew
Benji was a dick, right?
What you didn't know...
[keyboard clacking]
He was a murderer.
He killed an innocent kid.
- He's, he's playing dead.
- He's playing dead.
Oh, shit!
[camera fumbles]
No remorse, I fully maintain
he was sociopathic,
and dangerous,
dangerous for you.
And Peach, oh, she was obsessed.
And she was
hoarding these for years.
She needed to own you, to trap
you, to make you her pet.
And what happened
once she was gone?
You blossomed,
you were published.
I... I get why you'd be freaked,
all stuffed in like this.
But they're just mementos,
you know?
Like holding on
to an old photograph.
Or you wearing
my shirt to sleep.
You can't tell me
that's so crazy.
It's the stuff
of a million love songs.
I know this is a lot.
Honestly, I'm terrified
sharing this with you.
But if we're being honest,
your life has been better
since you met me.
You just didn't
know how, or why.
Until now.
Beck, I love you.
And loving someone means
you will do anything for them.
[ominous music]
- Benji's.
- [exhales]
I had to burn his body.
- And Peach?
- Well, she tried to kill me.
That was
straight-up self defense.
- It was, it was self de...
- Oh, God.
- [sobbing] It's true.
- Please don't.
- No, please!
- No, no, calm down, please.
- Please don't hurt me!
- Please calm down.
No, you don't understand.
Please calm down.
- You killed them!
- Beck, Beck, Beck.
- You're a murderer, you freak!
- No, that's not true!
- No, you haven't...
- Get away from me!
- Please don't hurt me.
- You don't understand.
I would never
hurt someone I love.
Tell that to Candace,
you sick fuck!
You're not listening.
[tense music]
[grunts] Help!
Help!
Help me, please!
Please!
[soft music]
- Good morning.
- [screams]
- Get away!
- It's okay.
What were you
trying to do to me?
- I was just making it cozy.
- Look.
You were sleeping so deep,
I didn't want to disturb you.
Well, consider me disturbed.
Here, I brought you breakfast.
Somehow, being inches
from a bucket of my own pee
has killed my appetite.
Oh, well, I emptied the bucket,
in case you ever doubt what
I'm willing to do for love.
And you're not going to
want to pass up avocado toast.
From Dudley's, and uh, coffee.
Just how you like it.
I always wondered
what that was for.
Uh, oh, yeah.
Mooney claims he built it
for secure cash transactions.
I never saw anybody
down here but me.
I spent a lot of time in here
when I was younger.
I was always
getting into trouble.
Mooney...
he...
he was my Mr. Miyagi.
[tense music]
If Miyagi was
a Soviet prison guard.
- Who am I to you?
- You're an asshole.
Yes, but who else do you have?
Your father, who used
your armpit for an ashtray?
Your mother, who never
did anything to stop him?
Or maybe you miss that
insect ridden group home
that drove you to my doorstep.
[scoffs]
You don't care about me.
This place could be
your salvation.
Here...
you're safe,
surrounded by the
greatest works of humanity.
With no choice but to absorb
the wisdom of better men.
Beck, in the end, the cage
was a good thing for me.
I'm hoping it will
be the same for you.
Look, look, hence, typewriter,
paper, no distractions.
It's the low tech writer's
retreat you always wanted.
I feel bad for you, Joe.
[soft music]
- Was that pity?
- Disgust?
[door clanks shut]
Empathy?
Beck, I am really
putting myself out there.
The least you could do
is acknowledge that.
- Hey, not today, little man.
- Hey, look at me!
Are you out of your mind?
What do you think you're doing?
- Get your hands off him.
- Hey, I caught this punk
trying to steal
the gun from the register.
- Okay, okay, all right.
- It's not loaded.
Oh, it's loaded.
I'll handle it.
- This is not a toy.
- I know, I'm not dumb.
- I think you are.
- I think only an idiot
tries what you just pulled.
I know why you want a gun, Paco.
Even if you don't kill yourself
with this thing first,
the second you use it
on Ron, your life is over.
That is the definition of dumb.
[gun thuds, drawer shuts]
I'm sorry.
I know that was harsh.
[exhales]
It's a key to my place.
You can go there, it's safe.
Cool down, crash
as long as you need to.
And we'll talk about this later.
[tense music]
[cell phone dings]
I'm not thinking straight,
and it's your fault.
Beck, I can only
buy us so much time.
And my patience is wearing thin.
- Joe, where have you been?
- Hey.
- Whoo, hey.
- Let's skip the small talk.
I just want to know
if Beck is okay.
- Wait, what do you mean okay?
- We had a fight.
- I haven't heard from her.
- Oh, I think it's okay
to tell you,
she's on a writing retreat.
- Yeah.
- [both laugh]
- It's all good, relax.
- She's not texting us, either.
I just... I just want
to know she's safe.
Both: Yeah.
- [soft laugh]
What was the fight about?
Uh...
[sighs]
I caught her cheating
with her therapist.
- No way.
- What?
Oh, my God, no way.
- Dr. Nicky?
- Is she kidding?
- Oh, my God. Whoa.
- Beck!
- Joe, I am so sorry.
- Yeah.
- So sorry.
- I'm so sorry, we had no idea.
I... I thought we could
work through it,
but then, she ghosted me.
Wait, when she texted,
she said that her retreat
was therapeutic.
You don't think
that she's still...
I mean... yeah.
- Wow.
[scoffs]
I really thought
you two were endgame.
It just kind of
shakes your faith, you know?
- I don't know.
- Do you really believe
that Beck and I
are the real deal?
Joe, I've known Beck
a long time, and I have...
I've never seen her happier.
Or like,
more grounded, or whatever.
I really think that you
bring out the best in her.
I think she brings out
the best in me, too.
Hey, maybe it's not so bad.
Maybe... maybe she's really
on a writing retreat, you know?
Or maybe she's just
trying to dodge that P.I.
because she doesn't
feel like talking about Peach.
- P... wait, P.I.?
- What do you mean?
Apparently, a Salinger
would never commit suicide,
according to the Salingers.
It is so messed up.
They hired this guy,
I don't know.
He's been asking Lynn and I
all of these questions.
He even used
the term "foul play."
Can you believe that?
Joe, we both know what you did.
Why are you surprised?
[tense music]
I'm not going to finish these.
Any of these wontons,
you want them?
Okay.
Thank you.
- I recommend the ponzu.
- The sweet and sour's too sour.
Noted.
You haven't started writing.
I'm still waiting for that
surge of inspiration
I was promised.
You... you seem like you're
doing a little better.
[chuckles]
- Maybe it's relative.
- Mm.
I caught Paco trying to steal
a gun from the register today.
- What?
- Why?
Ron put Claudia in the hospital.
So Paco, I tried talking to him.
I think I just made him angrier.
Well, you got your girlfriend
locked up in a cage.
A P.I.'s snooping around,
and you're worried
about your neighbor's kid.
- I know, it's pretty dumb.
- No.
It's sweet.
[ambient music]
Joe.
I know...
there is a good heart
in there somewhere.
Joe?
Yeah?
I have to pee.
Oh, no, no,
tell me you're not using
Henry Pelham's cartography
as a seat cover.
Sorry, I couldn't
find any Dan Brown.
All right, I'll get out of here.
Joe.
Can I... can I just,
please use the bathroom?
Please, this is dehumanizing.
You can trust me.
Thank you.
Thank you, thank you, thank
you, thank you, thank you.
[gentle music]
- Joe...
- I can't.
I'm sorry.
Joe.
- Joe, please!
- I'll be back in a little bit.
Shit, shit, shit, shit.
[exhales]
I'm so stupid.
This whole time, I was wrong.
- How did I not see this?
- If you see this place
as a prison, that's all
you're going to be, a prisoner.
If you see it as an
opportunity for introspection,
and growth, voila,
we have a future together.
You say you're a writer.
I fell in love with a writer.
Maybe you should be writing.
Well, what now, Joe?
You're going to go
jerk off to my panties?
Or do you need to cut someone
up before you can get hard?
[yells]
[dramatic music]
How the hell
did you end up here?
[tense music]
Your life has been better
since you met me.
You just didn't know how or why.
You paint me up
to be this monster.
Someone who can hurt people,
who can do terrible things.
[typewriter clacking echoes]
You used to wrap yourself
in fairy tales like a blanket.
But it was the cold you loved.
Sharp shivers as you uncovered
the corpses
of Bluebeard's wives.
Sweeter goose bumps
as Prince Charming
slid one glass slipper
over your little toes,
a perfect fit.
But by the schoolyard,
real princesses
floated by you on fall winds.
You saw the gulf between
you and the rich girls,
and vowed to stop
believing in fairy tales.
But the stories
were in you, deep as poison.
If Prince Charming was real,
if he could save you...
You needed to be saved from
the unfairness of everything...
When would he come?
The answer was a cruel shrug
in a hundred fleeting moments.
The sneer on Stevie Smith's face
when he called you a fat cow.
Uncle Jeff's hand
squeezing your ass
in the Thanksgiving kitchen.
The accusation
in your father's eyes
when you told him what happened.
[typewriter clacking echoes]
From every boy masquerading
as a man that you let
into your body, your heart,
you learned you didn't have
whatever magic
turns a beast into a prince.
You surrounded yourself
with the girls
you'd always resented,
hoping to share their power,
and you hated yourself.
And that
diminished you even more.
And then, right when you thought
you might just disappear,
he saw you.
And you knew, somewhere deep,
it was too good to be true.
But you let yourself be swept,
because he was the first
strong enough to lift you.
Now, in his castle,
you understand Prince Charming
and Bluebeard are the same man.
And you don't get a happy end
unless you love both of him.
Didn't you want this?
To be loved?
Didn't you want him
to crown you?
Didn't you ask for it?
So say you can live like this.
Say you love him, say thank you,
say anything but the truth.
What if you can't love him back?
What if you're not the one?
No, now is not the time
to abandon principles.
I have to believe
love conquers all.
And if you love me,
it's only a matter of time.
But time is not on our side.
[tense music]
I don't want
to think worst case.
I don't like
having to scour your place
for evidence that'd
link me to your disappearance.
It's all starting
to feel a little dirty.
Because I'm not
doing it for you anymore.
I'm doing it for me.
And I'm not a selfish person.
[tense music]
You said you believe
I have a good heart somewhere.
I hope you don't mind if I
take a minute to look for it.
Claudia.
- Joe, what are you doing here?
- I'm looking for Paco.
- Is Ron around?
- No.
And I was hoping
that Paco went to find you.
I lost my cell phone when...
The nurses said they tried
calling the apartment,
but nobody answered.
So you... you have no idea
where your son is?
- Jesus, Claudia.
- [sighs]
So damn easy to judge, huh?
Who the hell are you?
I'm the only one in this city
who cares about
your son, apparently.
Why do you do this?
Why do you protect the man
who does this to you
over your child?
Over and over.
You're his mother.
Mothers are supposed
to protect their children
- from men like him.
- I don't need a concerned
neighbor bursting
in here and blaming me
for my own concussion.
[tense music]
Ron has connections.
He's made threats.
You want to know why
he's still in the picture?
I stand up to him,
I lose my boy.
I'm sorry, I didn't know that.
Yeah, of course you didn't.
You have no idea
what it takes to live my life.
They don't write books
about women like me.
No one would think to.
[distant sirens wailing]
Joe Goldberg.
- Hello, P.I.
- Have we met?
Hi, I work for the family
of Peach Salinger.
Just a couple
of quick questions.
- Oh, okay, sure, of course.
- How well did you know Peach?
He's asking,
but he knows already.
Not well, through my ex,
Guinevere Beck.
Well enough to
be saddened by her passing.
You been to
her house in Greenwich?
- That's where she died, right?
- No, no.
I heard about it through Beck.
I know that Peach
was having a hard time
when they were out there.
Um... yeah.
I think you should talk to Beck.
I've been trying to get
a hold of Beck, actually.
- Yeah, well, we... we broke up.
- [chuckles]
So I'm not really in touch.
In fact, if you found me,
that means
you probably found Lynn,
Beck's friend.
She's the one to ask.
Beck, she might be out of town.
Writing, she does that, so.
Good luck.
It was nice to meet you.
You spend a lot of time
at her place
when she's out of town?
Shit.
Well, I... He saw me.
I... I still have a key.
No... in fact, I had a key.
I returned it last night.
[suspenseful music]
Should I be worried?
Are you following me?
Did your ex ever tell you
that Peach had a stalker?
I mean, I know, um...
I remember the awful
Central Park incident.
Peach was attacked, right?
But I wasn't aware
it was anything
more than a random robbery.
Same individual may have been
in the house
the weekend Peach died.
- Seriously?
- Found an item.
- We're testing it for DNA now.
- Wow.
That would be crazy.
I forgot the goddamn jar.
Well, if it's true,
I hope you find the guy.
I should have pissed myself.
Let me know
if there's anything I can do.
Thanks, Joe.
You mind calling if you
think of anything else?
Yeah.
But does urine even hold DNA?
Will do, Ross, yeah.
One thing I learned from my
own time in the cage, Beck.
Never let yourself panic.
No matter how bad it is,
you find a way
to stay calm,
and keep your wits.
[soft music]
- I've been stupid to be mad.
- I messed up.
And you're trying
to help me do better.
I know it's hard to understand.
But sometimes,
we do difficult things
out of caring for someone.
I know the demons
that drive you.
I have them, too.
It takes discipline...
to prevail.
That's why I work you so hard,
why I demand perfection.
My love for the books, respect.
I'm trying to teach you
a code to live by so that
you don't end up
like your father.
And when I fail, you lock me in.
Exactly.
Because I love you.
I only hope it will be enough.
Hey.
Hey, I'm sorry that I...
That I went a little crazy
before.
What's for dinner?
[ambient music]
What's wrong?
What happened?
- Remember the P.I.?
- He paid a visit.
You should have seen him.
I don't think
he bought a word I said.
I'm not a killer.
I didn't plan this.
Like, if I was
some premeditated,
cold-blooded monster,
I wouldn't have missed
anything that would come back to
bite me in the ass like this.
What did you miss?
It doesn't matter,
unless it does.
In which case, you'll know,
because I'll go to prison.
You might get
exactly what you want.
I'll go down for
something I did for you.
And you love that, right?
I mean that's...
That's what you think of me.
No.
That's not true.
You're not a monster, Joe.
I know...
I know I've said some stuff,
but come on, you can't
expect me to be chill.
I mean, look at us.
For the record...
I don't hate you.
I am trying so hard
to understand you.
And can you blame me if I need
a little help getting there?
And what about Paco?
What about Paco?
If you go to jail,
the kid is screwed, right?
You think that's what I want?
You're the only person
who is there for him.
And I think about what happens
to people who don't have anyone.
Joe, for Paco, okay?
Let's try and figure out
a way through this,
so that you can...
So that we can be there for him.
[knocking]
Claudia?
Just open the door, I want...
I just want
to talk to you, just...
[knocking]
Hey, let me in.
I just want...
[dramatic music]
- [yells]
- [grunts]
[body thuds]
[weapon clatters]
You piece of shit!
[dramatic ambient music]
Paco.
Paco, come here,
I want to talk to you.
Paco, come here.
I'm not...
I'm not going to hurt you.
Paco?
Paco, get over here,
I want to talk to you.
Ah...
[suspenseful music]
Paco, come out here.
[gasps]
You're dead.
Hey, Ron.
[grunts]
[chokes, gurgles]
[coughs]
- Joe!
- Paco.
[stirring music]
Okay, this is what
I need you to do
so no one finds out about this,
because people are not really
going to believe us about the
way that it happened, right?
Okay, there's blood in the hall.
You need to clean that up
with soap and water.
And then hit those spots
with bleach, really pour it on.
All right, now this next part
might sound a little weird,
but I think
it might do the trick.
You see this, it's Ron's phone.
I'm going to be texting
your mom from it.
Maybe Ron's boss,
a few of his friends.
So they think he's still alive.
Exactly, so I'm going
to keep that going.
I'm going to take it far away
from here, get rid of it.
All you have to do is say
you don't know where he is.
Shit.
Ron will never hurt or scare you
or your mom ever again,
and I'm sorry.
I'm so sorry you
had to see that,
but it's over.
It's all over now, forever.
Right?
- He was a bad man.
- [exhales] Yeah.
He was.
Does that mean
it was right to kill him?
Sometimes...
we do bad things
for the people we love.
It doesn't mean it's right.
It means love is more important.
All right, go on.
I believe that, Beck.
Love is more important.
But the world is a cruel place.
If I get caught for any of this,
I doubt a jury will
see it the same way.
And you.
[typewriter clacking]
Will you?
There you are.
Read this, Joe.
[ambient music]
A blind verse rendition of
your love story with Dr. Nicky?
Keep reading.
What exactly is this?
It's the story
of everything that happened
once I started having an
affair with my therapist.
I was broken, and trusting,
and I needed help.
And he, little did I know,
he was obsessive,
and very sick, and would stop
at nothing to get closer to me.
And if you skip to the end,
there's this part
where I talk about
a box of mementos
that I found on
Nicky's property, evidence.
A jar of teeth.
Joe, don't you see?
Nicky is your way out, Joe.
Our way out.
It's perfect.
I get it now.
- You get what?
- You.
You did everything...
for me.
No one has ever loved me
the way that you love me.
I mean, you...
You gave me everything.
Let me give this to you.
I mean it.
I understand.
I was scared.
I could have done something...
Something really stupid
when I found that box,
But this, this...
gave me time to think.
- I hurt you.
- I scared you.
I understand if you hate me.
I love you, actually.
More than ever.
And I can wait
until you're ready.
It's not so bad in here.
You take care of me,
and no one has ever
taken care of me before,
not like you.
It's all I ever wanted to do.
And when you're ready,
we can take my story public.
And then, you and I, we can go
somewhere and start our life.
And... and I... I haven't,
I haven't thought beyond that,
but Joe, I...
I know that I am better
with you than without you.
[whispers] Beck...
Oh, if you were in here, this
would be our moment to kiss.
It's like, the music swells
and everything.
[orchestral music swelling]
But I know...
I know you don't
trust me enough yet.
I get it.
[exhales]
Oh, we're crazy.
[keys jingling]
[lock clicks, turns]
[ambient tone]
[ominous music]
[both grunt]
[groans]
[dramatic music]
Beck!
Wait, wait, wait, please.
Wait... I know...
I know you're angry, I know.
You have no idea what I am,
you fucking psychopath!
I knew it was
too good to be true.
What, all the
nice things I said to you
while I was locked in a cage?
You actually believe that all
of this is somehow justified?
- It is.
- Fuck, you are insane.
You think that
you did some bad shit,
and that I did some bad shit,
and that this...
This is equivalent?
Yeah, I lied, I cheated,
but I... I didn't stalk you.
I didn't hit you.
I didn't kill people.
I didn't do any of this!
There's not a line
in the world
that I wouldn't cross for you.
I didn't ask you
to swoop in for me.
But you did,
your life was a mess.
Yes, but it was my life.
And I didn't need some
sociopath on a white horse
to clean house.
I mean,
what gives you the right?
You thought that
I would be grateful?
[exhales]
You.
You're him.
You are the bad thing.
You are the thing
that you should have killed.
If you let me out...
- we can just talk...
- You know what I think?
I think that this was
all just an excuse.
An excuse to justify
creeping into girls' lives,
and violating
the shit out of them.
I think you love it!
- The power, you love it!
- No, I don't.
I think that this, this was
the perfect excuse
to take out people, like...
Like Benji, and Peach,
who have always
looked down on you
and your whole miserable life.
God, but you...
You are not special.
You're broken.
I could never love you.
Rot in there,
you psychotic asshole.
You're going to spend
the rest of your life in jail.
Joe?
[dramatic music]
[grunts] Help!
[muffled]
Help!
Paco.
Paco, thank God.
I need your help.
Open this door right now.
Joe, he is downstairs,
and he's crazy.
- Joe?
- Paco.
He has killed people.
He's going to kill me.
Open this door right now.
Paco, open the door!
Open the door, please!
Please, Paco, no!
No, Paco!
[muffled screams]
Keys, keys.
[gasps]
When Mooney locked me in,
I learned a big lesson.
Hide a spare key so you can
get out of the goddamn cage.
I didn't want it
to be like this, Beck.
I know.
I know, just...
put me back in there.
[dramatic music]
[screams]
[indistinct chatter]
These have been
selling like crazy.
Is it true she worked here?
- Uh, yeah, it's true.
- I knew her well.
- I'm so sorry.
- It's really tragic.
It's pretty weird when
someone dies,
and you literally can't
get away from them on the news.
Enjoy the book.
She was a really good writer.
You really were, Beck.
I miss you so much.
It's been a weird four months.
I had to do a lot
for you, in the end.
[somber alternative rock music]
You wrote the story.
All I did was bring it to life.
The story was perfect.
So everyone believed it.
- Doctor, Doctor!
- [indistinct clamoring]
What drove you
to murder Guinevere Beck?
Yes, she was definitely
having an affair
with her therapist.
That evil [bleep].
You know her friend,
Peach Salinger,
was trying to get Beck
to stop seeing him,
so it's like, did that
psycho kill Peach, too?
I received the
manuscript in the mail.
It was odd, but far and away
the most moving prose I'd read
since Zadie's second to last.
It was also the most horrifying
because I came to understand
that Beck was illuminating
her very own imminent murder.
That's when I knew.
I had to show it to
my literary agent right away.
It's true, maybe not everyone
was completely convinced.
Bullshit.
But you know what,
doesn't matter.
The evidence was overwhelming.
Thanks to your
hard work, and mine.
It's the last thing
we ever did together.
In the end,
you couldn't love me.
I feel at peace with that now,
because I loved you
the absolute best that I could.
And I gave you what you wanted.
I feel good about that.
I helped you become
the writer you so wanted to be.
Your lurid memoir
of Dr. Nicky was the lede,
but I cobbled
that manuscript together
from every one of
your pieces fit to print.
The book is yours, Beck,
and it made you famous.
It's sad you're
not here to see it.
But I know
you would be so happy.
- So, California.
- Yeah, that's great, you know?
You got the job.
Paco's going to love it.
- Yeah, I think so.
- Weather's so good.
- So, Ron?
- Disappeared into thin air.
I don't get it, but
you know, everyone knew
he was a troubled guy.
He had gambling debts,
who knows.
It's for the best.
I know I haven't always
been the nicest about it,
but, uh...
thanks for always
being so good to my son.
[scoffs] That's... it's nothing.
Really.
Yeah.
I'll let you say good-bye.
Hey, Pac.
- I'll miss you.
- Me too.
Hey, you know, it's okay
if things are hard sometimes.
You can still be a good person,
and have a really good life.
That's what I want for you.
This is good, a fresh start.
[soft music]
You can put the bad things
behind you.
Yeah.
You too.
I'm trying, I am.
But I'll admit,
it's getting harder to live
with so much heartbreak.
And there are days,
I just don't believe in love.
I tell myself
to keep my heart open,
that in the end,
I was wrong about you.
Every relationship teaches us
hard lessons, right?
That's their gift,
to make us ready for the day
when someone,
maybe the one, walks in
who could truly love us...
[clanging]
And we could truly love them.
Well.
Hello, there.
Who are you?
You've got that hoodie.
You don't like to be stared at.
But your legs are bare.
You like a little attention.
Okay, I'll bite.
[tense music]
Hey, bunny.
Candace.
- You're...
- Alive.
Yeah, so uh...
I think we have some unfinished
business to talk about.