So, do you want to see it
or not?
I don't know.
I don't like
Friday night crowds.
Oh, my God.
You're, like, agoraphobic.
Agoraphobic?
- Really?
- Yeah!
You would rather
sit on your couch
and watch a Phillies game
then go out to a movie
with your awesome girlfriend.
Absolutely correct.
Later, Jim.
- Kev, have a good weekend.
- Bye.
Okay, so this is
what's gonna happen.
You're gonna suck it up...
- Here we go.
And we're gonna go to dinner...
- Okay.
And then we're gonna go
to the movies.
- Sounds good.
- Hey, Halpert!
Hey.
Roy!
Ahh!
Roy, don't!
God!
Pam, please call security.
Every day for eight years,
I have brought
pepper spray into this office
to protect myself
and my fellow employees.
And every day for eight years,
people have laughed at me.
Well.
Who's laughing now?
No need for consternation.
Everything is under control.
Michael, last Friday
one of your employees
attacked another employee
in your office.
It was a crime of passion, Jan,
not a disgruntled employee.
Everyone here
is extremely gruntled.
Is Toby there?
- No.
- I'm here, Jan.
Wh-what is
the situation, Toby?
Well, we fired Roy, obviously.
And Jim won't press charges
against Roy or the company.
- Thank God.
- Yeah.
Um, but now apparently
Darryl has some issue with...
No, he has been wanting a raise
for a couple of months
and he's just using
this Roy thing as leverage.
All right, well, are
you gonna take care of this?
Yeppers.
What did I tell you
about "yeppers?"
I don't remember.
I told you not to say it.
Do you remember that?
Ye... sh.
I really don't want
to talk about it.
I don't mean to be rude,
but I just... I don't want
to comment on what happened.
It sucked.
I guess...
all things considered...
I was lucky Dwight was there.
And Roy was lucky that Dwight
only used pepper spray,
and not the nunchucks
or the throwing stars.
Hey, man, I never got
a chance to thank you.
For stopping Roy.
Thank you.
"Thank you" not necessary,
and thus not accepted.
I saw someone breaking
the law, and I interceded.
Okay.
Um... got you something.
Don't want it.
You don't know what it is.
Don't want it. Won't open it.
Don't need it. Won't take it.
Citizens do not accept
prizes for being citizens.
It was a little glass display
case for his bobble head.
That would have made
his evening, I think.
He saves my life, I get him
a box for his desk toy.
Even Steven.
No, don't call me a hero.
Do you know who the real
heroes are?
The guys who wake up
every morning
and go into their normal jobs,
and get a distress call
from the commissioner,
and take off their glasses
and change into capes,
and fly around fighting crime.
Those are the real heroes.
Angela.
Roy's check, he's coming
in later to pick it up.
Man...
I cannot believe
I missed the fight.
It was crazy.
You saw it?
Describe it, please.
Well...
I heard some shouting.
And I look over,
and Roy's by reception.
And you could just tell
he's gonna punch somebody.
Jim says something.
Roy stomps all over there.
All of a sudden... bam!
Roy goes down,
and Dwight's standing there
like an action hero.
Oh!
It was insane.
Well... good for Dwight.
Okay, I want you to be Darryl
and ask me for a raise,
because I need to try out
some of these
negotiation tactics on you.
Where'd you get that?
Wikipedia.
Wikipedia is
the best thing ever.
Anyone in the world
can write anything they want
about any subject.
So you know you are getting
the best possible information.
Okay, Darryl,
ask me for a raise.
Hey, Mike, since Roy left
I've been doing a lot more work,
and I need a raise.
Hmm, well, that's
interesting, Darryl.
I think...
that maybe you should...
I can't hear you.
What I'm saying is that...
Still nothing.
Okay, see what I did?
- No.
By leaning back
and by whispering,
I established a dominant
physical position.
Nice.
Okay, let's try another one.
- Okay.
Walking out of the
room unexpectently.
And what happens in this one?
That's a surprise.
- Go ahead, ask me for a raise.
- Can I have a raise?
Sex, Steve Martin,
Teri Hatcher. What?
What did you say?
I didn't say anything, I'm
waiting to see what happened.
This is interesting,
what your given.
I saw the perpetrator
advance towards the victim,
at a high rate of speed.
His head was thrown back,
his shoulder and arm cocked,
indicating an attack position.
Perp grabbed the victim,
I removed my weapon
from its secure hiding place.
- Which is where?
- Irrelevant.
Discharged it at a distance
of a little over a meter,
Into the perpetrators eyes,
nose and face area.
Rendering him utterly
and completely disabled.
Then I contacted
the authorities.
The end.
Thanks, Dwight.
That is the bravest thing
I have ever heard.
I can't imagine
what I would've done.
I do.
You would've left me
to fend for myself.
Like the time we were
on the Ferris wheel
and that kid dropped
a milkshake on me
and you just laughed.
Well, that was funny.
That's why.
Oh, it was?
- Mm-hmm.
Okay, well, the next time
that you get scared
that you think a murderer
is in your apartment
in the middle of the night
and you call me
to calm you down...
Can you stop?
Because I'm not gonna do it
anymore, Ryan, I'm not.
There's a bunch of people
back there maybe.
I call you
in the middle of the night
to tell you that I love you.
- Guys?
I don't think Michael
intended to punish me
by putting Ryan back here
with Kelly.
But if he did
intend that... wow.
Genius.
Yeah.
You ready for me?
Yes, yeah, absolutely.
Have a seat.
You know what?
Actually, let's go
into the conference room.
- Okay.
- No, you know what? Let's stay here.
No, let's go to the con...
Yeah, let's go
to the conference room.
Tactic number six.
Change the location
of the meeting
at the last second.
Totally throws 'em off.
Number 14.
Declining to speak first.
Makes them feel uncomfortable,
puts you in control.
I am declining to speak first.
Okay, I'll start.
It's pretty simple really.
I, um, I think
I deserve a raise.
I'm scheduled to get one
in six months,
but I'd like that
to be moved up to now.
Hmm.
Ohh, Darryl.
You are a good worker
and a good man.
I just... you know,
times are tight.
And I just don't think
corporate's going to go
for this right now.
Are you wearing lady clothes?
What?
Those look like lady pants.
No, this is a power suit.
That there's a woman's suit.
I do not buy women's clothes.
Would not make
that mistake again.
I'm gonna call Roy, man.
- Okay.
This is gonna make him feel better.
- All right.
This is too good!
All right, you know what?
Pam, would you please
tell Darryl
that this is not a woman's suit.
Oh, my God.
That's a woman's suit.
You're wearing a woman's suit?
No, I do...
I wear men's suits.
Okay, I got this out of a bin.
There were these huge
bins of clothes,
and everybody was rifling
through them like crazy,
and I grabbed one.
And it fit.
So I don't think
that is totally
just a woman's suit.
At the very least it's bisexual.
Who makes it?
Um, MISSterious.
And it is mysterious,
because the buttons
are on the wrong side.
That's the mystery.
It's got shoulder pads.
And did you see that lining?
Okay, would you stop it, please?
So, none of that tipped you off?
It's a European, okay?
It's a European cut.
Michael, the pants don't
have any pockets.
No, they don't.
See?
Italians don't wear pockets.
It's been a really
rough couple of days.
This helps a little.
Maybe you want to come over
and raid my closet.
No, I don't want to do that because
I'm twice your size anyway.
Yeah,
he look like Hillary Clinton.
Let's just do this in 15.
Okay. Can you stand
right there for one second.
I gotta send some emails.
Negotiations are all about
controlling things.
About being
in the driver's seat.
And... you make one
tiny mistake, you're dead.
I made one tiny mistake.
I wore women's clothes.
So Karen, how do you feel
that Roy tried to kick
your boyfriend's ass
over another woman?
I feel great, Kevin.
Thank you.
You must have been
scared out of your mind.
It happened so fast,
I didn't have time to be scared.
What happened exactly?
I wasn't here,
so I haven't really
heard the whole story.
Um, well, Jim and I
were talking.
Mm-hmm.
And Roy walked in
looking super angry.
And he's a big dude, you know?
And all of a sudden,
Jim pushed me out of the way.
And Roy cocked his fist.
And then... bam!
Dwight sprays him
and knocks him on his butt.
Goodness.
When I heard Jim and Pam
had kissed.
My reaction was to have
lots of long talks
with Jim about our feelings.
Roy just attacked him.
I'm not sure which one
Jim hated more.
Let's get down to business.
Why don't you tell me
why you think you
deserve a raise.
Well, it's simple Mike. We merged
these two branches, right?
So now, we're shipping twice
as many orders as we used too.
With Roy gone,
we have a smaller crew,
and I'm picking up
all his slack.
So, I think I should be compensated,
fairly, by getting a raise.
Those are very good points.
What?
I can't hear you.
Those are very good points.
I can't. What?
Mike, are you...
You make very
compelling arguments.
Sorry I almost got you killed.
Yeah.
That was nuts.
He could have broken your nose
or something.
Crazy.
It's just so stupid.
I mean, getting back
with Roy and everything.
I mean, what
was I thinking, right?
No, I mean, you guys really seem
to have a strong connection.
Not anymore.
It's, um...
it's completely over now.
We'll see.
I'm sure you guys'll...
find your way
back to one another someday.
Jim...
I am really... sorry.
Oh, yeah.
Don't worry about it.
I'm going to give you
a piece of paper.
I want you to write down
how much you want,
then I want you to slide it
back across the desk to me.
Why can't I just tell you?
Because, that is the way
these things are done.
In films.
No, slide... slide it, yes.
There you go.
Oh...
Come on... be serious.
I am serious, Mike.
That's a 10% raise.
That's what I want.
I can't give you that.
I-I don't make this much.
Come on, be for real, Mike.
I don't.
I'll prove it to you.
There is a pay stub.
Are you serious?
You're earning this?
Plus perks, yes.
Mike, this is barely
more than I make.
You've been here ten years, dog.
14 years.
Hoho!
No, please...
please don't...
Oh, sorry, Mike.
Some of my folks got
to hear about this one.
Ah.
Okay, let's take 15 again.
A boss's salary
isn't just about money.
It is about perks.
It... for example,
every year,
I get a $100 gas card.
Can't put a price tag on that.
Okay, if you don't want a gift
at least let me buy you a beer,
or lunch or something.
When Han Solo returns
to the Death Star
in the Millennium Falcon,
and shoots down the Tie Fighter
and saves the rebel cause...
Do you think he does so
for a free beer?
- Boy, I...
- No!
And why are you so interested
in buying me something, Jim
What's your angle?
It's like when he annoys me and I want
ot screw with him to get him back.
He never sees it coming.
But now I want to be nice to him
and actually give him something.
He's like an eel,
I just can't grab onto him.
It's infuriating.
Maybe you just feel
guilty about all the pranks.
Yes, that's probably what it is.
So, what do I do?
Hmm.
I don't know.
Maybe you should
go back out there and sell
paper, so we can go on a trip.
Michael.
Hmm?
Here's the, uh, $15 I owe you.
- Oh, thank you.
- Yeah.
I heard you might need it.
So... just take it.
Here's the $40 you gave me.
I didn't give you $40.
In a way you did.
Yeah, I heard how much
Michael makes.
I still think he's way overpaid.
14 years. 14.
I know.
Okay, I gotta go. Late.
Okay.
Okay, here's the straight dope.
No tricks, no Wikipedia.
What?
I talked to corporate,
and they told me
that I can only
give you a 5% raise.
That's 'cause of you, Mike.
They're not gonna give
the working man
more than the boss.
Well, what am I supposed to do?
Get your own raise.
You gotta get out there
and earn, son.
I'm not gonna go out
and ask for a raise right now.
That is ridiculous.
Well when they merged
the two branches together,
they put you in charge.
Okay, and we shippin' more now
than we ever have.
That's true.
You gotta call your girl...
and get paid.
Show her who wears the pants
in the relationship.
You know what?
I should.
Yeah you should.
I have been an loyal
employee for a long time.
14 years long.
You know what?
I deserve a bump.
Make it happen, Captain.
I am makin' it happen...
Sergeant.
I remember it was very late at
night, about 11:00 or 11:30
Big fellow came in screaming
about God knows what,
I think maybe Halpert
had stolen his car.
The big fellow pulls out a sock
full of nickels.
Then Schrute grabs a can of
hairspray and a lighter.
You're useless.
We'll talk next month after
the quarter ends.
No, Jan.
I've never asked for a raise
in 14 years.
This is long overdue.
I wanna do it today.
Today? All right.
Well, if you want to
do it today...
We should do it in person
and can you get here by Five?
Yeah!
yeah, I'll leave right away.
Well, uh, listen,
because of our, uh, situation,
we're gonna need to have
a third party present.
Yes, I'm bringing Darryl.
D-Darryl
from the warehouse?
Mm-hmm.
No, Michael.
We... we need an H.R. rep.
So uh, you should
just bring Toby.
Hey... I'd rather
kill myself.
Michael, he's your branch's
H.R. rep.
- Toby is terrible.
- And we need someone else in the room
- Toby is the worst human being
- because of our relationship.
- I've ever known... You know this.
- Michael!
Either Toby comes with you,
or we don't do it.
Fine.
- You are so mean.
- I don't know what you're talking about.
Yes you do, Ryan Bailey
Howard. You call me "stupid."
Toby, come on, let's go.
Where?
I'm gonna smack you in the head
with a hammer.
Come on, let's go.
All right.
- Comfortable, Mike?
- Yeah.
- What about you? You comfortable?
- No.
Don't ever touch
a black man's radio!
Chris Tucker.
Rush Hour.
You know?
I won't touch yours, by the way.
Thank you.
Well...
I haven't been to
New York in a long time.
Maybe I'll stay overnight.
Got a cousin live down there.
How would we get home?
Oh, you could stay too.
He's got a big place.
- Maybe I'll stay.
- It's not that big.
The busses will get
ya home quick.
And then all of a sudden,
Dwight stood up
and was like, "No!"
Then what'd he do?
Well, you should just
read the report that Toby did.
He took everyone's stories.
Customer Service, this is Kelly.
Yes, I can help you with that.
Let me pull up your file.
Okay, it seems here that you
ordered 12,000 reams of paper.
Oh, 12 reams.
Hey, guys.
Jan is ready for you.
Okay.
Okay, bring it home now.
And don't forget the new
black man phrase I taught you.
Pippity poppity,
give me the zoppity.
Yes, sir!
Remember that.
I'll be right outside
if you need me.
All right.
I want him to get the raise.
I...just can't
help myself.
Hey, man, uh...
I'm sorry.
Thanks.
Can I, like...
see you after work
for coffee or something?
I don't know.
Please.
I just got some stuff
I gotta say to you.
Jim!
Roy.
Look out!
Thanks, Kev.
I'm... good, though.
Thank you, Hunter.
Hello, come in.
Who's the boy toy?
My new assistant.
Were you going to tell me that
you hired James Van Der Beek
I have to call you when I get
a new assistant now?
It would be nice to get a memo,
We are lovers.
Hi, Jan.
Hi, Toby.
First off, Michael,
this a salary negotiation.
All matters regarding
our personal relationship
have to be set aside.
Are we clear?
Bippity boppity.
Right now, we can
offer you a 6% raise.
6%?
Mm-hmm.
After all we've been through?
Oh, God.
I got you jade earrings.
- Michael...
- No. No.
No. You're gonna
play it like this?
You give me a good raise,
or no more sex.
What are you writing,
perv-ball?
Just preparing
for the deposition.
This may be the first time
that a male subordinate
has attempted to get
a modest, scheduled raise
by threatening to withhold sex
from a female superior.
It will be
a groundbreaking case...
when it inevitably
goes to trial.
I'm so sorry, Pammy.
I really wasn't
gonna do anything.
But then I... kept thinking
about you two together, and...
I just thought you guys
were really good friends or...
or maybe he was gay
or something.
Not that that's wrong.
I'm sorry too.
I just... I think that we
both made some bad choices.
So you gonna start
datin' Halpert, then?
Um... no.
No, he has a girlfriend.
Oh, yeah.
Wait a minute, you broke off
our wedding for the guy.
No.
There were a lot of reasons.
You mean you're not even
gonna try to go out with him?
I don't get you, Pam.
I know.
What's this?
What's what?
"Certificate of Bravery
"from the Scranton
Police Department.
"Recognizing
outstanding citizenship
from a very brave young man,
Dwight K. Schrute"?
Wow, I guess word got around.
That's a nice honor.
Please, they hand these
out to little kids.
Look, there's a teddy bear
in a policeman's cap.
Mm... didn't think
you'd notice.
Why don't you just take that pen
and stab me in the heart.
This is me, Jan.
This is me!
Michael, why don't
we just take a break?
Okay.
No, no, no, no.
You do not try tactic
number 8 on me.
I invented tactic number 8.
Okay, Toby how about if you...
- Sure.
What's wrong with you?
Ohh.
It was a weird day.
I accidentally
cross-dressed.
And then Darryl made me feel bad
for not making any money.
And then I had to ride up here
with stupid Toby.
And then...
your assistant,
is all young and hot...
Okay, Michael...
I can offer you a 12% raise.
But...
you have got to ask for 15.
That's ridiculous.
I'm never gonna make...
No, just...
I just need you to ask for it...
so I can record
that you asked for it.
'Kay?
Ah, so...
All right, Levinson.
Here's the rub.
I would like a 15% raise.
No! But we can
offer you 12.
But you just said 15.
Negotiation is an art.
Back and forth, give and take.
And today, both Darryl and I
took something.
Higher salaries.
Win, win, win.
But, you know,
life is about more
than just salary.
It's about... perks.
Like having sex with Jan.
Michael!
I've been doing some
very interesting reading.
Really?
Mm-hmm.
Tales of bravery.
Hmm. Good stuff?
Mm-hmm.
I was thinking tonight,
we could...
read it together.
That sounds...
fun.
I...
will never say a word.
And now... we are even.
I graduated from anger
management the same way
I graduated from Cornell... on
time.
Now I'm back,
got a second chance,
and I'm not gonna blow it.
So look out,
Dunder-Mifflin!
I mean "look out" in a fun way.
You know, not like,
"I'm gonna hurt you."
Hey, guys!
Guess who's back?
Aah! Aah!
Ohh, God!
No need to thank me.
I am not a hero.
I am a mere defender of the
office.
You know who's a real hero?
Hiro from "Heroes."
That's a hero.
Also Bono.