♪ Stars shining bright above you ♪
♪ Night breezes seem to whisper
"I love you" ♪
♪ Birds singing in the sycamore tree ♪
♪ Dream a little dream of me ♪
♪ Say "Nightie-night" and kiss me ♪
♪ Just hold me tight
And tell me you'll miss me ♪
♪ While I'm alone and blue as can be ♪
♪ Dream a little dream of me ♪
♪ Sweet dreams till sunbeams find you ♪
♪ Sweet dreams that leave
All worries behind you ♪
♪ But in your dreams whatever they be ♪
♪ Dream a little dream ♪
♪ Of me ♪
Let's not forget that, uh...
That in all this...
I lost someone I love.
So, you still say
you didn't kill her?
Well, I say that
because I did not kill her.
You loved this woman.
You knew her. You knew her life.
Do you have some idea who did?
I do, yeah.
How you doing, Henry?
- Good, thanks, sir.
- Yeah?
Why were you there that night?
Outside her apartment?
Because I was walking.
Like I always do. I didn't know where
I was. I've told you this many times.
It is just such a coincidence,
isn't it, that...
I was having an affair with her,
and you were there.
- Just as I was, or just had been.
- Oh, my God.
What are you asking me?
Were you following me?
Was I following you?
Were you?
Were you following me?
- Are you fucking kidding me?
- Were you following me, Grace?
Don't you dare say that...
- You Jonathan Fraser?
- Excuse me.
- Can we take a selfie with you?
- This is wild!
- Johnny! Right here!
- No. No.
- Quick selfie.
- No. No. Come on.
- This is...
- Grace!
Grace!
How are we doing?
What's going on?
Um...
I think we're both, um...
A little pre-trial nerves, that's all.
Look, they have a strong case.
No question.
But it's circumstantial.
Nobody saw anything.
They don't have a murder weapon,
and some of the science actually helps us.
Their case is vulnerable.
So you keep saying,
um, although with a little more
anxiety each time you say it.
Here's my question.
What's our case, Haley?
Because I don't really have
clarity on that.
Our defense is wait and see.
I told you. It's fluid.
Fluid. Okay, great.
That gives me great confidence. Thank you.
It depends on what they throw at us.
Okay. Let's break it down.
Our case is you.
You say you didn't do it.
Explain why you ran.
And our case is you.
You say, "Believe what he just said."
I can't imagine that the word of a
devoted wife would carry much weight.
Are you devoted, Grace?
I'm here.
Under the circumstances,
I think I deserve a medal.
We have seven women on the jury.
These five are educated,
working professionals.
Just like you.
These two have been cheated on
by their husbands.
Just like you.
And then there's this guy.
He knows better than most
that infidelity doesn't mean murder.
He's having an affair himself.
- How could you possibly know that?
- I know all these people.
We piggyback on the algorithms
of both Amazon and Google.
I know where they go shopping,
Where they go to eat,
where they go on vacation. We know it all.
We're already targeting their
Instagram and Facebook accounts
- with pro-defense news feeds.
- Is that legal?
It's gray enough to get away with.
We do have one little problem.
The same question keeps coming up
in all our focus trials.
If you didn't do it, then who did?
We need to offer up another suspect.
Whoa.
Well, what about his alibi?
Oh, it stinks. I can nick it.
Take his hand, would you please?
I mean, now.
- Why?
- Because I said so.
Do it.
Feel his hand.
Feel hers.
Feel together.
If you two don't feel it,
neither will the jury.
I'm not feeling that.
What is the point of this?
The point is that you two
need to be one in the room.
In effect, you'll be giving testimony
every single day.
Every single minute of this trial.
The jurors will be studying you for signs.
Is he human?
Does she believe him?
Does she still love him?
They will constantly
be taking measure of you.
Individually, and jointly.
Look, juries don't like
to convict good-looking people.
They certainly don't like
to imprison doctors,
and they don't like
to punish the wealthy.
As much as we think we like
to stick it to the rich,
in the end, we don't.
We never do.
The idea that jurors don't
come into this with preconceived notions,
that's just preposterous.
This case has been
so well-reported,
I might go as far as to say
that these jurors are liars.
I mean,
to get on this panel,
they would have had to have declared
that they know nothing about this case.
Does anybody...
- It's just entertainment.
- Which you need to be a part of.
The jury will know who you are.
Haley says that they notice everything.
Your presence. Your reactions.
- It all matters.
- Grace.
You're doing this for your grandson.
I will be at your side,
tomorrow and beyond.
But the idea that this best serves Henry
is absolute nonsense.
Murderer or not, Jonathan must be kept
as far away from your son as possible.
FiveThirtyEight is reporting an 83 percent
chance of conviction this morning,
down three points from just yesterday...
Plans for a last-minute
plea deal either never materialized,
or were squashed.
How is Grace doing?
Are you speaking to your son-in-law?
Come on, Henry.
Take all the metal
out of your pockets, please.
Thank you.
Next, please.
Step up.
Take all the metal
out of your pockets, please.
Murder is ugly business.
I must warn you,
whatever you've heard,
whatever your predispositions,
this one...
It's worse than you think.
The evidence will show
that Jonathan Fraser was having an affair
with the victim.
That he went to the victim's studio
on the night of January 8th, 2019.
That he sexually penetrated her.
That he then violently, savagely,
beat her to death.
He then fled the scene
and went into hiding,
before he was captured.
Elena Alves was bludgeoned so badly,
so viciously,
she was unrecognizable
to her own husband.
She was first discovered
by her 10-year-old son,
Miguel.
She was hit with a blunt instrument
11 times.
The medical examiner found
that the wounds inflicted
were consistent with a sculpting hammer,
which belonged to the victim.
A hammer which was never found.
It could have been a hammer like this one.
He turned her skull into mush.
He just kept hitting.
And hitting.
It's worse than you think.
Such a beautiful, vibrant woman.
When bad things happen to good people,
we want answers.
We want closure. We want a conviction.
My client is the only option.
That's why the investigation
was so limited.
It wasn't sloppy, or lazy, or negligent.
It was specifically
and intentionally narrow,
precisely because evidence
of other suspects
would compromise their one shot
at a conviction.
My client made love to Elena Alves,
on January 8th.
His DNA, semen at the scene.
He guarantees reasonable doubt
to any other defendant,
so we're not even gonna look
for other possibilities.
He's the only one we can get.
Somebody else hit Elena Alves
with that sculpting hammer,
11 times, like the prosecutor said.
It continued after she was dead.
That's rage.
That's hatred.
Please.
A lot of hatred.
A crime of passion.
Primal fury.
We have to wonder.
Fernando Alves had motive.
He had opportunity. He was there.
Is he the killer?
Can we know for sure?
No.
Why?
In part, because he was never
really investigated.
Why?
Because his semen was found
inside the victim?
He's the only one we can get.
It shall be him.
It's not.
The problem is, once the
defense comes up with its own theory,
the jury expects that they're gonna have
some evidence behind it.
And the idea that
the husband did this,
there's no evidence for that,
as far as I know.
:::::: www.hiqve.com ::::::
Hello?
Hey.
How was your day?
Anything interesting happen?
I don't really have
anything to say. I'm...
Just sitting here in the quiet.
It's a bit oppressive.
I'm a bit lonely.
How's the boy?
Is he all right?
Yeah. I mean...
I'm gonna have to take his iPhone away,
because he's...
He's devouring all the coverage,
and I...
Well, good luck with that.
I tried it once, and he turned into
that kid from The Exorcist.
I was so scared,
I gave it straight back.
Don't suppose you'd like
to come over for a cup of tea?
Boat of Frosties?
I could rustle up some
"oeuf à la Jonathan."
No.
I do realize how brutal today was. Um...
Not least because,
well, there you are, the most private
person on the face of the earth,
who goes for walks to disappear,
thrust into the middle of
that God-awful circus. I'm sorry.
Mm-hm.
But I do think, I think we can get
our anonymity back.
Just a question of planning.
I think we should let ourselves go,
and get really alarmingly fat.
Stop grooming.
I think you should wear extremely frumpy
tweed skirts.
In fact, we both should.
I, I think we could have
a very peaceful old age.
Mm.
Tragic, isn't it? That was
my biggest fantasy when we met.
Getting old with you.
Doing all the,
you know, old stuff.
All the puttering around
the garden,
and being spiteful
about young people.
Joining a book club.
But we did that.
You got kicked out.
I was kicked out
because I was honest.
The book was crap.
You still there?
Yeah, yeah. Do you remember those
long phone calls?
Even when we had nothing to say,
we just...
We didn't hang up. What was that about?
I remember.
Yeah.
I'm gonna go to sleep now.
Yeah, okay. Bye.
Wait, um... Hang on...
I love you.
Hey.
Henry.
My God, you scared me.
- What are you doing?
- Sitting.
Where were you?
Why are you sitting here?
- What is it?
- I couldn't sleep in my bed.
Were you thinking about it all?
- Yeah.
- We've survived so far.
And we'll survive the rest. We will.
What is it?
What's wrong?
Something's wrong. I can tell.
No. No.
I'm fine.
No, you're not.
I saw them.
- Hmm?
- I saw them together.
At school.
Okay.
I should have told you.
If I'd told you, maybe it wouldn't
have happened.
Maybe Miguel's father,
or somebody else who was jealous,
maybe if, if...
Maybe they found out.
- Maybe if I told you...
- You had nothing to do... No.
- Then they wouldn't have...
- Shh. Would you just listen for a minute?
You had nothing to do
with what happened to Miguel's mother.
- You can't say that.
- You could never have put... I can.
No, but Mom, I saw them.
And that must have been very hard for you.
They weren't doing anything.
I mean, they weren't kissing,
or anything, but...
I just knew,
when I saw them.
I knew. And when he saw me,
he just smiled.
Like it was nothing.
He saw that I saw.
He knew that I knew.
Well, he put you in a terrible position.
A position no child should ever be in.
- I wanted to tell you.
- Mm-hm.
I wanted to tell you, but...
I just...
I felt like he trusted me.
It's all right.
You let him see.
You let him see you with her.
At his school.
And you know that he saw you.
- You know he did,
- No.
and he fucking worships you.
He would do anything for you.
Anything. You know that.
No more lies, Jonathan.
I got it. Yeah. Yeah.
- Jonathan. At school...
- Grace, Jonathan.
We're about to take on the lead detective.
He needs to be my focus,
- and he needs to be yours.
- What, I'm meant to go out there now?
- And sit out there like this?
- Listen to me.
- Haley.
- Jonathan, why?
- You did that to our son.
- Jonathan.
We got to the scene at 8:57 A.M.
Nine minutes after
the husband made the 911 call,
and about 30 minutes
after the body was discovered by the son.
And what did you find?
We discovered a woman, deceased.
Her head badly lacerated,
her skull crushed.
Identified as Elena Alves by her husband.
Though any facial recognition
was difficult to discern.
Yes. I'd like to show you
a series of photographs.
I'm sorry, I can't...
Do these photographs fairly and accurately
represent the crime scene as you found it?
They do.
Thank you.
- Order in the court.
- It's okay. It's okay.
The forensic evidence you spoke of,
detective.
My client's sperm, saliva,
and skin fragments.
They could all be
the product of Jonathan Fraser's
and Elena Alves' having sex. True?
That would not explain her crushed skull.
No, it wouldn't.
And yet, when asked by Ms. Stamper
to give evidence as to
who crushed that skull,
the evidence you gave
to incriminate my client is...
- Sperm, saliva, and skin fragments.
- And his bloody footprints.
Which he could have left
if he'd returned to the scene
- after she was killed.
- And the fact that your client fled.
Yes, he fled.
I suppose when we have
two people come upon the scene,
one flees, the other doesn't,
it's usually the one who flees
who gets put on trial.
- It's not as simple as that.
- In this case,
it is.
There were no eyewitnesses to this crime.
No security cameras in this building
to monitor the comings and goings,
to see if anybody else came or went.
- There were not.
- The footprints,
fingerprints, and saliva
found at the scene,
belonging to two people.
My client, and the husband.
Fernando Alves went
to the scene after his son alerted him.
He went to his wife's aid.
- He tried...
- His DNA. The DNA
that belonged to the husband,
Fernando Alves.
You cannot scientifically
exclude the possibility
it was left the night before. Can you?
- Did you not hear my question, detective?
- I did. I did hear your question.
And I also heard your opening statement.
It was offensive.
We don't stick our heads into sand
in order to jam through quick convictions.
An innocent person got slaughtered.
Our intent was to find out who did it.
Our only pursuit here was the truth.
- However much that disappoints you.
- And the truth is that man's DNA...
He had an alibi.
- A man with motive.
- His son was with him.
They were together at the family apartment
over 10 blocks away.
His 10-year-old son.
He was awake the whole time?
There are cameras
in and outside the building
that would have shown if Mr. Alves left.
Cameras in the back, as well as the front?
He could have gone out the back.
There is no evidence,
either by security cameras,
street cameras, or eyewitness accounts,
that place Mr. Alves
on or around the scene that night.
Street cameras, however,
did capture your client.
Anybody else?
No.
- Where was this taken?
- A full block away.
- From the scene?
- Yes.
At what time?
A little past 9:30 p.m.
- The night of the murder?
- Yes.
A block from the scene,
and at the time of the murder.
Who is this in the picture? Do you know?
Grace Fraser.
The defendant's wife.
Near the scene, at around the time.
- Gee...
- Are you suggesting she killed her?
I'm actually not.
What I am suggesting
is that you just lied.
I'm suggesting that you had evidence
of another person, one with a lot of motive,
being at or near the scene
around the time of death,
and you never bothered
to question her as a suspect.
We absolutely questioned her.
As a suspect?
You gave her Miranda?
Did you advise Grace Fraser
of her Miranda rights
before questioning her as a suspect?
We did not.
Wouldn't that be the law
if you considered her to be a suspect,
to read her her rights?
It would be, if she was a suspect.
But she wasn't.
We had security cameras
capturing her walking.
Continuing on.
We had and still have no reason to believe
she ever entered the dwelling,
nor there was any of her DNA present.
If her DNA had been present,
you would have considered her a suspect?
Of course. But it wasn't.
His was.
Did you ever read Fernando his rights?
You made an exception for Fernando Alves.
Was it because admitting
your suspicions of him
might weaken your chances of getting him?
Fernando Alves had an alibi.
Yes. His sleeping son.
- Dad.
- Yeah.
They're calling the detective
a squirmy worm.
They're saying, like,
"Can't make the prosecutor feel good
having your whole case
ride on a squirmy worm."
Turn the phone off. Turn the phone off.
Just turn it off. Thank you.
It's not often that we get
to eat together, the three of us.
Here we are.
He'll pour it. Thank you.
Thank you.
Did you know she was gonna do that?
Pull up that picture?
I did.
And you're okay being a suspect?
I'm not a suspect.
That was Haley's point. That...
They should have taken
a more serious look at me,
just as they should have
taken a more serious look at Mr. Alves.
And they didn't. They just had tunnel vision
for your father.
So, Hen, your mom told me
that you saw me and...
Me and Elena Alves at school.
And I'm really sorry about that.
I behaved incredibly badly.
It was repugnant of me
to allow you to witness anything.
I think we're gonna win.
Do you?
I don't know.
Thank you.
I don't...
I don't know but I think we might
have made a colossal mistake.
I think Mr. Alves is obviously
very sympathetic,
and there's no real evidence
to show his guilt. So...
Did you mean what you said?
If we survived this far,
we can survive anything?
I said that?
- Last night.
- Oh.
If we can survive this trial,
I think this family can survive.
- All right... Well, I...
- Don't you?
- We need to talk about that another time.
- No.
I want to talk about it now.
No, we're not talking about it now.
It's not the time.
You tell your patients
that marriages can go on,
- even after somebody cheats.
- Come on.
You tell them that marriages
can even sometimes grow stronger.
- Is that a lie?
- I said, it's not the time.
- Is that a lie, or do you believe that?
- Henry, stop. Shush.
You would never cheat again. Would you?
- No. No.
- You would never cheat... See?
- See?
- Henry.
We can still be a family.
You know, we could even get a dog.
Finally.
I'll take care of it, so you won't
have to worry about what happened before.
What do you mean?
I asked you a question.
Mom told me about the dog thing.
About your family blaming you.
Well, she shouldn't have done that.
You know, I'm gonna get some air.
What did I say?
Mom, what did I say?
It's all right. Just wait here.
Jonathan.
Jonathan!
I'm sorry. It was just
the stress of it all. I...
Taking its toll, I suppose.
I don't believe you.
What was that about?
Jonathan, what was that about?
I didn't kill the family dog.
We never had a dog.
I had a sister. I...
I killed the family sister.
What?
Katie.
Katie the Kitten, we called her.
I was babysitting her.
I was 14. She was 4.
And...
Somehow she sneaked out of the house
while I was in the kitchen making
a cheese and tomato sandwich.
I heard the sound of the brakes,
and then another sound,
that I will never get out of my head.
Your sister got hit by a car?
It was your sister?
You should add that to my list of lies.
Except I also tell myself this one.
You know, that it wasn't my fault.
That it was just an unfortunate thing,
but, of course, it was my fucking fault,
because Katie the Kitten was put
under my charge.
And she...
And she got hit by a car
when I was making myself a snack.
- How is it you have never told me this?
- Because we don't talk of it.
You know. Ever.
Ever.
It's probably...
why I went into pediatric medicine.
I don't know. You're the shrink.
You know better than me,
but I will tell you this.
Every patient I treat,
every single one...
is little Katie.
Yeah.
All this time, he was carrying that burden
and I never saw.
In your professional opinion,
is a past trauma like that
likely to render a person
more compassionate?
Or more psychotic?
I tried calling his mother.
A few times.
And she never returned.
Even his family doesn't want
to have anything to do with him.
Turn, please.
Thank you.
Morning.
Turn, please.
- Thank you, sir.
- Yeah.
Turn, please.
After she hadn't come home,
or replied to any of my calls or texts,
my son Miguel, he went to check on her.
I thought he'd gone to school.
I was just having a busy morning
with the baby.
She wasn't there,
so I told him to just go on.
See himself to the bus. And he didn't.
He went to see his mom.
He went to the studio.
Yes.
And then you went there?
After he'd come back.
He was...
Crying, screaming.
- And so you went there, and...
- Yeah.
What did you find?
It's...
Elena.
My wife.
She was just lying there.
There was just blood everywhere.
Her face, head. They were like mush.
So, you called the police?
Yeah. I called the police, and...
Ambulance.
Thank you.
Mr. Alves.
I cannot imagine your pain, sir.
That's a lie.
I'm sorry?
You feel nothing for me.
Or my pain.
You tried to blame me.
I actually didn't.
I simply tried to point out
that you cannot be eliminated
as a suspect.
That others cannot be eliminated.
For that, you should direct
your contempt to the police. Not me.
- Objection.
- Sustained.
See, my wife is dead,
and you're just...
playing games.
That's it.
You disgust me.
I don't mean to incite your rage.
You spoke of your love of Elena.
You loved her very much.
- She was everything to me.
- I'm sensing that.
But you weren't everything to her.
And there were other men.
- Including my client.
- No, no, no.
There were no other men.
He was the only one.
- How can you know that, sir?
- Well, because I do.
Did you know that she was
romantically involved with Jonathan?
Elena was able to keep
part of herself from you.
Maybe that's why she kept
a separate apartment.
- To keep part of her separate.
- No, that's not what that was.
That was an apartment for her art,
because she was an artist, and...
And she needed to focus
and she needed to work.
That's what that apartment was for.
It wasn't just for her art.
She'd been using it to have an affair
with my client.
Did you know, sir?
Not at first.
But at some point?
And at some point, you learned that
your daughter...
That my client was the biological father.
That must have been
an awful thing to learn.
Forgive me, but I have to ask.
Was your wife receiving
any psychiatric treatment?
Objection.
- Overruled.
- Was she?
- Yes.
- What for? Do you know?
You are vile.
My question only goes
to who else could have possibly done this.
We cannot rule out that she saw other men.
That maybe one such man
had the capacity for explosive jealousy,
- or violent rage.
- Objection!
These are the very questions
you'd want the police asking, am I right,
- to find out who did this?
- Your Honor...
- He did this! He did this!
- Your Honor, may I approach...
Mr. Alves,
- are you receiving any psychiatric help?
- Objection!
- I don't mean to be insensitive.
- Well, you're doing a great job of it.
You have put this witness on the stand.
- Your Honor, may I approach?
- It's cross-examination.
Mr. Alves, what you have
to be going through,
- are you getting any help?
- Your Honor...
How do you think it's going?
Your objective opinion?
Look, to... To me,
It's more likely than not that...
That Jonathan did it.
But more likely
isn't the standard.
It's beyond all reasonable doubt.
That puts you ahead.
That, and he has the best attorney
money can buy. So...
Grace, I...
I probably shouldn't ask you this, but...
What are you actually thinking?
Yeah. You shouldn't ask that.
Another reason I couldn't have done it.
I loved her.
Quite madly.
Not something
I could say to Grace, you see.
It didn't diminish my love
for my wife. It was just, uh...
Different.
It's going well,
but you'll need to testify.
We need to account for why you fled.
Only you can do that.
Don't pretend to be honest,
because you've told too many lies.
Don't pretend to be a good husband,
a decent father,
because you are arguably neither.
We don't need to give them a good man.
Just someone who didn't commit murder.
Janet.
Hello.
Grace.
- What time is it there?
- It's 4:00 a.m.
I couldn't sleep, so,
I thought I would use the time
to return your call.
Well, thank you.
Thank you. I'm sorry it's...
been so long since we've...
Since the wedding, Grace.
We haven't seen each other
since the wedding.
Jonathan's doing, I realize.
How is he?
I can't imagine well.
No. None of us are doing great, so...
- Is.
- I'm sorry?
None of us is doing great.
"None" is a contraction of "not one."
It's singular.
The verb is singular.
And, uh, Henry.
He must be looking
like a grown man by now?
He's getting there.
I've sent you some pictures, but...
Grace, I don't blame you.
It was Jonathan's decision
to no longer be part of his family.
A decision he made long before
he met you.
Well, I'm just trying to piece
everything together right now.
You can probably understand.
Yes, I can.
I just learned that Jonathan
had a younger sister.
Katie.
And that he feels responsible
for her death.
As he should.
He was responsible.
He allowed a 4-year-old
to wander out onto a busy street.
Where she was struck dead.
That must have been unspeakably awful.
- It was.
- Janet, um...
The grief and the guilt, and... And...
Jonathan growing up with that.
Did he ever get professional help?
He did not.
He suffered from neither.
No guilt, no grief.
We kept waiting for it.
We surrounded him
with family support,
certain that once the shock wore off,
the suffering would begin.
But it never did.
Jonathan doesn't know
how to suffer.
After his sister was killed,
he never even said
he was sorry.
After his sister was killed,
he never said another word about it.
He just went on living here,
until he was old enough
to leave,
and never come back.
Which is what he did.
Her name was Katie,
and he was responsible...
That he allowed her to wander...
She was 4. Out of the house...
And that after, he suffered
neither guilt nor grief.
Grace,
I want to be very clear.
I want to understand
exactly what you're telling me.
You're saying that Jonathan's mother
said he suffered
from neither guilt, nor grief.
In essence, his own mother
identified him as a sociopath.
Yes.
Jesus.
:::::: www.hiqve.com ::::::