Sorry, mate. I'm sorry, mate.
Excuse me, mate.
What are you...
What are you doing?
English?
If you're taking the mickey, you
picked on the wrong person.
Let me tell you that. No, I'm
not picking on you at all.
You're English, correct?
Yeah, big time, yeah.
I'm working on
an English character.
Would you mind... It's
called Reginald Poofter.
Oh.
David Brent, my liege.
How are you?
Michael Scott.
Oh, bloody hell.
I do characters as well.
I got a Chinese fella.
Not politically correct,
but he's called Holy...
That's what it
sounds like.
"Herro! Herro!"
I do Ping.
"Herro. I'm Ping." You
can't do that these days.
You can't.
I'm Ping! No.
No, no. And people
don't understand
that it has nothing to do with making
fun of a different nationality.
No, no, no.
No, comedy is a place
where the mind goes
to tickle itself.
That's what she
said.
That's good.
Pleasure to meet you.
Where are you working?
Dunder Mifflin.
Any jobs going?
No, not right now.
Just let me know.
All right.
See you around.
Bye, bye.
What a nice guy.
Your first student is
here, Mr. Bernard.
That's actually "Master
of Ceremonies" Bernard.
Last year,
I went to a seminar
called "The 10 Secrets
of Real Estate."
Turns out it was just a ploy to
sell me timeshares in Idaho.
Cut to, you know, I'm
spending a weekend in Boise,
terrible time,
super lonely.
But I get to thinking,
maybe I should put on my own
seminar to lure clients.
Oh.
Hello, I am here for the
small business seminar.
Michael?
Nein, I'm Greek!
My name is Mykonos.
Ooh.
Oh.
Wait, Michael?
Michael?
Okay.
I am the plant.
Every great seminar has one.
My job is to make
the speaker look good,
and I do this through the
techniques of leading questions
and laughing at all jokes.
And the character, Mykonos,
is just a little added flavor.
Mykonos is loosely based on
another character I do, Spiros,
who is more about the ladies.
Thank you so much,
Tuna Turner.
You are simply
the best.
Listen, this isn't a
favor, all right?
This is a good idea.
We all win.
Go higher.
All right.
I get super flexible
when I'm nervous.
Wow.
Stop, stop,
stop, stop, stop, stop.
Hey, Andy, I'm really, really
sorry to do this to you,
but I have
a meeting today
that I totally forgot,
so I can't be a part
of this seminar.
No! What?
You can't do that. You are a
critical part of this seminar.
You're the charming warm-up guy.
I know.
If the seminar was a meal,
you'd be the amuse-bouche.
You signal the flavors of the whole night.
I'm really sorry. I can't do it.
You can't. You can't.
I can't have
this go badly.
I'm a terrible salesman,
and I haven't been making very
many sales lately, or ever.
This is my only idea on how
to turn things around.
If it goes badly,
I might lose my job,
which would suck, because this is the
only job I've ever been good at.
Will you let me know when this
whole seminar thing's over?
What's going on?
Do you know that guy?
I just have a meeting,
outside the office.
Hey.
How are the marks?
What are some of your
small business ideas?
I was thinking we could buy up a
bunch of abandoned mineshafts.
That's great.
There's a big,
big future in that. A lot
of mines in Scranton.
Um,
what about you?
Uh, credit cards.
Uh-huh.
My company will act
as an inter-medium
for, like, 0.2 cents
off every transaction.
Wow!
Or something
with cell phones,
like, every time you make a
phone call, I'd make 0.2 cents.
Or anything. Like, any online
shopping, I get 0.2 cents basically.
Right. Okay?
Yeah.
Okay.
You promised us whales.
These are worms.
They're not worms,
Dwight, okay?
They're just people
with tiny businesses.
They're baby whales, which
is even cuter. I'm out.
Stanley, you're
supposed to close.
I'm out, too.
What?
I already lost Jim.
Salesmen are supposed
to help each other out.
We're supposed to be a team.
We're no more a team
than the people staying in
the same hotel are a team.
You know what
might be kind of fun?
I was thinking, you know,
Andy's having a seminar today?
What if we went in
as a Greek couple?
Mykonos and... Oh, I
don't know, Michael.
I'm not feeling up to that.
Okay.
Holly broke
up with A. J. last week,
which is the greatest thing
that has ever happened to me.
To Holly, it's been the
worst week of her life,
and I know for a fact that there
was a week for her in High School
when she got mono
and her first period ever.
Too much information?
That's what I thought.
But you know what?
Here I am using it.
If you change your mind, why
don't you talk to Mykonos?
Is Mykonos Greek?
He sounds Italian.
Ugh. You're the fifth person
to tell me that today.
Maybe Mykonos ran away
to join the Italian circus.
Okay, yeah, like
a character history.
Good. Tom Hanks does that.
Yeah.
Is "JLP" a word?
"Jelp?" J-E-L-P?
No, J-L-P.
Like, "I Jlp...
I Jlp you!"
I don't think
that's a word.
I'm playing
scrabble with Gabe,
and I've never
won a game.
The winner gets to pick the movie we watch.
I have won no games.
So far I've seen
The Shining,
Rosemary's Baby,
The Ring.
Not really my thing.
Although, I... I do like the
early parts of the movies
where they have a perfect
family and everything.
You want some help?
Really?
Mmm-hmm.
Yes.
K-A. "Ka?"
What does "ka" mean?
It means you're playing someone
who's going to destroy you.
Why did you play "moo?"
Because I'm
playing to win.
I'm playing "moo," I'm playing
"milk," whatever it takes.
Okay, but look, you
could have hit "mood."
Would have played a...
A triple word. Ah.
Like the cow
mood yesterday.
God.
Or moon.
The cow jumped
over the moon.
She's stuck on
that one thing.
You know it doesn't have to
just be cow stuff, right?
Kevin, Jim dropped out of
my seminar, and I'm just...
I was wondering if you could replace
him as my charming warm-up guy.
Andy, I'm no Jim. I'm...
The only way that I'm Jim
is in the movie version
when Jim sees what his future would
be like if he never met Pam.
Hey, that's crazy talk.
I think you're great.
Then I won't let you down.
Pink.
Indigo.
Hi, Ryan, you went to
business school, right?
Yeah.
I need somebody
to talk to this
seminar about business.
And? Can you do it?
Okay.
I don't... I don't like committing
to things just like that.
So, no?
No, I don't like committing
to not doing things, either.
That's just as big a commitment.
Oh, baby.
What do I put you
down for, bro hombre?
Yes.
All right!
Yes, I'll do it.
Okay, thank you so much.
It's gonna be awesome.
And if I flake, I flake. What?
Kevin, you open it up. Yep.
Ryan, you come in with your
small biz expertise, right?
And then Creed, guest
speaker extraordinaire.
And then I come in and just
close all the sales and stuff.
Okay, here we go.
One, two, three!
Team!
Creed!
Welcome everybody.
Awesome to see you guys.
My name's Andy Bernard, but you
can call me "The Nard Dog."
Hi, Nard Dog.
I'm Lu Peachem.
Let's get things
started, shall we?
You guys ready to hear from the
Dunder Mifflin business experts?
Good. Well, as you can
see on your program,
first up is a speech called,
"Don't just dream it, do it."
Yes! Please give a big hand to Mr.
Kevin Malone.
Four, five.
Yes!
There are some people
who have charm
and some people
who don't.
Guess which type I am.
Charm type.
Dream big. Right?
So, what I
want you to do
is dream the biggest
that you can.
And then double it!
Are you okay?
No. Yes!
Here.
Mmm-hmm.
I'm fine.
Okay, from here now.
The first lesson that
I'm gonna teach you,
right, is about
finding success.
And the key to finding success
is to picture a winner.
Okay, so then, what are
you picturing right now,
right this second?
'Cause the universe
is yours, people.
Get out of the way.
I'm really excited to introduce
you guys to Ryan Howard.
He has achieved a
great deal in the last...
But perhaps no
achievement is greater
than his on-again,
off-again girlfriend.
What are you...
Who am I?
I'm Kelly Kapoor,
the business bitch.
It is important
to brand yourself,
so I have a couple
of things in the works.
The business bitch,
the diet bitch,
the shopping bitch,
the etiquette bitch.
I could sit here, and I could tell
you the 10 secrets of business,
and you would
have a great time,
learn a lot.
But who better
to tell you
than the Yale University adjunct
professor in management,
Professor Scott Powell,
who I have on my BlackBerry.
It's ringing.
Hey, Kelly Kapoor.
What a delicious surprise.
Professor Powell,
you are on speakerphone.
Uh, why?
Do you think you could tell us
the 10 secrets of business?
Um, there aren't
really 10 secrets.
Come on, Scott,
please. It's me.
Uh, all right. Well,
Uh, I guess know your
market would be key.
Practice fiscal discipline.
That brilliant little bitch.
A little treat for
our old friend, Gabe.
Put that "Q"
right there.
Wait. Why?
Put the "Q"
there, sweetie.
I think there's better...
Put the "Q" there!
Sorry I yelled.
You could have just told
us what you were thinking.
There's no theater
in that.
There's no yelling in that, either.
Well...
What do you do
in your free time?
Practice Olympics.
Do you like movies?
I like the
musical Grease,
or as we call
it, "home."
We have to try this
out on somebody.
Hello.
Look, you want
to order something?
She will have
a greekaccino.
I don't know
what that is.
It...
It's a very strong coffee
with milk from a goat.
I can't
believe it.
It's a miracle.
She can talk.
No more brain damage.
No more brain damage!
I don't know.
Ladies and gentlemen, our special
guest speaker will provoke you.
He will inspire you.
He is...
Creed Bratton.
Two eyes, two ears,
a chin, a mouth,
ten fingers,
two nipples,
a butt, two kneecaps,
a penis.
I have just described to
you the Loch Ness monster.
And the reward
for its capture?
All the riches
in Scotland.
So I have one question,
why are you here?
Okay! All right,
ladies and gentlemen,
it is now time for
the rarest of things,
an actual free lunch.
There's sandwiches in the back.
Certainly help yourselves.
We'll meet back
up in an hour.
I picked out our movie.
It's called Suspiria.
It pushes all
the boundaries.
All your preconceived notions about
what horror can be, come crashing down.
When I win,
we're gonna
watch Wall-E,
where all the boundaries
of color are pushed.
It is hard to explain why
Erin is doing so well today.
The only thing I can
think is Erin is living out
some Slumdog Millionaire
scenario,
where every word she's playing has
a connection to her orphan past.
It's possible.
So what's your crazy
business pipe dream?
Well, I started my own
golf supply company.
Really? It's taken off
faster than I expected,
so I came here to learn about
creating manageable growth.
Phyllis?
Some of these
people are for real.
Hey, friend.
How's it going?
Oh, you know what? Let
me steep that for you.
Thank you. Hey, you know what?
Good news.
We're back in.
Let's go sell some
paper, buddy. Huh?
Really?
Excuse me.
I got it. I got it.
Hey, do you
need a lozenge?
They're a bunch
of jackals.
What?
They left you
in the lurch,
and if they want to jump in,
it means you're almost there.
You did this.
Bring it home.
Let me tell you what you can
do with your offer to help.
You can table it and offer
it up another time.
Just know that I really
appreciate the gesture.
Hi. Hope you
enjoyed your lunch.
Welcome back.
Ooh, well, hello.
Welcome to the seminar.
Hey, man.
What's going on?
You're gonna blow it.
Maybe.
Only maybe.
We got it.
Wow, we got it.
Oscar, wait. I think the victory
would be more meaningful
if Erin puts the
last word in herself.
Yes, Pam.
Yes, most definitely.
Yes.
No.
Although I must say, I will
have apoplexy if you lose.
Do you understand? Apoplexy
is what I will have.
Apoplexy.
Yes.
Got it.
Oh, Oscar.
Oscar?
I played "ape."
I just want to make a point to
that last caller. I disagree.
I don't think it is the
running game at all.
I think we do have to make a
few moves in this off-season.
Wow!
What a day, right?
Guess you guys are
probably ready to go.
And you got my
business card, so...
You know,
I like you.
I'm going to give you
my secret gyro recipe.
Come out here, since it's a
secret, and I'll tell you.
All right, you have
to close right now.
Yeah, I'm getting to it.
No, you're not.
You're getting past it.
You have to close.
Do it. You can do it.
Yeah, yeah.
Andy, what's
the problem?
This is hard
for me. I'm a nice guy.
You know, Kelly
and Creed, Kevin,
they believe in you.
Don't let them down.
Don't let yourself
down, Andy.
I'm gonna go back in. I'm going
to stall them for a little bit.
I want you to get your head
together, and then come back in.
I want you to close.
What is taking that
guy so long?
Psst!
You think this thing's
gonna go much longer?
I don't know.
They're still in there.
Goodbye.
Stop.
Out with it.
Here's the story.
That guy in there is Jim's
childhood friend, Tom.
Tom Witashkin.
One of my best
buddies, actually.
And when they were both
in the third grade,
Jim was placed in the
top reading group.
I was blue group,
so I was second from the top.
And Tom...
Was in green group.
And Jim's
mom suggested
that Jim spend time hanging with
the kids in his reading group,
because she thought that they
would be a good influence.
And that's what I told him.
Right.
But how'd
you say it?
"My mom thinks you're too
dumb to hang out with."
Okay, who would
like to purchase
this small business
package from me right now?
Yes, we got one.
Okay, the snowball is rolling.
Who else?
You can put it off
for a couple of days,
but I guarantee you,
eventually you're gonna
realize you need this.
So the only thing that's
gonna be different
is you'll be a couple
of days behind
where you would be if you
bought this from me right now.
So who's gonna
buy one right now?
I'll take one.
Yes! Awesome!
All right, anyone else?
Sold! Anybody else?
Yes! All right!
- Yeah, bitch.
- Good choice.
The rest of you
are dead to me.
You made the stupidest
decisions of your life.
No, no, no.
But it was a pleasure
meeting you,
and you've got my information,
so feel free to call anytime.
Hey, you think it's coo I
if I grab a soda? Yeah.
Yep, absolutely,
go ahead.
Hey.
How's it going?
Pretty good. Good.
It's been a while.
It has been, yeah.
So you work here, huh?
Sales.
Must be a front for some
kind of famous laboratory.
'Cause you're so smart.
Oh, man. You remember
that, huh?
Barely. I'm so dumb,
you know, stuff goes
in, stuff goes out.
Not like you probably remember
every paper sale you ever made.
Paper salesman genius.
All right, good catch-up.
Yeah.
See you.
Where's your jetpack,
Zuckerberg?
Andy.
I didn't think
you had it in you.
Well, I guess when
you looked in me,
you forgot about my balls.
They're on the outside.
Don't know how
you missed 'em.
Wonderful seminar!
Almost as good
as the day when
we first met.
You are the
love of my life.
Come to me, Necropolis.
Put your lips on
my lips. Come on.
Michael, I should
get back to work.
What? Come on.
It's time for grapes.
That was a fun day.
So, I won.
I know.
You get to pick.
Well, that's actually what I
came to talk to you about.
I know how much you
want to watch Wall-E.
Yes? So I got us a compromise.
This movie is
called Hardware,
it tells the story of a killer
combat robot, just like Wall-E,
that the government
invented to destroy humans.
It's some of what you like and
some of what I like. And...
Erin, I heard you talking
about movies before and...
Anyway, I just watched
this over the weekend.
I thought you'd
really like it.
There's a Shrek 2?
Oh, yeah.
See you tomorrow.
Nice guy.
Ooh.