Previously on Dexter...
Our primary suspect
is Sergeant James Doakes.
- Doakes?
- He is not your man.
I think the Bay Harbor Butcher
is alive and still in Miami.
Doakes was the Bay Harbor Butcher,
end of story.
I found a blood slide
at the crime scene...
...like the ones we found in Doakes'
car and Doakes never had a boat.
Here is a list of Miami Metro personnel
who still do.
Its point of origin...
...front centre mass
burned upward, downward.
Can we close the doors?
This void, it's the same thing
that happened with the first car victim.
"Bobby"? Maybe the victim
was letting us know who did this.
You fucked my girl?
You could learn a thing or two from
her. She takes her job very seriously.
You always been this afraid
of the water?
Ever since my father thought the best
way to teach me how to swim...
...was to march me down
to the local pond and throw me in.
- That's horrible.
- Six years old...
and I already knew what it felt like
to be dying.
- Look, I think you have the wrong idea.
- Shut up.
I know who you are.
I know what you are.
Dexter, you don't have to save her.
You shouldn't even be with her.
It's not even like
you have a fucking future.
All I know is that
when I'm with you, I feel...
...safe.
I saw a man,
he was coming through the flames.
- He was wearing a silver-coloured suit.
- Our Phantom Arsonist.
- He looked like an alien.
- Or a monster.
I swear, he was 7 feet tall.
Monsters, aliens, phantoms,
none of them are real.
The thought that an actual person
could do this is too awful...
...so our imaginations create a way
to make it easier to take.
But the strongest of imaginations can't
protect us once we know the truth.
I called you last night.
Wanted to go over the case.
- We can go over them now.
- Where were you?
Oh, you were with Hannah.
- Find anything? DNA? Prints?
- Nope, nada, zip.
Same accelerant as the other four fires,
though. Kerosene.
He left another "Bobby" in the soot.
Fuck, that's five Bobby's
in two weeks.
- He's gotta be signing his name, right?
- Only thing that makes sense.
None of the victims were named Bobby,
but fuckload of good that does us.
There are thousands
of Bobs and Roberts in Miami.
What do we know
about the latest victim?
Mom took her daughter to the
bathroom. Both went up in smoke.
Kid was 6 years old.
What kind of sick fuck does that
to a 6-year-old kid'?
Maybe the kind who isn't bothered
by the sight of a dead child.
- Hey.
How you feeling?
You get your stitches out?
Yeah, I'm gonna have
a really sexy scar.
- How was your day?
- It was fine.
You don't sound fine.
The Phantom started another fire
today. it killed a mother and child.
- What?
- Why do I get the feeling...
...you wanna wrap him up in plastic?
It doesn't matter.
I promised Deb I wouldn't take
any cases from the police.
If you always listened to Deb,
you wouldn't be here.
I can't kill him, okay?
Okay, fine.
Sorry. I'm just...
"frustrated.
As much as I wanna be here...
...my Dark Passenger wants
to be somewhere else.
I'm sorry. Your "dark" what?
My Dark Passenger.
- That's what I call my need to kill.
- Why?
It's like this thing living inside me...
...telling me what to do,
saying I have to kill...
...not leaving me any choice.
You're not a puppet.
Of course you have a choice.
Actually, I don't.
Come on, Dex. It's just you.
You want the arsonist dead.
And I don't blame you. Who wouldn't?
- It's not the same.
- What do you mean?
Ignore that. I wanna understand this.
How is it different?
A lot of people feel they wanna kill,
but I have to follow through.
I follow through
and I don't have a Dark Passenger.
You don't get it.
I'm trying to.
But, no, I don't get it.
- There's a man in the window.
- What?
- Hi, banana.
- Oh, my God. That's my dad.
I'm sorry if I surprised you. I didn't
even know Hannah had a boyfriend.
- I haven't spoken to you since--
- Go ahead and say it.
Since before I went to prison.
Clint McKay, convicted felon.
Nice to meet you.
No need to get nervous.
I was just in for cheque kiting
and I got out early on good behaviour.
- Dad, what are you doing here?
- Well, let me just get to the point.
I don't know what Hannah's told you...
- ...about me.
- Not a lot.
- Well...
- Just that you almost let her drown.
Well, the truth is...
...I was a real, genuine asshole
of a father.
And I needed to admit that
to you in person.
Can we please not do this
in front of Dexter?
If you two are together,
then I want him to hear this.
I spent a lot of time with a prison
shrink, working through my issues.
It's important to take responsibility,
so that's what I'm here to do.
- Okay.
- Now, I don't expect you to forgive me.
Don't see any reason that you should,
not after everything I put you through.
But it's important you know...
...no matter what,
I always loved you.
I always will.
I've got something for you
in my truck.
Let me give it to you
and I'll be on my way.
Surprise.
It's your dollhouse.
Repainted and rebuilt.
It was in your Aunt Cindy's garage.
I figured you loved it so much as a kid,
you might like to have it now.
Dex, give me a hand?
Well, I guess I'll be on my way.
Let you two get back to your dinner.
There's a diner at the Purple Flamingo,
where I'm staying.
They say they make
a pretty decent burger.
Okay.
Well,
I guess I'll see you around then.
Nice to meet you, Dexter.
You look good, banana.
Happy-
Glad to see you're doing okay.
I'm sure he meant well, but he
could not have given me a worse gift.
Brings up so much shit.
What kind of shit?
When I was 8,
he took me to a poker tournament.
Lied to my mom and said that we
were going to a county fair...
...and stashed me in a motel room.
Went to play cards
and didn't come back for three days.
That's awful.
When he came back,
he brought the dollhouse...
...bragging about a big win,
saying he'd never leave me again...
...and making promises
that things would get better.
- And did they?
- No. Of course not.
I don't know. I'm...
He's trying, right? Maybe...
Maybe this last stint in lockup
did him some good.
Yeah, maybe.
Most likely we're looking
for a male suspect.
Egocentric, manipulative.
Possibly in or on the outskirts
of law enforcement.
He's methodical.
Fastidious in his appearance,
poor social skills.
This list
is by no means comprehensive.
Should give you an idea
of what we're looking at.
Bosso's profile of the Phantom,
he may as well be describing himself.
An arsonist
who works for the fire department.
- It's almost too easy.
- What else?
Hands-on learner.
Prone to self-aggrandisement.
Thank you, Investigator Bosso.
Where are we on tracking the suit?
There's at least a hundred sites
that sell that on the Internet.
Almost impossible to trace.
- Are you interviewing witnesses?
- Nobody's seen the guy's face.
- More coming.
- Let me know what you find.
Simms, Miller, any leads
from the tip line?
None so far.
Mostly girlfriends trying to get back
at their exes.
Keep at it.
Maybe something will come through.
This fuck has killed seven people
in two weeks.
Let's stop him
before he makes it to number eight.
Hannah's wrong.
Of course I have a Dark Passenger.
There's no other way
to explain this compulsion.
I hope she knows what she's doing.
Who's sending you hugs and kisses?
No one.
Bullshit. That was a girl.
Was she sexting you?
You got pictures?
Come on,
I gotta restock my spank bank.
- Angel, know about Dexter's girlfriend?
- Hannah McKay?
- How did you--?
- Jamie told me.
My man.
Hannah McKay.
Yeah, that is so awesome.
Excuse me, what is awesome
about my brother dating a killer?
You guys heard Sal Price's recording.
Hannah confessed.
Come on, she was 15
when she did that.
When I was 15,
my parents thought that I was retarded.
Hey, hey-
I get it.
Hannah is an attractive girl.
But you should probably be careful.
Yeah,
you should definitely be careful...
...of getting burned
because she's so freaking hot.
Can I see you in my office, please?
I didn't realise you and Hannah McKay
had gone public.
We hadn't until a minute ago.
That's kind of dangerous.
Don't you think?
Dating someone so notorious
when trying to stay under the radar.
I don't wanna talk
about Hannah right now.
Can you just leave it?
Fine, yeah. I'll butt out.
I mean, we're all responsible adults,
right?
You live your life, I'll live mine,
and Hannah will live Hannah's.
Great. You'll leave Hannah alone?
I'm saying that I'll stay out
of your relationship.
I'm not gonna let her get away
with murder again.
- That's not what I meant.
- Dexter, I am fucking serious.
I have compromised the shit
out of myself for you.
I am sure as fuck not gonna do it
for Hannah McKay.
Fine. I get it.
Why are you standing here?
We have a Phantom to catch.
She did say "we."
Philip Bosso.
In his last 27 arson investigations,
he found the fire's origin point.
Either he's great at his job or all he
had to do was look in the mirror.
Okay, it says here
that you work as a janitor...
...at the Y in Brickell Bay
where the Phantom set the first fire.
Did you see anything suspicious
when making your rounds that night?
No, I didn't even know it happened
until I saw the fire truck.
It was horrible.
Right, right, right.
And did you see anyone
in a fireproof suit?
Don't you think
I would've told you if I had?
Bosso's SUV.
But where did he go?
Is he about to strike again?
Electric fuses and camping fuel.
What are you doing here?
That's not a fireproof suit.
Dexter,
you a Civil War re-enactor too?
You here for the battle?
- Yeah.
- Which side are you fighting for?
- The North.
- Oh, why you blue belly.
I should buck and gag you right here.
Were you there last weekend at the
sixth Maine battery cannon firings?
No, damn. I guess I missed that one.
It's a whole weekend affair.
I was in charge of special effects.
Ground, air bursts, artillery fire.
Which explains what's in his car...
...and gives him an alibi
for Saturday's fire.
- Wanna see some pictures?
- You bet.
Bosso's not the Phantom.
He's just strange.
But if he didn't set those fires,
then who did?
Hang on just one sec.
I guess coffee went better
than expected.
After coffee, Hannah wanted
to show me the flower mart.
So we're walking around
and I catch a whiff of this flower.
It smells just like liquorice.
- I ask Hannah what it is...
- And I tell him it's anise.
So I tell the lady in the booth
that her anise smells delicious.
You didn't pronounce it right.
Don't know what I said,
but she did not react well.
Well, do you blame her?
Sounds like you had quite a day.
Yeah, we really did.
How long are you gonna be in town?
Oh, just another day or so.
And then I'm off to Louisiana.
What's in Louisiana?
A poker tournament?
No. I am all done with that. I am looking
for an honest way to make a living.
And I think I found the perfect thing.
You ready?
- Crawfish.
- Crawfish?
Yeah, a crawfish farm.
I got a line on one near Lafayette.
Gonna call it Big Clint's Crawdaddies
and I will ship them fresh anywhere.
- There's a market for that?
- You bet there is.
Hey, ain't nothing like a crawfish boil.
Weddings, bachelor parties,
Fourth of July.
Everybody likes crawdads.
Well, I'm excited for you, Dad.
And I'm proud of you.
Well, thank you, honey. Means a lot.
Why don't you check out of that motel
and come and stay with me?
You're starting a business.
You're gonna need to save.
No. I couldn't do that.
- I wouldn't wanna intrude.
- Oh, you're not.
Yeah. Don't worry.
I was going home tonight anyway.
Why don't I bring you guys breakfast?
Best doughnuts you ever tasted.
Okay.
- What are you doing, man?
- Get out!
Everybody, come on!
Come on! Come on!
Man, it's like I died
and went to heaven.
I think if I had one more of those,
I probably will.
I'd like
to make an orange juice toast...
...to the cutest damn couple
I have ever seen.
Outside of me and Bubba in prison.
- That's just a little joke.
- Right.
Well, to you, Dad.
The king of crawfish.
There's no stopping me.
I just gotta get the money together.
So where are you at with that?
That's something
I wanted to talk to you about.
Figured you might like to get in
on the ground ﬂoor.
- What do you mean?
- Well, invest.
I only need about 20 grand more.
No, it's a great opportunity.
There's a guaranteed 10 percent a year
back on investment.
I'm sorry, Dad. I can't.
My money's tied up in the business.
Oh, come on, now.
Not all your money.
There's gotta be a little wiggle room
there somewhere.
- You could re-mortgage your place.
- I don't think so.
- Gotta be worth a pretty penny.
- It's not gonna happen.
Well, fine.
Whatever. Forget it.
I'm sorry. I just don't have the funds.
What kind of daughter won't even help
her own father?
Jesus, Dad.
Look, I need some air.
I'm gonna go for a drive.
Dad, you don't have to go.
You think I was wrong
telling him I couldn't?
- Of course not.
- But I feel like I should help him out.
- Why?
- Because he's my dad.
The same dad
who almost let you drown?
Who left you alone for three days?
He's trying to change.
I doubt it.
I know he's done some bad things,
but there's good inside of him as well.
Right, you've known him for 24 hours
and you think you understand him?
- I have a sense for this thing.
- Oh, yeah, you and your Dark--
Whatever-- Part of you.
- That you don't think exists.
- Because it doesn't.
I gotta go to work.
It's the arsonist again.
Look, I'm just trying to help here.
I know. I know.
I appreciate it. I'm sorry.
I'll be fine. Go.
Okay.
I gotta check.
Sorry what happened to your sister.
Another "Bobby."
"It's Bobby."
He added an "it's."
Like we didn't know it was Bobby.
Make sure you get this.
Well, did you see anything?
I really have no idea.
Did you see Bosso?
- Sniffing the body.
- Probably for accelerant.
Still, it was kind of creepy, right?
I mean, I know it would be
the biggest cliché in the world...
...the arson investigator turned out
to be the arsonist, but does he...?
Does he set off anything
in your brain?
I don't think Bosso's the Phantom.
He has an alibi.
- You vetted him?
- I looked into him.
You said
you weren't gonna take any cases.
- I didn't take it.
- Fuck, Dexter.
Why put yourself in that situation?
Good question. Why did I?
Hey, L.T. We got a security camera.
I'm gonna take the hard drive...
...see if we can get eyes
on the Phantom.
Good. We could use a break.
Hey, Hannah.
Wait, hold on. Slow down.
What happened?
I'll be right there.
I came back from the flower mart
and it was like this.
Well, I had a couple of drinks
to take the edge off...
...but I might have overdone it
a little.
You did this to get back at me for not
giving you the money that you wanted.
Oh, talk about paranoid.
But then,
maybe you've got reason to be.
Must be a lot of folks hate you
for all the pain you've caused.
How can you even say that to me?
Playing Mother Nature in here
with your stupid, little flowers.
Won't even help out
your own fucking father!
- I don't wanna help you!
- You got any idea what it's like...
...to be the father
of the infamous Hannah McKay?
You're a goddamn curse,
you ungrateful little shit!
That's enough, Clint.
Stay out of this.
This is family business.
You know you killed your mother,
don't you?
She died of a broken heart
after your spree...
- ...with Wayne Randall.
- I'm sorry.
Everybody would've been better off if
I'd let you drown that day at the pond.
Get out of here.
Now.
Fine.
I said what I had to say.
Well, it looks like
Hannah's found herself another winner.
You two deserve each other.
I can cut a body up into pieces...
...but how do I help Hannah
put herself back together?
Could you have picked
more of a dump?
Come on, Maria. It's perfect
for all this cloak-and-dagger bullshit.
It's the kind of place you take hookers
and ugly broads.
So nobody sees you.
You should know.
I followed up on all the names
you identified on my list.
Yes, the list
of suspicious police employees...
- ...who own boats.
- They were all dead ends.
All except for Dexter Morgan...
...who conveniently moved his boat...
...when we were closing in
on his marina...
...during the official investigation.
You really think Dexter
is the Bay Harbor Butcher?
- It's worth looking into.
- No, it's a waste of time.
Now, start thinking logically.
If Doakes really wasn't
the Bay Harbor Butcher...
...that means
somebody probably framed him.
- Right.
- That same person killed him...
...the real Bay Harbor Butcher.
So the best thing to do is to look
into Doakes' final days.
We should start with the cabin
in the Everglades. Where Doakes died.
Makes sense. First let's eat.
- Okay.
- Waiter.
You went all out.
Well, you had a rough night.
I figured you could use a pick-me-up.
Sit.
You were right about my dad.
I'm sorry I was.
I just-- I feel like such a sucker.
I don't fall for anybody's bullshit,
but when it comes to him, I--
I get it. Fathers can be complicated.
I just don't understand
why I keep holding on to this idea...
...that, underneath it all,
he's a good person.
Maybe because the idea that he's not
is just too hard to take.
I just hope he's gone for good.
You sure scared the shit out of him.
That voice.
I hadn't seen that look on your face
since you took me to see the snow.
Is that what you were talking about?
Your Dark Rider?
Dark Passenger.
Fine. it sounds a little silly
when you say it out loud.
No, I get what you mean.
You do seem
like a different person...
...so it makes sense that you
would name that part of yourself.
Does it just take over?
Where do you go?
Does Dexter Morgan just disappear?
No, I'm still there.
Do you hear a voice, or--?
Not exactly. It's more like a...
.“need.
So it's just like a feeling.
Well, I should get to work.
- Unless you need me to...
- No, I'm good.
I got pancakes.
The good news is that we
have the Phantom entering the bus.
The bad news
is that he never shows his face.
My promise to Deb
is getting harder and harder to keep.
This is more than just a feeling.
- There's no way to ID him?
- I didn't say that.
Right there.
He grabs a rail bare-handed.
We might have a print.
Pull the fucking print off the rail.
- We might get lucky and get a match.
- Let's go, bro.
Hey, baby. What's up?
What? Motherfuck. I'll be right there.
- What's wrong?
- Novikov's sending Nadia to Dubai.
He's holding her. I gotta get her out.
- Alone?
- Got no choice.
- He's putting her on a flight tonight.
- Let's go.
- Where do you think you're going?
- I'm here to see George.
Why don't you stay here with me?
Well, well, if it isn't Sir Lancelot.
- Where's Nadia?
- Nadia?
Let me get her for you.
She's got something to tell you.
Get over here.
All right, tell your boyfriend
who you belong to.
- Let her go.
- Tell him.
Fuck you.
You touch her fucking again,
you're dead.
Oh, what are you gonna do?
You're gonna shoot me
in my own club?
Fuck.
Don't move.
Nadia, get behind George's body.
I want you to take this gun, Nadia.
I want you to shoot me in the arm.
Okay, sweetie? It's okay.
Shoot me in the arm.
What the--? Are you okay?
He pulled a gun and shot me.
I had no fucking choice.
He just grazed me.
Christ.
Go to the safe. Get your passport
and the money and go.
What? She's a witness.
I'm not gonna let her take that money.
She's earned it. She can't be a witness.
The Koshkas will kill her.
And she's here illegally.
- I'm sorry.
- It's okay. Go, go, now.
So did you find a match?
We'll see.
I'm running the Phantom's prints
through AFIS now.
- Nothing.
- Fuck me.
So, what now?
You hand the whole thing over to me
and let me take care of it?
I can't stop thinking
about this Bobby thing.
You know, that somehow
that's the key.
It's a kid's name.
Nobody calls an adult Bobby.
He wrote "it's Bobby" on the bus.
Like Astor and Cody blaming
each other. "it's Astor." "it's Cody."
The fires have to do
with his childhood?
Could be.
Maybe his urges started back then.
I wish we could run that print against
juvie records, but that shit's sealed.
Back to square one.
Not for me.
Government workers
never miss a break.
There's your Phantom.
"Arrested for burning down
his school's gym at age 12.
Spent time in detention,
set his roommate's bunk on fire."
Got sent to a psychiatric facility
in 2006.
Just released a month ago.
That explains why the fires
only just started now.
Gonna turn that over to Deb?
Call it in on the tip line?
I'm not sure I can.
Deb was right. Now that I have proof,
my urges are beyond my control.
Your Dark Passenger. Where did you
come up with that, anyway?
- Thought I got it from you.
- I gave you the code.
The Dark Passenger was all yours.
You said it got into me too early
in that shipping container.
- You thought I was possessed.
- I meant you were traumatised.
Not possessed.
The first time you said it,
you must've been about 12.
I just let it go. I couldn't let you
blame yourself for feelings...
...that were too complicated
for a young boy to understand.
But you're not a boy anymore.
Oh, you sound like Hannah.
Maybe she's right.
Maybe the Dark Passenger
is just a feeling.
- It can't be.
- Why?
Because if there's no Dark Passenger,
then I'm responsible...
...for everything I've done.
It sure is simpler
to just pin all the blame...
...on something else, isn't it, Dexter?
It's much scarier to think...
...that the Dark Passenger
is no more real than I am.
- This is where the cabin used to be.
- Yeah...
...before it got blown to smithereens.
Juan Alonso?
I'm Captain Maria LaGuerta
from Miami Metro Homicide.
- This is Thomas Matthews.
- What do you want'?
Were you the owner of this property
back in 2007?
And did you rent it, at that time,
to a James Doakes?
Bay Harbor Butcher.
No, no, no. I told the cops back then
I had nothing to do with that.
Then how did Mr. Doakes come
to be staying here?
I was renting to Santos Jimenez.
- Jimenez?
- Some kind of Colombian drug guy.
Not that I knew it.
I'd never rent to a criminal.
Of course not.
Now, why does that
sound so familiar?
Now I know why the name
Santos Jimenez rang a bell.
He wasn't just a drug runner.
One of the men responsible for killing
Dexter Morgan's mother, Laura Moser.
- Moser?
- Yeah.
Some drug lord put a hit out on her...
...because he found out
that she was Harry Morgan's Cl.
She was butchered by Jimenez
with a chain saw...
...in front of Dexter
and his brother, Brian.
Brian Moser?
The Ice Truck Killer,
that was Dexter's brother?
Yeah.
So...
...that means that Dexter
watched his mother get chopped up...
...just like the Bay Harbor Butcher
chopped up his victims?
So, what are you saying?
- Where's Jimenez now?
- He disappeared.
Murdered by the Bay Harbor Butcher?
Who was more likely...
...to want Jimenez dead,
Doakes or Dexter?
- Oh, come on, Maria.
- No, Tom.
We can't ignore the facts.
The Bay Harbor Butcher
took blood slides from his victims.
Dexter is a blood spatter analyst.
And Doakes always thought
there was something off about Dexter.
What if Doakes was on to him?
Jesus. What if Dexter
is the real Bay Harbor Butcher?
What if he isn't?
- I am gonna go question him.
- No, you're not gonna do that.
- Now, I don't think you're right.
- Trust me, I hope I'm not.
If somebody's gotta talk to Dexter,
it's gonna be me.
I've known him since he was a kid.
He trusts me.
What's more,
I'm a lot less likely to fuck it up.
The only thing between me
and killing the Phantom...
...is a slightly deflated water wing.
You sure we can't talk you
into coming for a swim?
I'd love to, but I got something
I gotta take care of.
Put your hand through there.
Do this one too.
There you go.
- Well, well, who's this big fella?
- That's my son, Harrison.
Harrison. Isn't that fancy?
And who are you?
I'm Jamie, Harrison's nanny.
Boy. They didn't have nannies like you
back in my day.
We're gonna go swimming now.
You ready? Ready, little man?
Yeah.
Boy, the way they coddle kids today.
They're all gonna be expecting
a helping hand.
The world isn't like that.
It's sink or swim, sonny boy.
Have fun.
What do you want'?
Well, Dexter, I can tell
that you care about my daughter.
- I'm here to find out how much.
- Get to the point.
I have information...
...that could be very damaging
to Hannah.
Now, I could give this information
to the police...
...or you could pay me a nice, tidy sum
to keep it.
What are you talking about?
When Hannah got out of juvie, she
killed a counsellor at a halfway house.
She fed him rat poison.
Her roommate,
little gal named Arlene Schram...
...saw her do it
with her own two eyes.
The cops could get her
to spill her guts.
You're lying.
I read Sal Price's book on Hannah.
He mentioned the counsellor,
nothing about the roommate.
- I hadn't told him about it yet.
- What?
Where do you think he was getting
all those juicy, little plums?
Price was paying me
to dish dirt on my daughter.
I was saving the good stuff
for a bigger payday.
Then the son of a bitch
went belly-up.
And... there went my meal ticket.
You'd sell your own daughter out
for a crawfish farm?
Fuck crawfish, man.
I'm up to my ears in gambling debt.
But you do what you gotta do.
So you gonna give me my money...
...or do I send Hannah to jail?
Get out of here
before you see my bad side.
You might wanna ask Hannah
about Arlene...
...before you come
to a final decision.
Then we'll talk numbers.
What exactly were you doing here?
It was a personal matter.
My girlfriend works at the club.
Jesus, Quinn.
I came to talk to Novikov
about Nadia.
The conversation got heated.
He pulled out a gun, shot me.
I returned fire. Self-defence.
- Plain and simple.
- Write up a report.
I want it on my desk in the morning.
There's a little problem
with your story.
There's a time lag
between the first shot and the second.
I want the truth.
I told you the truth.
I went down when George shot me.
He started to beat the shit
out of Nadia.
I reached for my gun.
He wheeled around,
ready to blow my head off...
...and I took him out.
That's what happened.
- Okay. Then we'll go with that.
- Minus Nadia.
Yeah.
- Hey, where's Dexter?
- I don't know.
But I'd like to point out
that I am here, doing my duty.
- What?
- Nothing.
I feel like I'm gonna be sick.
How can that be my own father?
I'm sorry to have to tell you this...
...but I needed to know
that he was telling the truth.
Arlene Schram is the only person
who can put me in jail.
She saw me put poison
in that counsellor's food.
- I'm gonna have to pay him.
- That's not gonna solve anything.
I don't see any other option.
When other people have threatened
you, you've found other options.
I can't.
He's my father.
I'm gonna call my bank.
I know what you're thinking.
I'm not thinking anything.
Clint McKay doesn't meet the code.
But Joseph Jensen does.
It's not as much fun when you're not
wearing your suit, is it?
Who are you? I can't see you.
Maybe I'm a phantom.
Then again, maybe not.
A phantom can't hurt you.
Oh, God. Please don't.
- Who's Bobby?
- Let me go.
Stop whining. Who's Bobby?
Bobby Hamilton,
my best friend when I was 12.
That's when you set your first fire.
I didn't set it. Bobby did.
It was all his idea.
But then he died and I got caught.
Sent me to the nuthouse
like I was crazy.
It's all because of Bobby.
Fucking asshole.
So does he still talk to you?
Is Bobby the one telling you
to set these fires?
No, that would make me crazy
and I'm not fucking crazy.
I only hurt people because of Bobby.
No, you're the one
who's setting those fires.
The one who's burning people alive.
You can't blame it on something
that happened when you were a kid.
You're not a kid anymore.
It's time for you
to take responsibility.
Fuck.
The caller said
they smelled kerosene.
Looks like we have the right place.
Holy shit.
It's Joe Jensen.
I interviewed this guy.
Dumb fuck must've passed out
from the fumes.
He's still alive.
I guess we found our Phantom.
Who'd have thought it'd be so easy?
- Yeah.
- Guys, come on down.
Got your call. Glad you came
to your senses. You got my money?
Yeah. It's right back here.
What's with all the plastic?
You'll find out soon.
What the hell?
This isn't the way
to make a good impression...
...on your girlfriend's father.
But I can't allow you to hurt Hannah.
Oh, please.
I won't talk to the cops.
I'll leave town.
I promise,
I'll never come near Hannah again.
I wish I could believe you.
Actually, I don't
because then I couldn't kill you.
- Oh, please, you don't have to do this.
- That's what I'm realising.
I don't have to.
But I want to.
Even though you don't meet my code,
I really--
I really want to.
Because unlike you,
I care about Hannah.
You got the devil inside you, boy.
No, I think it's just me.
Sink or swim, Daddy.
- Hey, Deb.
- We arrested the Phantom...
...thanks to you. Now I know
why you weren't at The Fox Hole.
- Consider it a gift.
Bullshit.
You want something in return.
I'm guessing it's for me to lay off
your girlfriend.
- Well, now that you mention it.
- Forget it.
I always give in to you.
But not anymore.
I understand.
I got the money for my dad.
I left him a message.
He should be here soon.
He won't be coming.
How do you know?
I had a talk with him.
I made it clear that I wouldn't allow him
to hurt you anymore.
And I think he understood.
So he's gone?
He won't be bothering you again.
Thank you.
The Dark Passenger has been with me
ever since I can remember...
...pulling the strings,
running the show.
But as it turns out, I'm no puppet.
And you should know,
you were right.
About what?
The Dark...
...Rider.
He doesn't exist.
Turns out maybe you understand me
a little better than I understand myself.
I love you.
I think I love you too.
Hey.
I need your help.
We need to find a woman
named Arlene Schram.
Sure. Who's that?
According to a message I got last night
from Hannah McKay's father...
...she's a witness to a murder.