Previously on Dexter...
You really believe in nothing?
I suppose I believe in a certain set
of principles...
...so that I don't get into trouble.
- Like something I might teach a puppy.
- Is that so bad?
Ladies and gentlemen,
I give you Lieutenant Debra Morgan.
If I could have feelings...
...I'd have them for Deb,
she's the only person who loves me.
You've been the one
constantly good thing in my life.
- There's something inside.
- Holy frankenfuck! Snakes!
- So it's begun?
- Yes.
- It's begun.
- No!
Is this Doomsday?
I'm taking a lot of heat
on Doomsday.
Are we making any headway?
I'm about to interview my top pick
for detective.
So far, our Doomsday killer
has given us three tableaus...
...most likely referencing Revelation,
chapters eight through 10.
- I think I found a new lead.
- Who's this?
Latest and greatest intern
from my forensics class.
The game is about homicide...
...but in my game,
you can be the serial killer.
I think this is offensive.
Who would choose to be a serial killer?
Are you out of your mind?
You fucked a person of interest?
- Maybe you're jealous.
- This is a job of trust...
...and I can't have a partner
I can't trust.
I don't know how to act,
what to do, who to hire.
You're too smart to think
this was gonna be easy.
Did you really think...
...Matthews made you Lieutenant
because you're ready?
It's all politics to get back at me.
Every time shit hits the fan,
I go to him.
He's your safe place.
You're making it sound like
I wanna be with him or something.
Well, do you?
You didn't really think you could foil
God's plan, did you?
- I have to stop him.
- What happened to saving him?
Travis' dark passenger
is a part of him.
He can't be saved from it
any more than I can from mine.
I think Travis is gonna kill again.
The eclipse is here, Travis.
This is not how it's supposed to be!
It is exactly as it should be.
Oh, God.
It's simple human nature
to keep little secrets about ourselves.
We all do it.
I dye my hair.
I watch internet pornography.
But what if your whole life
is a secret?
- A lie.
- How can I help you?
One economy class ticket, flight 449.
- To Budapest.
- Correct.
And exposing the truth
could destroy everything you are.
What do you do?
- Run?
- Oh, God.
- Get the fuck away from the body.
- Deb, it's me.
- Who's on the altar?
- Travis Marshall.
Dexter, what the fuck?
- Oh, shit.
- Talk to me.
Could you lower your gun?
Please?
I came to do one last forensics sweep
like you asked me to do...
...Travis was here.
He came at me with his sword.
I fought him off.
I knocked him out.
How did he end up
wrapped in plastic on the altar?
I snapped.
You Snapped?
What the fuck does that mean?
There's been a lot of anger inside me
since Rita died...
...and when I looked at Travis
and thought about everything he did...
...I wanted him dead, so I killed him.
That still doesn't explain
why he's wrapped up like that.
I didn't even think about it.
I'm a forensics expert.
I guess it's just second nature
not to leave a trace.
Jesus, Dex.
Why the fuck didn't you call me?
I wasn't exactly
in the best state of mind.
- Are you hurt?
- No.
Physically, I'm okay.
- Who are you calling?
- The station.
- I've gotta get everyone down here.
- No.
Please wait.
Why?
How does this look?
- Pretty fucking weird.
- Exactly.
An investigation
could complicate our lives...
...more than either of us
are prepared to deal with.
But it was self-defence.
Yeah.
But it's pretty fucking weird.
I have to call this in.
You had a moment
of temporary insanity.
We can fix this.
How?
I'll get you the best fucking lawyer
in the city.
Even if I'm lucky enough to get off
due to temporary insanity...
...they'll still put me in some
psych ward.
I'll lose my job, my career.
And probably even Harrison.
- So what then?
- Travis is dead.
- Yes.
- Nothing's gonna change that.
Maybe we should just get
rid of the body.
What?
I could put it in my car,
take it somewhere and dump it...
- ...where no one would ever find it.
- No.
- If I'm careful--
- No. Use your head.
If you get caught with the body,
everything's ten times worse.
We're not moving
the fucking body anywhere.
Okay.
We make it look like a suicide.
Frustrated the world didn't end
like he predicted...
...Travis committed ritual suicide
at the church altar...
...stabbing himself with his sword.
Maybe.
But not before first
setting the church on fire.
Fire...
...is biblical.
One last tableau.
And it'll erase any trace
that we were ever here.
How do we do that?
It would have to burn so fast.
Gasoline. There's a station nearby.
- I'll go get a couple of gallons.
- No, Deb, go home. I'll do it.
- I know what I'm doing.
- Bullshit.
Jesus, Debra.
He's a good doggy.
- Hey, Deb.
- His name is Banjo.
- Where did that dog come from?
- The Millikans' dog had a litter.
- I couldn't resist.
- No dogs in this house ever.
- But why?
Because.
- Harry, look how much Debra loves--
- End of discussion.
Dexter.
Don't even think about it.
I have to do whatever it takes
to keep Deb from the full truth.
I have to keep my secret safe.
Otherwise, my life, her life,
will never be the same.
Oh, fuck, Dexter, I don't know
if this was the right thing to do.
It's only a matter of time
before we get called back here.
- We have to go.
- Go where?
- Go home.
- I don't wanna be alone.
I don't want you to be alone.
Well, just follow me.
We can't stay here.
This is all wrong.
I should be on my boat right now
dumping the bags overboard.
I can't let this get away from me.
Morgan.
All right, everyone knows their jobs.
Let's do this.
The arson investigator said...
...the fire started somewhere
in the middle of the church.
The melted remains of a gas
can seem to confirm that.
I was also able to get
one fingerprint...
...that does give us
preliminary confirmation...
...that this is Travis Marshall.
Travis appears to have doused himself
in gasoline as well.
He then climbed up on the altar,
grabbed his sword at the hilt...
...and plunged it into his heart.
One final tableau.
- He died instantly.
- Please tell me he felt a little pain.
It makes sense.
World didn't end like he predicted
so he had to end his.
Good. Saves us the trouble
having to do it.
Cheer up, Lieutenant.
This is a big win.
Would have been better
to catch him alive.
Plastic.
After all he did? Fuck him.
Masuka. Masuka.
Is it possible to kill yourself
with a sword?
Oh, yeah, sure.
The ancient art of hara-kiri
has been well established...
...particularly amongst
my own ancestors...
...as a penance for
various embarrassing...
...and humiliating transgressions.
Congratulations, Lieutenant.
Miami has one less murderer
on the loose.
- Thank you.
- There's a large press gathering outside.
This is a good opportunity for you
to make a statement.
Still a lot to be done in here.
She's not as comfortable lying
to the world as I am.
It's okay, Lieutenant. You can go.
We're just wrapping things up.
- Go talk to them.
- Come on. I'll be right behind you.
I'll sneak out back.
If the press sees me...
...they'll only want to talk to me
and you're the hero this time.
But it's more heroic if you do it...
Hey.
Hey, you. Come here.
Would you make sure
this gets logged'? Thanks.
Even if I put Deb in the uncomfortable
position of lying for me...
...at least I've kept the bigger truth
from her.
It'll all be okay.
Oh, hey, Dexter.
- What are you doing here?
- Jamie's putting Harrison to bed.
I didn't wanna wake him.
You used my computer
without my permission?
I just wanted to check
the basketball scores.
- I thought it would be okay.
- It's not okay.
Okay, well, I'm really, really sorry.
I don't give a shit if you're sorry,
Louis. Never touch my things.
- Louis, here you are.
- Yeah, here he is.
What are you doing here?
This is Dexter's side of the apartment.
I didn't realise there were
different sides. I'm, like, super sorry.
- Is Harrison asleep?
- Yeah. He's out.
- You should go home.
- Okay.
Shit.
It'll all be okay.
You know, everyone acts
like Dexter's such a great guy...
...but he's really kind of
a pompous jerk, don't you think?
No.
Come on.
He's all like,
"Don't touch my shit, man."
- What a dick.
- Louis.
What is your problem?
Dexter's my boss, okay?
And he happens to be very good to me.
I still don't understand
why you were on his side.
Well, I told you.
I just wanted to get some water.
Right.
You know, the more I get to know you,
the weirder and weirder you get.
And we go live to this
Breaking News 9 special report.
I can only speculate but I think it's fair
to say that Travis Marshall felt...
...the intense pressure of Miami Metro
zeroing in on him...
...and that led to his decision
to commit suicide.
Lieutenant, are you ruling out
the possibility that this was a murder?
- Hey, Mike.
- Just had a thought.
Where was his car?
- Whose car?
- Travis Marshall's.
His car wasn't found at the scene,
so how'd he get to the church?
I'm guessing that a man that was
about to stab himself in the heart...
...with a sword probably wouldn't see
a long walk as a big deal.
Probably right, but still...
Sure. Yeah. You should check it out.
I Will.
First thing in the morning.
Good night, Lt.
- Need some help?
- No. No, thank you.
- It's okay. I can fix it.
- Relax. I'm a cop.
- Where's your lug wrench at?
- No!
How were you so perfectly
prepared to kill Travis?
- What do you mean?
- The plastic wrap?
You just happened to have
that with you?
I found it in the storeroom.
What about the knives?
You said Travis came at you
with a sword.
Where did you get the knives?
There was like a whole roll of them.
Travis had them with him.
They were his knives.
I don't know where he got them from.
You weren't in your regular
work clothes.
You changed.
You had a rubber apron.
Plastic sleeves.
I'm just trying to put this together.
Deb, I'm sorry
I put you in this situation.
- You look pretty stressed.
- Yeah.
But...
You know, my job can get messy.
I always keep a change of clothes
in my car.
And the apron, all that other stuff,
is just part of my kit.
Every blood spatter guy's got them.
What about when you said,
"I know what I'm doing"?
When you tried to get me to go,
you said, "I know what I'm doing."
What did you mean?
I meant I work crime scenes
every day.
I know what people like me look for,
so I know what to cover up.
This doesn't feel right.
I know it doesn't.
Deb, I never meant to get you involved
in any of this.
But I am.
We gotta go to work.
What's wrong?
We had to give Banjo back.
I am so sorry, sweetheart.
I never should have gotten him
without talking to your dad.
- This is all my fault.
- I want Banjo back.
No. It's all my fault.
Deb.
Look, I made a huge mistake.
I admit it.
But other than saying I'm sorry
again and again...
...I don't know what else to say.
Morgan. What?
When?
Jesus, fuck.
That was Dispatch.
Mike's been shot.
- Is he okay?
- I don't know.
- I'm right behind you.
- Now, Dex.
Deb, I gotta find my keys,
put my bag together.
I'll get Dispatch
to text me the address.
I'll be two minutes behind you.
My getaway pack.
I don't want to run.
But if Deb doesn't let up,
that may be my only option.
Mike Anderson. One of our own.
Whoever did this to Mike
is gonna be very sorry.
- He'll be very fucking dead.
- Hey.
We do everything by the book.
We're cops, not killers.
But being a killer would feel
so very good right about now.
She suffered blunt force trauma
to the head.
From something narrow
and cylindrical.
- Steel pipe? Tyre iron?
- Yeah, something like that.
The first blow was the left side
of the head...
...and then three more blows to the top
much harder. She...
Her skull was fractured...
...and she haemorrhaged,
as evidenced by the blood...
...that's trickling from her ear.
When will she believe me?
- What happens if she never does?
- When do you think she bought it?
Rigour has set in. She hasn't been
moved from this trunk...
...and judging from the lividity...
...and pooling on the right side
of her face...
- ...I'd say eight to twelve hours ago.
- Not long after we all left the church.
- Yeah.
- What a fucked up couple of days.
I couldn't agree with you more.
We're looking for one shooter
at a minimum.
The shooter hits this girl,
dumps her in the trunk, speeds off.
Gets a flat tyre.
He repays Mike's kindness by
shooting him and fleeing in Mike's car.
His car was found in an industrial park
near North West 52nd.
- I've got people there. Start canvassing.
- And here? Any witnesses?
None so far.
Maybe somebody saw something.
I'm on my way to talk to Mike's wife.
All of her family's in Chicago
and she's gonna need all our support.
Anything she needs.
Hopefully Dexter and I will win
the DNA lottery...
...because it looks
he wiped the car clean.
Nothing on prints, except for hers.
Well, judging by her attire
or lack of it, she was a stripper.
And on duty at the time of her death.
I've got an ID on the fingerprints.
A Kaja Soroka.
Same person this car's registered to.
We'll find out where she works.
The steering wheel, shifter,
door handles, seatbelt buckle...
...they're all wiped clean.
But there's always one place
they forget to clean: the turn signal.
- You're clear.
- Oh, fuck.
The road's clear.
Thank you.
Fuck.
Excuse me.
I need to see the files
on the Ice Truck Killer case.
- Row F-17.
- Thank you.
Kaja Soroka was a Ukrainian national
here on a work visa.
She worked at the Fox Hole
gentleman's club in Pinecrest.
The same owner is listed as having
five other strip clubs in Miami.
Looked into them with Narcotics.
Figured they were...
...using the places to launder money
but we never got anywhere.
Let's get somewhere now.
Quinn and I
is gonna take the Fox Hole.
The rest of you split up
the rest of the clubs. Let's go.
All the prints belong to Miss Soroka
except the one from the turn signal.
But there aren't any matches
in Florida AFIS, FBI or DHS.
There's always Interpol.
I had this weird flashback
of being on Rudy's ta...
Brian's ta--
Whatever the fuck you wanna call him.
Your brother's table.
Sorry. That must have felt
not good for you.
It didn't.
But what bothers me about it
is that I was set up on that table...
...the same way Travis Marshall
was set up on the altar.
- Deb--
- I mean, how do you explain that?
I don't know, I was there too.
- I pulled you off that table.
- I was on that table.
I almost died on that table.
You would think that I would remember
every fucking detail.
But even I don't remember it
that clearly.
Dexter, you were somehow able to...
...perfectly duplicate
how he set everything up.
The same positioning.
The same amount of plastic wrap.
They are the same, Dexter.
They are exactly the same.
Because Brian was imitating me.
This is crazy, Deb. I know that.
It's crazy that I did what I did.
It's crazy that you just happened
to walk in and see me doing it.
I mean, what were you doing
in the church, anyway?
It was just...
I was just fucking checking to see
if everything was okay.
I'm sorry for all the questions.
I'm just-- Dexter, I'm trying
to make sense of this.
Deb, it's not gonna make sense.
- Did you find anything in the car?
- No, not yet.
Give up, Deb.
Give up and just leave this alone.
We have a match.
Viktor Baskov.
When you're losing control
of your entire life...
...it helps to focus on
what you're good at.
My little secret.
I shouldn't be doing a kill now.
The irony is that's the only way
I can maintain control...
...the only way I can keep this
from Deb.
Someone packed in a hurry.
Blood.
And gunshot residue.
Looks like you're our man, Viktor.
How careless were you, Viktor?
One first class one-way ticket to Kiev,
Ukraine leaving in less than two hours.
Very careless.
How can I help you?
One economy class ticket, flight 449.
- To Budapest.
- Correct.
That will be $1890, please,
Mr. Hartwell.
- Dog track.
- Lucky you.
Yeah, lucky me.
- You're all set.
- Thank you.
- Step through.
- Please wait.
- Wait, sir. What are these for?
- Diabetes.
I have a prescription
if you wanna see it.
Go ahead.
Hello, Viktor.
Right here, sweetheart.
- Kill the music.
- Good afternoon, everyone.
I'm Sergeant Batista
from Miami Metro Homicide.
We are investigating the suspected
homicide of one Kaja Soroka...
...as well as the homicide
of a Miami Metro police officer.
And no one is leaving
until they've been questioned.
Employees of the club
up against this wall.
The rest of you perverts, this wall.
- Is there a manager here?
- Yeah, I'm the manager.
- You heard him.
- Let's go.
- George Novikov.
- Oh, my God.
An employee and a pervert.
I don't know which wall you go to.
- You know this guy?
- Yeah, he was a low-level scumbag.
- Now I guess he's a mid-level scumbag.
- Nice to see you, Detective Quinn.
What can you tell me
about Miss Soroka?
Kaja wasn't the smartest girl
in the world.
No?
These girls come here from
little villages, still stinking of cow shit.
They think they're gonna land
some rich husband.
Hook up with the wrong guys,
end up over their heads.
- Is that what you think happened?
- I really have no idea what happened.
Look, I'm sorry Kaja's dead, you know?
She was a sweet kid.
And I'm sorry about
your police officer too.
Their deaths have nothing to do
with us.
We can start with you supplying me
with a list of all of your employees.
Sure.
Can I get a head count list
at the main bar'?
Something cold to drink?
- Your name, please?
- Foxy Raven.
All right. Is that the name
your mother gave you?
And maybe you could show me
some form of ID.
- I do not speak English.
- No, of course you don't.
One of our guys found blood
outside the door.
- Sir, I have your wheelchair.
- I don't need a wheelchair--
It never matters your destination.
The smart traveller must be prepared
to make last-minute adjustments.
- Lieutenant, you got a second?
- Yeah, what's up?
We shut down the strip club questioned
everyone, but didn't get shit.
We know she worked last night.
She signed in at 10, never signed out.
We found blood in the parking lot
which we believe belongs to Soroka.
With that,
we still haven't gotten anywhere.
- No one saw her leave?
- No.
No one remembers any customers
she might have talked to.
No one remembers seeing her car
in the parking lot. No one saw shit.
- She's a fucking ghost in a G-string.
- Bullshit. She walked out of a club...
...in the middle of her shift.
Someone saw.
These places are mobbed up,
Russian, Ukrainian crime.
Strippers who are brought in,
they know not to talk.
- How would you like us to proceed?
- Shut down every club...
...every night until someone talks.
We're on it.
I'm gonna need more coffee.
- Coffee truck?
- No.
I already got so much caffeine
in my head, I can barely think.
You know what, you're not gonna
get anything done tonight.
Just go home.
It's been a very long,
very fucked-up day.
I'm too worked up to sleep
but I could use a drink.
- Knock one back in Mike's honour?
- Lead the way.
- You coming, Lieutenant?
- Rain check.
- But slam a double for me.
- Sure.
- Good night.
- Night.
Good night.
- What's up, Lieutenant?
- Any progress?
We know our shooter
was wearing size ten Prada shoes.
Very pricey.
We know he was right-handed.
So that narrows it down
to about 800 million people.
- Dexter here?
- No.
I told him I'd work late
if he came in early.
Scotch and whatever my friend
is having.
I'll have a vodka.
Don't you mean Shirley Temple?
What, I can't toast to Mike?
- To Mike.
What if your union rep sees?
Aren't you in some kind of programme?
I start next week.
Good. Sooner you address
your problem, the better.
- I'm tired of your shit.
- Still breaking my balls?
You lose one girlfriend
and the wheels come off.
- I'm a sensitive guy.
- I lost two wives...
...and countless girlfriends.
I managed to keep my shit together.
I wish my life was more like yours.
You're living the fucking dream.
Keep it up. I'll put in for that transfer.
I don't care what the union says.
- I'll make it happen.
- I thought you put in for my transfer.
Didn't quite get around to it.
So you were just fucking with me?
You didn't want me to leave.
- You were trying to get me to shape up.
- A lot of good that did.
- You still fucking love me.
- Fuck you.
I try to help you and you go running
to your union rep like a little bitch.
That was weak.
- Well, actually--
- What?
I plan on talking with him
as soon as I find out who he is.
- What about this programme you're in?
- That's bullshit.
You know I don't have
a drinking problem.
Or maybe that's just me in denial.
Who knows?
- We may never get to the bottom of this.
- Just deal with your shit.
Mike was a hundred times better cop
than we'll ever be.
I'll drink to that.
Hello, Viktor.
Where am I?
You're in a place
where things are forgotten.
Never to be used or seen
or touched again.
It seems fitting for a cop killer.
Not to dismiss Kaja Soroka.
She counts too.
- Who are you?
- Good question.
It all depends on who you ask.
Who sent you?
You should not fuck with me.
I have very dangerous friends.
If you knew how many times
I've heard that over the years.
What do you want? Money?
I can get you a lot of money.
- I've heard that a lot too.
- Why are you doing this?
You want the long version?
That could take a couple of hours.
Short version.
Because I have to.
Because I need control.
I'm trying to make things go back
to the way they were.
You're crazy.
There's really no need
for name calling, Viktor.
Is there anything I can do
to keep you from killing me?
- No.
- Then get it over with.
Normally, I don't take orders.
But in this case...
How can I help you?
- This is Isaak.
- Viktor left on an evening flight.
He arrives in Kiev
at 5:25 p.m. your time.
Good. What about
the dead police officer?
That's still a problem
but they don't have shit on us, so...
- I'll make it go away.
- Good.
Ridding the world of people like Viktor
is the one thing I'm good at.
When I'm stressed
near to the breaking point, like now...
...it centers me.
Maybe nothing has to change
with Deb.
Hello?
- Hi, Jamie. ls Dexter there? It's Deb.
- No, he's working late.
- He's at work?
- Yeah.
He said with Mike's shooting and
everything, he might be there all night.
Oh, yeah, right.
Does that happen a lot?
I mean, I know I should know his hours
and everything.
It's just that
I'm always juggling things, $0...
Oh, yeah, he works crazy hours.
Lots of nights till 3, 4 a.m.
- All right. Okay, thanks.
- Want me to have him call you?
No.
No, I'll see him at work tomorrow.
- Okay.
- Good night.
- What's his name?
- Banjo.
- Are you okay?
- No.
Why did Daddy
take the real Banjo away?
- What did I do wrong?
- You didn't do anything.
It's me. It's my fault.
Why? What did you do?
Dexter's allergic to dogs, sweetie.
That's why we can't have them.
Sorry.
- What were you going to tell her?
- The truth.
What is the truth?
That you got rid of the dog
because you thought I might kill it.
- But I wouldn't.
- I couldn't take that chance.
But what's more important
is that you mustn't ever...
...tell Debra the truth about yourself.
- Why?
- If you think she's upset now...
...that's nothing compared to how
she'd feel if she learned what you are.
- She'd be terrified.
- But she loves me.
Dex, she loves
who she thinks you are.
If she ever saw the real you,
she'd never get over it.
Son, your mother and I
aren't gonna be around forever.
Someday Debra will be
all you have left.
You don't wanna lose her, do you?
My mistake was stepping outside
the code.
I should have killed Travis the instant
I met him rather than try to save him.
Compassion does not fit me.
- You're ready?
- Yes, I'm ready to join you.
But I can't. Not Deb.
No, you can't be a killer and a hero.
Vincent.
- You're working late.
- Yeah, well, lots to do.
Everyone's doing double shifts.
I know you're working on Mike's case
and that's top priority.
Wondering if anyone had a chance to go
through the evidence from the church.
Sorry. It's all in those boxes over there
but I'm kind of swamped here.
Of course.
Hey, does our forensics team ever take
blood slides at crime scenes?
No. If any of the evidence
is transportable, we bag it.
Otherwise, if it's blood,
we absorb into cotton squares...
- ...then we bag it.
- I see.
Only one person who ever worked at
Miami Metro ever took blood slides.
- And that was?
- Sergeant Doakes.
And that was only because of his
side gig as the Bay Harbour Butcher.
Right. Of course, Sergeant Doakes.
Thank you.
None of us want to be
fully revealed...
...all our faults and weaknesses
laid bare for the world to see.
All the more reason to make sure
I never again stray...
...from what Harry taught me.
Did you kill all these people?
I did.
Are you...
Are you a serial killer?
Yes.