Previously on Dexter...
LaGuerta found a blood slide
with Travis Marshall's blood on it...
...at the fucking church.
Talked her into letting me help with the
Bay Harbour Butcher investigation...
...so I can keep tabs
on what's happening.
You what?
That toy isn't bringing back memories
of being scared.
She was straddled by her assailant.
Wayne didn't kill that woman.
Well, it was someone smaller.
Stabbed the woman
until the knife got so bloody...
...her hand slipped along
the edge of the sharp blade...
...cutting her palm very deeply.
Everything you've said is a lie.
That's my story...
...and I'm sticking to it.
Did you get the blood report back?
From the bodies from the dig?
Yeah.
Anything I should know?
Nope.
Just forget about work.
Joey Quinn. Used to have
an understanding with him.
Leave a bag of cash in his car
and he'd do whatever we asked.
He drew his gun as the attacker fired.
This blood
is from a defensive wound.
So you got arrested, there'll be a trial,
you'll go to prison for a long time.
Does that mean this is over?
No.
Hannah McKay.
She stabbed a woman five times.
And since I found out, all I can think
about is giving her what she deserves.
Maybe she deserves a little slack.
When she killed that woman,
she was only 15.
Scared of Wayne. On the run.
It could have been a one-time thing.
I saw the way she touched
her trophies. Nostalgic.
And when you like to kill,
you don't just stop.
She must have killed again
since Wayne.
You have no evidence
to support that.
Her husband died
of a heart attack at 40.
Perfect health, no family history.
- Seems suspicious.
- You're really reaching here, Dexter.
I know she killed her husband.
I can feel it.
I just need proof.
Don't you have
more pressing concerns?
Debra, LaGuerta, Isaak.
Why do you think I need a kill
so badly?
- Where do you think you're going?
- To talk to her.
Get her to slip up about her husband.
Give me a lead.
What makes you think
she'll tell you anything?
Last time you saw her,
you accused her of murder.
Good point.
I need a peace offering.
And this is a big opportunity
for the department.
Arresting the head
of the Koshka Brotherhood is good.
Sorry I'm late.
I can't even be late
without making Deb angry.
You all did great work.
The arraignment went well.
Sirko was denied bail.
He has a small army of lawyers, and
they're putting his bail up for review.
No way he'll get out.
- Not on three counts of murder.
- Hope you're right.
So do I. As long as Isaak's behind bars,
I'll have time to deal with Hannah.
Of course he's right.
The guy killed three Colombians.
Plus, we have evidence
that puts Sirko at the scene.
None of that will matter...
- ...if his team claims self-defence.
- It's a solid case.
We still need to make sure...
...the captain is prepared
for any questions the DA may ask.
Look, we have all seen cases that we
thought were a sure thing go south.
The right lawyers, the right jury,
anything can happen.
Which is why the DA wants
to make sure it doesn't.
At least I can make a peace offering
to one woman in my life.
If I want Hannah to give me
the time of day...
...I need to show her I'm not a threat.
And how do you intend to do that?
I haven't filled out the blood report
for those bodies we dug up.
I could fudge it.
Omit some key facts.
Forget to run the blood on
the victim's dress for Hannah's DNA.
The cops think Wayne Randall
killed those people.
If I don't tell them otherwise,
they won't know different.
Didn't you promise your sister...
...you wouldn't take cases
from the police?
Hannah has immunity.
Nothing the cops can do.
Telling Deb will only make her crazy.
Then what? You think you'll just show
Hannah this report and she'll confess?
Tell you she killed her husband?
What other choice do I have?
You're blocking my view.
It's a wall.
To you, perhaps.
To me, it's a blank canvas.
A projection screen for the mind.
You killed three of our boys, smartass.
You're not gonna sound so smart
when you're bleeding like a stuck pig.
Right.
You and your Colombian friends
haven't really thought this through.
Now, as a businessman, I've found
you have to weigh short-term gains...
...against long-term consequences.
True, you and your men could retaliate.
In the short-term, I'd be dead.
But I'm not the only member
of the Koshkas.
I could have 100 men here should
anything happen to me, understand?
Yeah.
We outnumber you. We out gun you.
Quite frankly,
we're smarter than you.
So I'm afraid in the long-term...
...your plan falls a little short.
Now, the art of any deal
is negotiation.
Have we come to terms?
Yeah.
Hi, you've reached George Novikov.
Leave me a message.
George, it's Isaak. I need you
to pay me a visit. It's urgent.
Hannah should be on her way back
from the flower mart right about now.
I'll be able to catch her
before I go to work.
I've watched her for days.
She never changes her schedule.
Hannah.
Great, you're a stalker.
- What happened to Peter Cottontail?
- Poison.
Rabbits kill my plants, so I kill them.
You could just trap them
and let them go.
When you do that, they come back.
I do what I have to do.
Remind me to never show up
on your property uninvited.
Too late.
So you've accused me of murder,
animal cruelty.
- Anything else?
- Actually, I came to apologise.
It's a copy of the blood report
from the bodies you helped us find.
Wayne Randall's victims.
Wayne's victims, huh?
The blood evidence was inconclusive.
I realised it when I got back to my lab.
I shouldn't have accused you.
I'm really sorry.
Thanks.
It takes a real gentleman
to admit when he's wrong.
- What?
- You have a little...
Dirt.
Occupational hazard.
I can get pretty dirty.
Right.
Remember why you're here.
Dead husband.
Since I'm here, I could use
a plant for my apartment.
Really? A plant?
Follow me.
- Any idea what you're looking for?
- Just a plant. Something planty.
You're the expert.
Well, why don't you tell me
about your place?
So I can get a better idea.
It's a one bedroom on the water,
lots of sunlight.
- You live alone?
- Currently, yeah.
- You?
- And before?
- I was married for a little while.
Unfortunately, he passed away.
How about this one?
If you take good care of it,
it'll last for years.
Really? I always figured
once you took flowers home...
...they had already started to die.
- That's kind of a morbid outlook.
- Is it?
Yeah, I guess I'm kind of
maybe a morbid guy.
So how'd he die, your husband?
Heart attack, but we really don't need
to talk about it.
We can though if you want to.
I mean, I understand. My wife died too.
Oh, what happened?
She was murdered.
Oh, God, that's...
That's awful.
Yeah.
Different from your situation,
obviously.
Yeah.
All this doom and gloom.
You mind if we change the subject?
I do, actually. If her husband's
off-limits, I'll have to take another tack.
- So how long have you had this place?
- About a year.
Worked for the previous owner
before that.
Beverly Grey, amazing woman.
I've kept the business exactly the same
as when she ran it.
Same clients, same schedule.
I even kept her handyman on.
- Where is she now? Retired?
- She passed away about a year ago.
That's when I took over.
Dead husband, dead mentor.
It was actually a really sad time,
so I'd...
I'd rather not talk about it.
Sorry, I wasn't going
for more doom and gloom.
Seems you have a knack.
- I should get going. I gotta get to work.
- But you still haven't picked a plant.
That one.
Pink. Really?
What do I owe you?
Consider it a gift.
Thanks.
See you around.
Since Hannah stabbed her first victim,
two people close to her have died.
Seems I'm not the only one
with a knack for doom and gloom.
Beverly Grey. The deceased mentor
of Hannah McKay.
I paid a visit to the clerk of county.
Beverly's will listed Hannah
as her lone beneficiary.
Makes sense.
No children, no immediate family.
Why wouldn't Beverly
leave Hannah her legacy?
But if Hannah
were Beverly's heir apparent...
...it'd give her motive
for murder.
The question is,
is Hannah responsible for her death?
- Cause of death, heart attack.
- Just like her husband.
- Seems suspicious.
- Or not.
Heart disease is the leading cause
of death in this country.
Hell, it got me.
What about poison?
That's the way women usually kill.
- Safe. Detached.
- She poisons rabbits, Dexter.
It doesn't mean she poisons people.
Why are you so convinced
she's still a killer?
I know that face.
Sal Price.
Maybe he can tell me something
about Hannah I don't already know.
Hey, was that Sal Price?
- Yeah. What do you care?
- I read his book. I'm a fan.
Since when do you read true crime?
Since we started working
on the Wayne Randall case.
I'm learning new things about you.
What was Price doing here?
He heard we dug up more
Wayne Randall victims.
He wants to reissue his book.
He asked if he could see the case files.
- I said I'd have copies made.
- Shit.
The case is closed.
What's the big deal?
I fudged the blood report
for starters.
No, it's just... Was he leaving?
I wanna ask him to sign my book.
Went to the coffee truck
while I'm having copies made.
I'm sure he'd love to.
- Coffee.
- Mr. Price?
Hi. Dexter Morgan. I'm a big fan.
I was hoping
maybe I can get an autograph?
Yeah, sure. Of course.
Morgan.
- Any relation to the lieutenant?
- Yeah, she's my sister.
She says you're writing an update
on the new bodies. That's exciting.
Is she single?
Yeah, last time I checked.
Look, I should warn you, since we're
talking about a solved crime...
...I didn't put much time
into my blood report.
That's okay, I usually have my own guy
take a look. Just in case.
What are you hoping to find?
I have a little theory...
...that Hannah McKay deserves
her own sequel.
So does your sister date, or--?
You're writing a book
about Hannah McKay?
What are the highlights?
Come on, give me something.
Just a teaser for a fan.
Only if you put in a good word
for me with your sister.
Sure.
So? Hannah McKay?
Right, so get this.
Right out of juvie,
Hannah moves into a halfway house.
Seems like all's well
until she accuses some counsellor...
...of abusing her sexually.
- So, what happened?
- Nothing. Guy gets a slap on the wrist.
But a couple of weeks later,
he drops dead.
Rat poisoning.
Sound like a coincidence to you?
Wow, I don't know.
Three makes a pattern.
Maybe they all got in her way.
Well, that's all you're getting out of me.
You want the rest, read the book.
I'm gonna go check on those files.
Pleasure to meet you, Dexter Morgan.
I will read your book, Mr. Price.
But I won't be waiting
for it to come out in hard copy.
You are now officially
my favourite lieutenant.
Can I buy you an adult beverage
as a token of my appreciation?
Some place dark and not too loud?
That sounds like a date.
Not to me. it sounds
like a beautiful police lieutenant...
...sharing an evening
with a handsome crime writer.
Can I take a rain check?
- Sorry.
- Don't be. I get it.
Me coming here, asking you out.
You think I'm trying
to write your story.
- Which, I'm not by the way.
- My story?
Being engaged
to the Ice Truck Killer.
- I'm sure you got--
- That hadn't occurred to me.
- That what you're doing?
- I wasn't.
How do I know
that's not some tactic?
Are you always this defensive?
Sorry, I didn't mean to be defensive.
I'm just not really in a dating mode.
Dating mode. That's a thing.
My life is really fucking complicated.
Fine, but for the record,
I like complicated.
So if you happen
to change your mind, give me a call.
Oh, sorry, had garlic for lunch.
You have gum in here, yes?
What is that?
George left it in my car
the last time I was at the club.
Figured you knew about it.
Why would he do that?
He used to give me cash
to look the other way...
...when I worked Narcotics.
I thought you were joking
when you said you were a dirty cop.
I was joking. I'm a good cop.
- I also like money.
- Joey.
I know.
I figured George was gonna
ask me for something small...
...but now that lsaak's been arrested
I'm not sure...
...I wanna do whatever it is
they're gonna ask me to do.
You're sure you didn't know?
If I did, I would have told you
to give it back.
- You're giving this back, right?
- I'm thinking about it.
Joey, these are dangerous people.
You know,
there's like 10 grand in that bag.
What good is money if you're dead?
I'm not for sale.
Take care of yourself.
Price is going through my evidence
at the police station.
Turnaround is fair play.
Hopefully his thoughts about Hannah
are a little more organised.
Looks like Price and I
share an obsession.
But he's had years
to follow Hannah's every move.
I need to catch up.
Price's source material.
I'll have to come back to see what
he has on me.
Right now, I have to get in
and get out.
A blood test
for Hannah's mentor Beverly Grey.
Whatever it means,
I'll bet Price wrote about it.
Yeah, I'm good. Fine, fine.
- So have you heard from Louis?
- No.
Thank God.
I mean, hookers?
Gross. Who does that?
Yeah.
Gross.
So, what do you think of this place?
I guess it's cute.
Kind of a dive.
Because the owner's thinking
about selling...
...and I'm thinking about buying.
How are you gonna find
the time to run a restaurant...
...with all the hours you put in?
I could just retire.
I've put in my 20 years.
- So you're just gonna quit?
- Retire.
- Do something else?
- Yeah.
Look, Angel, you're my brother
and I love you.
But this is a big decision.
And we both know you're impulsive.
You get these crazy ideas,
like, you wanna buy a--
- I don't get--
- You do and then you end up divorced.
With a broken down Trans Am and
barely enough money to pay the rent.
I see you brought Jurg.
So good to see you both getting on
in my absence.
You kidding?
Since you've been arrested...
...can't take a shit without Lurch
breathing down my neck.
Well, someone has to keep an eye
on you while I'm in here.
So, what's the big emergency?
You need to get me out of here
as soon as humanly possible.
- What happened?
- Nothing. Yet.
But I'd really like
to avoid killing anyone in here.
It would get in the way
of my being released.
Have you heard
from Detective Quinn?
He...
He gave back the money.
Which is weird, because he's never
turned down a payoff before.
George.
Do not disappoint me.
Hi.
Quinn. Reservation for two.
Your other party's already arrived.
- Right this way, Mr. Quinn.
- Okay.
Enjoy your dinner.
What the fuck is this?
Where's Nadia?
If you hurt her, I will put a bullet
through your motherfucking head.
Easy, detective. Don't make a scene.
Nadia is a valuable commodity.
We wouldn't do that.
Not unless we had to.
- What do you want from me?
- I don't want shit. But Isaak Sirko...
...he wants you to lose the blood
evidence linking him to the murders.
- Why the fuck would I do that for you?
- You took our money.
And I gave it back.
I don't owe you shit.
Not the way Isaak sees it.
Now, he did you a favour by taking out
those Colombian scumbags.
As soon as you let him go,
he'll head back to the Ukraine.
You'll never hear from him again.
- It's not that big a deal.
- Then find someone else.
Now, why would we do that
when we have you?
Joey, come on.
You know we got you.
What happens if I don't cooperate?
I'm thinking of transferring Nadia
to one of our sex clubs in Dubai.
But she's a strong girl.
She'll last a couple weeks
before she slits her wrists.
If I do this...
...Nadia's a free woman.
You give me her fucking passport,
understand?
Deal.
And I'll do you one better.
You can even keep the cash.
See, Joe? Just like old times.
It's Nadia. Leave a message.
Nadia, it's Joey.
Call me as soon as you get this.
- You wanted to see me?
- Yeah.
- How was the meeting with the DA?
- Fine.
He's confident that we have
enough evidence to put Sirko away.
Thank the sweet fucking
baby Jesus.
That's not what I wanted
to talk to you about.
I had my last two interviews
yesterday.
With families
of the missing persons...
...who could have been victims
of the Bay Harbor Butcher?
And? Any leads?
Not a one.
It's frustrating.
So I started looking into open cases.
I figure a lot of homicide suspects
vanish into thin air.
What if the Butcher
took some of them out?
That's good thinking.
- Did you find anything?
- Maybe.
Remember the barrel girls?
A swamp full of blonds in barrels,
all of them...
...raped, electrocuted and embalmed?
Yeah, how could I forget it?
All five suspects, including
self-help guru Jordan Chase...
...went missing before we could build
a case against them.
You're thinking
the Butcher could have killed them.
- There were two vigilante killers.
- Maybe he took on an accomplice.
One of the victims
who was looking for justice.
I know it's a reach.
But it's possible.
Wasn't the theory that Jordan Chase
killed the accomplices...
- ...then fled the country?
- Yes.
But even if Chase killed
the other four suspects...
...the Butcher still could have
killed Chase.
I don't think so.
Jordan Chase was very high profile.
It would be too risky.
Still...
It's worth looking into.
Find what you're looking for?
It says here Price bribed
the funeral director to get access...
...to Beverly Grey's body
before she was cremated.
He stole a blood sample
and ran it for aconite.
Aconite?
The queen of all poisons.
Ingesting it causes a heart attack.
Price says it's been growing on
the greenhouse property for years.
Poison. You were right.
- Didn't show up on the autopsy?
- It wouldn't have.
Not if they didn't know
what they were looking for.
Her blood test.
Positive for aconite.
Proof that Beverly was poisoned.
But not proof
that Hannah did the poisoning.
Hannah said her handyman was there
when Beverly was still alive.
That could be worth a conversation.
Jesus, now she's showing up
where I live.
- What are you doing here?
- You picked the wrong plant.
I knew I could do better.
Hopefully you won't kill it.
- What is it?
- It's a spotted phalaenopsis.
See the red on the petals?
Remind you of anything?
- Blood spatter.
- Which reminded me of you.
You came all the way out here
just to bring me that?
- How did you find me?
- Google.
Now who's the stalker?
I should ask her to leave.
So you wanna come in?
Yeah, sure.
I'll help you find a place for it.
I need a spot near a window,
but not directly in front of it.
No, that's the bedroom.
No plants in here. Not enough light.
You could open the shades.
I like the dark.
So do I.
Why is she here?
What does she want?
There.
Now you can look at it
when you wake up...
...and when you go to bed.
Sorry, I gotta take this.
Hey, Deb. What's up?
Nothing, just that LaGuerta might have
another theory...
...that could royally fuck us.
- Can you meet me?
- I'm in the middle of something.
Dex, this can't wait.
All right, I'll meet you in 20.
I'm telling you, Dexter, LaGuerta's
not just gonna forget this one.
Jordan Chase is long gone.
So are the others.
There's nothing
to trace them back to me.
Are you sure about that?
There are no loose ends?
What about the person
you were working with?
- I don't know what you're talking about.
- You know what I'm talking about.
There were two vigilante killers,
not one.
Who was helping you?
She wasn't helping me.
I was helping her.
- Was she one of their victims?
- It doesn't matter.
If LaGuerta tracks her down,
which is next to impossible...
...she won't incriminate herself
or me.
- How do you know that?
- Trust me, I just do.
Motherfucker.
You were together.
Like a couple.
I remember having a thought...
...that whoever was doing this
was doing it for love.
That was right after Rita died.
You had that tenant
with that weird fucking name.
Lumen.
- It was her, wasn't it?
- It doesn't matter.
It was.
Jesus fucking Christ, Dexter.
You moved your girlfriend
into the house...
...where Trinity murdered your wife...
- ...so you could kill together?
- It wasn't like that.
I felt guilty
about what happened to Rita.
I thought
that maybe if I helped Lumen...
- I was trying to make things right.
- Of course.
By murdering five other people.
Why can't the past stay in the past?
Do we have to keep talking about this?
We do, as long as LaGuerta
has a bug up her ass.
Let me worry about LaGuerta, please!
You just worry about yourself.
Go out. Have fun.
Go on a date.
That guy, Sal Price. He was into you.
Get out of my house.
What did I say?
I really need to kill someone.
Hannah's become a real thorn
in my side.
Maybe her handyman can give me
what I need to finally fix my problem.
Excuse me.
Is Hannah here?
- She's at the flower market.
- Oh, man.
I drove all the way.
You know when she'll be back?
An hour or so. It might be sooner.
You could wait.
How long have you been
working here?
About 10 years.
So you knew the previous owner.
Beverly Grey?
Hannah said she passed away.
Heart disease. Sad story.
Yeah, Hannah said they were close.
It must have been hard on her.
I'm sure it was,
but she never let it show.
- Not the emotional type, huh?
- I never saw anything like it.
Even when Beverly got sick,
Hannah never complained.
Never asked for help.
Help with what?
Taking care of Beverly.
Hannah bathed her, fed her,
took her to the doctor's.
All alone?
She was stubborn, man.
I figured it had something to do
with growing up on a farm, you know?
Just ploughing through.
Look, I tried to help out.
Hannah dug her heels in.
Wouldn't let anybody near Beverly.
Which means Hannah was the only one
who had the access to poison her.
Hey, Hannah mentioned a purple
wildflower that grows on the property.
Thought it would look great
in my place.
I'm thinking I could take a look
while I wait.
All the wildflowers are over
in the southwest corner.
Aconite.
Price is right. Yet again.
Beautiful and dangerous.
Just like Hannah.
She's harvested it.
Maybe she's set her sights
on a new target.
You're after her.
Who's to say she isn't after you?
But Why?
She doesn't think I'm a threat.
She accepted my apology.
Don't be naive, Dexter.
You think she's a killer
but not a liar?
Dexter?
What are you doing here?
I was in the neighbourhood.
Well, come on in.
I'll make some coffee.
Careful, it's hot.
And potentially deadly.
Hannah, I wish I had more time,
but I gotta get to work.
You know, I don't understand you,
Dexter.
I can't figure out what it is
that you really want.
- Nothing. I don't want anything.
- You want something.
- You keep making excuses to see me.
- They weren't excuses.
It's getting creepy
that you keep coming by.
Creepy? You came to my place too.
Why don't you just save us
both the trouble and spit it out?
I wanna take you out.
On a date?
- That'll work.
- Well, that's sweet.
But I don't date.
- I get too attached.
- Really?
- You don't strike me as the type.
- Well, I'm not who people think I am.
So who are you?
On the inside?
Probably still that 15-year-old girl
who ran away with Wayne Randall.
The girl who stabbed a woman
in cold blood.
Except now I know better.
What do you mean?
I mean, he promised me everything.
He was gonna take me to Disney
World and Santa's Holiday Adventure.
Some little Christmas-themed
shithole just outside of Miami.
You know it?
It's the only place in Florida
where you can see the snow.
I was obsessed.
Then we were gonna live
in Argentina on a farm...
...and have this picture-perfect life.
Sounds pretty good to me.
Yeah, it was all I could think about.
I longed for it.
I needed it,
and I knew that until I had it...
...I would never be satisfied.
The craziest part is that somehow
I had myself convinced that Wayne...
...was the only one
who could give it to me.
Wayne? Really?
Why?
I had it in my head
that he was the answer.
That he was gonna fill
the emptiness that I felt inside.
So I didn't care when he turned
out to be the bad guy.
I didn't care if he shot somebody.
I didn't even care
if I ended up in juvie.
Not until later anyway.
It was worth it...
...just to hold on to the fantasy.
You still feel that way?
No, now I do whatever it takes
to make sure I don't lose myself...
...like that again.
But I do still wish
I had gotten to see the snow.
You know I'm not Wayne, right?
I'm not gonna land you in jail.
- I still think it's a bad idea.
- Why did you come to my apartment?
You know why.
Go out with me.
Come on,
I'm just gonna keep stalking you.
I'm just-- I'm just trying
to do the right thing.
Do the wrong thing.
Fine.
One date.
- But if I end up in jail--
- I'll pick you up at 8.
A date?
Really?
She caught me off guard.
I had to think of something.
Nadia, it's Joey. I stopped by the club
last night and you weren't there.
I know I've called 50 times.
I'm worried about you.
Please call me back.
Let me know you're okay.
You got a sec?
- Not really, I--
- Do I seem impulsive to you?
Jamie says I make bad decisions.
But I have this opportunity,
and I'm thinking about retiring.
Holy shit.
- You're retiring?
- No, I didn't say that.
- I'm just considering my options.
- Can we talk later? I got shit to do.
Hey, you know Angel's thinking
about retiring?
Masuka.
Is that true?
I wanna buy a restaurant.
- Give us a minute?
- Yeah. For the record...
...studies show that men who retire
are usually dead in five years.
It's a fact. Look it up.
Where is this coming from?
Is this
about Mike Anderson's murder...
- ...because we've been through this.
- I think I'm burnt out, Deb.
I don't date.
I hardly see my kid.
I'm so focused on work
that I forgot to have a life.
And I know this may sound crazy...
...but the idea of buying this restaurant
actually makes me happy.
Doesn't sound crazy at all.
Sal Price.
Sal, hey, it's Debra Morgan from--
Lieutenant Morgan
with the potty mouth.
Right, with the potty mouth.
- To what do I owe this pleasure?
- Are you still up for that drink?
Yeah, absolutely.
But I thought you said--
I think I need to get a life.
Yes, you do.
- Case number?
- Nine-eight-seven-six-zero.
That's the Dixon case.
I gotta testify in court next week.
Need a refresher on the evidence.
Dry section. Bin 51, shelf four.
Third one over.
Back and to the right.
- Case number?
- Case 16258.
It's Layva.
Should be two or three boxes.
It goes to arraignment next month.
Fuck me.
Oral fixation?
Sorry. Bad habit.
When I quit drinking,
I picked up smoking.
When I quit smoking,
I picked up chewing on things.
Straws, pens, toothpicks.
Turns out I have a problem
with moderation.
Me too.
That and an obsessive personality.
Which is great for work,
but it's really shitty for relationships.
Are we talking about me or you?
So, what are you working on right now?
You're updating your book, right?
That and another project.
Which I probably
shouldn't tell you about.
Why? Is it a secret?
- Because trust me, I can keep a secret.
- I don't know.
You're the Lieutenant of Homicide, and
when I tell cops about my theories...
...they tell me to go fuck myself.
That won't happen here, I promise.
Come on, don't be a cop-tease.
A good theory
totally gives me a girl boner.
Okay.
Off the record.
You know that stuff in my book
about Hannah McKay...
...being this innocent young girl?
A victim
of Wayne Randall's influence?
- Yeah.
- Well, I think it's bogus.
I think Hannah killed her first victim
right along with Wayne.
And I think she kept right on killing.
Go fuck yourself.
If that's true, we're fucked.
We gave her immunity.
It's true.
I have evidence to back it up.
It's in my bag right now.
Wait, you have it here?
- Why, do you wanna see it?
- You have to show it to me.
- I'm the Lieutenant of Homicide.
- Look at you. Like a dog with a bone.
If you show it to me,
I'll totally make outwith you.
Best first date ever.
Okay.
So these are the spatter photos
from the bodies you dug up.
I've seen those. Dexter said
the evidence was inconclusive.
My blood guy disagreed.
Well, there's no way.
My brother's never wrong.
My guy said the pattern
on this body indicates a killer...
...much smaller than Wayne Randall.
Smaller.
Smaller like Hannah McKay?
Fuck balls.
You gotta be kidding me.
I thought this place
was closed for the season.
It is.
So how are we gonna get in?
How do you feel
about a little breaking and entering?
Yeah.
All of us have some kind of longing.
A need crying out to be met.
What is this place?
Wait.
Some of us get what we want
and we're happy.
The snow.
I thought maybe if you saw it,
you could finally get some peace.
Thank you.
But some of us are never satisfied.
When I said I wanted to take you out,
this is what I meant.
You said you wanted to see the snow.
This is what keeps me up at night.
This is what I long for.
This is what I need to...
...fill my emptiness.
Do what you gotta do.
Dexter.