Previously on Dexter...
Our primary suspect
is Sergeant James Doakes.
- Doakes?
- If Doakes really wasn't...
...the Bay Harbour Butcher, best thing
to do is look into Doakes' final days.
We should start with the cabin
in the Everglades where Doakes died.
- I was renting the place to Jimenez.
- Jimenez?
He was one of the three men responsible
for killing Dexter Morgan's mother.
What if Dexter
is the real Bay Harbour Butcher?
If somebody's gonna talk to Dexter,
it's gonna be me.
All right,
tell your boyfriend who you belong to.
- I'm sorry.
- It's okay. Go. Go, now.
He died in my apartment.
Figured it would kick in while Price
was on the road. An auto accident.
- How'd you do it?
- Price liked to chew on his pens.
Last one had a little something on it.
She is a killer.
You will never be safe with her.
When Hannah got out of juvie...
...she killed a counsellor
at a halfway house.
She fed him rat poison.
Her roommate, a little gal
named Arlene Schram, saw her do it.
He won't be bothering you again.
I love you.
I think I love you too.
I need to find Arlene Schram.
Sure. Who's that?
According to a message I got last night
from Hannah McKay's father...
...she's a witness to a murder.
I've never thought about the future.
About growing old.
Maybe because the future
has never been kind to people like me.
Or their loved ones.
Bye, Dad.
Bye, Harrison.
But, suddenly,
my future seems very possible.
And growing old
is not only a possibility...
...it seems appealing.
- Hello.
- Am I speaking with Dexter Morgan?
- Yeah, that's right.
- This is Department of Corrections.
Hector Estrada
is having a parole hearing.
- What? When?
- This morning at 10 a.m.
I know this is sudden.
Okay. Thank you for letting me know.
You're welcome, sir.
That was the Department of Corrections.
Hector Estrada is up for parole.
He thinks there's good chance
he'll get it.
Estrada?
Remember I told you about my mother
and how she died?
Oh, God.
Was he--?
Was he one of the men that killed her?
He was the leader.
He gave the order.
What about the others?
Dead.
Estrada is the last survivor.
I'm sure you'll have something to say
about that.
Look at it this way.
Maybe it's the universe
giving you a Christmas present.
No one but you
would see it that way.
Maybe killing Estrada
will close this chapter of my life...
...and open me up to a future
with Hannah.
Panel has reviewed
all the pertinent data in this matter.
We find that the prisoner
meets the requirements for parole...
...under the
Compassionate Release Statute 463.
Have you read the statute?
You understand your obligations?
I understand what's expected of me.
I won't screw up.
At this time, we invite any victims
present to enter a statement...
...either for or against
the board's decision.
I have no objection.
Nadia, it's me again.
This is my fifth message.
Just wanna know where you are.
Give me a call.
Did you get a bad news?
Just trying to find Nadia.
Hey. Taking a survey.
Secret Santa this year
or no Secret Santa?
I got enough presents to buy, man.
Man, the Christmas spirit around here
sucks big reindeer dicks.
Deb.
I found Arlene Schram.
Oh, fucking amazing.
She's living out in Hialeah.
Two drug arrests since juvie,
has two kids from different fathers.
Temporarily lost custody a year ago
due to her drug abuse.
Good to know. I'll have to go hard.
I might have to take away...
- ...her Mother of the Year trophy.
- Any luck in locating Hannah's father?
No, zero. He dropped the dime
on his daughter and then skipped town.
Well, he's a drifter.
He could be anywhere.
Maybe we should let your brother know
what we're doing.
- We're investigating his girlfriend.
- I told Dexter...
...that if I found anything on Hannah,
I'd act.
- I still don't feel right about this.
- And I'm telling you it's my call, okay?
Matthews made his choices.
Now he spends Christmas alone
with his boat.
How close was I to the same fate?
Oh, hand me one of those zip ties
on the table there, will you?
Thanks.
Fucking Christmas lights.
Every year I put them up, and
every year I wonder why I bothered.
You said you wanted to see me.
Yeah. Yeah, thanks for coming out.
Sit.
I wanted to give you a heads-up on this
idea that Captain LaGuerta has got.
What?
The Bay Harbour Butcher.
Maria's convinced
that Doakes was innocent...
...and that the real killer
is still at large.
Actually, she thinks it might be you.
Me?
I know. Personally, I think
she's had one too many Mosquitos...
...or whatever they call
that goddamn drink.
But, anyway, here we are.
What makes her think
I'm the Bay Harbour Butcher?
She knows your life story,
your childhood...
...what you saw
in that cargo container.
Most people,
that would screw them up for life.
Your brother went through the
same thing, look what happened to him.
He saw your mother dismembered
before his eyes...
...then he went on
to dismember his own victims.
Drink?
No.
The Bay Harbour Butcher
also dismembered his victims.
Of course,
your brother wasn't the Butcher.
The murders continued
after his death.
But it's weird, huh?
Another thing that's weird,
that cabin where Doakes died.
What about it?
Was rented to a man named Jimenez.
He's one of the men
who killed your mother.
I mean, what are the odds?
He's interrogating me.
You knew my father,
you've known me my whole life...
...do you think
I'm the Bay Harbour Butcher?
Of course not.
But if I don't ask these questions,
Maria will.
You know, I always had a bad feeling
about Doakes.
He obviously didn't like me
too much...
...from the get-go.
Not exactly a secret.
But then
that whole Bay Harbour Butcher case...
...came along
and something happened...
...that I've never told anyone about.
- What?
- I saw Doakes on his boat.
Doakes had a boat?
Yeah.
I figured he used it
to dispose of his victims.
He kept it at the same marina as mine.
I moved my boat to get away from him.
Why didn't you come forward?
Because I didn't know
what he'd do to me or my sister.
Yeah.
Doakes was a pretty formidable guy.
I can imagine how scared
you must have been.
Sorry to put you through all this,
Dexter.
I'll talk to Maria...
...get her to move on.
No hard feelings?
None.
I've given them a boat to search for.
Now I just have to make sure
there's something for them to find.
Hey, don't splash your sister.
I'm not gonna tell you again.
Sorry, they are non-stop.
No, I have a nephew their age,
so I can relate.
Traded one vice for another.
At least they can't take your kids away
for tobacco.
First Christmas clean and sober,
and it won't be the last.
Knock on wood. Just wanna
keep looking forward, you know?
That's kind of why I'm here, Arlene,
to keep you looking forward.
To keep you out of jail, actually.
- Why would I be going to jail?
- As an accessory to murder.
He was a counsellor at a halfway house
where you resided 10 years ago.
Someone spiked his coffee
with rat poison.
- I don't have any idea.
- I'm not after you.
I'm after Hannah McKay.
She was your roommate at the time.
It was her idea,
but you had part in it.
You either helped or you kept quiet.
- What do you want'?
- I wanna know what happened.
In return, I'll promise immunity
from prosecution...
...keep you out of jail, make sure
your kids have their mother...
...to put presents under the tree.
I'd like some time
to think about this.
Okay, do that.
And play with your kids. Because
depending on what you decide...
...you might not get to do that
for a really long time.
Quiet now.
So turn this way now.
Do you remember the first and last time
Dad took us to see Santa?
You yanked his beard
and I asked for a gun.
Where the fuck are you, the North
Pole? You haven't said anything.
What is it?
You sure you wanna know?
Oh, Jesus.
Tell me.
LaGuerta is still looking
into the Bay Harbour Butcher.
Shit.
I talked to Matthews.
She's pulled him into the investigation.
- What?
- It gets worse.
They think it's me.
You weren't gonna fucking tell me?
Do they have anything?
I don't know.
I need to put them off this
once and for all.
How?
Give them proof
that Doakes was the Butcher.
It will mean planting evidence.
You can't do that,
not with those two on your case.
I'll just have to be very careful.
Now, were you a good boy?
So, what do you want for Christmas?
- Fuck it. It's too risky for you. I'll do it.
- Deb, no.
I'm not gonna let Harrison grow up
without a father.
I just want this to be the end
once and for all.
Hey, guys.
Hey.
- Ready? Say "cheese," everyone.
- Cheese.
I'm sorry, I don't think Dexter Morgan
has anything to do...
- ...with the Bay Harbour Butcher.
- You're letting your feelings...
...completely cloud your judgment.
You're letting whatever you had with
Doakes make you blind to his guilt.
I've heard of people
fucking their brains out, but God.
- Well, that's low even for you, Tom.
- Look, let's just follow up on this boat.
Look, if James had owned a boat,
I would have known.
Well, call it a wild guess.
But if he was using it to dump victims
into the ocean...
...he would have tried
to keep its existence a secret.
I swear, I never told anyone
I saw you poison that man.
I don't get how that stanky detective
could know about it.
Must have been my dad.
Why would he do that?
He needed money and I wouldn't give it
to him. You know my dad.
Yeah, unfortunately.
I can't go to jail, Hannah.
Lose my kids again, I couldn't take it.
I'm not gonna let that happen.
Hey, look at me. When that counsellor
was putting his hands on us...
...and I shut him down for good,
you backed me up.
Always stuck together.
That's not gonna change now, is it?
But that detective's
gonna come back.
She's not gonna let up.
I'm gonna figure something out.
You just have to stay strong, okay?
Not this one.
This one looks like Doakes.
Did you have to get the biggest tree?
Well, anything smaller than this
looks like a Charlie Brown tree.
By the way, you still doing Christmas
day with Debra and Harrison?
Yeah. You can join us.
Not sure if Debra and me
in the same room...
...would be very Christmassy.
Okay.
Maybe we could start a new tradition.
Christmas Eve...
...this year and next year,
the year after that.
I like that,
except there is one problem.
- What?
- I haven't got you a Christmas present.
I don't really need anything.
Suit yourself.
Guess I'm just gonna have to go out
and buy you a pair of socks.
Hold up! Hey! Hey!
That's not the walk of a dying man.
I guess freedom
was the tonic he needed.
But I'll soon change that.
- Jenna.
- Hey, Quinn.
I'm looking for Nadia.
Know where she is?
Hey, pal, find your own.
Sorry, does your wife know
you're here?
No, so shut the fuck up.
Nadia's in Vegas.
- What are you talking about?
- She moved there to work.
Got a job in one of the casinos.
- When?
- Couple days ago.
She left you a note. It's in my locker.
- I probably shouldn't have read it.
- What did it say?
She's sorry,
but she needed a new start.
Staying here was too hard for her.
She was really broken up.
That all?
Oh, that you mean a lot to her and
she'll never forget what you did for her.
I'll be done in a few minutes
and I can go get it.
Thanks.
Last Christmas,
I was down in the Keys.
This Christmas, your garage.
- No one's forcing you to be here, Tom.
- Oh, I'm too afraid to leave you alone.
You might decide I'm the
Bay Harbour Butcher and haul me in.
- What is it?
- Come here. Take a look.
It's a tackle box.
These are deep-sea fishing lures.
Meaning?
Meaning they're the kind you need
a boat to use.
Jeez, what a mess.
Well, it's been empty for years.
Doakes probably scrapped his boat
once we were closing in on him.
We don't know Doakes used this place.
You're jumping to conclusions.
This address came
from the tackle box...
...which came from the cabin
where Doakes died.
This isn't jumping to a conclusion.
This conclusion's hanging
from your ass.
- That private forensics team of yours?
- Yeah, what about them?
Get them out here.
I think we just struck oil.
The blood's too degraded to analyse,
but we found one print on the hilt.
It's a match for James Doakes.
You're certain?
No question, captain.
Well, that sews it up.
Tom.
This evidence
could have been planted.
Dexter is a forensics expert...
- ...and he has the skills--
- Maria, it's over.
The fat lady isn't singing,
her song is done.
She's getting humped
in her dressing room.
Jesus Christ, Tom.
What is wrong with you?
Maria, why can't you let this go?
I guess because I feel I owe it to James
to clear his name.
Why?
Because you two were a couple?
Because he was innocent.
You're not an investigator, Maria.
Your talent's in playing the game,
and you play a great one.
Hell, you beat me.
But either way...
...I'm done here.
Now, I expect you to live up
to your end of the bargain.
Forty-year pay scale on my pension.
I remember, Tom.
Don't worry,
you'll get what's coming to you.
I expect to.
Feliz Navidad, Mafia.
What the hell are you doing here?
Don't tell me we're neighbours.
I'm not here to fight with you
or trade insults.
That's a good thing,
you probably wouldn't last one round.
I came here to talk to you
about Dexter.
Dexter?
If you care about him,
listen to what I have to say.
Just hear me out, that's all I ask.
I'm all ears.
Dexter is happy..-
...and I know him well enough
to understand...
...that this is a pretty big deal.
He's been through a lot of trouble
and a lot of pain.
- I can't deny that.
- I think for the first time...
...in really a long time, he's actually
looking forward to the future.
He talks about it.
About me and him together.
And I think that Dexter
could be a whole lot happier...
...if he knew that you and I
could find some common ground.
- For Dexter's sake.
- Yeah.
He really does seem
to like having you around.
I love him.
- And I know that you do too.
- Yeah, you bet I do.
Can't we work out our issues?
I think we can.
It's because I love Dexter...
...that I'm willing to do whatever
it takes to protect him from you.
I'm not gonna give up until your
murdering ass is behind bars for good.
That's how we're gonna work out
our issues.
But, hey...
...thanks for stopping by.
Okay.
Son of a bitch.
You got a dead one.
Yeah.
Well, it's gonna have to stay dead.
There's only so much a man can do.
- What brings you around?
- Merry Christmas.
- I noticed you were on empty.
- Thanks.
I was thinking
about the last conversation we had.
I owe you an apology.
I should have come forward
with my suspicion about Doakes.
- More people would be alive.
- If anyone should apologise, it's me.
I was stupid.
I should never have entertained Maria's
theory about you being the Butcher.
- You think she'll ever accept the truth?
- She already has.
- We found Doakes' boathouse.
- Really?
What's even more amazing
is what we found hidden inside it.
I won't go into details, except to say
it leaves no doubt as to Doakes' guilt.
Believe me, you won't have to worry
about LaGuerta anymore.
Well, I gotta say, that's about the best
Christmas present I could've imagined.
You and me both.
Have a good Christmas with your boy.
We Will.
Christmas just got a lot less merry
for Hector Estrada.
My late lamented Dark Passenger
would be very pleased.
If I can break this last strand
from my past...
...do I get the future I want?
- Yeah.
- I went to see Matthews again.
They're calling off the investigation.
You sure?
Yeah. They bought it. Everything.
Well, let's hope they stay bought.
Thanks, Deb.
- You're Hector Estrada?
- I know you?
You do now. Steve Gaskill.
Come on, man. You're a legend.
You're gonna be a stain if you
don't crawl to where you came from.
I know I'm way out of line.
I gotta tell you about my situation.
I have this contact in Honduras,
an old Army buddy.
He sends me a crate of sativa
every other month.
I've been trying to lay it off. You know,
college campuses and whatnot.
But it keeps piling up.
It's too much for me to move.
- How much are we talking about?
- Enough to make you shit your pants.
I've been trying to find a way
into the Hispanic market.
- Here you are. It's Kismet.
- Kiss who?
It's good luck for both of us.
I can show you the stuff.
If you're interested,
maybe we can work something out.
Let me hear you say
you're not a cop.
I'm not a cop, man.
Jeez, we know a lot of the same people.
Tuerto, Pepe Chap.
- I've sold plenty of shit to them.
- Fuck.
Long time since I've dealt
with those guys.
- Where and when?
- Thirty-five Quayside Road. Tonight.
Ten o'clock. Unless you got something
else to do on Christmas Eve.
I'll see you then.
- Yep.
- Dex, it's Angel.
Debra's at St. Joseph's.
She's been in a car accident.
I'll meet you at the hospital.
Did you fill out all the questions?
- Dex.
- How is she?
She's fine.
Her wrist is broken, lots of bruising,
but she'll be out by tomorrow.
What happened?
Apparently, she blacked out
or something behind the wheel.
Does Debra have a prescription
for anti-anxiety medication?
Not that there's a problem.
Most people do.
Yeah, she does. Why?
Doctor said there was a lot of that
in her system.
Almost three times the normal dose.
Maybe she lost track
on how much she took.
You know, it happens.
Well, why is she here in Hialeah?
Where was she going?
Debra drove here for an interview.
A second interview with a woman,
Arlene Schram.
Now, look, Dex, maybe I should've
told you this before now...
...but Deb got a tip...
...that this woman, Arlene Schram,
was a possible witness to a murder.
A murder committed
by Hannah McKay.
You should've told me.
Debra has a bug up her ass
with this girl.
Maybe that's why she took
all those anti-anxiety pills.
Because she's convinced
that her brother is dating a killer.
I don't know what happened.
I was tired. I was driving.
I kept getting sleepier.
And, I don't know, I must have
closed my eyes for a second.
- But the next thing I knew, I was--
- Hanging upside down in a ditch.
Hanging by my seat belt.
This is the most fucked-est
Christmas ever.
And you were gonna spend it
with Arlene Schram.
Hannah told you?
Hannah knew?
She was at my house yesterday...
...asking me to back off.
Arlene must've called
after I left her house.
Hannah was at your house
yesterday?
Yes.
And now I'm here.
- Fucking hell, Dexter. It's like--
- She didn't poison you.
Well, I sure as shit didn't swallow
a handful of pills.
The doctor said that it's possible
the drugs built up in your system.
I took one.
One. Last night.
That drug has a short half-life.
Gotta hand it to her.
That's a really good plan.
Making it look I accidentally took
too much of a prescription that I have?
It's not a hard drug to get.
- How would she know you were on it?
- You must have mentioned it.
I never did. No.
That's the thing about people
that poison people.
They're really fucking sneaky.
So she what, poisoned you
while she was at your house last night?
I didn't let her inside my house
last night.
- Deb--
- I went for a run.
Maybe she broke in after I left
or something.
She broke into your house
and did what?
- I don't know how she did it.
- Because she didn't.
Fuck, this is what happened
to Sal Price.
He got close to knowing the truth
about Hannah, she killed him.
There's no proof
she killed Sal Price...
...and no proof
that she poisoned you.
Well, maybe we need
to find the proof.
There's another explanation
for what happened.
You took more of those pills
than you think you did.
You've been under a lot of stress,
Deb.
No shit, Sherlock.
So you took one and you lost track.
You took another.
And another.
It's possible. It happens.
You have to admit that, right?
Deb's more right than she knows
about what happened to Sal Price.
But Hannah wouldn't do that to Debra.
Would she?
I make my living at crime scenes,
proving what happened.
But now can I prove
what didn't happen?
Prove that Hannah
didn't poison Debra?
Is this proof that Hannah was here?
Did she break in?
Or did she simply walk through
an open door?
Or did this fall off me?
Did I track this in just now?
The drug works quickly. Deb would've
passed out minutes after ingesting it.
Sorry for your loss.
- No, my sister's doing fine.
- Yeah.
Can't say the same thing
for this poor baby.
You'll have to go in
through the passenger side.
I'll see what the lab has to say
about what's in this bottle.
Hannah didn't poison Debra.
All I want for Christmas
is for that to be true.
Merry Christmas Eve.
We're having a Nochebuena
at the restaurant later.
Auri will be there.
You should come by.
Thank you, but I'm not up for it.
Holidays, family, cheer.
They're keeping Debra overnight
at the hospital. You should know that.
I know.
You wanna tell me
the real reason you're here?
I've been thinking about
what's next for me.
Yeah?
I'm enjoying the restaurant,
even with all the headaches.
It's real.
Straightforward.
You open up, you feed people...
...you clean up, you close up,
then you go home.
That's it. That's your day.
You don't carry it with you.
- Not like this job?
- No.
And up until, I don't know...
...Mike's death maybe...
...it never got to me.
It's time, isn't it?
You ever think about what's next?
Sometimes.
I've been looking back a little too.
You know, wondering
about some choices I've made...
...wishing I'd made different ones.
Are you talking about me?
Are you talking about you, about us?
Are you wishing
that it would've worked out?
No.
Okay, just checking.
So when are you retiring?
Thought about putting papers in
on the first.
Happy New Year.
Let's hope.
Dexter, hey.
I was worried about you.
- Look who's here.
- Daddy's home.
Come here, bud. Oh, yeah.
- Thanks for staying over tonight.
- My pleasure.
Ever since I've gone vegetarian,
watching my brother...
...roast a whole pig grosses me out.
Besides, you guys are family too.
Yeah, and so are you.
How's Debra?
Yeah, how's she doing?
She's fine.
She should be out tomorrow.
Oh, I'm glad to hear that.
Well, I hope you're hungry, Dexter.
Look at her. So beautiful.
But can you ever fully trust
a poisoner?
Okay, Dexter?
Dexter.
Earth to Dexter.
I think your food coma's hitting
way early.
- You're right.
- What do you want'?
A little bit of everything.
Christmas is a time of expectation.
If you're good, a red-suited fat man...
...will break into your house
and leave presents.
But Santa Claus doesn't exist.
The most wonderful time of the year
celebrates a lie.
Is the future I imagine with Hannah
nothing more than a vision...
...dancing in my head?
It's funny how we started off
in Santa's Holiday Adventure...
...and here we are,
Christmas Eve together.
A place I never thought I'd be
with anyone again...
...much less you.
Thanks.
I'm not saying this quite right.
All the men that I've been with...
...there was a lot of running away.
But when I'm with you...
...I don't wanna go anywhere.
Stay with me tonight.
No, I can't. I have somewhere to be.
Debra?
Estrada?
Good for you.
He's somebody you've wanted
for a long time.
Someone I thought I'd never get.
I imagine that will be
deeply satisfying.
When Deb had her accident...
...she was heading
to Arlene Schram's house.
She was hoping Arlene
would give her a statement...
...that would let her arrest you.
But Deb never made it there.
She blacked out behind the wheel.
- Does that sound familiar?
- Familiar?
Sal Price.
It's what you hoped would happen
to him before you poisoned him.
Are you...?
Do you think that I had something to do
with Debra's accident?
Did you?
Oh, I can't believe you would
even think something like that.
Say something.
You will do whatever it takes
to protect yourself.
That does not include
trying to poison your sister.
You yourself told me Arlene saw you
poison that counsellor's coffee.
And I can't tell you how many times
I saw Arlene shoot up.
I was nervous about what she could do,
but then I went to see her...
...and she's a mess...
...that any law student could discredit.
She's not a threat to me.
But Deb is.
Do you think I would be that stupid...
...to try and poison
the lieutenant of Homicide?
And to think
that you wouldn't figure it out?
Wouldn't exactly bring us
closer together, would it?
You know I love you, right?
Yes.
Do you love me?
I don't know if I believe you.
You were at her house last night.
I thought if she knew how much I cared
then she would back down a little.
But she never will.
What happens next week
when Deb has a heart attack?
Do you hear yourself?
If anything happens, I'll wonder
if you had something to do with it.
Well, that's your problem,
your lack of trust.
Your inability to trust.
God, it's like...
It's like you have something
deep inside of you...
...that you think is undeserving
of love.
- Don't turn this back on me.
- You're accusing me.
I ju-- I know what you're capable of.
Okay, I'm not sure
quite how to say this...
...but I've never made a mistake.
If I had poisoned Debra,
then she would be dead.
If you know me
the way that you say that you do...
...then you know that that's true.
Maybe it all was just an accident.
It must have been really scary
to see her in the hospital like that.
It was.
It's understandable
you would try to make sense...
...of a situation
that doesn't make sense...
...but you're doing that
at the expense of this relationship.
I'm not trying to. I...
I don't wanna lose you.
I'm sure about you.
I'm 100-percent sure...
...but you need to be able
to say the same thing about me.
I know.
We could have it all.
I think you need to figure out
what it is that you want...
...and what type of future
you wanna have.
It's right in here.
What the fuck is this, huh?
Where's the stuff?
Fuck.
Estrada.
Estrada, it's time.
The Department of Corrections
kept that for you.
That was very thoughtful.
You've changed a lot
in the past 40 years.
So have I.
Three men murdered my mother.
Juan Pablo Aliso,
shot in another deal.
Santos Jimenez.
You remember him.
He testified against you.
I cut him into six roughly-equal pieces
with a chain saw.
Just like he did my mother.
Like I'm gonna do to you.
Holy fuck, you're Dickie Moser.
Dexter Moser.
I am Dexter Moser.
And I'm gonna kill you.
Is that what all this is about?
I was 3 years old
when you left me in that container.
Who am I gonna be
when you're dead?
Still some fucking freak, probably.
We'll see.
You're working with her, aren't you?
What?
That fucking cop bitch,
the one who got me out.
Oh, yeah, they said
that there was a big push...
...for my release
from the captain of Miami Metro.
LaGuerta?
She fucking set me up.
You're not the one who was set up.
Officer.
We followed him here,
but we lost him.
Till we heard the gunshot.
That's when we called you.
- All right. Anything else since?
- No.
Show me where.
What is going on in this place?
Keep looking for Estrada and anyone
else with him. Estrada's not alone.
Don't make a fucking sound.
Around the other side.
It wasn't the universe giving me a gift.
It was LaGuerta.
I can make sure one member
of the Morgan family...
...has a good Christmas.
Yes.
It's Sergio. You told me to call you
when I ran that water you brought in.
What'd you find?
That water's like
40 percent alprazolam.
That's an anti-anxiety drug.
Someone must have wanted
to knock themselves out.
But this time of year,
who can blame them?
- Thanks.
- You got it.
It was no accident.
Hannah dissolved the pills
into Deb's water...
...so that she'd pass out
behind the wheel.
A problem in Hannah's life solved.
Hannah poisoned Debra.
It's not the future I had wanted
with Hannah...
...but maybe it's what I deserve.
You barely said two words
on the ride home.
I have something for you.
A present?
A new car, I hope.
I guess it's a present.
It's Sal Price's pen.
If you test it, you'll find traces
of aconite on the end...
...and Hannah's prints.
So that's how she did it.
I found it the next morning.
I kept it out of evidence.
I can't believe
you're gonna turn her in.
As long as she's free,
you're not safe.
Dex, I know how hard this must be
for you.
You're here.
Does that mean
that you know what you want?
Yes.
- Hannah...
- You have to kiss me or it's bad luck.
What's the matter?
I'm sorry.
Sorry?
Hannah McKay, you're under arrest
for the murder of Sal Price.
You should have killed me.
I should know better
than to count on the future.
All you can ever believe in is now...
...this moment.
Because in a blink...
...everything can change.