Previously on Dexter...
Who is Dexter Morgan?
He's just a jerk who works
for Miami Metro Homicide.
Now can I please go?
Yes.
So you're not interested in alcohol
or looking at naked women.
You may be in the wrong place.
I'm taking out the trash that would
otherwise be left to putrefy.
There is a legal system for that.
If it worked as well as you think
it does, I wouldn't be so busy.
Just gonna get a swab
from your cheek.
You do this for a living?
Well, I hate it, but I get it,
what you do.
But what I don't understand
are the blood slides.
They're trophies.
They're like Speltzer's earrings.
I'm nothing like Speltzer.
My bosses at the club,
they ordered me to get close to you.
These men are dangerous.
I can't go back to them with nothing.
I'm not gonna let anything happen
to you.
- He's gone.
- Motherfucker. He has a girl in here.
We have to find her.
She's dead.
Just when it seems like Deb and I
are making progress...
...we take a left turn.
I showed her a monster,
Ray Speltzer...
...a killer who chased his victim
through a maze.
I could have prevented that murder,
and Deb accepts that.
But she hasn't accepted me...
...what I am.
And I'm not sure she ever will.
I'm getting nothing.
- You?
- No.
That maze man, he's good.
He knows what he's doing.
My hat's off to any killer good enough
not to leave any DNA...
...at a murder scene.
Plenty of his DNA
in this place though.
Well, if this cemetery was his office,
it's like this place was his break room.
Something was here.
Something special.
Like a trophy maybe?
From one of his victims.
Killers hate
to leave their trophies behind.
That means Speltzer stopped
by here after he killed that girl.
But there's none of her DNA here.
No blood, no fibres, no hair.
No reception.
Speltzer is loose in the world...
...and Deb will do everything
in her power to find him.
But will she and I be able
to find our way back to each other?
Deb.
Will you?
Will you be mine?
- Morning.
- Coffee. Now.
- Rita.
- Another left turn.
- Trinity killed her.
- Yes.
- Why?
She didn't fit the pattern at all.
Because I was coming after him.
So while we were hunting Trinity,
you were too.
I figured out who he was
before you did.
And you didn't help us get him?
He knew who I was, where I lived,
that I had a family.
- I was trying to protect them.
- You wanted to fucking kill him.
And I did.
When?
- He's dead. That's what matters.
- When?
I took care of him.
- Did you love her?
- Why would you ask that?
Because I have no idea what's
the truth and what's a lie with you.
- I loved her.
- If you were concerned about family...
...then why were you going
after Trinity?
Is that what a loving husband does?
- Are you even capable of love?
- I love you.
How?
How can you love me
and also love to--?
It's how I've lived my whole life.
Before you walked into that church...
...did you ever question the way
I felt about you?
- Why is it any different now?
- Why?
Jesus, Dexter.
Morgan.
Okay.
That was Batista.
They found Speltzer.
A security guard spotted him
at the scrap yard.
And he had the good sense
not to be a hero.
- It took four officers to take Speltzer.
- He put up a fight.
Came close to shooting. If Speltzer
had a weapon, they would've.
- Speltzer is a weapon.
- He was mine.
He hasn't asked for a lawyer.
This is your one shot.
A confession is our only shot.
He was wearing a mask so I couldn't
make an ID that would stick.
Can't believe DNA
wasn't at the scene.
Masuka and I went over it twice.
Yeah, Dexter and I, we checked
Speltzer's mausoleum man cave...
...for evidence of his victim there,
but no luck.
Dexter and I can't make
the evidence appear.
If you don't get a confession,
you won't get Speltzer.
Are you two ready?
Fuck, yes.
- That's Dexter Morgan.
- His face. It looks familiar.
I put everything Jurg dug up
on Morgan in there.
He's not a cop. He's a lab rat.
- Blood splatter.
- It's spatter.
Blood spatter.
Whatever. He's from Miami.
Normal guy.
Except his wife was murdered
by a serial killer a few years back.
The man we killed on the boat?
Louis Greene.
He was an intern for Miami Metro.
The boat's owner, this Dexter Morgan.
He works for Miami Metro too.
Viktor's death.
Is it payback
for killing that detective?
Viktor fucked us real good here.
Of all the people he could've shot,
it had to be a fucking cop.
- So it's Viktor's fault he's dead?
- Yeah. He was a loose cannon.
Never listened. At least not to me.
Everything was going great
until he showed up in Miami.
Viktor was a good man.
He was loyal. He was committed.
And he was here
to do what you couldn't.
Keep the Colombians
from taking over our traffic!
- Fuck.
- Gentlemen. Let's go. Get up.
And here we go again.
- Why?
- Come over here, please.
Good afternoon, everyone.
I'm Detective Quinn.
I'll be your pain in the ass
for the day.
Can we get that music turned off?
Ladies to the left,
customers to the right.
Keep it behind the bar.
Ma'am, I need you to go ahead
and stand over there.
- Officer.
- It's detective.
Detective Quinn.
Do not tell me you are fucking her.
No. What makes you think that?
You're not the only one
who's a detective.
You really think a stripper's
a good idea?
No, it's a horrible idea.
Seriously,
how long is this gonna go on?
I'm thinking every day until
we lock up Mike Anderson's shooter.
Or you could say a number.
It'll be just like old times.
You leave your car unlocked...
...you'll find some cash,
maybe some blow.
All this goes away.
I don't know what you're talking about.
Get the fuck out of my face.
None of this makes any sense.
Viktor's dead. They got him.
Not everyone at Miami Metro
knows this.
Otherwise, they wouldn't be here.
Maybe this Morgan and Greene
were working alone.
Why the fuck would these two
assholes cover up Viktor's murder?
I believe Dexter Morgan knows why.
Well, say the word. I'll take him out.
- No. I wanna talk to him.
- Talk?
Hey, what are we supposed to do
in the meantime?
We got two boats waiting
to drop off our supply...
...even though we can't move
what we already have.
We are bleeding money.
The bartender, Alex.
One of ours, isn't he?
Yeah.
So let's give them what they want.
For my money, four on one
is not really a fair fight.
I did a little boxing myself
back in the day.
I didn't take on four cops,
but, you know, I held my own.
You don't wanna chitchat. I get that.
Here's the thing though.
My lieutenant is gonna come
in here...
...and say that she saw you
at the maze where that waitress died.
- Don't know what you're talking about.
- Right, guy like you was at the gym.
But she's a woman.
They get shit wrong all the time.
And this one, man, she's my boss.
If you can believe that.
I have to fucking answer
to her skinny ass every day.
And she's always squawking at me,
you know?
Her beak is,
"Squawk, squawk, squawk."
To tell you the truth, I envy you.
I've been wanting
to pop my lieutenant...
...in that beak of hers for years.
She's dying to get a shot at you.
Should we let her? Could be fun.
Right?
- Nice job in there.
- He's all ready for you.
Deb.
Good luck.
He was mine,
but Deb needs this more than me.
And she needs to get him her way.
Remember me?
I saw you just the other night.
That is some maze that you built.
What is it for, Ray?
Are you sure
you don't remember me?
Maybe I'm not pretty enough.
Your morn sure was pretty.
She died a few years ago, right?
Cast a long shadow, I bet.
Hard for any girl to measure up
to those looks...
...but you keep trying, don't you?
What do you think about the girls
that go home with you?
That they're stupid? Easy?
That they're whores?
They'd have to be, right?
To go home with you,
take their clothes off for you.
Girls like that are vulgar.
But girls like that
sure do look like your mom.
So I have to wonder.
Your morn was so pretty.
She probably had a lot of admirers,
right?
Men that would go home with her
and watch her take her clothes off?
And then take her
any way that they wanted her?
Shut up.
There are many ways
to break a body down.
You could hear it, couldn't you?
You could hear her
through those thin walls...
...that the two of you shared.
You could hear how much she loved
getting fucked by all those men.
You could hear her kissing them.
All the things that she might do
with her mouth...
...that same mouth
that she would kiss you with.
But be honest, Ray.
You kind of liked it, didn't you?
Weren't you kind of wishing
that it was you inside her?
I should've killed you like
I killed that other bitch!
Go to hell.
We got him.
- Way to go, lieutenant.
- Good job.
Congratulations.
Hey, Deb.
Jamie said she was good to watch
Harrison till late tonight...
...if you wanna grab a drink
or something.
I thought you'd be in the mood
to celebrate.
I'm really glad we got Speltzer,
but celebrate? No.
Melanie Garrett is still dead.
But you got Speltzer.
He'll never hurt anyone again.
- Well, outside of prison.
- Dexter.
I've been thinking a lot about Rita.
About how she died.
She died because of you.
Because you were selfish.
You have a son.
Harrison is three years old.
- Someone needs to protect him.
- I do.
Someone needs to protect him
from you.
He could go live with Astor and Cody.
- With their grandparents in Orlando.
- I am a good father.
I am the right person.
The only person
who can and should raise my son.
Who, like me, lost his mother.
It is not fair of you
to expose a child to your life...
...choices.
- You have to decide. Your desires or--
- No, I don't.
You said it yourself, Dexter, that you
can't stop, that you don't wanna stop.
And if you keep doing this,
you're like a fucking magnet.
Bad shit is gonna find you.
And if that happens, I'll handle it.
What if you had been three minutes
later to Speltzer's fucking maze?
- But I wasn't.
- You were too late for Rita.
I should've killed Trinity
the first time I saw him.
- That's the mistake I made.
- That's the mistake?
Yes! And I will never, from this
moment on-- Do you hear me?
I will never ever make
that mistake again.
It is not in your control.
Everything is in my control.
I am not giving up my son.
Mr. Sirko, George.
I wasn't expecting visitors.
That's all right.
We don't stand on ceremony here.
Have a seat, Alex.
You have a beautiful family.
Thank you.
That is why I came here.
They are still in Kursk.
Your son and daughter,
what are their names?
My son's Zakhary
and my girl, her name's Yulia.
- They're twins, yes? How old?
- Five.
- Their birthday's in April.
- Wow, five.
That's the best age.
Learning to read, walking,
seeing the world...
...and yet, they still want to be held.
You're probably wondering
why I stopped by. Well, you see...
Tell me, how much money do you
send back to Kursk each month?
- From your job at The Fox Hole?
- Seven-hundred-fifty dollar.
I take out only my rent,
my food, some money for my car.
A sacrifice for you, I'm sure.
But still, it's not very much.
What if your family
could have a lot of money?
Security.
College for Zakhary and Yulia?
- You'd want that for them.
- I would give anything for them.
That pleases me.
Because that is why
I came by here today.
- To ask you a favour, Alex.
- Yes, of course. Anything.
I have a problem.
One of my men killed a police officer...
...and I have to give the police
a suspect so they'll stop harassing us.
- And that suspect is you.
- But I didn't kill anyone.
- Sure, you did.
- I want you to write a note.
Pen, paper?
This is what I want you to write.
Kaja...
...I cannot live with what I have done.
I'm very sorry.
I will take care of your family now.
Zakhary and Yulia
will want for nothing.
That's for you. It's the gun
that killed the police officer.
What do I do with it?
Bang.
Look at your children's faces.
They're looking at you.
Wanting you to give them the best life
this world has to offer.
- You will do this for them.
- And if I don't?
We'll kill you anyway.
And throw your wife
and fucking kids in the river.
No need for threats.
We're all friends here.
But I think you understand
the situation.
You won't feel a thing.
It'll be quick.
Like turning off a light.
For my family?
Hannah McKay.
She spent six years in juvie...
...after pleading guilty to being
Wayne Randall's accomplice.
She always claimed she was just
another one of his victims.
Wayne called her the Robin
to his Batman...
...but with better legs.
Dexter Morgan.
You look a little lost.
Well, I haven't been inside a police
station in 15 years.
Still smells the same,
like fast food and sweat.
Hospitality isn't exactly
our main concern.
I heard the sheriff's department found
the body of one of Wayne's victims.
Yeah, they went back one last time
after Wayne died.
And expanded the perimeter.
Is that what you're doing here?
To help us find the other bodies
Wayne buried?
My lawyer said it was for the best.
There's a rumour going around
that you were the last person...
...to talk to Wayne before he...
...died.
His last words were about you.
He said something about every day
being like an unwrapped present.
Yeah.
I remember when he got that fortune
from a cookie.
You two didn't stay in contact?
Too painful.
Where were you
and Wayne going anyway?
Or was there a plan?
Not much of one at first.
We were just trying to get out
of Clopton, Alabama...
...which isn't even a town.
It's an intersection and a cemetery.
But somewhere around Sarasota,
a plan did begin to form.
Argentina.
We were gonna go find a farm
in Argentina and settle down.
- What?
- We were living on farms in Alabama...
...like somehow it would all be
so different in South America.
Do you miss him?
I miss the way I felt with him
on the road.
That life was just beginning,
and that anything...
Anything was possible.
You know the feeling?
No.
It's my lawyer.
I'm sure he's wondering
where I got lost to.
We have a big problem.
Get down.
Stay down there.
- What's the problem?
- Watch the Miranda.
Put him on the fucking car.
You know how this goes.
If you want an attorney...
...we'll get one for you,
even if you can't afford one.
Do you understand your rights?
Do you understand?
Did you guys see that?
Looks like a yes to me.
Fucking cocksucker.
Never got confirmation
that Speltzer understood his rights.
- No.
- But Speltzer fucking nodded.
He didn't say yes.
And at Speltzer's arraignment,
his PD was able to make the case...
- Don't.
- ...that because Speltzer...
...was knocked unconscious,
it is possible...
...that he did not understand
his rights.
That it wasn't a nod.
That it was a temporary blackout.
And the judge fucking bought that?
The judge threw his confession
out of court.
- He walked.
- When?
- Two hours ago.
- Motherfucker.
And apparently, Speltzer's planning
to file a lawsuit against us.
Use of excessive force?
- I don't believe this.
- So all that's left to do is...
- Is what?
- Yeah, we--
- We'll wait till he kills someone else?
- There's nothing else we can do.
- But there is something I can do.
- Fuck that. Fuck all of this.
The bartender from The Fox Hole
blew his brains out last night.
Why don't they wear uniforms?
There's no respect.
You would never know
they were police.
Unless you knew
who you were looking for.
We got a single gunshot wound
to the right temple...
...what appears to be GSR
on the right hand.
It was through and through. Based on
the height of the bullet in the wall...
...Alex was sitting at the table.
He put his gun to his head.
- We got a White Russian on ice.
- Very funny.
I'll have you know
I have a major following on Twitter.
This gun is a 9-mil. Same type
of weapon used on Mike Anderson.
I'll go to Ballistics
and run this through.
And confirm this turd is our shooter.
But I know that Viktor
killed Mike Anderson.
Why would Alex take the fall for him?
Unless there's someone at the club
who wants the investigation to end...
...as much as Miami Metro does.
Quinn, read that note again.
"Kaja, I cannot live with
what I have done. I am very sorry."
- Sorry to Kaja?
- Yeah.
It makes sense. It's obvious this
Alex Dubrozny had feelings for her.
And she was in love with Tony.
Which probably
didn't sit very well with him.
So he kills her, kills Tony...
...and Mike was just in the wrong
place at the wrong time.
I mean, this guy still has pictures
up of his kids, his wife.
Yeah, he probably feels horrible
having to look at her face all day.
That's just it. He doesn't have to. Take
the pictures down. Put them away.
Leaving the pictures up
tells me he cares for them.
He's a guy. Once something's up,
why bother taking it down?
- I don't know.
- What don't you know?
- I don't know if it all adds up.
- Look. We'll talk to the neighbours.
See if they saw anyone coming in
or out of Alex's apartment...
- ...if it'll make you happy.
- It's not about happy.
Angel.
Angel, this is our fucking guy.
Everyone yearns for clarity,
for closure.
But is that ever really possible?
- Jamie?
- Harrison's outgrown half these toys.
I know we had to go through them.
Didn't know it was gonna be now.
I'm almost done.
I wanted to do it while he's asleep.
Anything we're unsure about,
we can put in the keep-for-now pile.
- What's the other pile?
- Trash.
- You put Lamby in the trash?
- Lamby smells like pee.
And Harrison hasn't slept
with Lamby in more than a year.
Used to be he couldn't go to sleep
without it.
I remember. Keep?
No.
Yeah, a lot of kids sleep with security
blankets when they're little...
...but once they start socializing...
...you know,
learning how to be part of a group...
...they don't need it.
And Harrison, because he's a genius,
hit this milestone early.
He was so small.
Lamby was a gift from Rita's mother
when he was born.
Maybe we should keep it for Harrison.
For Harrison, of course.
Some toys are more difficult
than others to part with.
Speltzer is already back at work,
digging graves.
He should start by digging his own.
Miami Metro impounded
Speltzer's little pied-é-RV...
...when he was arrested...
...but they had to give it back
once he was set free.
Ray's been juicing.
At least he doesn't mind needles.
I can hide up here,
wait for Speltzer to come home.
I'll use the RV as my kill room...
...and transportation
to get rid of Ray's body.
And his trophies.
I'm still alive, but I don't think
I'm going to like the reason why.
Speltzer couldn't have done
all of this in a day.
Is this place his masterpiece?
I don't run. I make people run.
However, I do run if there's a bull
coming after me with an axe.
You should really try taking
a shower once in a while.
Where are you?
Speltzer keeps forcing me
down to the next floor.
So if he wants me to go down,
what happens if I go up?
He knows my face now.
If I want a rematch,
I'm gonna have to be smarter.
To take Speltzer down, I have
to make sure I have nothing to lose.
Harrison's only going to Orlando
for a few weeks, Dexter.
- Yep, I know.
- He's gonna be fine.
All he'll wanna do is follow
Cody around.
Thanks for driving him up.
I actually might spend a few days
there, see what trouble I can get into.
- Knock yourself out.
- Thanks.
I'll take these down to the car.
Astor and Cody
are excited to see you.
I want you to be good for your
grandma and grandpa, okay?
I'm not sending Harrison to Orlando
because Deb asked me to...
...but because Speltzer
is a problem I need to solve.
Once I do, Harrison will come home
where he belongs.
- You mean more to me than--
- Pizza!
That's right. Pizza. Let's go.
I will avenge your death.
Everything I do...
...is for you.
- Deb, you okay?
- Yeah, yeah.
I wanna get back to the station...
...finish up the paperwork
on Mike's shooter.
Be there in a minute.
Motherfucker.
You impotent fuck.
- You got some mouth.
- What are you doing?
- Haven't you done enough?
- Oh, I'm just getting started.
You fucking motherfucking
cocksucker!
- All right--
- You fucking piece of shit!
- Deb, get your shit together.
- You're so easy, just like the others.
Get the fuck out of here.
Come on.
Fuck you up.
I'll you see around.
Batista called.
- I'm sure he did.
- What happened?
I fucking lost my mind.
I saw Speltzer at Melanie's funeral.
- Fucking smiling at the hearse, and--
- What'd you do?
I fucking attacked him!
I wanted to fucking kill him.
Fuck you.
Is that why you came here?
To prove some fucking point
that everybody wants someone dead?
I came here to see how you are.
That's all.
I'm just fucking great.
Is this ever gonna get easier?
Nothing's really all that different, Deb.
The only thing that's changed
is now you know more about me.
What I know about you...
...makes you a completely
different person.
But I'm not.
I'm the same person I've always been.
Your brother, the same person
who will always be there for you.
Maybe the question
is whether you'll be there for me.
I don't know if I can feel
the same way about us.
I do.
And I don't too.
Are we sure this Alex Dubrozny guy
shot Mike Anderson?
- Why are you trying to rattle this?
- It smells like a set-up.
And what does a set-up smell like?
This bartender had no record
back in Kursk.
Suddenly he decides
to murder three people?
Alex had a short fuse, a broken heart
and a loaded gun.
A gun that Masuka confirmed
was the same one used on Mike.
And we got a sweet little suicide
note...
...that helped us solve not just
Mike's murder, but two others.
That's what a set-up smells like.
It's all too neat, too easy.
Alex wasn't even on our radar.
- Why would he off himself now?
- His conscience got to him.
Let's just swing by the club
one last time, ask around.
This is Mike we're talking about here.
Fine. Not tonight.
- What's her name?
- Nadia.
- The stripper?
- She's a dancer.
- Doesn't keep a lot of clothes on.
- You serious about her?
I don't know what I am about her...
...but she was real close to Kaja and
Tony and all this is real hard on her.
I'm so glad
you're there to comfort her.
- Come on.
- I'm just jealous.
At least you got someone
in your life.
She's got a lot of pretty friends.
I'm a twice-divorced detective staring
down the barrel of retirement.
I'm already a cliché.
Don't need to add a stripper
to that list.
Fine. We'll go by tomorrow. Make sure
Alex isn't some patsy for the mob.
Have a good night.
Fight or flight.
That's a part
of everyone's lizard brain.
Speltzer may have a lizard brain
like me...
...but his shortcoming is he doesn't
have much of a human brain.
What the fuck is this?
The end of your run.
Get me out of here!
Yell all you want.
No one's gonna hear you.
Fuck. Fuck!
Fuck! Fuck!
Feels good. Fuck!
Now is when I'd slice your cheek
with my scalpel...
...and get a drop of blood
to remember you by...
...but I can't risk anyone finding
a blood slide ever again.
You're a fucking freak.
Everything's different now.
The memory of killing you
will have to be enough.
I'm gonna kill you.
That would be a twist.
But not one that's gonna
happen tonight.
You were supposed to be a way out
of the tangle I was in with my sister...
...a thread she could follow
to understand me better...
...to accept me even.
But she and I lost each other.
She almost lost herself
going after you.
She wanted to catch you
just as much as I did.
Who knows, maybe our relationship
can rise from your ashes.
No. No.
It's time for everyone to move on.
Goodbye, friends.
You came.
I wasn't sure you would.
Me neither.
What am I doing here?
That smoke.
It's Speltzer.
Did you do this for me?
No.
How do you feel?
Glad.
What does that make me?
Human.