Previously on Dexter...
Who is Dexter Morgan?
He's just a jerk who works
for Miami Metro Homicide.
- That's Dexter Morgan.
- His face...
...it looks familiar.
Only one person who worked
at Miami Metro took blood slides...
...Sergeant Doakes,
the Bay Harbor Butcher.
Same type of weapon
used on Mike Anderson.
Are we sure this Alex Dubrozny guy
shot Mike Anderson?
Because it smells like a setup.
Hannah McKay,
she spent six years in juvie...
...after pleading guilty to being
Randall's accomplice.
She always claimed she was just
another one of his victims.
That what you're doing,
to help us find the other bodies?
My lawyer said it was for the best.
Do you understand your rights?
He didn't say, "Yes." He walked.
- There is nothing we can do.
- Fuck that. Fuck all of this.
But there is something I can do.
That smoke.
It's Speltzer.
How do you feel?
Glad.
What does that make me?
It never ends, does it?
The maintenance.
I don't mind it.
It's the one thing
that never changes.
The waves keep rolling in...
...wearing everything down
in their path a little more every day.
Harrison's coming home.
I wanna have the boat ready.
- So life's back to normal?
- A new normal.
Deb's not poring over
the past anymore.
We're on course, moving forward.
Life can be less complicated now.
You don't believe that.
- Why not? She didn't abandon me.
- She didn't accept you either.
- She doesn't know what to think.
- She's adjusting.
I did everything in my power to protect
her from you, what you really are.
- A monster?
- Your words.
Your thoughts.
You didn't think she could handle it
because you couldn't. Deb is stronger.
For now.
But the long-term exposure...
...it's going to eat away at her,
like salt water on steel.
Blood.
It's not from Viktor.
I never leave a mess behind.
Who's been on my boat?
This is too much blood.
Someone died here.
Someone I didn't kill.
Who are you?
If I'm getting shit-canned
and you know something about it...
...just give me a heads-up, all right?
We're bros.
First of all, we are not
and never will be bros.
Secondly, I've told you a million times,
I don't know anything.
Really? Then why did your voice
just rise?
Look, I took a class
in paralinguistics.
Change in pitch,
dead giveaway for lying.
Get away from my desk.
- Am I getting the axe?
- You are if you don't get out of my way.
I got off the phone and LaGuerta's
processing evidence at a private lab.
What are you talking about?
A charred blood slide containing
the blood of one Travis Marshall.
I asked myself, "Vince, if your
boss is processing evidence...
- ...at another lab--"
- Blood slide? Are you certain?
Increase in vocal volume,
indicating emotional dissonance.
You know something. I'm fucked.
I am sure that LaGuerta is using
an outside lab...
...because she knows
how slammed you are.
- I'll look into this, so just fucking relax.
- Okay. Thanks, LT. You rock.
- Got a second?
- Sure.
Masuka got wind that you're using
an outside lab to run evidence...
...and he thinks he's gonna get fired.
Is there anything I should know?
I needed a second pair of eyes
on something.
It's nothing.
Does this have anything to do
with the Bay Harbor Butcher?
Lundy carried that notebook
everywhere he went.
Get the door.
This has to remain between
you and me.
Of course.
I had a lab analyse a blood slide
that I found at the abandoned church.
A blood slide,
like a Bay Harbor Butcher trophy?
Travis Marshall's blood was on it.
Doakes was the Bay Harbor Butcher
and Doakes is dead.
Well, what if it wasn't Doakes?
What if the Bay Harbor Butcher
is still alive and at work?
What if he killed Travis Marshall?
Except Travis Marshall wasn't cut up
into pieces and put into bags.
But the fact
that the Bay Harbor Butcher kept...
...blood slides was never released
to the public.
It's probably not some copycat.
How do you explain this?
I can't.
I know it sounds impossible but...
...I never believed that Doakes
was a killer.
And from his notes,
Lundy had his doubts too.
Well, you can add me to that list.
Doakes was my partner.
He was a good man.
Is there anything I can do to help?
You have no idea how good it is
to hear you say that.
I've been keeping this all to myself.
Your eyes only.
My eyes only.
Fuck.
Motherfucking suck bag.
You cock-munching,
fucking fuck nugget.
Fuck.
The blood on my boat belongs to...
...Louis Greene?
Louis is dead?
Why was he killed on my boat?
Why would he have even been
on my boat?
Why...
- ...Is my sister looking at me like that?
- Dex.
We are in a storm of fuck.
LaGuerta found a slide
with Travis Marshall's blood on it...
...at the fucking church.
- That's not good.
- How the fuck do you lose a slide?
Deb, you know that night
wasn't my usual scenario.
Are you saying it's my fault...
...LaGuerta thinks
the Bay Harbor Butcher is alive?
No, that's not what I meant but...
...that night at the church
wasn't exactly by the playbook.
I talked LaGuerta into letting me help
with the investigation...
...so I can keep tabs
on what's happening.
You what? No.
I'll deal with this.
I don't want you involved.
Well, it's a little fucking late for that.
She wants to talk to the friends
and family of everyone on this list...
...who's gone missing
since Doakes died.
They all the fit the victim profile
of the Bay Harbor Butcher.
Anyone here that you recognise?
These three are mine.
This is never gonna end, is it?
They were bad people, Deb...
...who would've continued
to do bad things.
This is the only one
with family in Miami: Phillip Barnes.
So when LaGuerta and I
split up the list...
...I'll make sure I get his family.
- No, I don't like you doing this.
- I don't give a fuck...
...what you like, Dexter.
It's beyond that. This is my ass too.
Tell me what I need to know
about Barnes.
He was a wedding photographer.
He would find a guest from out
of town. Young, female, by herself.
He would charm her,
invite her back to his hotel.
She'd never come home.
He took pictures of what he did.
So, what did you do?
He was going out of town
for another job...
...so I nabbed him after a reception.
A reception?
A fucking wedding reception?
Dexter, what if Barnes
got a picture of you?
- Deb, it was a wedding.
- What if someone remembers you?
Everyone was concentrating on the
bride and groom. I slipped in and out.
It's fine.
- What if you're wrong?
- I'm not.
LaGuerta will not tie me to this.
There's no body, no proof.
Stay away from it, okay?
First thing I have to do is find out
why Louis was killed on my boat.
My curtains are open.
With Harrison gone,
Jamie is not around.
Someone has been
in my apartment.
Maybe still is.
Hey, Dex. It's Sam.
Just wanna confirm we're still on
for 1:00 at Schooner or Later...
...at 12th and Bayshore Drive.
See you there.
I've met him before at the bar
at The Fox Hole...
...owned by the Koshka Brotherhood.
The man who killed Mike Anderson,
Viktor Baskov...
...was one of the Koshkas.
Could they have figured out I killed
Viktor and sent a hit man after me?
- Excuse me.
- Yes.
I think I have a phone call for you.
A small coffee, please.
- Hello?
- Why were you in my apartment?
Well, aren't you Mr. Smarty-Pants?
Answer the question.
What were you doing in my place?
I was looking to have a discussion
about a friend who's gone missing.
Viktor. I'm sure you remember him.
I have no idea
who you're talking about.
- I don't care for lies.
- I told you, I don't know who that is.
You're wasting both our time.
Louis Greene,
who I found on your boat...
...the boat that was used
to dump Viktor in the ocean...
- ...gave me your name.
- So you killed Louis.
We had a conversation
that ended rather abruptly, yes.
What else did Louis say?
I believe he may have referred
to you as a douche bag.
- You think you're very clever.
- I do, actually, yes.
Your bosses
at the Koshka Brotherhood...
...they sent you?
You've done your homework.
There are no bosses telling me
what to do.
Viktor was a friend of mine.
This is personal.
So an eye for an eye, huh?
Your friend Viktor kills
an innocent woman and a cop...
...and killing me somehow
settles the score?
Oh, you misunderstand me.
I'm not stopping with you.
I also want any of your police officer
friends involved in this little vendetta.
- Wait.
- Including your lieutenant sister.
I've done my homework too.
It was just me.
She had nothing to do with this.
Hello, handsome.
I work alone.
I killed Viktor, only me.
I'll see you around.
That's the plan.
Why in fuckville are you telling me
to meet you in the parking garage?
Because of him.
- Do you wanna be more specific?
- His name is Isaak Sirko.
He's part of the Koshka Brotherhood.
He's after me.
But don't worry.
I'm gonna take care of it.
- What did you do?
- But you could be in danger too.
That's why you need to know.
That's why we're meeting--
- Dex.
- But I'm gonna handle this.
Why is he after you?
Viktor Baskov.
Viktor Baskov disappeared.
- You killed him.
- He killed Mike Anderson.
What about the guy
that said he killed Mike?
The bartender
that blew his brains out?
Someone put him up to it,
Isaak probably.
So that you would close the case
and move on.
This is un-fucking-real.
Viktor Baskov was on his way back
to Kiev. I had to kill him.
I didn't have any time.
There wasn't--
Time? You didn't have time
to make a phone call...
...so that I could arrest him
or something?
- His flight was leaving.
- His fl--
How do you know he killed Mike?
I found his fingerprint at the scene.
And you didn't tell me?
You kept it from
the Police Department?
Dexter, what happened
to you only taking care of people...
...that slip through the cracks
of the justice system?
You can't rip a case open...
- ...so that it falls into your fucking lap.
- I know.
Obviously you don't know, Dexter,
because this is normal for you.
But trust me, this is not
fucking normal for me, not at all.
How am I supposed to do my job?
Which is the be-all, end-all
of hypocrisy...
...because I am the lieutenant
of Homicide...
...and I have already helped you
cover up two murders.
Three. This makes three.
And the fucking bartender.
Oh, my fucking God. Oh, my God.
How did this become my life?
- Deb, where are you going?
- I'm gonna arrest Isaak.
- Take him to jail.
- On what charge?
- I'll find something!
- No.
We can't--
I can't afford to risk him talking.
Look, I will handle this, but until I do,
we need to take extra precautions.
Isaak is convinced
that there's some police conspiracy.
He thinks we all killed Viktor,
so you're at risk too.
- What?
- But I can keep you safe.
We're gonna go to a hotel.
A place where no one knows
who we are...
...no one asks any questions,
a place where we'll both be safe.
This is fucking fantastic.
He might be watching the precinct,
your home.
I need you to take a car
from the motor pool...
...make sure you never
leave the same way twice.
Make sure no one follows you.
I'll do the same.
- I need you to promise me something.
- What?
That you will never take a case
from the Police Department again...
- ...from me, ever.
- Okay.
Are you lying to me?
- I don't think so.
- You don't think so?
- You don't fucking think so?
- I'm not lying.
I have no way of knowing, do I?
When you begin a stalk,
you start with what you know.
And with Isaak, that isn't much.
Isaak isn't just some hit man.
He's a boss.
- Yes?
- Dexter, Hannah McKay...
...is on her way in.
I'm kind of tied up with something
right now.
Dexter, Hannah is gonna
talk us through her road trip...
...with Wayne Randall and help us
find the rest of the bodies.
This is important. Get here now.
Right. I'm on my way.
In that first week...
...Wayne shot a gas station attendant
in Ashford, Alabama.
That's where these are from.
And Wayne shot another attendant
in Lake City, Florida.
And then he shot a guy outside
of Sarasota...
...who stopped to help you fix a flat.
You then get picked up in Miami
trying to sneak on board a cruise ship.
That week you guys were in Miami...
...that's the story we don't know.
The people Wayne killed,
the bodies we'd like to find.
It looks like it starts here.
We got to Miami and
we were the only thing on the news.
We were desperate.
No money, cops everywhere.
Wayne decided that we would
hide out in the motels...
...until we could make it
to that cruise ship.
He killed people
so we could take their rooms.
We buried the bodies close
to the motels.
- Where were the motels?
- One was by a Frosty Swirl.
- Wayne's favourite.
- That's where Ms. Dubois was found.
- What about these?
- Those two go together.
- Together?
- They were a couple.
Husband and wife, I guess.
- Where are they buried?
- Close to one of the ports.
- I remember big ships unloading.
- And the motel?
Small, one storey, I think...
...I would recognise it, but so much
of that time is just a blur, you know?
Everything changed in Miami.
Wayne, most of all.
I was so scared.
I thought that he was gonna kill me.
He forced me to dig those holes and
every time that I dug one of them...
...I wasn't sure if I was digging
my own grave or not.
I understand how difficult this is
for you, but if you'll excuse me...
...I'm gonna get the ball rolling
on the next dig. Tomorrow if possible.
Sure. I'd like to get this over with.
That toy isn't bringing back
memories of being scared.
She's nostalgic.
No touching.
Can I have your giraffe back,
please?
It's Wayne's.
Wayne's giraffe.
It was wrapped in your shirt.
What, are you a detective now too?
Sergeant Batista will give you
the details for tomorrow.
Will you be there?
I hope so.
Killing Isaak would make
a lot of Koshkas very angry.
But a lot of Colombians very happy.
The goddamn shower has
two settings, scalding and freezing.
It's a cheap motel. That's the point.
I'm not doing this another night.
Hopefully you won't have to.
Does that mean
you're working on a solution?
I have a plan, yes.
Does it involve you killing someone?
I'm not killing anybody.
That's my bed.
Closest to the door.
- Tell me your plan.
- No.
Dexter, I'm hiding out in this
fucking motel room. I'm a part of this.
But not any more
than you need to be.
This is not how I ever imagined
spending tonight.
We've stayed in hotel rooms before.
Yeah, when we went to Myrtle Beach
to visit Mom's sister.
There were seashells embedded
in the plaster in the walls.
No air-conditioning, just ceiling fans.
There was sand
from the beach everywhere.
Even in the beds.
You kept your eyes on me all day.
I didn't want you to drown.
You were my hero.
Good boy. Good.
Hot as hell out here...
...even with the ocean breeze.
Think we'll find anything?
The motel Hannah and Wayne
stayed at is still here.
Nothing's changed much
since their spree.
Pretty good odds.
Can I ask you something?
This bartender who shot himself,
Alex Dubrozny.
Do you think it's a suicide?
Masuka matched his handwriting
to the note he left.
His fingerprints were on the gun,
GSR on the hand.
He definitely pulled the trigger.
Fucking bugs.
I'm gonna go get some spray
from the car.
This part of the job?
Stand around and stare?
I'm not needed unless
there's a body or blood.
I don't know how you do it.
First time Wayne killed somebody,
he shot him right in the chest and I...
I couldn't move. Never seen
that much blood in my life.
First crime scene I ever worked...
...a woman stabbed her husband
after fixing him a sandwich.
By the time I got there,
he looked like he was asleep...
...just floating on a sea of red
and the sandwich next to his head.
Seemed so sad
that no one was gonna eat it.
Look at us talking blood and gore
like we're on a date...
...sharing our
first sexual experience.
I've got work to do.
There you are.
Aren't you supposed to be talking
to the Connors?
They were less than cooperative.
This was on my way back
to the station, so I thought I'd sit in.
Great.
Hi. I'm Captain Maria LaGuerta,
Miami Metro...
...and this is
Lieutenant Debra Morgan.
I talked to your morn, Patricia.
Is she home?
No, sorry.
She got called into work.
- Oh, we'll come back.
- Is this about my dad?
She said you guys had called.
I could try to answer any questions,
if you want.
- That would be very helpful.
- Yeah.
- Thanks.
When was the last time
you saw your father?
May 19th, 2007.
The best fucking day of my life.
How so?
Because he never came back.
So wasn't it hard growing up
without a father?
It was a lot better
than growing up with a father...
...who beat me and my mom
every chance he got.
I'm sorry.
Then one night,
he didn't come home.
I swear everything got better.
My morn wasn't crying all the time...
...and I wasn't constantly looking
over my shoulder.
Ty, you mentioned the last time
you saw your father...
...he was working a wedding?
Yeah, my mom printed out some
pictures for you from that night.
- She thought you might want them.
- Great.
What are you hoping
to find in these pictures?
Special Agent Lundy
had this theory...
...that the Bay Harbor Butcher
was in law enforcement.
If Barnes was killed by the Butcher--
His face might be
in one of the pictures.
We might even know him. Or her.
- Would you mind?
- Yeah, no.
Okay.
What are you looking for exactly?
We think your father
may have been abducted...
...and murdered
the night he disappeared...
...and the person responsible
could be in these pictures.
Mom would finally know
he's not coming home.
This is a big wedding.
A lot of pictures.
You know, maybe I should
take these back to the station...
...and spend the day
going over them.
You're right.
We shouldn't rush this.
Thank you, Ty. Thanks.
Right here. Put it down.
Go ahead, detective.
"Till death do us part"
didn't quite work out for these guys.
Get it? Because they're dead
but they're still together.
Okay, moving on.
Shower curtain helped preserve
the bodies and the clothes.
Our lucky day.
It's a safe assumption
that Wayne started with the male.
Would've been important
to immobilise him first...
...because he presented
the biggest threat.
There are defensive wounds
on the arms and the hands.
He put up a fight.
Judging from the cuts in the fabric...
...we're looking at perhaps
a 6-inch knife.
Numerous shallow wounds...
...until Wayne was able to inflict this,
the fatal wound.
Once he was done with him...
...he moved on to the female victim.
Stabbed numerous times.
The spatter pattern suggests
the victim fell on her back.
And these voids here
likely indicate that...
...she was straddled
by her assailant.
Who was much smaller
than Wayne.
If Wayne didn't kill this person...
Dexter.
What does it mean?
I'm not sure.
It could mean a lot of things.
I won't know until I get back to the lab
and run some tests.
I guess we're done here.
- Why did you stop?
- Stop what?
You started to describe
how Wayne killed that girl...
...and you got halfway through
and then you stopped.
Yeah, I did.
- And then you looked right at me.
- I did.
Why?
The spatter told me a story
that conflicts what you say happened.
Really?
How so?
How did you get this?
It's a little something I got
for talking back to Wayne.
- He got angry and slashed at me.
- Bullshit.
- Do you know something that I don't?
- Wayne didn't kill that woman.
He was too busy with the male.
It was someone smaller.
Someone with a different knife
who was inexperienced.
Got carried away
with the frenzy of the moment.
Stabbed the woman over and over
until the knife got so bloody...
...her hand slipped along the edge
of the sharp blade...
...cutting her palm very deeply,
exactly like yours...
...leaving a passive spatter stain
on the victim's dress.
Everything you said is a lie.
That's my story.
And I'm sticking to it.
And you don't even care.
You have immunity, don't you?
The DA gave you immunity
for cooperating with us.
From any crime committed
with Wayne, yeah. Yeah.
A girl's gotta protect herself.
I'll see you around, Dexter Morgan.
Isaak. I knew
you would show up eventually.
Don't worry. I'm not gonna lose you.
Welcome to the wrong side of town,
Isaak.
Not used to strangers here.
Koshkas.
And certainly not used
to their sworn enemies walking in.
But Isaak, being from out of town,
won't know any of this.
Definitely not as much fun as
putting Isaak on my table.
But it does mask his death...
...as the resulting war
between rival heroin dealers.
Who's saving whose ass now?
- What's up?
- I know you're busy.
I also want you to know
that I'm not trying to stir up any shit.
Of course not.
It's about this
Alex Dubrozny suicide.
There's something about this guy
being Anderson's killer...
...that's just not right.
Sorry. It's Dispatch.
Sergeant Batista.
Okay. Got it.
Gonna have to rain check this.
Homicide at a Colombian hangout.
Got blood, Dexter.
- Where we going?
- Mateo's Bar.
- Know it?
- Nope.
I'll meet you there.
Holy shit.
It's like somebody turned on the hose
and sprayed blood everywhere.
Great.
I left Isaak here outnumbered
and expected to find only his body.
So where is he now?
Do we know these guys?
This is Andres Rodriguez.
He's a member of the Rojas Cartel.
We ran into each other a few times
when I worked Narcotics.
Is it possible Isaak did all of this?
Why do drug hits
have to be so messy?
You gotta make a big show.
Who you think is good for this?
The 87's?
- Or the Koshka Brotherhood.
- Koshkas?
What happened here, Dex?
Considering this one
was closest to the door...
...he's probably first to see
the attacker, first to respond.
He drew his gun
as the attacker fired.
The misting on the jukebox...
...and the wall indicates multiple
bullet hits all through and through.
- Victim number two.
- Looks like he got a shot off.
But, that didn't stop the assault.
The attacker returned fire.
Twice in the chest,
once in the stomach.
Judging from the lack of pooling
around the body suggests...
...that the victim was dead
before the third shot.
Wait. How many people
were here shooting?
There's only evidence of one killer.
- One brutally efficient killer.
- Jesus, fuck.
Looks like our attacker
ran out of bullets right around here.
It's from a defensive wound.
Looks like it was a deep cut,
forearm maybe.
Obviously not fatal.
The attacker grabbed the nearest
weapon, hit his victim over the head...
...inflicted a massive skull fracture...
...and walked right out the door.
So, we're looking
for the fucking Terminator.
Let's get the blood
running through the system.
Maybe we can match it to a name.
Everybody outside. Let's let Dexter
and Masuka do their thing.
Sarge, you mind
if I run an errand real quick?
Was this part
of your fantastic plan?
I never said my plan was fantastic...
...but no, this is not
how I thought it would go.
Do we have an even bigger problem
on our hands now?
Not if we can find a match
for this blood.
You'll be able to make an arrest.
The sooner the better.
I couldn't agree more.
Right here, baby.
Your car is fixed.
You have to start using it.
But I like having a chauffeur.
Come on.
Let me show you how much I like it.
I wish I could, but I have work to do.
Oh, just forget about work.
We're gonna have to
fucking pay them back.
I'll get some guys,
do it myself if you want.
- No.
- Well, they're sure as shit...
...gonna come after us.
And we can't sit around
and do nothing.
Shit.
We don't need a cop here now.
- Who is he?
- Joey Quinn.
He came up from Narcotics,
and now he's Homicide.
We used to have
an understanding with him.
What kind of understanding?
Leave a bag of cash in his car,
and he'd do whatever we asked.
Mostly just look the other way.
Fuck.
Well?
Lieutenant,
are the cuffs necessary?
Probably not.
Would your client
like to have a little chat with us?
My client has nothing to say.
He's exercising
his American right to silence.
Well, fucking God bless America.
Get this guy to Booking.
Your client's going to jail
for the rest of his life.
Nice to meet you,
Lieutenant Morgan.
Maybe now that lsaak's behind bars,
we can have...
...that face-to-face
he's been so desperate for.
So you got Isaak Sirko.
We got Isaak Sirko.
Congratulations. It's a big deal.
May I?
- Our earlier conversation.
- Right.
I don't think Alex Dubrozny
shot Mike Anderson.
It doesn't make any sense.
Alex has been in this country
for two years...
...and according to every stripper
I interviewed...
...all he talked about
was his wife and his kids.
He didn't show
any interest towards Kaja.
I think someone put Alex up to this.
Someone connected to Isaak Sirko.
Deb, I still think Viktor Baskov
killed Mike Anderson...
...and Viktor just disappeared
into thin air.
- But if we can find--
- Sergeant.
- Your dedication is admirable.
- Deb, you don't have to talk like that.
- It's--
- And a year ago...
...I might have been right beside you,
fighting for what I thought was right.
But the hardest lesson
that I've learned as lieutenant...
...is knowing when
to back the fuck down.
You don't believe me?
You don't have concrete evidence
to support your theory.
And I can't afford to reopen
a murder investigation.
This isn't any murder investigation.
This is Mike.
- He--
- Mike's killer's dead.
Mike got justice.
Let it go.
That's an order.
Okay, lieutenant.
You got it.
- Hello, Isaak.
- Hello, Dexter.
I underestimated you.
You come here to taunt me?
I thought maybe you could help me.
Why is it so important
that you kill me?
Well, it's quite simple, really.
You killed Viktor. I liked Viktor.
Like or not,
he killed Mike Anderson.
Is that why you killed him?
Revenge?
Yes.
There was the briefest flicker
of hesitation there.
But if you're telling the truth...
...then you don't require
any explanation.
You understand the need
for vengeance.
So you got arrested. There'll be a trial.
You'll go to prison for a long time.
Does that mean this is over?
- Over?
- Yes.
I had a great uncle...
...my grandfather's brother.
He was a hero.
Fought with the Red Army
during the Second World War.
When he returned to Kiev afterwards,
some fat, little party official...
...resented the fact
that everyone admired him...
...so he decided
to make an example of him...
...by taking away his house.
When my great uncle protested...
...he was hung
in front of the council chambers.
My grandfather was just a teenager.
When that party official saw
the hatred in his eyes...
...he had him arrested
and sent to Siberia.
And the years rolled by.
And my grandfather got on
with his life as best he could.
He was a patient man.
Finally, when the Soviet Union fell,
he returned to Kiev...
...and celebrated in front of city hall
with all the others.
And that's when he found
that fat, little party official...
...and he got to enjoy the pleasure
that belonged to him and him alone...
...by sticking a 6-inch knife into
that fat, little man's kidney.
So you ask me if this is over.
No.
I'm afraid not.
- There's only one problem.
- And that is?
I'm not some fat, little man.
That's true.
I don't know who you are.
If you ever find out, you'll regret it.
Hey. Come on in.
See this?
What is it?
It's me lifeguarding your ass
for a change.
I took it from LaGuerta.
- I told you to stay clear of this.
- Well, you're lucky I didn't.
- Deb--
- She would've seen you, Dexter.
So you saved me.
Yeah.
Thanks.
That's yours. It's not mine.
I don't wanna be involved in
that part of your life.
I don't want you to be.
I know you're not gonna stop.
But I don't wanna know about it.
Okay.
I had to lie to Batista.
Batista. For you.
And that was the moment I realised
that I don't wanna be a part of this.
I can't do it.
It took me forever
to wrap my brain around the idea...
...that you're not
who I thought you were.
But it doesn't mean
I have to change.
All of your stealing and your lying
and your covering up...
...that's not me.
So you think
LaGuerta's investigation is closed?
No.
Lundy didn't figure me out.
No reason to think LaGuerta will.
Oh, if Lundy could see me now.
And you.
I've been thinking about our vacation
to Myrtle Beach a lot.
How we spent our days.
On the beach.
Running up and down the shore.
And at low tide,
running in and out of the water.
I was always chasing you.
I could never catch you.
You wouldn't take off your flippers.
Even if I did, you were always...
...just out of reach.
Maybe, we're learning
it's better that way.
Did you get the blood report back
on the bodies from the dig?
Yeah.
And?
Anything I should know?
Nope.
As kids, Deb and I
would try to outrun the waves...
...but I would always end up
diving under them.
I would swim deep because I could
withstand the pull of the tide.
But Deb was always safest
at shore.
From here on out,
I'll face the depths by myself.