Previously on Dexter...
Miami is still overcrowded by one.
I'm not suggesting a coup here.
More like a realignment.
- Do you recognise him?
- It's one of George's men.
Sent here to kill me.
So much for brotherhood.
This guy had a slip.
Dexter Morgan.
- Are you sure?
- Yeah.
Chief Lane has somehow come
to learn about my indiscretions.
He's asking me to retire.
He thought that I ratted him out.
We both know it was you.
This is how the game is played,
Morgan.
- I don't owe you shit.
- Not the way Isaak sees it.
He did you a favour by taking out
those Colombian scumbags.
So, what do you know
about this Isaak Sirko?
I know that he wants to kill me
and that I need to kill him first.
I have never been able to talk
to anyone about my kills.
Not like this.
You should cut your losses, Isaak.
Go back to Kiev.
The one thing that made my life worth
living in Kiev, you tossed in the ocean.
- You and Viktor were--
- Lovers.
You took from me the one thing
that money and power can't bring back.
Till next time.
I know who you are.
I know what you are.
I think you'd be surprised
at the things you don't know about me.
Being with Hannah is worse...
- ...than being a killer?
- Yes!
Feel like if you love me,
you'll accept this.
If I love you? I'm in love with you.
You're in love with me?
Will you please just go? I really--
I can't look at you.
There are no two stronger
human emotions than fear and love.
In many ways, they're not so different.
Both can make you do crazy things.
Tell your own brother
you're in love with him.
Put your life at risk
to hunt down the man...
...who took away your beloved.
Could you maybe not do
that turny thing?
- How you doing back there?
- Oh, you know, I'm fine.
Or do something
that scares you to death...
...because you may be in love.
I didn't think it was gonna be this
choppy. Turn into the waves.
Otherwise it's worse.
Well, I wouldn't want that.
You know, could we maybe stop
for a minute?
We don't have to do this.
We can go back.
No, no, no. I just need a minute.
I thought I'd outgrown this.
When you said your nanny
was taking the kids back to Orlando...
...a morning on the ocean alone
sounded“.
...better in my head.
LS your--?
You're shaking.
You always been this afraid
of the water?
Since my father thought that the best
way to teach me how to swim...
...was to march me down to the local
pond and throw me in.
- That's horrible.
- Yeah.
- Where was your mother?
- She was right beside him.
She noticed pretty quickly
that something was wrong...
...but he wouldn't let her come to me.
He wouldn't save you?
Six years old and I already knew
what it felt like to be dying.
I came to on the dock.
A fisherman heard my mother
screaming.
A complete stranger saved my life
instead of my father.
Have you ever been that scared?
Not--
Not really.
You've never felt that at all?
It's okay if you have.
You can talk to me...
...about this kind of stuff.
I know.
It's work.
There's a body. I have to get back.
Okay.
You're positive?
After George's attempt on your life...
...the brotherhood has taken matters
into their own hands.
They've sent two men to kill you.
They're most likely already here.
Who?
Mickie and Caffrey.
You know there's still time for you.
You don't have to stay.
I'm not going anywhere.
You're safe here for now.
They won't be able to trace this room
to you.
Your phone.
I've made both these men very rich
when I required their services.
Let's see if they're as loyal as you.
- Oleg, it's--
- Isaak.
Good to hear your voice.
- How's your mother?
- Good days and bad.
So I hear you're in town.
Don't suppose we can talk about this.
I've already accepted the contract.
What's done is done.
Right, then.
We'll see you soon.
We're gonna need some help.
Hannah keeps wanting me
to open up...
...get to know the real me.
The only problem is I'm not so sure
there is such a thing.
Relax. You're safe.
As for me, I wish
I could say the same thing.
- What are you doing here?
- Circumstances have changed greatly.
Koshkas have sent two of their own
to kill me. Need your help to stay alive.
I'm feeling rather exposed out here.
We wouldn't want these two men
to know where you live now, would we?
You don't seem like someone
who needs help.
Even a man dangling from a cliff will
stretch out a hand to his worst enemy.
Where's your assistant?
As resourceful as Jurg is,
he's of no use to me now.
These men know who he is.
What I need
is the element of surprise.
And that, Dexter...
...is you.
You're scared.
If you knew
who these two men were...
...you would be too.
What's in this for me?
Your life.
I'll take my chances.
Very well.
If the enemy of my enemy
is my friend...
...I should be rooting for the men
who want Isaak dead.
But crazy as it sounds, I'm not.
Maybe because I still want Isaak
for myself.
Or that he and I are more alike
than I want to admit.
Know what would be great
at the restaurant? S'mores.
- The ones you make at your own table.
- Don't mention the restaurant.
Health inspector stopped by.
How can you think of food with this?
Four violations and seven days to fix
or they're gonna shut me down.
Mind if I take a look?
I'd rather you not.
At least till I'm done here.
- Little heads up next time?
- What would be the fun in that?
Arson investigator.
There's an empty canister of accelerant
under the passenger seat.
I'm detecting an oily residue.
There's also...
...an ID badge.
- What do we have here?
- Watch.
Holy filet-o-fuck.
- Who are you?
- See, it never gets old.
Phil Bosso.
We met a while back.
That church burning?
- Have an ID?
- Danny Yamiro. Paralegal.
Badge says he works downtown.
Think you got a suicide here.
Hara-kiri.
Self-immolation.
What is it with my people?
First in math, first to check out.
It's actually self-incineration.
Immolation is a form of sacrifice
by any means. Isn't restricted to fire.
Well, excuse the fuck out of me.
Hey, what about the backseat?
The burn rate behind the driver's side
is different than the rest.
- Are you sure it's a suicide?
- You're the blood guy?
- Right.
- Exactly.
- Crime scene's all yours.
- Thanks.
Let me know what you find.
Gonna have unis canvass the area.
- I can do that.
- No, no, I got it.
Deb's been afraid
of her feelings consuming her.
If I can't find a way to extinguish them,
I'm afraid she might be right.
- Deb, wait up.
- I have to get back to the station.
- What you said--
- I don't wanna talk about this.
I'm glad you said it.
How? When every second of every day,
all I wanna do is take it back.
Because on some level,
I've always felt the same way.
- You don't have to do this.
- I do. I am your brother, and I love you.
Just not in the same way
you think you love me.
- Dex--
- And it's okay.
I understand. It makes sense.
It's logical.
Like...
The way I love M&Ms,
even though I know I shouldn't.
M&-fucking-Ms?
I'm trying here. Just hear me out.
Why, Dexter?
It's sure as shit not logical.
Consider everything
we've been through.
You are the one person on the planet
who's been down the same road.
Same road, very different cars.
Deb, we've always been the one
constant thing in each other's lives.
It's like you and I...
...we endure.
Maybe that's what love is.
Endurance.
- You think you're in love with me.
- Please stop saying that.
- But it's gonna be fine.
- No.
It's--
Logical. Because it is.
You're not crazy.
Fuck. That, coming from you...
Should make you feel better.
It does.
God, Dexter. You, me, Dad.
It's like Mom got cancer
to take the easy way out.
I don't know.
Maybe it's better that it's out there...
...and it's not controlling me
anymore.
Do you feel that way
about your secret?
Not really.
Deb?
Hannah?
I saw your van outside. Are you--?
- Here?
- Dexter. You're just in time for tea.
Hope you don't mind, I let myself in.
That's far enough.
I just want to talk.
Where's Hannah?
Jurg's been keeping tabs on you.
For me.
Your comings and goings.
Where you spend your nights.
Seems this Hannah's quite important
to you.
- Where is she?
- I assure you she's perfectly safe...
...and quite comfortable.
Jurg is seeing to that.
Let her go.
This is between you and me.
Not quite.
There's the small matter
of the two men who want me dead...
...and your stubborn refusal to help.
You asked me
what was in this for you.
Well, if your life doesn't matter...
...I'm betting hers does.
Well, I guess I have no choice
but to take you up on that tea.
Splendid idea.
I have a better idea. I kill you, and
leave you out for the Koshkas to find.
Yes, you can do that...
...but that leaves Hannah with Jurg.
I'm afraid he's not as honourable
nor as forgiving as I am.
What makes you think
Hannah means anything to me?
Well, if she didn't,
I'd be dead by now.
You have the wrong guy.
This isn't what I do.
You killed Viktor as well as the man
waiting for me in my apartment.
He had a gun, you had a knife.
I think I have the right man.
And if I help you, then what?
You get Hannah back...
...and I walk away from Miami
and from you.
No matter what you may think of me
or my methods...
...I'm a man of my word.
I need to know she's alive.
Hannah, I trust you and Jurg
are settled in.
- Why are you doing this?
- The reason, my dear, is right here.
Dexter.
- Don't worry.
- That's enough.
- Now, you behave.
- No, wait! Dexter--
Your life is in his hands now.
Listen to me carefully.
Scream, make noise, I hurt you.
Try to escape...
...I hurt you badly.
Clear?
Here.
Find something for us to watch.
And none of the American
reality shit.
Here.
Oleg Mickie. Ex-military.
Efficient, methodical.
Which is why I've employed him
more times than I can count.
- And that one?
- Benjamin Caffrey.
He's a Yank, like you.
Out of New York.
Less reliable but, as you can see...
...just as deadly.
Any weaknesses?
I need to know everything.
Caffrey likes it up close and personal.
Knives, piano wire.
And as you saw...
...he's a vicious little cunt.
Whereas Mickie doesn't like
to get his hands dirty.
- Guns?
- High-powered riﬂes specifically.
He's a slave to ritual.
He'll buy a rifle locally...
...and be compelled
to test it out first.
Point of a rifle is to hit a target
from a long distance.
The range would need
to be outdoors.
That's his favourite.
A Savage Arms 110 sniper rifle.
Most ranges don't sell the kind
of magazine rounds this one uses.
That's where I'll start tomorrow.
Well, just where are you running off to,
all helter-skelter?
I'm hungry-
You've been tasked
with helping kill two men.
A loved one's life hangs in the balance,
and you're hungry?
- It's late.
- Let me ask you a question.
Just how many men have you killed?
A lot.
I asked Mickie
the same question once.
He answered 16. And the bastard
was almost pounding his chest.
But you...
...you don't seem to revel
in what you do.
Why?
You trying to have a moment?
I don't bond.
Most men kill for money.
Some for the sheer brutality.
Others like me, revenge.
But you, Dexter...
...with everything
I've put you through...
...I get the sense you could walk away
without the need to kill me.
My needs are different.
Why do you do it?
Why are you a killer?
If anything happens to Hannah,
you'll find out.
I need a favour.
Okay. If you do me one
and watch where you're dripping.
Isaak Sirko.
What about him?
Call off the 24-hour surveillance.
Like hell I Will.
What the fuck is going on?
Someone's after Isaak.
Two someones.
You know, like the guy
in his apartment but worse.
Actually, much worse.
So you want me to pull the surveillance
so the two someones can...
...do what they're hired to do?
Not exactly.
Well, then I'm not pulling
the surveillance.
- He'll come after you.
- No, he won't.
Because he and I...
...are working together.
- Are you out of your fucking mind?
- Isaak took Hannah.
He got wind about these two guys
coming after him...
...and he took Hannah
as leverage against me.
- He's gonna kill her if I don't help him.
- And I should give a shit why?
Because I do?
Dexter, you don't have to save her.
You shouldn't even be with her.
It's not even like you
will have a fucking future.
You're both what you are.
I don't know what's in our future.
I don't want Isaak to kill her, that's all.
Right now.
Who do you think has her?
His assistant. Jurg.
If I can find out where, Isaak won't
have any more leverage on me...
...and I can kill him.
Well, how do you expect to find Jurg
if you're hanging outwith Isaak?
I'll figure it out.
You know what happened
this morning?
I was lying in bed,
staring at the ceiling...
...feeling the sun,
and listening to the waves, and...
For a second,
everything was just like it used to be.
Steaks and beer...
...and bad movies on the couch.
And then I blinked.
And now it's burritos...
...and hired killers and favours...
...and Xanax
to get me to tomorrow morning...
...so I can have that half second
of peace.
I'll pull the surveillance...
...but don't you ever expect me to be
okay with who you're doing this for.
Deal?
Deal.
Tom.
And a great creature arose
from the depths.
Tokyo's that way, Maria.
Nice to see you too, Tom.
I thought I'd stop by
and see how you were doing.
- I mean, it's been a while.
- Bullshit.
Now, you have exactly the time
it takes for me to finish my drink...
...to explain why you're really here.
Little early for Scotch.
The joy of retirement.
I have no place to be,
no one cares what I do.
If I'd known you were dropping by,
trust me, I'd have made it a double.
So?
I think the Bay Harbor Butcher
is alive and well...
...and still in Miami.
Clearly I'm not the only one
who's been hitting the sauce.
Doakes was the Bay Harbor Butcher,
end of story.
I found a blood slide
at a crime scene...
...exactly like the ones we found
in Doakes' car.
Bad people are still going missing,
and Doakes never had a boat.
Here is a list of Miami personnel
who still do.
Oh, and I'm on it too.
Are you fucking kidding me, Maria?
Torn, you know I have to follow
every lead.
You sound like a real cop.
Except a real cop would've
remembered my hernia operation.
And after the surgery...
...I could barely lift my ass
out of a chair let alone a dead body.
- You check the dates against the kills.
- I will.
Since I'm here,
do any of those names look familiar?
Go home, Maria.
The only help you'll get from me
is a lift back to Cuba.
Only two firing ranges outside of Miami
sell high-calibre rounds...
...and this is the only one
near the airport.
But the target I'm interested in
isn't out there.
It's beside me.
Mickie is dead.
Fast work.
I see I chose wisely.
You're not out of the woods yet.
When he finds out his partner's dead,
Caffrey is gonna be harder to kill.
- What does he know about you?
- Everything, I suppose.
I'm sure the Koshkas
would have saw to that.
What if he knows you're after me
and can't track you?
- He'll come after you hoping to find me.
- So let's let him.
You're willing to be bait?
You're the one who wanted
the element of surprise.
I got your text. What's going on?
Unis found Jurg's car at a park,
but it was abandoned.
That's all I could find.
You're not supposed to be finding
anything. I told you I've got this.
You've got this? It sounds so casual.
Facts without emotion.
That's pretty much
how you've always seen the world.
Pretty much.
Except when it comes to Hannah.
Will we be getting a call
about a body?
No, it's outside
of Miami Metro jurisdiction.
That's good.
I guess.
How do you know that Isaak
is not gonna kill Hannah anyway?
I don't.
And if you find Hannah
and you take care of Isaak, then what?
Well, according to you, Hannah and I
don't have a future together.
I had no right to say that.
And it wasn't out of spite.
Fuck, I don't know, maybe it was out
of spite. I don't even know anymore.
It's just...
I'm saying this to you as your
fucking sister and nothing else, okay?
Dex, she is a killer.
You will never be safe with her.
You're safe with me.
Promise me you'll think
about what I said.
I Will.
Breathe.
What the fuck? Aren't you supposed
to be hunting down Isaak?
Hey, I can't reach Mickie.
I think Sirko got to him.
Great.
That's just fucking great.
You realise he'll be coming after me...
...if this goes sideways?
Then I need a way to find him.
Morgan.
I wanna talk to Hannah.
She hasn't been harmed.
I've done everything you've asked,
but I need to know she's still alive.
And figure out where she is.
Has anyone ever told you
you've got serious trust issues?
Is it over?
Not quite.
Put Hannah on.
Someone wishes to speak to her.
Hey.
Hey, my God.
It's so good to see you.
- Has he hurt you?
- I'm fine.
So those Ukrainians
you were telling me about?
This would be them.
- Everything's gonna be okay.
- I know.
I'm sorry they're using me like this
to get to you.
Don't be.
It's not your fault.
Well, it doesn't matter anyway.
Just do what you have to do, okay?
I want you to take me out
on that stupid boat of yours again.
Promise?
I--
I miss you.
Likewise.
Touching.
I have to get back to work.
If I had the chance to speak to Viktor
again and he told me he missed me...
...I think I'd like to think
I could come up...
...with something better
than "likewise."
I'm not you.
Yeah, but there she was,
trying to comfort you...
...and you just couldn't manage
to do the same.
- Why do you even care?
- Well, look around.
There's no one else here for me
to talk to because of you.
Viktor got exactly
what was coming to him.
- Fuck you.
- That what these questions are about?
Wondering what kind of killer I am,
trying to decide if I should die...
- ...because of what I did to him?
- He was my life!
But still...
...you sent him to Miami.
You put him in over his head.
You put all this in motion.
And now you're terrified, Isaak.
You're terrified
that I'm not really responsible...
...for his death.
That you are.
No.
You're the reason he's gone.
If you really believed that,
I'd be dead by now.
Go.
Hey, Quinn, it's me.
I'm having a real shitty day here.
So how about you return
one of my fucking calls?
- Go get changed.
- My shift just started.
Yeah, well, we're gonna take a break.
Your boyfriend's got me in a mood.
Viceroy's just down the road.
We had some good times there,
right?
I'll get my things.
Isaak is consumed by guilt,
drowning in grief.
He'll never recover.
You took the risk. How did you know
he blames himself for Viktor's death?
I did the same thing with Rita.
Even though it was Trinity
who killed her, I still felt responsible.
Now it's happening all over again
with Hannah.
If something were to happen to her,
and it's my fault...
- ...will I end up like Isaak?
- You recovered after Rita.
Barely.
Harrison reminds me of her
every day.
But with Hannah...
It feels different.
I've spent my entire life
trying to mask who I am...
...Wha'[ I do.
But she sees through it all,
and accepts that part of me.
So where's the problem?
If we get through this...
...maybe it's the human side of me
that'll push her away.
Juan Pablo.
It's a Colombian soccer player.
The men Isaak killed in that bar
were Colombian.
And dead men don't return home.
It's the last place these killers
would think to look for Isaak.
And the perfect place
to hold Hannah.
Dex, grab your kit. We got another
burn victim near the university.
It's the man Isaak showed me.
Caffrey.
He's taken the bait.
I need to keep him close...
...but not too close.
Fucking mould.
With all that it's gonna cost me,
the universe is giving me the finger.
And with proper lubrication,
nothing wrong with that, hombre.
Yo, Dex. You wanna join the party?
Victim's name is Leo Santolongo.
He's a grad student.
One punch away from getting
free coffee at the student union.
What the hell?
Two burning men in two days.
Looks to be the same accelerant-
Petroleum-based.
--As your car victim.
Same oily residue.
- Another suicide?
- Typically with a suicide by fire...
...the gas or fuel
is poured over the head, like so.
This fire's point of origin...
...was front centre mass.
It burned upward and downward.
Can we close the doors?
This void. It's the same thing
that happened with the first car victim.
We have a phantom.
- Bobby.
- Maybe the victim...
...was letting us know who did this.
Or was it the last person
he was thinking of'?
You Okay?
Never seen anything like this.
If this was a person...
...then they'd have to be wearing
some kind of protective suit.
He blocked the victim from escaping
and watched him burn alive.
Oh, it's not as horrific
as one might think.
Destruction of vital tissue,
nerve endings...
...quickly induce shock or asphyxiation
making the event relatively painless.
Relatively.
I need my camera.
- What does he need his camera for?
- Evidence we have a killer...
...using fire as a weapon
and a first name. Bobby.
Wonderful.
Quinn, is there a security camera
on this level?
Yeah, one.
I'll get the tape from the company.
Well, if there's no blood,
I'm gonna head back.
- Vince.
- Yeah, I've got it, Exter-Day.
How can there be only one
security camera in this entire lot?
Deb, you got a minute?
Be right back.
Who's Juan Pablo?
He plays for the Colombians.
You remember Mateo's Bar?
Yeah,
the three Colombians Isaak killed?
Yeah, I grabbed this off of his phone.
I think Hannah's being held
at one of the dead men's homes.
I'll look into it.
But that's all, and thank you.
- Dexter.
- Your man, Caffrey?
- He sees you?
- Yeah.
I'm leaving a crime scene now.
Lead him to the port.
Pier 18, northwest corridor.
There's a cargo ship, the Fearless.
It's one of ours.
I'll be waiting there.
This is George. How can I help you?
It's Caffrey.
Did you find Isaak?
- Please tell me that fucker's dead.
- Not yet.
I'm tailing Morgan. Any reason
he'd be headed down to the port?
We got a boat down there.
You think Isaak is luring Morgan
to him?
That's what I'm hoping to find out.
- Hi.
- Hey.
Joey, what are you doing here?
I was on my way from a crime scene.
Thought I'd see if you can get off early.
No. George wouldn't be happy.
Fuck him. Can't one of the other girls
cover for you?
Hey. ls everything okay?
Yes.
Please, just go.
Well, did something happen?
Would you please talk to me?
This job is hard with you...
...and the things
that are expected of me.
I don't have a problem
with you working here.
Promise me you won't be upset.
Depends on what it is.
Nadia, what happened?
You fucked my girl?
Technically, if the dancers
are on the clock, they're my girls.
Maybe you'd know that
if you ever returned my fucking calls.
You left me high and dry tonight.
That's gonna stop.
You could learn a thing or two
from her.
She takes her job very seriously.
You're gonna be sorry!
Piece of shit!
Consider that her fucking notice.
Come on.
Really? Cornflakes? Again?
That's all there is in the cupboard.
Eat.
How about you let me introduce you
to some good old Southern cuisine?
My grandma has this great recipe
for fried green tomatoes. It's amazing.
I saw some tomatoes
growing in the garden out back.
I can't let you outside.
Okay, fine.
You pick them, then.
It's not like I'm going anywhere.
Well, just remember, not too ripe.
I think I'm on to something.
One of those Colombians was single.
The other two lived with their family
or an apartment.
But he has a house on Coral Road.
I'm heading there.
- Deb, no.
- I don't wanna hear it, Dexter, okay?
And just so we're clear,
I am not doing this for Hannah.
I am doing this so you don't end up
dead. If you catch Isaak first, so be it.
You kind of need to hurry. I'm leading
one of these guys to Isaak now.
- Please be careful.
- I was gonna say the same to you.
That's the plan.
Sweetheart.
See? A man of my word.
- Here you go.
- Thanks.
Your assistant told me
I'd find you here.
We need to talk.
About what?
The horrible things you said to me?
You cost me my job, Maria.
Was nine months shy of a 40-year
pension before you stuck the knife in.
Before you could return the favour.
It's not my fault...
...I beat you at your own game.
So why don't you take
your own advice? Go home.
Now, why would I wanna do that
if I'm here to help?
Don't fuck with me, Torn.
That little list of yours?
You'd be surprised what I know
about some of the names on there.
- Which names?
- Oh, not so fast, no.
I help you,
you support my reinstatement.
Just long enough for me
to get my pension bump.
Boats are fucking expensive.
So the question, Maria...
...is how bad do you want this?
Looks like a table just opened up.
Careful, they're hot.
Isaak hasn't checked in yet.
If anything has happened to him...
...it would be a shame
to kill you after a lovely meal.
Well, let's hope
that doesn't have to happen.
In case you want some more.
- Water.
- I'm sorry.
Grams always went heavy
on the pepper.
Never cared much for that man.
We should go before we're spotted.
So this is over?
And still you don't trust me?
Well?
You can talk.
The knife?
How'd that get there?
In the water. I'll do the same.
Fine. Together, then.
You go ahead.
I'm gonna hose this down to be safe.
I'll wait for you below.
Isaak was right.
I could have walked away if he'd let me.
But I was wrong about him.
I never thought he would.
What the hell happened to you?
Well...
What are you waiting for,
you little shit?
God.
Don't move.
I can get you to a hospital.
The bullet's still inside.
We both know I'm a dead man.
There's a kit in my car.
- I can help with the pain.
- No.
I need you to do me one better.
Fuck.
- Dispatch.
- This is Lt. Morgan requesting backup.
And a fucking ambulance
at 2085 Coral Road.
We're sending someone right now.
Sorry for the bumpy ride.
You're forgiven.
We're here.
Indulge a dying man.
What do you intend to say to Hannah
when you see her again?
I guess that I'm sorry.
You guess?
Fuck's sakes, Dexter. She needs
to know how you feel about her.
It's not that easy.
How is it you can be absolutely
fearless in the face of death...
...and yet so afraid to live?
I'm not...
...afraid.
Then what is it?
Death has always calmed me.
It's soothing.
Predictable.
Inevitable.
With a knife in my hand,
I feel it's mine to control.
It gives you intimacy.
Yes.
But it never lasts.
It's over...
...then you move on.
But now, with Hannah...
...I feel
like I don't have any control...
...and I'm not sure I wanna move on.
I was like you.
So detached.
Until Viktor.
Was it worth it? Your feelings for him
cost you everything.
Oh, God, yes.
Being with him...
...I never had to hide.
I was finally...
Alive.
There's hope for you yet.
Watch any Western, and you'll know
a man out for vengeance...
...should dig two graves.
One for his enemy
and one for himself.
I won't be needing mine.
But I'll see to it
that Isaak isn't alone in his.
And you have no idea
why you were taken by the deceased?
No.
He barely spoke.
So he chained you up, you got free...
...he stabbed you,
and then you beat him to death.
As I stated, it was self-defence.
Oh, I know.
Still, there was a lot of blood.
I mean, I know it's not the first time
you've gotten your hands bloody.
Are we finished?
I wanna make sure what you're telling
me reflects what really happened.
But, yeah, sure, we can be done.
How is it that you were the one
that found me?
I'm a cop.
It's my job to follow through
on anonymous tips.
Where was your backup?
Lieutenant's prerogative.
Doctor said I was in pretty bad shape
when you found me.
Yep.
So given your feelings about me,
why not just let me die?
I was doing my job.
Was it because of Dexter?
No.
I think it's about fucking time
I start doing things for myself.
Maybe you can be fine with being
responsible for someone's death...
...but I can't. That's...
That's not who I am.
I got here as fast as I could.
Everything taken care of?
All taken care of.
Then I guess I'll go.
You gonna be okay?
Yeah. I'm gonna be fine.
It's only 12 stitches.
I'm gonna be out of here tomorrow.
God, you're shaking.
When you asked me on my boat
if I'd ever been scared like that, I have.
Twice.
When I was 3,
seeing my mother murdered.
And when I realised
these past few days...
...that I might never see you again.
Well, that wasn't so hard, was it?
I don't know.
I'm not sure what this is...
...exactly.
Or what's...
...coming.
Maybe that's how it's supposed to be.
Out of my control.
All I know is that when I'm with you,
I feel...
...safe.