- Yeah?
- I'm at the county line.
Seventeen minutes since they got off 80.
You should have them
in about 30 seconds.
- No stops?
- Same route four days running.
Does this entire town
smell like cow shit?
Yeah, you got to stay upwind.
Okay, I have them.
And they're waiting.
And there he is.
- The old man?
- And the son. Same drill.
Sounds like somebody
got micromanagement issues.
Wherever we do hit them, it won't be here.
Baby, before they see you
is always your best bet.
Not with all that hardware.
We're gonna have to take them on the road.
Who the fuck is that?
That's Sugar. He's with us.
And when did we become
a motherfucking committee?
- Did I miss a vote?
- You'll meet soon enough. Don't worry.
Sounds older than God and you
call him Sugar. Why should I be worried?
I'm sorry. All the other
potty mouth drag queens were busy.
Hmm, repartee.
How motherfucking exciting.
Do you have any idea
what it takes to crack a truck like that?
No, none at all. That's why you're here.
This sucks. All right?
Can't we go back
to the city, man? Any city.
We could do a bank, do diamonds.
Something more suited to our skills.
This is a stagecoach.
It's the motherfucking
Wild West up in here.
Hey, we're rebuilding. Raising capital.
- We're slumming.
- You wanted in, Job.
Only because I had to torch my salon...
thanks to you, motherfucker.
Cost of doing business.
Fuck you.
Fuck each and every one of you.
- There you go.
- Thank you.
Come on. Let's go, you guys.
- Don't fall behind.
- Hurry up!
Hey, Mom.
Why do they wear those masks?
They're banshee masks.
The evil spirit of a murdered Kinaho bride.
- Deva.
- What, Mom? He can take it.
Yeah, Mom, I can take it.
- It's just a legend.
- What's the legend?
Just that the spirit
of the murdered Kinaho bride...
stayed behind to haunt
the white men who killed her.
So naturally we turned it into a festival.
That is one sweet-ass MILF.
- Fuck off, douchebag.
- Deva!
What? They're being assholes.
Yes, and we don't need
to encourage them.
- Here you go, Mrs. Moody.
- Thanks.
- Their pies are so good.
- Yeah.
Hi. Last year
you had some terrific peach cobbler.
- How much?
- Five dollars.
Only 20 and she's had problems.
Mr. Proctor.
Oh, hello, Alex. Good to see you.
- Can I get you a sandwich?
- Oh, no, thank you.
I haven't seen Benjamin.
My father's not feeling well today.
But he did hear about your legal issues
and asked me to look in on you.
You tell him I appreciate that...
but I fully expect the case
to be dropped shortly.
Maybe so, but it is a murder charge.
So I'm sure that you can understand...
that your involvement in the casino
expansion is now an impossibility.
It's too much exposure for us.
I'm a silent partner,
as you like to point out.
So I don't really follow your logic.
Banshee's a small town.
These things have a way of coming out.
We simply can't allow you to be involved.
But I already am involved, Alex.
No.
I don't think so.
If that were true, I'd know about it.
After all, I'm next in line to be chief.
I'll give my father your best.
- Sorry I'm late.
- Sheriff Hood, we're just getting started.
This is, uh, Special Agent Dean Xavier
with the FBI.
What's the FBI's interest in Kai Proctor?
I coordinate with the DEA
and the Philadelphia P.D. on narcotics.
Every few years,
Proctor's name comes across my desk...
but we can never tie him to anything.
Now we've got him for murder.
Are you still going forward
with the grand jury?
I am.
Can't say the case
hasn't been compromised...
but we've still got the victim's hand
and Webber's cell phone.
Your case was circumstantial at best.
Even with the eyewitness.
Now that you've lost him...
The goddamn wall
was brought down with C4.
Please,
you couldn't have done any better.
I wouldn't have been
there to begin with.
A roadside motel? Seriously?
Hey, did you come here
to piss on my department?
I apologize, Deputy Lotus.
I didn't mean to imply
that you were at fault here.
Yeah? Well, I was the only one there.
And that's why I'm here now.
Look, I'm sure you're all
very good at your jobs.
Sheriff,
you've been here less than a month,
you've got Proctor
by the short hairs.
Frankly, the Bureau
should steal a page from your book.
Is that why you're here?
To steal a page?
Your lost witness
raised some eyebrows in my office.
This is bullshit.
I've been sent here to monitor the
situation until the grand jury is in.
You want to keep an eye on things,
that's your business.
Just do it at a safe distance.
From what I hear about you,
that'd have to be pretty damn far.
We're all on the same side here, right?
- That it?
- Ahem.
Look, this doesn't have to be a thing.
Yeah, well, it is to me.
Don't worry, Gordon.
It's not.
You believe this shit?
Don't worry about Xavier.
He'll be gone in a few days.
- Grand jury won't take long.
- Hey.
You think I fucked up here?
I think we fucked up.
And by we, you mean me, right?
No, we should've had Webber
on lockdown at the Cadi.
- That's on me.
- So let's go find him.
Whoever took out that wall
didn't do it to leave Webber alive.
So, what, we do nothing?
You heard Hopewell. The physical
evidence is enough. We're okay.
Proctor's out on bail, our witness is gone,
we're not okay.
Webber got taken from me.
You got rolled, Brock.
It happens. Shake it off.
That the sum total
of your reaction to this?
It is.
- Shit happens, huh?
- Yup.
Hello, Mr. Bates.
How you doing there, Mrs. Hopewell?
- How's the cider this year?
- Oh, it's got some kick to it.
- Yeah?
- Mm.
- Mm. That's pretty good.
- Heh.
Mom, Max wants a buggy ride.
- Oh, I don't know.
- Come on, it's a fair.
I'll take him. It'll be fine.
- You have your inhaler?
- I left it in the car.
Okay, you guys go and have fun.
I'll grab it and catch up with you.
Okay. Cool. Come on, buddy.
Nice kids.
- Mr. Bates.
- Call me Sugar.
Okay, I'll call you Sugar.
Listen, Sugar, about the other night.
You got nothing to worry about.
I have plenty to worry about.
Yeah, well, I suppose you do.
But what I'm saying is...
you ain't got nothing
to worry about with me.
Thank you.
No.
On the house.
Aw, she got some treats for us.
Hey, is that our friendly
neighborhood MILF?
Wait a minute, baby.
Where you going?
- Excuse me.
- Mm-mm.
You want to smoke some weed with us,
honey?
Get out of my way.
- You're making a mistake.
- Yeah?
She put you down, man.
Let go of me!
- Get her over there.
- Fuck you!
No, fuck you.
- Get away. Unh.
- Come on, girl.
You don't want to do this.
Back the fuck off.
- Man, this bitch is in shape.
- Fuck you!
I guess you picked
the wrong street to go down.
Don't fucking move, bitch.
What's going on here?
Mind your business, old man.
What say we let this lady join her children
and I'll buy you all some cider?
I asked you once nicely to get the fuck...
- Leave him alone.
- Shut your mouth, bitch.
All right, let her go now.
Heh. That's it, man.
All right. All right. No.
No, no, no. I don't want no trouble now.
So we got ourselves a fighter.
Are you any good?
In my day.
My companion Schroeder here boxes.
What do you say?
Come on. Get them up, old man.
Get them up, motherfucker.
All right, look...
Impressive, old man.
What do you say we just, uh, let her go...
and we call it a day? We call it a day.
Sugar!
Get back over here.
Lie still, bitch.
I'm not finished with her yet.
- Tally craves some intimacy.
- Ow!
You sick fuck.
Shh.
- Relax, baby.
- I said get the fuck off of me!
That man needs an ambulance.
We all have needs, baby.
I'm gonna fucking kill you.
Yeah? Maybe later, baby.
But right now, this ass is mine.
Police! Drop the gun!
I said drop the gun.
You okay?
- Hey, is she okay?
- I'm fine.
I'm fine.
Jesus. You look like shit.
Yeah, I've been hit worse.
Look, uh, call Oakey, will you?
The number's on the back of the register.
He can look after The Forge
till I get back.
Sure. Okay.
Hey, what happened?
He tried to...
He had a gun...
and she showed up
before I could take him out.
- One guy?
- No.
There was like four of them. Five.
Sugar took out two
before this other guy showed up.
Mom!
Yeah. Hey.
- Are you okay?
- Yeah, I'm okay.
He had a gun. He was on top of her.
No, it's all right. It's fine.
It was him or you. You're good.
Oh, my God. Are you all right?
It's just... He didn't drop it.
He was assaulting a woman.
He was armed. You did your job.
Hey, none of us here would have
done it any differently, all right?
Yeah, get her out of here.
Come on.
I did a quick canvass,
in case you were wondering.
They, uh, all cleared out
pretty quickly after it all went down.
- All right. We know them?
- Yeah, they've been through before.
Itinerant, town to town.
You know, looking to party.
We book one or two
of them from time to time...
on a D and D,
they spend a night in the tank.
But nothing like this before.
- How do I find them?
- I or we?
We can put out an APB,
but by the time we get a hit...
they could be all the way to Pittsburgh
or out of the state, so...
Let me know if you get anything back.
Will do.
Fuck Tally.
He decided to go for the broad
and he got burned.
- Now they'll be looking for our asses.
- Yup.
That woman and the boxer guy,
they can finger us.
- Oh, bullshit.
- I'm with Biggs. We need to get gone.
We need to fucking roll.
Listen to you guys.
We took an oath, man.
- What are you talking about?
- Hey, fuck Tally.
Will you shut the fuck up?
Just shut the fuck up.
Tally went down for it
and now they're gonna be looking for us?
Maybe so. But Tally was our brother.
He wore the ring.
And all we have is the road and each other.
- That's it. That is fucking it, right?
- He's right.
So nobody is going anywhere
until our brother is avenged.
Look, Tally is dead...
and they're having
their little festival?
No.
I don't think so.
- To Tally.
- Tally.
- Hey.
How you doing?
You know, just trying to
get this report done.
You shoot one guy,
they want you to write a book about it.
Tell me about it.
I've never killed anyone before.
He had a gun pointed at you.
I know. I know.
Look, killing someone
shouldn't be easy.
But don't let that
make you doubt what you did.
You won't forget the guy you killed.
That's yours.
But don't forget the
woman you saved either.
It's not just that.
There's something else.
It's like the way she was fighting him.
And then we found
his gun's clip ejected.
I don't know. It's like...
It was like she...
I got to head out on patrol with Emmett.
Why don't you stay around here today?
Let things settle.
Sounds good.
Fuck!
- What happened?
- A flat.
I only saw one of them.
Any idea where they might be?
No. But I'll start looking.
- Yeah.
- Okay, I'm coming with.
No, that's not a good idea.
I'm the only real native here and I know
this county better than either of you.
Hey. I'll join Brock at the festival.
Stay in touch.
Hood, look out!
Hey, you okay?
(Hey. He)'
Ladies and gentlemen.
- Please settle down.
- We'll settle down when you tell us...
what you're going to do
to protect this town.
Yeah!
Everybody's gonna have
a chance to be heard.
They trashed my fruit stand.
Who's gonna pay for that?
They haven't been arrested.
What if they come back?
You need to cancel the festival.
There's no need to cancel the festival.
My office is going to be
processing any and all...
reasonable claims of property loss.
- Look...
- Ladies. Ladies, gentlemen.
If I may.
What are you doing here, Proctor?
You know you're out on bail.
And innocent until proven guilty.
Which is a good thing, uh I must admit...
considering how often
our young mayor here has me arrested.
You all know me.
And whatever you might think of me...
you know that I look out for this town.
My own business was victimized today
by those lowlifes.
It's damn hard to sell prime rib
with tire tracks on it.
But you know I'm gonna try.
The Spirit Festival is our
hallowed tradition...
stalled by our Native American brethren...
over 100 years ago.
It now belongs to all of us.
And I'll be damned if a few vagrants...
are gonna ruin our cherished event.
- Yeah!
- So I'll be at the festival.
I'll be at the festival tomorrow barbecuing
as much free meat as you all can eat.
And... And I can assure you that my own
security personnel will be on hand as well.
No, he's talking about hired
thugs with criminal records.
I understand that Betsy Denton...
was dragged behind a motorcycle.
That her jaw is broken in three places.
You ask me, we could have used
a few thugs out there today.
Huh?
Settle down.
If you don't settle down,
I'm gonna have to clear the room.
We've already taken one of these guys down.
If they come back, we'll be ready for them.
Yeah, you and what army?
Two deputies and the cheerleader?
- What's your name?
- George Gutterson.
Yeah, well, George,
why don't you shut your mouth?
The festival stays on.
What happened today will not happen again.
They have you outnumbered.
It's true.
Well, I'll tell you what, Mr. Proctor...
I won't tell you how
to slit a cow's throat...
you don't tell me
how to police this town.
Fair enough.
The festival stays on.
- I'll be at the Cadi.
- Yeah.
Emmett, follow her home.
For Christ's sake, boss.
I'm an armed deputy.
Yeah, good point.
Emmett, follow her home.
- Sheriff Hood.
- Yeah?
Oh, hey.
Sheriff Hood...
I attacked a man in town today.
One of the bikers, with this.
Give it to him.
You stabbed one of them?
I'm ready to face the legal
consequences of my actions.
What, are you serious?
She was defending herself.
No, that is not for us to decide.
You are the lawman.
Okay, well, consider it decided.
No, you keep that.
Come.
- Hey.
You checking up on me?
Nope, I came to get you.
You shouldn't stay here.
Are you kidding me?
What, do I have a curfew now too?
No.
Well, this is my house and I'm not leaving.
Well, I guess I'm staying too, then.
When the time comes for you to spend
the night, it won't be to protect me.
You can let yourself out now, boss.
I'll have the deputies
pass by throughout the night.
You got a deputy right here.
Okay.
I guess you could give me
a quick call before you turn in.
I'll be up.
Sure.
Nurse Davis to Pharmacology.
Hey.
How you feeling?
I feel like I've been hit in the
back of the head with a damn stick.
I'm gonna fucking find them.
No, no. Let it go, man.
Guys like us, we get hit sometimes.
You go trying to settle accounts
for every cheap shot...
you'll never get any sleep.
What, do you have a speech for everything?
I'm a bartender.
Wisdom is an occupational hazard.
Well, I'll let you get some rest.
Hey.
I don't suppose you're
gonna take my advice.
That would make us both wise.
Where's the fun in that?
Yeah. Heh.
Hey.
That's a good look for you.
I want my knife back.
Hey.
You bastards!
Motherfuckers!
No!
God damn it!
Fuck you.
Fuck you!
You motherfuckers!
Fucking kill you!
So those elders...
your father...
they wanted me to arrest you.
I wish you had.
Now I have to openly repent
or I'll be shunned.
For defending yourself?
The knife was kind of my last straw.
"Turn the other cheek and do not resist him
who is evil, sayeth the Lord."
My people don't believe in violence.
What about you?
What do you believe?
Well, I don't know much about religion...
but this right here
doesn't feel like repentance.
It's not a joke.
Fuck.
Hey, hey.
I'm sorry.
It's like I'm trying to be two people.
I've been there.
Yeah?
So there's nothing she could've done.
Fire Department's got it under control.
She's over there.
You okay?
What time is it?
Um, a little after 1.
Today's my birthday.
I was born in that house.
You're staying with Emmett
and Meg until this is over.
Emmett.
Take her home. She's staying with you.
Hey.
I heard about your deputy's house.
What are you gonna do about it?
What's your plan?
Well, what's it to you?
Where'd you find him?
One of my guys spotted him
at a liquor store in Danville.
He tell you where they're holed up?
He's been extremely forthcoming.
Hmm.
So what now?
You arrest these guys,
they'll make bail, stick around.
I'm not planning on arresting them.
What's in it for you?
You motherfucker!
And where am I dumping these?
They got warrants in Cleveland.
- You sure they're alive?
- They're sleeping it off.
Oh, as requested, Officer Paul Hibbert.
Oh, no, it was easy. Podunk cage like that,
bitch, took me five minutes.
Uh, thanks.
I am legit worried about you,
motherfucker.
- Carrie?
- Hey, Marjorie.
Honey, I heard about what happened.
- How are you holding up?
- I'm fine.
- Yeah?
- Mm-hm.
I'd hoped you would
have called me by now.
I really don't think you
should underestimate
the trauma that
you've been through.
I really recommend
that you get some counseling or...
I appreciate that, Marjorie.
I'll certainly consider it.
Yeah, no, I just mean
with everything else you're going through.
Everything else?
Well...
I mean, I heard that Deva's
having a little bit of trouble in school.
- Skipping classes and whatnot.
- Where'd you hear that?
Oh, no, sweetie, please don't be upset.
I mean, really, kids this age,
they live to test us, right?
My point is that these
are the years as moms...
we got to be at the top of our game.
So I just don't want you
to sweep this under the rug.
You know, the sooner that the victim
of a violent crime...
- I wasn't the victim.
- No, I know.
He's the one that got carted off
in a body bag with a slug in his chest.
And since you've been so generous with the
friendly advice, here's some for you:
If I hear that you and your PTA twats
have been talking shit about my daughter...
there will be more
than enough trauma to go around.
Enjoy the fair, Marjorie.
- Were you just hearing them?
- Put it on.
No, no, no.
You're not putting that on me.
She's a great kid.
Yes, she is.
So walk me through this.
How do a frozen hand
and a bagged cell phone...
disappear from your evidence locker?
Everything was here
when I checked out last night.
I'm told there was an authorized entry...
at 7:03 this morning.
A security clearance card was used...
by Officer Paul Hibbert.
That's right.
- Who is that?
- I have no idea.
He's in our system as an evidence officer
with a clearance card for this room...
but I'm telling you,
nobody by that name has ever worked here.
And I've been the chief property clerk
for going on 13 years.
Well, then you would know.
Hello, sir. This is Special Agent Xavier.
Yup, gone.
It's no surprise, really.
With the systems they got here,
all it took was a routine hack...
and somebody with the balls
to walk in and take it.
Well, there's something in Banshee
that stinks worse than the cows.
With your permission, I'd like to stick
around for a bit and follow the stench.
Yes, sir.
I'll keep you posted.