Mama?
No, no, no. Mama!
No.
Don't let them do this.
Mama, please! Please, Mama, please!
Don't do this, Father.
You did this.
Daddy!
You did this!
Mama!
Mama, don't do this to me!
Mama.
Please.
Don't go.
Please don't.
- Ana.
- Don't.
We can leave.
Ana, we... We can go anywhere.
This is my anywhere.
Carrie Hopewell is not real.
She's a hiding place.
You have to let me go.
There's nothing in this world that
makes sense if there's no you and me.
Nothing.
You know that, the same way I do.
You're still in there. I know you are.
The whole time I was in prison,
you know what kept me alive?
You, not Carrie Hopewell.
- Ana, your Ana, is dead.
- No.
What we had back then, that's dead.
- That's what's not real.
- No.
- This is what's real.
- You're wrong!
Things change.
I changed.
I know how much you loved me.
I loved you, but I don't anymore.
- I'm not Ana anymore.
- Yes, you are!
You were last night and
I fucking know that!
Last night?
You and I never got a chance
to say goodbye.
That's what last night was, it was goodbye.
And now you have to move on.
What, just like that?
I went to prison for you.
I know. It's not fair.
I'm sorry, but I have a family to protect.
It's my family!
I knew she was mine
the first moment I saw her.
Say it.
She's yours.
She is.
She's yours. I'm sorry.
What did you tell Gordon?
Well, he must have known she wasn't his.
I told him you were dead.
- Perfect.
- Hey.
I was broke and I was pregnant
and I was all alone.
I couldn't fence the diamonds.
If they hit the street,
Rabbit would have been all over me.
Job had given me Carrie,
but I had to find a safe place to stop.
And Gordon,
he just got out of the Marines...
and I was a waitress,
he always came to my restaurant.
I don't wanna hear this shit.
I had to find a safe
home for your daughter!
I didn't fall for him.
I was waiting for you.
Deva came, this beautiful little girl.
My little girl.
He raised her like his own.
She's not his.
She's mine.
It's not about you and me anymore.
How many lives are you willing to destroy
to take back yours?
Look...
do you honestly think Deva
would be better off with you?
I think she deserves to know the truth.
Look at you.
Look at me.
The last thing any of
us needs is the truth.
You say you love me.
If that's true...
the best thing you could do is leave
and forget about Deva and me.
If I don't?
Then what?
You've already turned me into Rabbit.
If you don't, I'll kill you myself.
Stop following me, damn it. You can't...
Hello, Ana.
Olek.
Your father would like to see you.
But he did say
I could kill you if you became a problem.
Are you going to be a problem?
No.
You look good, Ana.
- He has missed you terribly.
- He's insane.
He loves his daughter.
Olek, you can't bring me to him.
- Please.
- We'll take my car.
- Get in.
- I'm not getting in there.
- Olek...
- Yes, you are.
Hey, Olek.
You can stay here as long as you like.
Thank you.
I really didn't have anywhere else to go.
I'd have been offended
if you went anywhere else.
I was just 19 when I left.
These men, thugs, really...
were preying on our farmers'
produce wagons.
They wanted us to pay protection money.
But anyway, I got tired of turning the
other cheek, so one day, I didn't.
I took three of them apart
with an old ball-peen hammer.
You should have seen the looks on their
faces when this Amish kid came at them.
Not what they expected.
But the elders condemned my actions...
wanted me to show contrition
for defending them.
I guess I wasn't built for contrition.
Whatever happens,
you'll always have a home here.
Thank you.
Why don't you get yourself settled?
I'll leave you some lunch downstairs.
I've got to run out for a few hours.
When I come back,
we can talk all this through.
- Okay?
- Okay.
He's going to torture you.
You will beg to be killed.
Why don't we, uh,
skip all the ominous threats
and macho bullshit,
stick to the facts?
Good.
- Is Rabbit here?
- No, but he's coming.
Well, he hasn't made any calls today.
No texts, nothing.
He knows where I am.
He gave you everything...
and you pissed all over him.
He's a sadistic fuck and a murderer.
He loved you. We all did.
I was his prisoner and you
were his goddamn warden.
Okay, English, please.
Fuck you!
That's better, thanks.
Great.
Now look what you've done.
What the fuck are you hiding?
Bullshit!
I asked you to leave. I begged you.
He's gonna kill all of us.
- Not if I kill him first.
- Oh, please.
Think about it.
Olek, he put you in the trunk.
He didn't kill you.
He was here to bring you back.
Rabbit must want you before me.
Olek hasn't checked in yet.
- That buys us some time.
- Okay. Time for what?
- We go to New York, we take him out.
- Jesus Christ.
- It's the last thing he's going to expect.
- It's suicide.
- He's gonna be waiting for us.
- So is staying here, Ana.
Oh, my God, my babies, Gordon...
- I've put them all in danger.
- You have.
We were safe until you got here.
How many other mothers
carry guns in their purse?
Or fake license plates in their car?
You knew this day was coming.
You've known it
since the day you landed here.
And every one of those days
you lied to your family, not me.
Carrie Hopewell was never built to last.
You've been on borrowed time
since you got here and you know it.
I love my family.
I'll die to keep them safe.
I won't let anything happen.
I promise.
This room smells of sex.
I wonder...
is it still adultery
if your marriage is a lie?
- Thank you.
- You're welcome.
Always sneaking around, you two.
Even back then,
always this forbidden love...
like Shakespeare.
- So romantic.
- We're getting off topic.
I wonder, how do you think he knew?
What?
How did he find out? Rabbit.
You were so careful all the time.
The way you met in his apartment...
the hours you kept,
the special phones you had.
Oh, yeah, I knew about the phones.
You're the one who told him.
Yes.
You were like a brother to me.
And he is like a father to me.
I loved you.
You betrayed us.
Us?
What are you talking about?
How did I betray you?
Who's here?
- Who's here?
- Uh-oh.
- Who is it?
- Shit.
Uh, it's no one. It's no one.
I'll take care of it.
Keep an eye on him, all right?
- Hey.
- Hey. I was just coming to see you.
Yeah, listen, um,
I'm kind of busy right now.
- Can we do this later?
- I really need to talk to you.
Okay, look,
you just can't be here right now.
I've been hearing that a lot today.
Aw, shit.
- I'll give you a lift. Come on.
- To where?
I know it may not seem this way,
but your father loves you very deeply.
He will still kill you, I think.
But this is what love does, right?
It kills us.
- It's gonna kill you.
- What?
You think I don't remember
how you used to look at me?
How you would hug and kiss me
every time you saw me?
That's bullshit.
That's why you told Rabbit about us.
Because you thought it would
clear the field for you.
And that's why you came here alone.
Because you wanted to see me alone.
That's insane.
You're crazy.
Olek, it's okay.
It is.
I know you love me.
I would have been good to you.
You bastard.
- I should kill you right here.
- Kill me.
Help me.
I can't.
You should run.
I've been running my whole life.
You should run now.
You don't belong here.
How is he?
This is a sacred ritual.
It's not for outsiders.
I just want to say goodbye.
Please?
He was a great man...
and a good friend.
I know you will continue his work.
Goodbye, Mr. Proctor.
Fuck.
You've been training.
You knew you would have to
face me one day.
Sure, make it all about you.
Your punches are sharp.
You have speed and your balance is good,
but you're still a woman.
So it's not dangerous, not really.
It's just cute.
Cute enough for you?
Why can't we talk at your place?
No, that's... That's, uh, not a good idea.
What, are you married?
No, no. It's, um...
This is not a good time to be around me.
It was a good time
when you were fucking me.
You, uh... You got enough money?
I'm not a whore.
No, no, no. No. Hey, hey, hey.
Oh!
What the hell is wrong with you?
Take the boy and go.
No.
Stay here.
You should hear this.
It's your family too.
Do you know who I am?
I'm your uncle.
Your mother's my sister,
just like Rebecca's yours.
Your mother treats me like trash,
like a stranger.
- Kai!
- Oh, shut up, Miriam.
You haven't spoken my name in 20 years.
There's no reason to start now.
You asked me to speak to her,
and then you shunned her before I could.
When we spoke, I did not know
the full extent of her transgression.
What kind of father turns his back on his
daughter at the time she most needs him?
- Our church is very clear...
- Fuck your goddamn church!
Kai.
Suddenly, everyone remembers my name.
This is not your business.
- Take the girl back.
- She is not a girl.
She is a woman.
And we did not reject her.
You should know as well as anyone
that it was she who rejected our ways...
just as you did.
Yeah.
And now in the absence
of true contrition...
you'll toss her out like garbage.
What about your own contrition?
Who calls you to account
for these inquisitions of yours?
What do you feel when you see me?
Hmm?
Does it even hurt you at all?
My son is dead.
And I finished mourning him years ago.
You are a criminal and a trespasser.
I insist you leave our land at once.
Or what?
Hmm? Or what?
Be careful, Father.
I have swallowed your insults for years...
but don't mistake
my tolerance for weakness.
You all live here
because I choose to allow it.
Not God. It's me, your dead son!
I allow it!
And if I decide I don't
want you here anymore...
there's no God that'll be able
to protect you from me.
I'll show you all what it feels like
to be cast out.
Fuck.
Come on, Anastasia.
You were always such a stubborn girl.
You can't be finished yet.
Sheriff.
I was just coming to see you.
- Listen, I gotta go.
- I was hoping that we could talk.
About what?
My superiors are
starting to take an interest.
I just got word there's
going to be a formal
investigation into
yesterday's shooting.
What, are you fucking kidding me?
They were career criminals.
They're murderers.
That's what you get for making news
during an election year.
Politicians, they love their hearings.
But me, I'm like you.
- See, I like results.
- I really do have to go.
I thought we might combine resources
to figure out what happened...
to that evidence against Proctor.
How it found its way out of a locked room.
- Because that was a tough...
- Okay, listen.
Call Alma, set something up, okay?
- I can't do this right now.
- No, we're gonna talk right now.
I'm starting to wonder about you.
I keep coming up against these walls
everywhere I go...
but I can feel them
starting to crumble.
Something tells me
it's gonna be worth it...
to stick around and watch
them all come tumbling down.
Nola.
Hi, Mom.
- When did you get back?
- Just now.
There's still time. You should go to him.
I didn't come here for him, brother.
- Well, he'd be glad to know you're here.
- Which is why I'm not gonna stay.
I'll be crashing at your place.
Let me know when he's dead.
You look just like her.
- What?
- Your mother.
You have her face.
Almost exactly.
I was only a boy when she died...
but I remember her very well.
She was a beautiful woman.
So sad you never got to meet her.
He never got over her death.
When a woman dies in childbirth...
It wasn't my fault.
You were all he had left.
But you were also the
thing that killed her.
Maybe he made mistakes...
but everything he
did, he did out of love.
- It breaks my heart to hit you.
- Then stop.
I can't do it anymore.
Olek, he's gonna kill me.
- He's gonna kill me.
- No.
He will kill you and your family.
You betrayed your family.
You don't deserve to have another one.
You're right...
I did love you.
But there are things in
life bigger than love.
You fight with passion.
Your father would have
been proud to see it.
Don't worry, I will tell him all about it.
Daddy.
Hey.
Hey, I thought that you and Max
were over at the Frears' pool.
Yeah, I got bored.
Max is fine. He's playing with Sammy.
Dad, what is going on?
Well, that...
That's not an easy question to answer.
Did you and Mom have a fight?
No, no, no, baby.
No, nothing like that.
Jesus, you're smoking pot?
Yes, I am.
You know, sometimes when
the pain in my shoulder gets bad...
the only thing that works
is a little bit of really good weed.
It's not something that would help me
get reelected so I'm careful about it.
Your Iraq wound?
Yeah.
Hey.
Here's the thing.
I don't want you to lie to me...
but I'm not really dying
for you to tell me the truth either.
Just...
Just promise me
that everything's gonna be all right.
Shh, shh, shh.
Everything's gonna be all right.
Mm.
What does that mean?
It means "With God's help"
Mm-hm.
"we will drink together again."
When will you learn to speak Ukrainian? Eh?
I'll speak Ukrainian when you sing
"The Star-Spangled Banner."
- Ooh.
- I can sing "The Star-Spangled Banner."
- Listen to this. Listen.
- Do it.
Oh, beautiful America
God bless thee, America
- "God Bless America."
- That's fucking, um...
That's "America the Beautiful."
- You're not trying to speak Ukrainian.
- Listen. America.
A toast.
- Hey.
Hey!
What does "budmo" mean anyway?
It means:
"We shall live forever."
I'll drink to that.
Get out.
- Get dressed and get out.
- Why are you doing this?
Get out.
Stop it. You're hurting me!
I'm hurting you? You fucking whore.
- I opened my house to you. I took you in.
- No. Why are you doing this?
You're not here two hours and you're
already out there fucking someone.
That's not what happened.
- Don't lie to me.
- I'm not lying.
- I'm not lying!
Uncle Kai, wait. Please.
I'm sorry.
I lost my home today.
I miss my family.
I know I don't
belong there anymore, but still...
I don't know where I belong anymore.
I know you know how that felt.
I do.
And there's a part of you
that will never stop feeling like that.
The sheriff...
You can have nothing to do with him.
He's no one to me.
I'm so sorry.
I just... I've never been on my own before.
You're not on your own.
Hello, Anastasia.
I've missed you.
Leave me alone.
You are alone.
You have been alone
ever since you betrayed me.
And now you have betrayed
your husband, your children.
Tell me, is there anyone in your life
you have not betrayed?
No, that's not true. That's not...
My sweet, lost daughter.
You have been lying for so long...
you have no idea what truth is anymore.
You've always been such a stubborn child...
so certain you knew best.
Yes?
And look at you now:
broken, bleeding, finished.
No.
Even now you fight...
when the fight is already lost.
My poor, broken Anastasia.
- My name is Carrie
- No!
Olek.
Ana.
Hey.
Come on, Ana, pick up.
Goddamn it.
Ana!
Ana.
Ana. Ana, baby.
Open your eyes.
No, no, no, no.
Baby. Come on. Come on.
Fuck. Jesus. Ana, open your eyes.
Ana. Oh, Jesus Christ,
don't you fucking do this to me.
No. You come back to me now.
You come back.
Ana. Open your eyes. Come on.
Yes.
Ana, Ana.
- Ana.
- It's Carrie.
You're okay. You're okay.
Come on. Come on.
Oh, Jesus.
Okay, okay.
Ana!
Just hold on, baby.
We shall live forever.