Afraid you'Il fall in love?
Something like that.
WelI, I can see you have good taste.
This is the one.
1 962 Coupe de Ville.
Does everything but make breakfast.
What are you in now?
I had a Dodge.
Those are wonderful
if you want to get somewhere.
This is for when you've already arrived.
Is that right?
Of course, someone like you,
you don't need to see yourself in a Cadillac.
You're walking about in one every day.
How'd you like your car to look like that?
Look at you.
I bet you'd be as comfortable in one of these
as you would in your own skin.
Wayne Kirkby. Do you have a card?
Sterling Cooper.
Did Roger Sterling send you?
Yes.
Let me go and get the keys, Mr. Draper.
Don't you want to hold onto these?
I don't know. The '49 rattled.
This is the 1 950 model.
It's quite different under the hood.
Don't talk to me.
Talk to him. It's his money.
I'm just here to make sure
you don't shake his hand
and take his fingers.
Charlie, this car is two years old
with only 25,000 miles on it.
It's what you want.
This must be Mrs. Wheatley.
No.
Why don't you sit in it again?
You two talk.
May l help you, ma'am?
Are you Donald Draper?
Yes, I am.
If it's about my circular,
many of the models are gone,
but l'm sure we can find you something.
I'm not here to buy a car.
You're a hard man to find.
Excuse me?
You're not Don Draper.
Mr. Draper?
Everything okay?
Yes.
Let me take you for a ride.
No.
Thank you.
I don't hear that a lot.
Well.
Have a good day.
Good afternoon, Miss Siegal.
Mr. Sterling.
Is your boss in?
No, but he will be.
Where'd you get that sweater?
l want to make sure
my daughter never buys it.
Klein's.
I doubt your daughter shops there.
Union Square, right?
Is that where you live?
I've told you, all you have to do
is look at my file.
That's cheating.
How was your lunch, Mr. Draper?
Good.
Mr. Sterling's here to see you.
Get Mr. Phillips.
Mr. Draper, Mrs. Barrett called again.
Did she leave a message?
No.
ShalI I tell Mr. Phillips you returned?
Yes.
I'll bet she suffers in silence out there,
hoping you'll notice her.
I don't think she cries at night
from lack of attention.
Wait till she finds out about your Cadillac.
She'll be waiting naked
right in front of this window.
Now you're thinking about her.
Didn't you go see Wayne?
I'm going to eliminate
your objections right away.
First of all, you can afford it.
Do you know how invigorating it is
to go in and write a check for $6,500
and not care?
Secondly,
not to get too deep
before the cocktail hour,
but do I need to remind you
of the finite nature of life?
Mr. Phillips.
Send him in.
Like the song says, enjoy yourself.
It's later than you think.
Martinson Coffee.
Martinson's.
They changed it.
Change it back.
Jim Van Dyke told the people at Grey
they're under review.
So Grey must be scrambling.
It's hard for them to do a lot of new work.
They just redesigned labels,
displays, and dropped the S,
but they have some kids
working on print and TV.
Are they better than our kids?
We'll find out.
WelI, you're welcome.
I spent Saturday birding with that man,
and by birding l mean sitting on a stump
with a pair of binoculars, whispering.
Did you see anything unusual?
A refrigerator floating in a pond.
Mr. Smith and Mr. Smith are here.
Just a minute.
Did you let them stay up late?
- I'd love to hear this.
- l don't know.
If l fill you full of any more
confidence, you'll burst.
You don't dance,
or you don't dance with me?
Leave her alone. Let's go.
Heard you're gonna knock 'em dead.
Look, Don, it's pretty clear
why we're here.
You want to know
how our generation feels.
Okay.
So, I get this letter
from my friend back in Michigan.
He's still in school, man,
and it's got this, I don't know,
60-page rant in it.
So dig it.
"We would replace power
"rooted in possession,
privilege, or circumstance
"by power and uniqueness
"rooted in Iove, reflectiveness,
reason, and creativity."
That's a beautiful sentiment.
Does your friend know
what you do for a living?
Yeah, there was a shitty note with it,
but this whole concept is deep.
"Students for a Democratic Society."
That's a hell of a focus group.
It's how our generation feels.
It is what it is.
It's idealistic.
That's nice.
Your generation wants to talk
about that newly designed can
and the premium beans,
but we don't want to be told
what we should do
or how we should act.
We just want to be.
You just want to be
selling Martinson's Coffee?
Just listen to this.
So, the thought is,
every maternity ward will get a visit
from a registered nurse
with a doll and a crate of Pampers,
and she will extol their virtues,
which are many.
What did Draper say?
He liked it,
but he said the same thing
he keeps saying.
I can't get them to lower the price.
Do you know the years of R&D
P&G put into this?
Besides, they're worth it.
No boiIing, no diaper service,
no plastic pants.
And the greatest benefit of all,
you can throw them away.
1 0 cents apiece,
you kind of think you should reuse them.
Mr. Draper went over these ideas
and had thoughts he would
like you all to discuss.
WelI, it's 5:00. Are we going out?
I don't know, sweetheart.
Maybe.
I'll take those papers.
Good night, Miss Olson.
Jane, would you mind
helping us clean this up?
I'm meeting with Cooper tomorrow.
He said he wants to see me and only me.
Isn't that from West Side Story?
You know he's going
to ask you about the picture.
What picture?
Some new painting.
He calls people in to see what they think.
No, I think we're going to discuss
expanding the television department.
I heard it cost $1 0,000.
How does everybody know about this?
Are you making it up?
Last year, Harry went up to the roof
looking for cosmonauts.
Has anyone seen it?
Dale.
It's abstract expressionist.
What the hell does that mean?
Thank you all for ruining this.
You're the one who walked
to the opposite end of the office
to tell us you had a meeting.
Well, if you're lucky,
you'Il have a meeting.
And I'm not going to telI you anything
about the damn picture.
Why don't you just go look at it?
I'm sorry, Jane,
but you just don't walk
into his office like that.
But he's gone for the day.
That doesn't matter.
Miss Blankenship won't mind .
I'm going to go up and see it.
I'll go anywhere you go.
WelI, she's gone.
What are you doing?
It's open.
Are you suicidal? Let's go.
I can't believe you all.
Take off your shoes.
I feel like we're skinny dipping.
Call me from jail.
You're gonna keep a lookout?
Just don't touch anything.
It's a Rothko.
Why the hell didn't Dale say that?
$1 0,000.
So it's smudgy squares?
That's interesting.
Two possibilities--
either Cooper loves it,
and you have to love it,
like in an "Emperor's New Clothes" situation,
or he thinks it's a joke
and you'll look like a fool
if you pretend to dig it.
People like him pretend
they understand this.
Maybe he has a brochure in here,
something that explains it.
I don't think it's supposed to be explained .
I'm an artist, okay?
It must mean something.
Maybe it doesn't.
Maybe you're just supposed
to experience it.
Because when you look at it,
you do feel something, right?
It's like looking into something very deep.
You could fall in.
That's true.
Did someone tell you that?
How could someone tell you that?
This is pointless. Let's go.
I'm ready.
Harry actually took the stairs.
We could have stolen it, couldn't we?
Who are you?
I was thinking I could write
a great short story about this--
you know, "The Day We Looked
at the Painting."
I'm a writer.
I thought you were an accountant.
Accounts.
I've been published.
The Atlantic Monthly, Parabolas.
That's right.
The story about the maple tree.
It was beautiful and sad.
Really? You read it?
Everybody read it.
People were jealous.
Where are you headed?
Are you hungry?
No. Good night.
So you're stilI working here.
You missed something,
my yellow-bellied friend.
Jane Siegal is a genuine thrill.
Breaking and entering.
I don't care about Jane.
Tell me about Coop's painting.
What about Mr. Cooper's painting?
Enjoy that.
Can l get another coffee here, please?
I'll tell you what I heard.
You, Mr. Cosgrove, and Jane
were in Mr. Cooper's office
looking at his painting.
Anything you'd like to correct?
Mind your own business.
I had nothing to do with it.
Thank you.
Nothing happened.
Look, if Kurt says we don't need artwork,
we don't need artwork.
Is that what Kurt said?
Is that what you said?
Don has his signature.
It's nice down here.
Hey.
Kenneth.
3:00, and he doesn't talk in the meeting.
How about last night?
Quite an adventure.
Listen, I was thinking about
what you said about my story,
about it being sad and beautiful?
You're not Iike everyone else around here.
I don't know if that's true.
Okay. Here goes.
Would you mind taking a look at this?
Are you kidding?
I don't want you to pull any punches.
Unless you hate it,
in which case, don't tell me.
I'm kind of fragile.
I'd be honored.
WelI, great, then.
Take your time.
Ken.
Yeah.
You know, I can probably
read it by Sunday,
and you can come over for dinner,
you know, with Kitty and I .
I know you need a home-cooked meal.
You have plans?
No.
Are you sure it's okay?
You want me to give this back?
Young people do not drink coffee,
and that can become a lifetime habit.
Now, we're aware
that unsuccessful attempts
have been made--
puppets and so forth--
to capture the attention of youth.
That's why we're here.
There's an old saying.
When one is in Indian country,
one needs a man who knows Indians.
Mr. Smith?
So.
Where do we start?
Joe Martinson.
Old cup of Joe.
They named it after him, right?
That's just ancient history now.
There have been a million ways
that the folks on this avenue
have tried to telI our generation what to do.
Except we don't want to be told what to do.
That's over.
We want to find things for ourselves.
We want to feel.
Okay.
Martinson's is a great coffee.
It's delicious, and it's hot, and it's brown.
That's all you need to say.
We don't need more than that.
Peggy. Sweetheart?
I don't know if I understand this.
It's a jingle, right?
It's a song, and it's a mood,
and it's a feeling.
It's definitely more than a jingle.
What do you think?
It stays with you.
What are the pictures that go with this?
If you sign, we'll tell you.
So Media Purchases.
Starting in March,
I'm looking at column 5,
under Regional Affiliates.
Mr. Crane, focus, please.
We didn't make you head of television
just to shorten your attention span.
I'm sorry, sir.
I was admiring your painting.
The eye is drawn to it.
It's very modern.
Mark Rothko. I've read about him.
And?
What do you think about it?
Nobody has ever asked me that.
Probably because it's none of their business.
Right.
How does it strike you?
Sir, I know nothing about art.
Mr. Crane, you're here because of numbers.
Stick to that.
Don't concern yourseIf with aesthetics.
You'll get a headache.
Of course.
People buy things
to realize their aspirations.
It's the foundation of our business.
But between you and me
and the lamppost,
that thing shouId double
in value by next Christmas.
Where were we?
Column 5 here--
Regional Newspaper Affiliates.
Your hair is turning green.
You have to wear the bathing cap.
It squeezes my head .
Don't leave your wet suit on the floor.
Draper residence.
Is this the belle of the Hudson River Valley?
Who is this?
It's Jimmy Barrett, sweetheart.
Mr. Barrett.
Are you Iooking for Don?
Because he's at the office.
I know exactly what I'm doing.
ABC picked up Grin and Barrett,
my TV show, 39 episodes.
That's wonderful. Congratulations.
We're having a shindig at the Stork Club.
Donnie didn't get back to me,
so I figured if you're anything like my wife,
you book the dance card.
Monday night,
so the celebrities can come.
That sounds like fun,
but celebrities make me shy.
Keep playing that, gorgeous.
It works wonders.
I'll talk to Don about it.
Don't you want to go?
You can't leave me alone
with those people.
Ride the horse in, like Lady Godiva.
I think I should hang up now.
Betty,
it would mean a lot to me
if you were there.
We wiIl try. Have a nice day, Jimmy.
Mr. Phillips.
Right now there's a little boy
running over here from Martinson Coffee
with a check in his hand.
It's done. Congratulations.
Thanks.
You want me to send
for something for you?
No, but don't let me
dampen your spirits.
Unfurl the sails, please.
That was good advance work.
That's my job.
Maybe we'll get a shot at LifeSavers.
Mr. Cooper wants to speak with you.
We'll be right there.
He just asked for you, Mr. Draper.
Thanks again.
CongratuIations, Don.
Sit with us.
Thank you.
But I didn't do it alone.
Fascinating.
Jim Van Dyke of Martinson Coffee
was thoroughly impressed.
He's inviting you to join the board
of the Museum of Early American Folk Arts.
That's nice.
What is it?
Doesn't exist yet.
But I've seen the opening exhibit.
Whirligigs.
Do they need a campaign?
No. Philanthropy is the gateway to power.
If you say so.
We need you to continue
your excellence in advertising,
but also to start treating this
like part of a bigger business,
which it is.
I will.
Do you understand what this means?
You're going to be wearing
your tuxedo a lot more.
It's time for the horse to catch the carrot.
Roger, would you mind?
Would you agree that l know
a little bit about you?
A little.
There are few people who get to decide
what will happen in our world .
You have been invited to join them.
Pull back the curtain
and take your seat.
You're back.
I had a feeling.
You want to take it for a drive?
Wayne, I would like to buy this car.
Jane, would you come with me, pIease?
Is something wrong?
Just tell me.
You want to have this conversation here?
Fine.
You broke into Mr. Cooper's office
with some executives after hours.
That's not true.
I'm not in the habit
of making empty accusations.
They made me. l had no choice.
Please. They'll do anything you say.
You work for Mr. Draper.
What's wrong with you?
With me?
Yes.
Are you the only one who's allowed
to have fun around here?
What?
Please. I don't need a mother.
I'm 20 years old .
Collect your things.
What?
Get your things.
You can't be serious.
You want to have this conversation again
in front of Mr. Draper?
I'm going to the break room
to find your replacement.
See that you are gone
by the time I return.
Don!
You like it?
I don't know what to say.
It's gorgeous.
Slide over.
It's like the cockpit of a jet.
What's this for?
That is a headlight sensor.
It automatically dims the lights
as you approach another car.
And these seats.
It was expensive.
- Do you love it?
- I do.
WelI, you deserve it. You work so hard.
I can't wait to pull up
to the Stork Club in this.
Any time you want.
Monday night?
Jimmy Barrett's throwing
a party for his TV show.
He called for you.
He called here?
He should have gone
through my secretary.
I think he likes talking to me.
The kids won't be home for an hour.
Want to take her around the block?
Not in here.
Mr. Sterling?
I'm sorry. Ginger stepped away.
Well. Hello there.
I just wanted to say good-bye
and thank you for being so kind to me.
Good-bye?
I've been fired.
Draper's a tough desk, honey.
Actually, it was Miss Holloway.
I can see someone wanting
to reprimand you seriously.
But firing? It's a little permanent.
Do you want a drink?
Not like you work here anymore.
Would you Iike
to tell me what happened?
You don't need to bother with this.
I want to.
I'm just trying to do my job.
Miss Holloway is. . .
WelI, she's going through a rough time.
She's engaged, you know.
Tell you what.
You go home--
Where do you live?
In the Village.
Jane Street.
Jane on Jane Street.
That's a pretty picture.
Listen, you go home
to your little apartment on Jane Street.
By the time you come back here
on Monday morning,
this will all be taken care of.
Are you sure?
No more tears.
I don't know what to say.
Thank you, Mr. Sterling.
Thank you so much.
Roger.
That's my favorite tie.
He's late. I was expecting that.
He is a bachelor.
You could smell heaven in the street.
I'd like to take credit,
but it's all the maestro.
These are beautiful.
Don't forget to put
an aspirin in the bottom.
Keeps 'em fresh.
I know that. I told you that.
Can l offer you a drink?
Beer if you have it.
But wine with the spaghetti. Okay?
Your place is. . .really wild.
Once we decided not
to look for a bigger place,
we just Iet ourselves go.
How did you two meet?
It's a boring story.
No, it's not.
I grew up a block away from him
in Baltimore.
l guess I just always had
a crush on an older man.
As soon as I moved my mother up here,
Kitty came along.
Come, come. Taste this sauce.
Now, tell me what you think,
and be honest.
I'm fragile.
It's really good.
It's better than a restaurant.
I don't want this hanging in the air.
- What are you talking about?
- My story.
I don't want to sit here
the whole meal worrying
and then find out you didn't read it
or that you did and you didn't like it.
Are you kidding? I loved it.
- Loved what?
- His story.
Yes. He wouldn't stop talking about it,
but he won't let me read it.
I didn't know how you felt.
I wonder if one day
they'll rent this apartment
by bragging about the fact
that you ate here once.
I'm going to be eating here all the time.
To "The Gold Violin,"
by Kenneth Cosgrove.
You really liked it?
I did. It was lovely.
I saw one at the Met.
It's perfect in every way,
except it couldn't make music.
Oh, my.
Well, shall we?
Is Bobby in the car again?
No. He's running around.
So I don't understand.
You'd rather play checkers
than my "look at the clouds" game.
I'd rather play with Silly Putty.
I don't want it jammed between my seats.
You know what, Sally?
Go play with Bobby.
We should do this more often.
We should only do this.
I have to go pee-pee.
Go behind a tree there.
No one's looking.
I want to tinkle outside.
I don't know.
It's different for boys.
I think everybody should go
before we get in the car.
Do you have to go?
No.
You kids are lucky.
When l was a little boy,
back on the farm,
we had an outhouse
way out in the yard.
And on nights
when there was no moon,
there was this rope,
and you had to feeI for it in the dark
and pull yourself across.
I'm glad we didn't live in the olden days.
Are we rich?
It's not polite to talk about money.
I did it!
We should probably get going
if we don't want to hit traffic.
Sally, pack up the checkers.
Check their hands.
Okay.
You get the last of it.
Should I get another?
You can have mine.
Harry tell you anything about his meeting?
Harry's meeting with who?
Mr. Cooper.
He says he knows the answer now.
Well? What was it?
He says I wouldn't understand.
Where do you live, Ken?
Murray Hill.
I can waIk to the office, but I don't.
I wonder if you're gonna get a call.
I'm pretty sure he's going
through the whole roster.
Although, Cosgrove
comes before Crane, right?
My cousin has an advertising agency
in Montreal.
He's not interested in that.
How the heck did you
end up in accounts?
Me and a bunch of my college buddies
heard there was dough.
I was the only one who got a job.
What about writing?
That's just for fun.
It's your hobby.
I should go.
You can't.
Don't you want coffee?
Would it be rude to say that I have
a long ride back to Manhattan?
I can wrap up a piece of pie for you.
- It's pine nuts and pineapple.
- If I eat any more,
I'll burst.
You two have been wonderful.
Thanks for reading the story.
You can let her read it.
I can't wait.
I'll see you tomorrow, l guess.
Do you want to have some pie?
No. I'm not hungry.
I'm just going to clean up.
Do you even care that l want dessert?
Of course I do. I'll go get it.
I'll get it.
What's the matter, Kitty?
I don't work where you do.
I've met these people once.
How am l supposed to talk about them?
Come on, Kitty.
Do you even see me here?
Well, of course I do.
WelI, you wouldn't know it, Salvatore.
I'm sorry.
We were just talking about work.
You're right.
It was rude.
I tried to include myseIf.
A lot of people find me
very interesting, you know?
I am so sorry, Kitty.
It's okay.
I'll get you some pie.
You put your feet up.
I'll take care of the kitchen.
Okay.
I have tickets for the Mets tonight.
Great seats for probably a terrible game.
I'll be by at 5.
No, you won't,
and please don't lurk near my desk.
I'm being watched.
Okay.
WelI, have a good day.
Good morning.
Morning.
I was going to calI Kitty today,
but I don't know what
it's like with Italian people
if you call someone's wife.
It's okay.
Give her a call. She'd like that.
WelI, I just wanted to thank her--
both of you, really.
Every once in a while,
you wish you weren't
a bachelor, you know?
And your home is kind of
what l have in mind,
the way you two are.
WelI, we really enjoyed having you.
What on God's green earth
are you doing here?
Did Mr. Sterling speak with you?
No.
What could he possibly have to do with this?
I'll do whatever you want,
but he said that you do this a lot.
Do what?
Lose your temper.
That you're impetuous
and it's not serious.
And what were you doing
talking to Mr. Sterling?
I ran into him on my way out.
Did you?
Is there a problem?
No.
There's no problem at aIl.
It's very clear.
Everyone looks so glamorous.
Believe me,
they're saying that about you.
It's my earrings.
Do you remember? Bermuda?
I do.
Here he is.
Don Draper.
I heard you had something
to do with this.
Very little.
Betty, this is Andrew Colhold with ABC.
A pleasure to meet you.
And you.
Isn't this a pleasant surprise?
Hello, Mrs. Draper.
You look stunning.
Don.
Hello, Mrs. Barrett.
Don, did Andrew tell you my idea
for working a few items into the show?
Not yet.
Why don't I get us some drinks?
That's okay. Let me get them.
I'll do it.
No, it sounds like you three
have business to discuss.
For example,
a woman's parking her car,
and then Jimmy runs out and says
she's run over his Rolex watch,
so then we show the watch.
Of course Jimmy will need
a Rolex, I suppose.
I don't care, as long
as we bury Candid Camera.
If you're trying to blend
into the wall, you can't.
Hello, Jimmy.
Hello, gorgeous.
What are you doing
standing here all alone?
They're talking business.
I fled.
I'd better not.
I've had too much already.
I insist.
The drunker you are,
the funnier l become.
ABC did research.
Come on.
Let's keep each other company.
I wish l was a mosquito right now.
I would never leave you alone.
Come to think of it,
l never do, do I?
No, you don't.
I'd want you on my arm.
Look at us, over here at the kids' tabIe.
What do you mean?
Them. Your husband.
I've been standing behind guys
like that my whoIe life.
I was lucky I was funny.
If I wasn't funny,
I would never have gotten to meet you.
- That's not true.
- It is.
It's hard to believe
there's anything better than you.
Hard to believe he could do
any better than you .
Please stop.
What do you think happened
between the two of them?
Excuse me?
Oh, come on. Look at them.
I don't like what you're saying.
All I know is I know her,
and you know him,
and there they are,
and they don't care where we are.
Stop it.
- Hold on.
- Let me go.
I don't like it any more than you do.
You people are ugly and crude.
What people? You mean comedians?
. . .a very unusual emergency.
You know what must really annoy him?
All the interruptions
when we're not at home--
signing for deliveries,
answering the phone,
turning on the oven.
You know I never ask him
to do that sort of thing
unless it's impossible
for me to be here.
How about that Thanksgiving
when your car broke down
and Daddy had to leave his office
every 1 5 minutes to baste?
Your father never complains or anything.
WelI, no. Daddy wouldn't.
I guess he wouIdn't.
Leaving so soon?
We didn't get to talk.
Betty's not feeling well.
Too bad.
Here, let me get that.
It's the least I can do.
Thanks to you,
I got everything I wanted.
I don't know if that's possible, Jimmy.
I got my relationship with Utz,
my show, my money, 39 on the air.
I'm gonna be an institution.
I'll tell everyone I know.
You know what I like about you?
Nothing.
But it's okay.
You got me everything I wanted.
What did you get?
Bobbie?
Lots of people have had that.
Excuse me?
Please. I laugh at you.
I go home at night, and I laugh at you.
I don't know what you think happened.
You. You want to step out, fine.
Go to a whore.
You don't screw another man's wife.
You're garbage.
And you know it.
Well.
Good night, you two.
It's been a gas.
Subtitled By J. R. Media Services, lnc.
Burbank, CA