Yeah, that is some detail.
That is some Western detail right there.
Western detail. Attention to detail.
He's even got spurs on the back
of his boots and they're sharp.
- Love it.
- They are.
The clock is gone on this piece,
Christine, so...
- Oh, my goodness
- Well, let's just move on.
Well, from time to time,
people make mistakes, that's okay.
This is our first Renoir of the evening.
This is a heliogravure,
which is an etching...
...it was hand pulled from a copperplate
in Paris in 1919.
We know this because
that's what it says on the back...
...where the certificate of authenticity
is located. Just as lovely as can be.
Look at the soft, delicate shading,
very feminine.
This is a limited edition.
This is what you're looking for
if you are a Renoir fan.
One hundred, oh, my goodness.
Right at the buzzer.
Good.
The few exceptions
is the African pancake tortoise...
...which has a flat, flexible shell
that allows it to hide in rock crevasses...
Big swath of light to moderate snow
from the Broken Bow area...
...down toward Kearney, Hastings,
Grand Island.
That is all moving in our direction,
so I do think around 7 to 8:00...
...the snow will become pretty steady
here across the region...
...with all this moving on top of us...
...and that's really gonna
knock down visibility.
And again, snow-covered roads are
gonna be definitely likely this evening...
...making it even slippier...
More slippery.
Than it is out there at this time.
There's that winter weather advisory
in effect...
...till very early tomorrow morning.
The bitter cold weather
helped break up the compactions...
...we created this fall in our fields.
Don't let false allegations bully you
into an unfair fight.
Hi, I'm Saul Goodman,
and I will do the fighting for you.
No charge is too big for me.
When legal forces have you cornered,
better call Saul.
I'll get your case dismissed.
I'll give you the defence you deserve.
Why? Because I'm Saul Goodman,
attorney at law.
I investigate, advocate, persuade,
and most importantly, win.
Better call Saul.
Do you feel doomed?
Have opponents of freedom
wrongly intimidated you?
Maybe they told you you're in serious
trouble and there's nothing you can do.
I'm Saul Goodman, and I'm here
to tell you that they're wrong.
It's never too late for justice.
Better call...
I think...
...your brain is just not all there yet.
If we were all held responsible
for what we did when we were 19...
I remember what it was like to be a kid.
Think back.
It's all... Judge, what would you say?
These boys, 19, I can't... I don't...
These three young men, just like you.
Just like...
Oh, to be 19 again.
You with me, ladies and gentlemen?
Do you remember 19?
Let me tell you, the juices are flowing,
the red corpuscles are corpuscling...
...the grass is green and it's soft,
and summer's gonna last forever.
Now do you remember? Yeah, you do.
But if you're being honest,
I mean, really honest...
...you'll recall that you also had
an underdeveloped 19-year-old brain.
Me, personally...
...if I were held accountable...
...for some of the stupid decisions
I made when I was 19, oh, boy, wow.
And I bet if we were in church right now,
I'd get a big "amen."
Which brings us to these three.
Now, these three knuckleheads...
And I'm sorry, boys,
but that's what you are.
They did a dumb thing.
We're not denying that.
However, I would like you to remember
two salient facts.
Fact one, nobody got hurt. Not a soul.
Very important to keep that in mind.
Fact two...
Now, the prosecution keeps
bandying this term "criminal trespass."
Mr. Spinauzo, the property owner,
admitted to us...
...that he keeps most portions
of his business...
...open to the public
both day and night.
So trespassing?
It's a bit of a reach, don't you think,
Dave?
Here's what I know.
These three young men,
near honour students all...
...were feeling their oats
one Saturday night and they just...
...went a little bananas.
I don't know. Call me crazy,
but I don't think they deserve...
...to have their bright futures ruined
by a momentary, minute...
...never-to-be-repeated
lapse of judgment.
Ladies and gentlemen...
...you're bigger than that.
- Kenny, are you rolling?
- Yeah, wait a minute.
- Yeah, baby. Yeah.
- Tone it down. Chill out, would you?
Hey, Miss Watson's fourth period
biology class, this one's for you.
- Watch and learn, losers.
- Oh, yeah.
- Oh, God.
- Dude, where'd all the blood go?
He's dead.
They suck it all out, dumb-ass.
- Awesome.
- Where do they put it?
All right, I'm through
the neck bone now, dude.
- Kenny, get over here.
- I'm getting it.
- Get a shot of this.
- Fine, fine.
- Let me do it.
- I got it.
All right.
- All right.
- Oh, my God.
You're sawing like a pussy. Let me do it.
Would you get off? Chill out.
- All right.
- Wait, wait. Okay. Wait for it. Wait.
Yeah.
- Come on. Yeah, baby. Yeah.
- Oh, my God.
I dare you to stick your wang
in the throat hole.
I will if you will, loser.
All right, all right.
- What the hell kind of math is that?
- Seven hundred per defence.
No, no, no. "Defendant." "Dant."
Three defendants, 2100.
Which, by the way, bargain.
What I did for them...
They going to jail, ain't they?
So since when does that matter?
They had sex with a head.
Look, didn't nobody tell you
to try all three of them together.
- One trial, $700.
- You're gonna miss me.
You are gonna miss me
because it'll be a cold day in hell...
...before I do any more PD work
for this shitty court. Sayonara, baby.
You have yourself a nice day.
Law offices of James McGill,
how may I direct your call?
Yes, Mrs. Kettleman,
so good of you to return.
Actually, I don't have Mr. McGill
at the moment, but I know he...
Oh, splendid.
Unfortunately,
our offices are being painted...
...and the fumes are quite horrid.
Could he meet you and your husband
at, say, Loyola's Café on Central?
Four o'clock it shall be. Cheers.
Three dollars.
I'm validated. See the stickers?
Well, I see five stickers. You're one shy.
That's $3.
They gave me... Look,
I'm validated for the entire day, okay?
Five stickers, six stickers,
I don't know from stickers because...
...I was in that court back there
saving people's lives, so...
Gee, that's swell.
And thank you for restoring my faith
in the judicial system.
Now, you either pay the $3...
...or you go back inside
and you get an additional sticker.
Son of a bitch.
Fine. You win. Hooray for you.
Backing up. I have to back up.
I need more stickers.
Don't have enough stickers.
Thank you. Thank you. Very nice.
Employee of the month over here.
Yeah. Hooray. Give him a medal.
Don't do anything, guys.
Just relax, all right?
Well, I'm just fuzzy as to why
you think he needs a lawyer.
I mean, Craig...
...the way you run your office
is beyond reproach.
- Beyond reproach.
- Yeah.
- I'm a stickler, you know...
- He is. He's a stickler with the money.
- He's definitely a stickler.
- Yeah. Yeah.
- He's certainly not guilty of some...
- Certainly not.
He's innocent of any wrongdoing,
that's abundantly clear to me.
And frankly, I don't go looking
for guilty people to represent.
I mean, who needs that aggravation,
right?
Right.
Look, all I know is
what I read in the paper.
And typically when money goes missing
from the county treasury...
- And the number here is 1.6 million?
- Well, that's an accounting discrepancy.
It's a discrepancy, absolutely.
But typically when that happens...
...the police look at the treasurer.
And since that person is...
I just think a little proactivity
may be in order.
I just think I'd look guilty
if I hired a lawyer.
Yeah.
Actually, it's getting arrested
that makes people look guilty...
...even the innocent ones.
And innocent people
get arrested every day.
And they find themselves
in a little room...
...with a detective who acts
like he's their best friend.
"Talk to me," he says.
"Help me clear this thing up."
"You don't need a lawyer,
only guilty people need lawyers."
And, boom,
hey, that's when it all goes south.
That's when you want
someone in your corner.
Someone who will fight tooth and nail.
Lawyers, we're like health insurance.
You hope you never need it,
but, man, oh, man, not having it? No.
How would we proceed
if we decided to...?
Well, this is a letter of engagement.
It's very simple, straightforward.
Please, read it closely.
But if you sign it...
...I can get started
on that defence strategy of ours...
...this very afternoon.
Craig...
...I think maybe we should sleep on it.
Sure.
- Don't you think, Mr. McGill?
- We should sleep on it.
Oh, please, call me Jimmy.
Absolutely. I mean, there's no rush.
Oh, and you know, Craig,
we gotta pick up the kids.
- At the...
- Right.
- Yeah.
Well, we will be in touch.
Thank you for the coffee,
and for the advice.
You're very, very welcome.
Here. Take this.
It's got my phone number on it.
- Yeah. Okay.
- Got it.
The number is 9456, 0054...
...4896, 0643,
and the expiration is 11, '04.
Okay, and the key word here
is "classy," all right? Super classy.
Use only flowers that look expensive,
but, you know, aren't.
And the note should say:
"Dear Betsy and Craig.
Best wishes from your stickler
for justice, James McGill."
Okay? And McGill is spelled M-C...
Well, run it again.
Well, no, no, no. It's paid up.
Run it again...
Oh, God, oh, God, oh, God.
Oh, my God, Cal. Cal. Look at me.
Buddy, look at me. Are you okay?
Say something.
What did you do?
What did you do to my brother?
- Why don't you look where you're going?
- He came out of nowhere.
You freaking hit him, man.
You ran him over.
You ran over my brother.
- I got the whole thing on video.
- It was an accident.
It was an accident. He didn't...
He didn't mean to. Look, let me just...
- It's broke. Is it broke?
- It's my leg.
- You broke his leg.
Why you driving around
and not looking?
Driving around breaking people's legs.
- Okay.
- Somebody call the cops.
- Don't call... Don't call the police.
- Police.
Don't call the police.
Call them myself.
- Don't call the police.
- Don't call the cops?
- No.
- How you gonna fix this?
What are you gonna do
to make things right?
I don't know, fellas.
What can I do to make it right?
I don't know.
Five hundred dollars.
Five hundred bucks? Yeah?
Yeah.
- What the hell, man?
- Listen, Starlight Express.
I'm gonna give you a 9.6 for technique,
0.0 for choice of victim.
I'm a lawyer.
Furthermore,
does this steaming pile of crap...
...scream "payday" to you, huh?
The only way that entire car
is worth 500 bucks...
...is if there's a $300 hooker sitting in it.
Now, let's talk about
what you owe me for the windshield.
I'll take a cheque.
Chào cô, ladies.
Chào cô, Mrs. Nguyen.
My, don't you look...?
My mail?
You work for people
who have sex with chopped-off head?
- Was it in the paper?
- I heard it from my cousin.
Why? Why you work for these people?
Just lucky, I guess.
Cucumber water for customer only.
You have zero messages.
Brenda, looking good.
Nice 'do. Where's Lord Vader?
- He's not quite ready for you yet.
- South conference room.
- How about you wait out here?
- How about I don't?
Oh, Sir Francis.
- James.
- Well groomed, as always.
- Okay.
- All right.
Keith, Karen. Yes.
You have meddled with
the primal forces of nature, Mr. Hamlin...
...and I won't have it.
- Do you want me to call security?
- It's okay, Brenda. We got it.
- Hey, Jack. Hey, Nate. Hey, Aaron.
- What can we do for you, Jimmy?
I'm sorry, it's this table.
Something just comes over me.
You can tell me what this
26,000 is supposed to be for.
That's money for Chuck.
Isn't that what you wanted?
A measly 26 grand? Jesus,
you're like Peter Minuit with the Indians.
Throw in some beads and shells
while you're at it.
It's just a start, there'll be more.
Unless you're gonna
just tear them all up.
And why was it made out to me?
Why not Chuck?
Can he make his way to the bank?
I just assumed it was best
to have the money go through you.
We can do it any way you want.
This isn't going away, Howard.
What Chuck did for this firm,
and damn near single-handedly...
...one-third of this place belongs to him.
Yeah.
What have you got, 12 chairs here?
Four of these chairs are Chuck's.
You got five of these
light thingamajigs...
...one and two-thirds are Chuck's.
Yeah.
How many Danishes? Six Danishes?
- You can have all the Danish you want.
- No, no. They're Chuck's Danishes.
And Chuck isn't greedy,
so he'll just take two...
...plus $17 million. In that ballpark.
I mean, we'll know once we get
the accountants poking around here.
Until then, no more penny ante cheques
designed to make it look...
...like Chuck still works here.
He doesn't. He never will again.
It's time to do right by him,
and cash him out.
So these are Chuck's own wishes
that you're conveying?
This is what's best for him.
So he personally told you that
it's his wish to withdraw from the firm?
See, that would surprise me.
It's been nearly a year
since he set foot in here.
I'm just doing...
- ...what's in his best interests.
- So am I.
And I, for one, believe
he's gonna lick this thing.
Until then, his office is just as he left it.
His secretary is still on payroll.
If Chuck can call this an extended
sabbatical, then so can we.
He's that important to us.
You know what?
Let's let a jury figure it out.
Yeah. They're gonna love you, Howard.
You're so down to earth and relatable.
And you will atone.
It's Ned Beatty from Network.
For chrissakes, guys.
Jimmy.
I almost forgot. This month's filings.
You can save me the postage.
Weren't you listening in there?
Chuck doesn't work here anymore.
Think I'm gonna help you
establish a paper trail?
- Jimmy...
- Stop trying to pawn that shit off on him.
Jimmy.
You know, Jimmy,
sometimes in our line of work...
...you can get so caught up
in the idea of winning...
...that you forget to listen to your heart.
Give Chuck my love, would you?
Oh, there you are. Betsy, Craig.
Hi.
Oh, Craig, you need your own purse.
- Did it work out?
- Yeah.
It was very nice.
- You look lovely today.
- Oh, thank you so much.
- Couldn't you just...?
- You know I can't.
Son of a bitch.
- You ground yourself?
- Yes, I grounded myself.
You gotta stop
putting bacon on the list.
That cooler's looking like
a trichinosis stew.
Perfect timing.
Professor Brans Vogelson?
University of Helsinki?
Yeah, you're gonna
have to get that translated.
- Into Swedish?
- Finnish.
Finish translating into...?
I'm sure there's someone at UNM
who can do that.
You do know I'm trying
to start a legal practice?
Vogelson's been working
on the effects...
...of electromagnetic fields
on zebrafish and...
Financial Times.
Yeah, I knew you missed it,
so I figured, what the heck?
Thank you. I know it's expensive here.
- That's not...
- I don't expect you to go out-of-pocket.
Go ahead, reimburse yourself.
Thanks.
Hey, Chuck,
can you not read that for a second?
Can we talk?
Are you all right? You look peaked.
I'm fine. Please, just sit.
You're not in trouble?
You gotta cash out.
- You gotta.
- Again? Really?
There's no other way.
I know that you don't wanna hear it,
but you've got to.
You know I'm going to beat this.
You know I'm going to get better.
Yeah, sure.
Well, then there's nothing more
to talk about.
I will beat this.
Ergo, a falsis principiis proficisci.
- Meaning...
- That's not...
- That's the one about false principles...
You proceed from false principles.
Your argument is built on quicksand,
therefore it collapses.
Yeah, you're not listening.
Fine. Let's take this
to its logical conclusion.
In order to pay out my share...
...suppose my partners are forced
to liquidate the firm.
- Then what?
- That's their problem.
My clients are out in the cold.
My cases are scattered to the winds,
126 people lose their jobs.
What happens to your cronies
in the mailroom?
The assistants, paralegals,
the janitorial staff...
...all of them out on the street.
Your friend Kim, a promising career,
over and done with.
Hamlin owes you everything.
You built that place singlehandedly...
...while he was at Four Hills
working on his bunker shot.
- Let's not exaggerate. I helped.
- You helped.
All the more reason not to tear it down
just for a little bit of cash.
Chuck, I'm going under. Okay?
For the third time,
with these bull-crap contract counsel...
- Bull crap?
- Bull crap, pissant, PD cases...
...at 700 bucks a shot.
Public defender work is some
of the best experience there is.
I just had a case, Chuck,
with three clients.
Arraignment, voir dire, jury trial,
the whole nine yards.
You know what I took home?
Seven hundred bucks.
I might as well head down to skid row
and sell plasma.
You're representing people
who have nowhere else to turn.
Money is beside the point.
Money is not beside the point.
Money is the point.
I keep telling you, have patience.
There are no shortcuts.
- Do good work and the clients...
- The clients will come. Yeah, I know.
Okay.
Hand to God, I wasn't gonna say this,
but you are broke.
I can't carry both of us.
I've been trying like hell, but I can't.
You're saying, what,
you think you have to provide for me?
- I never asked you that.
- You didn't have to ask, okay?
I've been doing my damnedest,
but the day of reckoning is here.
Soon, Chuck,
you're gonna be out on the street...
...with all the electromagnetism
in the world raining down on you.
Now, please, please, picture that...
...then tell me
that money is beside the point.
- This is what has you all worked up?
- Yeah.
Jimmy, there's nothing to worry about.
- Here.
- What is this?
A stipend.
There's gonna be one every week.
Eight hundred and fifty seven dollars
from Hamlin Hamlin McGill.
I'm gonna pay him back. Every penny.
I didn't wanna take anything,
but Howard was very insistent.
And I'm gonna pay you back too.
- Hamlin was here?
- It's not like I'm a recluse.
- He put his cell phone in the mailbox?
- He understands the situation.
- He grounded himself?
- Of course.
And the two of you agreed that since,
as everybody knows...
...you're going back to work
any day now...
...the firm should help you
make ends meet?
That's correct, minus the sarcasm.
Hamlin's making you a chump.
I'm going to get better.
I'm gonna go back to work,
and I'm picking up where I left off.
Sorry.
Sorry, Chuck.
I understand that
you're trying to look out for me...
...but you're missing the bigger picture.
I got it.
Speaking of which...
Howard brought this.
- He's concerned.
- What?
You have to admit,
it could be confusing.
Hamlin Hamlin McGill. James M. McGill.
- That's my name, I was born with it. I...
- Still.
How about "Vanguard Law"?
Or "Gibraltar." Ple...
Wait, so I'm not supposed
to use my name on Hamlin's say-so?
What's he gonna do, sue me?
Nobody wants to create
an adversarial situation.
I'm sure Howard would gladly pay
the cost of new matchbooks and so on.
It's simply a matter
of professional courtesy.
Chuck, whose side are you on?
There are no sides.
But, Jimmy...
Wouldn't you rather
build your own identity?
Why ride on someone else's coattails?
You wanna dance, Howard?
Let's dance.
Yeah, backside on it.
Go.
You can get closer than that,
you bitch. Come on.
All right, here it comes.
There you go. Better.
- How was that?
- It's all right. Here, take a look.
- So tighter. Everything...
- Tighter? What...? Tighter what?
I don't know, just stand tighter.
You know what I mean?
I don't know what you mean.
That's a... We can call that
a stylistic choice, I guess.
Hey, fellas. We got business.
How did you find us?
I know. Eerie, right?
Whoa, come on. Give me 30 seconds.
Could be the most profitable
30 seconds of your lives.
Let me tell you about a young guy.
Actually, he's about your age.
He lived a long way from here...
...in a town called Cicero, Illinois.
And in Cicero, he was the man.
I mean,
when he strolled down the street...
...all the corner boys
would give him the high five.
All the finest babes
would smile at him...
...and hope that he would smile back.
They called him Slippin' Jimmy...
...and everybody wanted
to be his friend.
Slippin' Jimmy.
What the hell kind of name is that?
Well, I'll tell you now.
Winters in Cicero are murder.
You guys, growing up out here
in the Golden West, you don't know.
Okay? I'm talking cold that'll freeze
the snot right in your nose.
I'm talking wind
that'll cut through your jacket...
...and carve you up like a Ginsu knife.
In fact, most folks in Cicero
were scared of winter.
But not Jimmy.
Jimmy would wait around all summer...
...and when September
finally rolled around...
...and he'd feel that first cold wind
come sweeping off Lake Michigan...
...he knew it was coming.
Was it Christmas? Was it Kwanzaa?
Better. It was slip-and-fall season.
As soon as it was cold enough,
he'd find a nice, smooth patch of ice.
State Street was good,
Michigan Avenue was better.
He'd pick his spot,
wait for it to get busy...
...then he'd walk out on the ice
and boom.
He would biff it so hard...
...people would come running
from five blocks away.
Yeah, but did he collect?
"Did he collect?"
Slippin' Jimmy had it dialled in.
One good fall, he'd clear 6, 8 grand.
That'd keep him in Old Milwaukee
and Maui Waui right through Labor Day.
- Eight grand?
- Eight grand.
Now, see, I look at you guys,
I see potential.
The skateboard's a nice wrinkle,
that makes it a year-round gig.
Clearly, you know how
to take a header. Right?
But I gotta ask you...
...your best day ever,
how much did you clear?
- Six hundred and thirty.
Six hundred and thirty bucks?
Was that for one fall?
- Two.
- Two falls in one day?
- Even at your age, that's gotta hurt.
- True that.
All right. Well, I got a job for you.
How's 2 grand sound?
Two grand for one hit?
One hit.
Plus you get to learn from the best.
- Nice boat.
- Yeah.
Discreet,
like a stripper pole in a mosque.
Forget the boat. Look at the car.
You know what that is?
- I don't know, a station wagon?
- It's a Mercury.
A 1988 Mercury Sable wagon.
Remember it. Burn it into your brains,
you got it?
It's a Mercury Sable wagon, sure.
Close your eyes. What colour is it?
- Brown.
No, it's medium sandalwood.
Keep your eyes closed.
How does the license plate start?
- Four.
- Give those gentlemen a gold star.
Betsy Kettleman's her name.
Every weekday between 2:25 and 2:50
she comes through here...
...on her way to pick up her kids
at Kit Carson Elementary.
You need a place where
she's gonna slow down, right?
- Yeah.
- All right. Well, there you go.
She slows down, she hangs a right...
...you come shooting out of there
and do what you did to me.
You go ass over teakettle,
you make it a blue-ribbon special.
When she gets out of the car,
you're suffering Saint Sebastian, right?
You're the hammer. You get in her face,
you scare the bejeezus out of her.
Give me your phone.
- It's kind of busy here, don't you think?
- Yeah. Witnesses are good.
Witnesses are pressure, all right?
Now, once you've got her
good and rattled...
...then you call for an ambulance,
but really you're calling for me.
I'm number one on your speed dial,
next to your weed dealer.
You call me, I hotfoot it over here.
I just "happened" to be driving by.
I stop to see what the trouble is,
and this is the important part...
...you don't know me.
We've never met. You got it?
- Sure.
- Okay.
Now, I'm Mrs. K's white knight.
We go mano a mano.
You light into me, okay? Get nasty.
No touching, leave the hair alone...
...but otherwise,
you know, open season.
Yell, stomp, call me a douche bag.
I'm gonna play it cool,
give you back some of the razzmatazz...
...and once she's seen the fireworks,
you fold like a lawn chair. Happy ending.
- When do we get our money?
- After.
- "After."
You get paid when I get paid.
I'm the rising tide
that raises all dinghies.
Now, pop quiz. What's the car?
- Mercury Sable wagon.
- Baby-poop brown.
- Okay, do you know me?
- No.
Damn straight. Go with God.
Well, I'm just glad
I happened to be passing by.
Happy to be of help, Betsy.
May I call you Betsy?
Please, call me James.
Oh, the kid will be fine. Don't worry.
He just got his bell rung a little.
I'll handle that.
Oh, no.
Oh, no, no. I wouldn't think
of taking your money for this, so...
The embezzlement case?
Yes, I'd be happy to talk it over.
Oh, shit.
Two-minute warning.
Got it.
Oh, my God.
What happened?
Call 911.
Oh, my God. Cal. Cal.
Look at me. Are you okay?
Buddy, say something.
Cal, look at me. Come on already.
What is she doing in there?
She making a sandwich?
Where's her sense of responsibility?
- What?
Hey. What the...?
Funny to run into you, Betsy.
I was just strolling the neighbourhood.
You were in an accident? Oh, that's...
Come on.
- Yeah.
- She took off on us.
- She what?
- It was textbook, man.
We were diamonds.
But then she just took off.
Okay, wait. She hit and run?
That's what I'm saying.
She bailed and wailed.
Okay, just stay where you are.
I'll come get you.
No, no, no. Screw that, man.
We're following her.
You're... How are...?
You're following her how?
We got our ways, yo.
Okay, okay, okay.
New plan. New plan.
You do know me. I'm your lawyer.
You got that? I'll meet you at the school.
No, she's way past the school.
She hooked a left on Juan Tabo,
now she's coming into Holiday Park.
Okay, stay with her.
When she gets where she's going...
...wherever that is, don't do anything.
- Wait for me.
- Wait for what?
You haven't been right even once.
Slippin' Jimmy my ass.
You fell into the honeypot, kid.
You get it? Hit-and-run is a felony.
- So what?
- "So what?" So more money.
He says we fell in the honeypot.
- He says more money.
- So, what do we need him for?
Cal, Lars, whoever...
Oh, damn it.
Come on, come on.
- Do it, do it, do it.
- Son of a bitch.
Come on. Come on.
- Hey, your leg.
- Oh, I'm gonna do this one.
Okay. Hey. Hey. Yo, hold up.
Hey, yeah, you.
What is the matter with you?
- You hit and run.
- You ran him over.
You felonied my brother.
- Habla English.
- We call... We call la policia.
- La policia gonna be pissed.
- I see you hit him.
You see that windshield? You did that.
- I did that.
- You did that.
- You did that to me.
- Now you pay.
Make with the dinero.
Sí, righteous dinero.
- Okay.
- Yeah, that's what I'm talking about.
Okay.
Let's go.
- Is that money?
- Yeah.
Watch the step. Watch the step.
Watch it. Watch the step.
Where are you?
Holiday Park.
Mrs. Kettleman, Betsy,
what are you doing here?
Hit-and-run? That's very serious.
I can mediate.
I represent their parents, so...
Come on, come on.
Open up, officer of the court.
Open up in the name of the law.
Good afternoon, this...