Glenoxi.
At last we meet.
Lord Zortac. I’ve been expecting you.
I've traveled
across four universes to fuck.
Let’s do this, you cosmic hunk.
Oh!
Get to the sex!
Oh, okay.
Ow! Ow! Aah!
What’s wrong?
Nothing, try again.
Retreat! Oh, retreat.
- Oh...
- Why won't it go in?
I don't know.
Haven't you got training?
Not going. Can't be bothered.
Hey.
You know what I said before...
Like, the whole, like, "I love you" thing.
I was seriously wasted.
So I don't expect you to, like...
say it back or anything, you know?
Okay.
Dad?
I'm home.
Go and get ready for school.
And please, be quiet.
Your mother’s been worried sick
and she's only just gone to sleep.
♪ Walk right in ♪
♪ Sit back down ♪
♪ Baby, let your hair hang down ♪
- Jesus.
- ♪ Walk right in ♪
- ♪ Sit back down ♪
- Ugh.
- ♪ Baby, let your hair hang down ♪
♪ Everybody's talkin'
'Bout a new way of walkin' ♪
♪ Do you wanna lose your mind? ♪
♪ Walk right in ♪
♪ Sit back down ♪
♪ Baby, let your hair hang down ♪
Morning, darling.
♪ Walk right in ♪
- ♪ Sit back down ♪
- Do you want any tea?
♪ Daddy, let your mind roll on ♪
♪ Walk right in ♪
♪ Sit back down ♪
Will you save the crossword
for me, please?
♪ Daddy, let your mind roll on ♪
♪ Everybody's talkin'
'Bout a new way of walkin' ♪
♪ Do you wanna lose your mind? ♪
♪ Walk right in ♪
♪ Sit back down ♪
♪ Daddy, let your mind roll on ♪
You’ve been very quiet lately, sweetheart.
Is there anything wrong?
I made some notes on your book.
The one about me.
You should consider using
a thesaurus in the future.
Your vocabulary is very limited.
Otis, let's talk about this
in a calm and rational way.
Not calm! Not rational!
We'll talk about it later, darling.
Come on!
Ow!
Stupid bike!
- Is this about your mum’s book?
- Oh, no, I mean,
it’s only a heavily researched,
meticulously detailed account
of raising a sexually repressed
16-year-old boy.
Me, by the way.
Chapter One. "Otis's surprise emission."
Sorry. Not funny. Very bad, Jean.
Look, well, at least you went to the dance
with an actual girl.
- That's progress, man.
- I called her a goat and she left.
Still, an improvement.
Anyway, I thought you called her
a house cat.
Yeah, I also called her a goat.
Do you like Ola?
Yeah, I... I do. A lot.
Then why did you call her a goat?
Promise not to laugh.
She seemed to think that
there was something going on
between Maeve and I, romantically, and...
Sorry, not the funny part.
I was trying to reassure her
how ridiculous that was,
because someone like Maeve
is never gonna be interested in me,
because I'm a loser
and she is a lioness.
Aaah.
Therefore, Ola is a house cat.
Wow.
Otis, you know, for a sex therapist,
you are surprisingly insensitive.
On the upside, at least you're gonna be
famous with this new book.
Like that man
that was born with tree arms.
Maeve Wiley
and Otis Milburn to Mr Groff's office.
The lioness awaits.
She’s still not talking to me.
Wow. Women really hate you.
Nice outfit.
- Thanks, Anwar. I love...
- There's really no need to respond.
Glad to see you back, Eric.
Uh... Thanks, sir.
Um...
- I've been meaning to apologize.
- Hey, it's...
Look, we all have bad days, you know?
But in every cloud, there is a rainstorm.
No, wait, sorry, that's not right.
"There is a rainbow in every cloud,"
is it?
- Okay...
- Basically, it's all in the past.
- Yeah.
- And, um...
- The two weeks of detention?
- Still very much in your future.
- Oh. Okay. Okay.
- Mm. So...
- I'll see you after school.
- Okay...
Look, about what... what happened...
I'm over it.
Maeve.
You're first.
I've been watching you
and your little friend.
Meeting up before school,
hanging around after hours,
secret whispers,
exchanging money.
Okay, well... we're just hangin' out.
I think you've been doing a lot more
than just enjoying each other's company.
I know all about your drug ring.
They're not mine.
You expect me to believe that
that spineless beanpole Milburn...
is responsible for dealing hard drugs?
Otis had nothing to do with it.
- These are study drugs, sir, they're not...
- You seem to know an awful lot about them,
considering you had absolutely
nothing to do with it.
Did you and your little friend
get them from your brother?
Oh, yes.
I know all about
your unsavory family history.
And you...
have let an innocent child
like Milburn be turned into a drug mule.
Otis didn't do anything.
Leave him out of it.
What are you doing?
I'm reporting your brother to the police.
Wait.
They're mine.
What happens now?
You're going to tell me exactly
what happened at the school dance,
and then you will face
an external tribunal
who will decide whether
you have a future at this school.
- Milburn.
- Yes, sir.
A word to the wise.
Beware the wild female.
They will chew you up and spit you out
like stale crisps.
Get to class.
Yeah.
You’re not in any trouble. I sorted it.
Okay, what... what happened?
Are we... are we not gonna
talk about this? Is that it?
I trusted you, Otis.
But...
I don't want to have sex with you!
Neither do I.
You were bad.
You played whale music
and you would not stop talking.
Then you had a panic attack
and I had to get your mum.
It was an appallingly awkward
sexual experience.
Look, I need some advice...
About my...
Clinic's over. Sorry.
I didn't tell anyone
about what happened.
You kind of owe me.
It wasn't fucking funny when I pushed you
out of my vagina, either.
Hello?
Jean Milburn?
This is Simone McAllister
at Bright and Sanders.
You sent us
the first chapter of Bringing Up Men.
We're in the midst
of a crisis of masculinity
and this feels potentially
quite zeitgeisty.
- Is there more to read?
- Yes.
- Yes, there is.
- Fantastic.
We're particularly interested
in the connection you have
with the subject.
It’s so personal.
We really feel it could
strike a chord with other mothers.
When do you think you could send
more pages over by?
Can I get back to you on that?
Yep. Absolutely.
Don't take too long, though.
I won't.
Thank you.
Shit! Shit, shit.
Oh, God.
- Yeah?
- Hello, Jakob? It's Jean.
I'm really sorry to bother you,
but I'm afraid my pipe's
burst under my sink.
- And the water's going everywhere...
- Jean.
You have to stop breaking things
when you want sex.
No, no... No.
That's... Er, it's a misunderstanding.
I, uh... No, it's really broken.
I think I have been very clear.
I want a relationship.
I do not want to be your handyman.
Goodbye, Jean.
- So, what seems to be...
- My vagina has betrayed me.
Okay. How, exactly?
I finally find someone who's DTF,
and he can't get his average-sized dick
in my stupid vagina.
Why is this happening to me?
Uh, well... um...
It just doesn't make any sense.
I've worked so hard.
The set, the costumes, the makeup.
Everything was perfect.
I couldn't even get my finger in there.
It's like my vag has lockjaw.
What do I do?
Well, you used the word "perfect."
Maybe it's a way of staying in control.
In... in your fantasy, you're in charge.
And reality can be...
just, quite different.
Nah, I just like aliens.
Do you like being out of control?
I guess not.
Like, I hate roller coasters.
Me, too. I do not like simulated danger.
I guess I am kind of type A.
Well, maybe...
you're unconsciously halting your progress
to stay in control.
But I want to have sex,
so why would I do that?
I don't know.
Okay.
I need this place spick and span.
I've got to do all of this on my own?
No! No. God, no.
That would be impossible.
Uh, no, you have company.
Okay.
I'll see you boys in two hours.
Okay?
Go ahead, Tromboner.
Get to work.
I don't need a plumber tomorrow,
I need a plumber today, you moron!
Otis, could you just...
Uh... You did not just hang up on me!
You did not just hang up on me!
Otis!
This emergency supersedes our argument!
Otis, open the door, please!
Leave me alone!
Jesus Christ, Mum! Get out, please!
While you are still under my roof,
- you are not to shut me out.
- ♪ I would say I'm sorry if I thought ♪
♪ That it would change your mind ♪
♪ This time I have said too much... ♪
- Oh!
- Why are you so angry?
- You're a hypocrite!
- What?
How? Wh...
- Descriptive words, please.
- Okay.
You say you're all about honesty
and clear communication,
but you're not honest at all.
You inveigle your way into everything
I do and then act like it's an accident.
You cross multitudes
of parental boundaries on a daily basis.
You're a... sneaky, sneaky woman!
That is a vast over-exaggeration.
Well, how is the book coming along?
This is becoming hostile now, Otis.
I want you to count to ten.
One, two, three, four, five,
six, seven, eight, nine, ten!
Please leave!
Ah, so, if...
If the book gets published,
of course I will change your name.
That's not the point, Mum.
I thought you were finally
listening to me,
that you were letting me be independent,
but you just can't help yourself.
It's like you want to consume me.
You're like the spider-mums
that eat their own offspring.
Like, you think I'm somehow part of you.
Well, you are part of me.
No, I'm not, Mum.
I'll get it.
Um... Ola!
You're at my door. Um...
Eh... Did you get my text?
It said, uh... "Hello."
But I guess it should have said, "Sorry."
My dad sent me to fix your sink.
Um, look, you don't... you don't need
to do that. My mum's called a plumber.
Uh... This is awkward. Um...
I mean, we kind of
went on a date, didn't we?
And now you're angry with me,
but you're also fixing my sink.
I'm fixing your mother's sink
as a favor for my father.
It's not about you.
Jakob sent her.
- Otis, we need to talk about our fight.
- I'm going out.
She's so selfish.
She pretends the crazy food regime
and early mornings is for my benefit,
but it's all about her.
I don't even know if I like
anything except swimming.
Shut up.
What?
You don't know how lucky you are.
She gets up every morning
to take you to swimming.
She goes to all your races.
- She cries when you lose.
- Wh...
She shows you every day
that she loves you.
- What's the problem?
- I'm not...
It might be annoying,
but at least she cares.
Okay.
Maybe just tell her the truth
about how you feel.
I didn't mean to snap, I'm sorry.
I need to go talk to my idiot brother.
Hey, sis, you wanna get baked?
No.
You said you were gettin' a proper job,
not sellin' shit again.
Yeah, I am.
My mate said he could
hook me up as a doorman.
You wouldn't last one day,
with your weak little arms.
My teacher wants me to apply
for the Aptitude Scheme at school.
Oh, what, you're serious?
What, so soon you'll be hangin' out
with a bunch of fuckin' virgins,
talking about astrophysics and shit?
If I get in.
I'll probably mess it up somehow,
I always do.
Nah.
You're way smarter than me.
You always have been,
ever since you were a kid.
You're smart.
Yeah, but...
You're, like, smart-smart, like...
You know,
could actually have a good life smart.
I just don't wanna be living here
in ten years, you know?
You won't be.
I'm gonna get that doorman job.
I'll save up and we'll rent a place
and we can really get our shit together.
Yeah, that sounds nice.
I'm really proud of you, sis.
Thanks.
You know, if you helped me,
we could get out of here a lot quicker.
Ouch! Stop it.
Asshole.
What did you say?
Were you born a bully? Or are you one
because your dad's one?
I saw you at the dance.
You were terrified of him.
Can't imagine being afraid
of my own dad.
What the fuck would you know, Tromboner?
You're doin' it wrong. Let me try.
- Give it here.
- No, it's fine.
Adam, it's fine, I can do it myself.
Just give it. It's fine.
- You can just leave it.
Leave it, man! What's wrong with you?
Get off!
Get off me!
Sorry.
Sorry, I didn't mean...
How do you like it?
I don't.
Yeah.
Didn't think so.
♪ He hit me ♪
♪ And it felt like a kiss ♪
♪ And I went down ♪
♪ Oh, whoa, oh, whoa ♪
So, what does this sheer and
perilous hill have to do with my vagina?
I think you have
something called "vaginismus,"
which is the body's automatic reaction
to a fear of vaginal penetration.
But I really want to have sex.
I don't think you're afraid of having sex.
I think you're afraid to let go.
Which is why
you are going to ride down this hill.
To face your fears.
I don't wanna fuck a hill.
Just trust me on this one.
Well, what about you?
What about me?
You had a panic attack
when I touched your penis.
Maybe we should do it together?
I... I...
You know what? Eh... forget it.
This is... silly.
So unsafe.
You know, your vagina's gonna open
at some point.
I can't wait for that!
Fuck it!
Whoo!
This is amazing!
This is amazing! Whoo!
Aah! I think that was my hymen!
Aah! Fuck!
Aaah! Aaah!
Otis?
Ow!
Fuck!
Otis?
Am I dead?
No, you're alive.
Thank God.
Ow! It hurts.
Ah, your head is bleeding.
So, this mean I can have sex now?
I hope so.
Why do you wanna have sex so bad?
What do you mean?
You just seem...
Ow.
You seem desperate to have sex,
I don't know why.
I dunno.
I guess I just feel like,
if I don't do it,
then I'll graduate school
and I won't have had sex,
and then I'll go to uni
and I'll be behind everyone,
and no one will have sex with me
because I'm just the weird virgin girl.
And then I'll never have sex
because I'll be too embarrassed
and weird and virginal,
and then I'll grow old
and die alone in my house,
where I'll be eaten by my pet python.
Okay, you've skipped
a whole load of steps there.
I just don't want to be left behind.
I just want it over with.
Look, I know it feels like
everyone's doing it, and...
yeah, some people are,
but most of us aren't yet.
It's not a race.
I think that makes sense.
Good.
We just rode down this hill
for no reason, didn't we?
Yeah.
Oh!
That...
What was that?
Adam, we should talk about...
If you ever tell anyone about this,
I will fuckin' end you, do you understand?
♪ Just take those old records
Off the shelf ♪
♪ I'll sit and listen to 'em by myself ♪
♪ Today's music ain't got the same soul ♪
♪ I like that old-time rock 'n' roll ♪
♪ Still like that old time rock 'n' roll ♪
♪ That kind of music
Just soothes the soul ♪
♪ I reminisce about the days of old ♪
♪ With that old time rock 'n' roll ♪
♪ Hey! ♪
How was detention?
Why? It very was boring.
Nothing weird happened.
It was a very average detention.
Maeve Wiley,
report to Mr. Groff’s office immediately.
Please tell us
why you should stay at this school.
Nothing?
Very well, then...
I'm really smart, sir.
I'd read all of Jane Austen
by the time I was 12.
Including her lesser-known work,
Lady Susan,
which is a severely underrated piece
of feminist literature.
Um... I can also debate
the inherent difference
between existentialism
and transcendentalism,
explaining why Sartre
is the prominent voice of the former,
and the latter is barely remembered
as a philosophical movement.
I can also gauge the depths
of Mr. Hendricks' personal despair
based on his choice of Hawaiian shirt.
I'm really smart.
I just got unlucky
in the family department.
I don't get any support.
And sometimes I do the wrong thing.
But I know I can be better.
And if you give me a second chance,
I will not waste it.
Thank you, Maeve.
Come.
Er, you wanted to see me, sir?
Yes. If you could just wait outside,
please, Jackson. I won't be long.
Okay.
We'll need some time
to consider your position.
Until we do so,
you are barred from campus.
The valves are shaped to stop them
opening in the wrong direction.
The day you arrive on time, Adam,
is the day I eat my hat.
Take a seat. There's one next
to your detention pal, Eric.
- He's not my detention pal.
- We're not friends.
- Right, okay. Well, just sit down.
- Okay.
Come on, hombre. Andale.
¡Andale! Where was I?
Oh, yes. Valves, yeah.
So...
Yeah, the sound of the valves closing,
here and here,
is what we familiarize ourselves...
That's the sound
we familiarize ourselves with,
that is actually our heartbeat.
Okay? Heartbeat.
Rhythm.
Now, these things here, the arteries...
The pulmonary arteries,
when these get blocked...
- What's goin' on?
- Nothing.
Didn't look like nothin'.
- Hey, why won't you talk to me?
- I said it's nothing.
Well, stop lyin'!
They're probably gonna expel me
because of some shit my brother did.
Is that what you wanna hear?
- Shit, are you all right?
- Yeah, I'm fine, yeah.
Hey, talk to me. What's up?
- Come here.
- Don't touch me!
- What?
- This is too much.
- What do you...
- You're too much.
Why am I always the last to know, Maeve?
- What's that supposed to mean?
- It means you don't trust me.
You never have.
Do you love me?
- Just say you don't and I'll...
- I don't.
Jackson, wait.
I think we both know that
you like somebody else anyway, Maeve.
Thank you
for coming to see me.
I fully appreciate, as head boy,
you have a very full schedule
with your fellow students,
er, and also classes to attend,
but I did feel that it was important
to tell you
that you are one of Moordale's
proudest achievements.
It would be a tragedy
to watch you waste your gift
and miss this race.
We all go through rough times,
but your future is very bright.
This isn't about my future, sir,
this is about your sports fundin'.
No, it's... Uh...
Well, ye... yes, okay, sure,
but... A little bit, maybe, but it...
We do really care about you.
Okay. I'll swim.
- Oh, fantastic!
- If...
you let Maeve Wiley stay at school.
You can't expel her.
Want me to swim? Then she stays.
Heard you're getting expelled, Cock Biter.
Oh, well, back to the caravan park, then.
Maybe you don't have to leave.
I hear they're looking for a new cleaner.
What the hell are you doing?
I'm dumping you. For her.
Are you mental?
She's a slag.
Yeah, you're right.
But so am I.
- I'm not a slag.
- Me either, it sounded good.
Just keep walking.
- You wanna play some Smash Bros?
- Oh, I can't, I've got detention.
Man, things have really changed
- since you started punching people.
- Mm.
Dude, why is your mum here?
I don't know.
- I'll see you later, all right?
- See you later.
I'm not stalking you, I promise.
I was passing and I just wa... Otis?
Will you talk to me, please?
Can you not shout, okay?
I wish you weren't so concerned
about what your peers thought.
You don't want to develop
a subservient personality trait.
What do you want?
You're right.
I am a hypocrite.
And you are my blind spot.
Since your dad left,
it's just been the two of us.
But you're growing up, and...
And I feel like I'm losing you.
So you decided to write a book
about my sexual dysfunction?
I thought that it might help me
to understand you better.
That's so messed up.
And you're not repressed,
or dysfunctional, or unusually stunted,
or any of the things
that I said in the book.
And I'm sorry.
Yeah, well, I am all those things, Mum.
And... some of it is your fault.
A lot of it's Dad's fault,
but mostly it's just...
it's me.
I'm not... I'm not normal.
Of course you're normal.
You're 16.
You're not supposed to know
the answers to anything.
You're going to be just fine.
Thank you for saying sorry.
Well, apologizing
isn't just social etiquette,
it's a hugely important human ritual
that brings relationships together
and helps people to move forward, and...
And you already know all that, don't you?
Do you want to go home?
Um...
Actually, there's something I need to do.
- But I'll be back. I'll be back later.
- Okay. Yeah. Okay.
You!
It's your lucky day.
Adam couldn't make it,
and there's a speed dating event
for jazz lovers
that I simply am dying to attend,
so, uh...
You can go!
Get out of here!
Eh...
Okay. Thank you, sir.
Okay!
♪ Whatever will I do ♪
♪ If this love turns out untrue ♪
♪ All those memories to erase ♪
♪ A drink will never do ♪
♪ With no one to drink it to ♪
♪ And I could never stand the taste ♪
Madam? Madam, come here! Come here!
♪ What all of your letters ♪
- Oh, you stupid dog.
- ♪ Just don't say ♪
♪ Well, I can read between the lines ♪
♪ And take a guess ♪
♪ But how could I face it? ♪
- ♪ Bitter day ♪
- Sean?
♪ And all these thoughts of you
Would linger ♪
♪ None of us can take it slow ♪
- ♪ Can take it easy, now ♪
- Mum?
I found Madam!
Oh!
- Hello!
- ♪ Easy now ♪
Hello, you!
Mum, don't make me go.
It's what your father wants.
One of you will be going home.
You are not just serving your food...
Yeah, yeah.
What? Oh.
It's not just pheromones.
I like you.
Christ, I feel like a teenager.
And it's been a long time since...
I've felt like this.
But?
But...
my son is the most important person
in my life.
And he really likes your daughter.
But my fear is he found out that...
we were in a relationship,
he just would...
never forgive me.
I understand.
It's for the best.
Yeah.
What are you doing here?
I'm buying all this cat food.
- I didn't know that you had a cat.
- I don't.
I'm buying all this cat food because...
I really like cats.
House cats in particular.
I like them way more than lions.
Is this supposed to be romantic?
Yeah. It was.
You're holding up the line!
Sorry, I'm... I'll just be a minute.
We're resolving a past wrongdoing.
Yes, I can see that.
It's not cute.
It's annoying.
We'll just be a moment.
Don't you take that tone with me,
young lady.
Very rude.
She's not rude, okay?
She just has a very direct manner.
She's rude and you're pathetic.
Now who's being rude?
- Ow!
- Stupid boy!
She hit me.
That was very brave.
And also quite emasculating.
Look, my shift is over in 15 minutes
and I'm gonna walk you home.
Whoo! Whoo!
- Go on!
- Whoo!
- Come on. Go. Focus! Focus!
- Come on!
Whoo!
Set...
Mail call!
A young lad dropped it off.
Skinny, sickly-looking fella.
Had some really interesting thoughts
about me and Jeffrey's marital problems.
Thanks.
- Have you seen my brother?
- Oh, yeah.
He told me to pass somethin' on to you.
He said... "Tell Maeve to stop hangin'
around with a bunch of geeks
talking about astrophysics and shit."
Something like that.
Did he tell you where he was goin'? Or...
Said 'e was doin' some shoppin',
but he had a big bag with him.
Okay. Thanks, Cynthia.
Jonathan.
Come on, Jackson!
Yes!
Come on, Jackson! Yes!
We knew you could do it!
Well done.
Is she staying?
I don't take bribes.
I suggest you forget about Maeve Wiley.
Hm?
There he is! Jackson! Well done, Jack!
- Well done!
- Darling!
- Well done.
Maeve, I'm so sorry that I hurt you
and betrayed your trust.
You saw something in me
when no one else did.
I was just this invisible guy
in the corner,
and I thought I liked being that way.
Then I met you and I figured out
I'm actually good at something.
I hope you can forgive me and that
we can keep doing the clinic together.
You're the smartest person I've ever met
and this award is yours.
Okay. Look, so...
Something I need to tell you.
There's a few things, actually.
So, uh...
This is my house.
You know that.
Um...
Eh... I'm an odd person.
What I mean is, I'm unusual,
and if you wanna be with me, then...
I mean, not like my girlfriend...
That's... that's too fast. I know.
Eh... No pressure. Just...
If you wanted to be, like,
a significant other, then...
Wow. That sounds like marriage.
I don't wanna get married.
I mean, maybe one day,
with the right person.
Which could be you.
But not in a weird way. Okay.
I can't breathe.
Eh...
Okay.
What I'm trying to say is...
I'm just new to all this
and I need to take things slowly.
Okay.
Do you want to kiss me?
Eh... Yeah... Yes, um... I do.
Stop talking and do it, then.
♪ Ah, now I don't hardly know her ♪
♪ But I think I could love her ♪
♪ Crimson and clover ♪
♪ Ah ♪
♪ When she comes walking over ♪
♪ Now I've been waitin' to show her ♪
♪ Crimson and clover ♪
- I think...
- Don't... don't talk.
- You'll ruin it.
- ♪ Over and over ♪
Yeah.
Text me?
- Cool.
- Okay.
Oh, God! Ugh!
I'm gonna learn
how to play Scabby Queen
if it's the last thing I do.
Will you teach me?
Yeah.
Madame.
Ugh! Sh!
Come on.
♪ The US bombs cruisin' overhead
Overhead, overhead ♪
♪ Overhead, overhead, overhead, overhead ♪
♪ Overhead, overhead, overhead
Overhead, overhead, overhead ♪
Come on.
♪ Psycho maniac interblend ♪
♪ Shoot it up, now shoot it up ♪
♪ Ready, right? ♪
♪ Shoot it up ♪
Whew.
Okay... Eh...
Fuck me!
- ♪ Shoot it up ♪
- ♪ It's ground base ♪
♪ Shoot it up ♪
♪ Teenage crime now fashion's dead ♪
♪ There goes my love rocket red ♪
♪ Shoot it up ♪
♪ Shoot it up, shoot it up, shoot it up ♪
- ♪ Shoot it up
- ♪ It's ground base ♪
♪ Shoot it up ♪
♪ Amondo teeno giving, giving, giving ♪
♪ There goes my love rocket red ♪
♪ Shoot it up, now shoot it up ♪
♪ Then we do the money ♪
You give us the bomb ♪
♪ Shoot it up, it up, it up ♪
♪ Shoot it up ♪
♪ Shoot it up, shoot it up, shoot it up ♪