Previously on The Better Sister...
The charge against the defendant Ethan
Macintosh is murder in the second degree.
The defendant is hereby remanded
without bail.
- [Nicky gasping]
- [Chloe] When do we get to see him?
- Ethan's legal guardian can go anytime.
- So, I don't see him.
[Catherine] The optics of your situation
are starting to worry the board.
Aren't you the board?
You and Adam Macintosh were working
together with a client, the Gentry Group?
- That's correct.
- [Bowen] Maybe Jake Rodriguez
really was jealous.
[Guidry] Single guy, spends a lot of time
with an attractive couple,
it's a tricky triangle.
But enough to kill him?
- [exhales]
- [Jake] She seems to have bought it.
The benefit of
a grieving widow's distraction.
She's not right in the head.
Even when she was a baby.
[Sanders] I got to level with you here.
From the outside, you look perfect.
But every family's got secrets.
It isn't mine.
[Sanders] You may want to keep this stuff
- in the past...
- Remember how I showed you?
...but whatever's happened
between you two,
it's very clear you both love that boy.
You want him home?
Tell me everything.
[haunting music playing]
♪ ♪
[indistinct chatter]
[man] I'd like to get my lawnmower back.
[chatter continues, echoing]
[Hank] Not too shabby.
The turnout.
I mean, not great, but not terrible.
- [laughs]
- Well, you were a mildly popular guy.
[Hank] Look at your mother.
Just miserable having to talk to people.
[both laughing]
[Chloe] Well, this blouse you're wearing
might cheer her up.
She never let me have enough fun.
It's my turn now.
Nicky isn't here yet.
She never showed up for shit,
why would this be any different?
True to herself, I will say that.
If you'll excuse me, I got to circulate.
Man of the hour, you understand.
[laughter echoing]
[hammer banging]
- [loud banging continues]
- This asshole. [laughs]
[breathing heavily]
[Young Ethan] Mom?
Can you hold this?
[gasps]
[exhales]
[♪ Warren Zevon sings
"Werewolves of London"]
♪ ♪
[Nicky] Aye.
- ♪ Ah-hoo ♪
- [music stops]
- Morning.
- Oh. Hey.
Wow, this is, uh,
ambitious for this hour.
[laughs] Well, I couldn't sleep.
Here.
Oh, thanks.
Now, I know it says we're supposed to wait
for this to "completely cool,"
but come on,
we got to enjoy some
while it's still warm, right?
No, no. I'm-I'm not hungry.
S-Smells good.
I had this really weird dream
about Mom and Dad last night.
- Oh, yeah?
- Yeah.
We were at Dad's funeral,
but he was there, he was...
cracking jokes and working the room.
His Vietnam buddies were there, you know,
hanging on every word,
like they always did.
- Mm-hmm.
- And Mom was there,
hammering nails into the casket.
[chuckles] Making sure he stayed put.
Yeah.
Do you remember when I got my period
and Mom immediately
put locks on our doors?
She was so weird about bleeding.
So uptight.
- Mm.
- [phone chimes]
- [Chloe] Oh, my God.
- [Nicky] What?
[Chloe sighs]
[Nicky] "Sister wife, double life."
- At least it's a good photo of us.
- This is everywhere.
Who gives a shit?
At least it's not about Ethan.
Yes, it is because
we all look fucking crazy.
Well...
[phone chimes]
Oh, great. Now Catherine wants me
to come to her house.
Well, I thought
that faux funeral thing was tonight.
Oh, no.
No, God, she's gonna cancel that.
But I-I have to handle this.
Hey, am I missing something?
People know where Ethan came from.
Yeah. Adam's ex.
We just never went into specifics.
We just really wanted
to have a fresh start.
Not all of us had that luxury.
Well, go.
I got to get ready to visit Ethan anyway.
Please don't tell him about the article.
- Okay?
- [scoffs] I'm pretty sure he's onto us.
- [bees buzzing]
- [̈Catherine] Look at all this color.
I've put some effort over the years into
cultivating an honest channel between us.
Wanted you to know you could count on me,
confide in me...
- I do.
- But you didn't.
For someone who's been dragged through
as much shit as I have,
humiliated, every part of my life exposed,
you didn't think you were safe with me?
Plenty of ugly shit
we knew about each other.
The board can't keep delaying the meeting.
I'll do what I can
to represent your interests.
I could use some time.
To go back to the city
and pack up some things.
I have to make home base
out here, closer to Ethan.
Yes, well, that's probably wise.
The article, whatever it is
you want to say publicly,
whatever you want to write,
we need to know. Soon.
- You'll have it by the end of the day.
- Can you do this?
I can. Yes.
[tense music playing]
- Hello, sweetheart.
- Hey, Mom.
Oh. Gorgeous.
Chloe.
You poor thing.
- May I hug you?
- Of course.
Hi, Janie. How are you?
Who cares?
How are you?
I just...
I cannot imagine.
- Yeah.
- I'm so looking forward
to tonight, I mean, we must gather.
I didn't think
we were doing that tonight--
Yeah, Mom and I've been arranging flowers.
It's important you be here
among people who knew you both.
Just to honor Adam.
And at a minimum,
to get some food into you.
We'll see how the day ends up.
The day will end up here.
Yes, this is Chloe Taylor.
My husband Adam Macintosh's body is being
held as a part of a murder investigation,
but the autopsy is complete.
The police are done.
Today.
I want him cremated today.
We've waited long enough. Thank you.
- [♪ Tori Amos sings "Crucify"]
- ♪ Why do we ♪
♪ Crucify ourselves ♪
♪ every day? ♪
♪ I crucify myself ♪
♪ Nothing I do is good enough for you ♪
[volume increases]
♪ I crucify myself ♪
♪ every day? ♪
[playing faintly over speakers]
♪ I crucify myself ♪
♪ And my heart is sick of being...
- [stomping]
- [Hank muttering]
Go to bed.
You hear me?
Go to bed!
I'm almost finished.
[clattering]
[slams cabinet]
- [clattering]
- [slams cabinet]
♪ Got a kick for a dog ♪
♪ Begging for love ♪
♪ I got to have my suffering...
I like that one.
Looks like my Uncle Jeff.
He had a hook arm.
- [stifled chuckle]
- [laughs]
He lost it in a conveyor belt.
[both laugh]
♪ Nothing I do is good enough for you ♪
♪ I crucify myself ♪
♪ every day ♪
♪ I crucify myself...
[Nicky] There were these mornings,
after whiskey hot chocolates,
that my dad would make
my sister and me go on these long drives.
He would swerve the station wagon
in "S" formations out on the highway.
It was such a fun game.
[clears throat] And always made me queasy.
Scared the shit out of my sister.
But I liked having
the whiskey in my belly,
I liked that feeling.
Even if it made me sick.
And I really liked having a secret.
He made sure of that.
Um...
It was something we shared,
me and him and...
Until we didn't.
Until he couldn't stand
the fucking sight of me.
So maybe I am the part
of my sister that she denies.
The slutty side, the...
"eats 25-cent White Castle hamburgers
with Mom for breakfast" side of her,
you know, that she just buried,
I mean, she buried it along with...
[voice breaking] ...along
with any evidence of me.
God, I feel so pathetic to be this old,
this old crying about my baby sister.
[sighs]
But maybe it's not so good
that I came here.
[knocking]
[door opens]
- Hi.
I assume you read it?
Yeah, okay.
So you probably have some questions.
I also still have questions.
But I would really like to just
say a few things, if that's okay with you.
- Uh-huh.
- Okay.
My sister has always had it rough.
Ever since she was a teenager,
it was, uh, booze and drugs and...
anything and everything
she could get her hands on.
I mean, s-she had the curse. She had it.
And I... I didn't.
I, um, I was spared, somehow.
[chuckles]
Clearly, I am perfect in almost every way.
[both chuckle]
But my mom just prayed
that being a mother would...
...calm my sister down.
Some magical thinking?
I remember
looking at Ethan and thinking...
"If a baby could, this one might."
He was perfect.
And the day he almost drowned
was unimaginable,
but from that moment on, I focused myself
on what is best for Ethan.
Like a mantra, "What is best for Ethan?"
And then when Adam and I...
...started to fall in love,
we knew we had to make some big choices.
And I was given something so beautiful
that I just wanted to protect it.
So we buried her.
And now, it...
Now sharks want blood.
Yeah.
And anything else that could possibly...
- Oh, yeah.
- You know?
Uh, um... [chuckles] Of course.
I get it.
So, I'm... gonna see you tonight?
At the wake?
- Yeah.
- Yeah, I wouldn't miss it.
There as acquaintances.
Thank you.
- How's Ethan?
- I don't know.
Nicky's seeing him today.
But Michelle Sanders
is working on getting me in.
Well, don't worry, Michelle's good.
I bet you she already has
six ways to use that article.
Look, you use whatever you need
to get Ethan home.
And then you take it from there.
I'm gonna go for a swim.
[mysterious music playing]
♪ ♪
[locks phone]
[sighs]
[seabirds screeching]
- [Ken] Good. I'll see you around.
- I'll see you.
Nothing wrong with White Castle.
Is that all you took from my rambling?
I hope.
I think your dad and mine
would've got along just fine.
[match strikes]
It's nice here.
- Yeah.
- [chuckles]
Can I offer some insight,
as far as holding on to secrets?
Slow poison.
- But secrets are like multivitamins to me.
- Mm-hmm.
What do you do with all your anger?
What anger?
Mm. [chuckles] Mm-hmm.
My experience, for what it's worth:
Tell your sister what happened, your end.
Take care of your side of the street.
I don't think she's ready for that drive.
- She might surprise you.
- Sure.
Crazier things.
[Guidry] All right, Molly,
don't be afraid of the ball, okay?
You just got to block it.
Just use your body, move around.
I don't care if you catch it.
- Yes, Coach.
- "Yes, Coach."
That's right, that's what I like to hear.
Yes, ma'am. Yes, ma'am.
[laughter]
Oh, I'll be damned.
Okay, here it comes.
Yes! So good!
Hey.
Nice to see your face.
- Thank you, I feel very weird without it.
- Well, it must be important.
Come out here
with your dress shoes in the dirt.
Chloe Taylor pulled the trigger
on cremating her husband.
[inhales sharply] It's her right.
All right, girls,
y'all take a water break.
Profile's rising on this case, Nan.
You see that article this morning?
More salacious gossip, I hope.
Forget that
"women are essential" bullshit,
it's the girls that matter.
I'm getting them when they're young.
Before they become wretched bitches.
Your contribution to the community.
Thanks so much.
You ever been hit by a 50-mile-an-hour
fastball in the mons pubis, Bowen?
- Nan. Come on.
- It's no picnic, Bowen.
Yet they don't make
protective cups for us. No, sir.
Went to the morgue to try to stop
the transfer of body, it was too late.
- Reason for doing that?
- Just wanted to see the deceased.
- Following a feeling I had.
- All right, first of all,
glad you're obsessed, that's healthy.
Second, get off the Internet.
Stop reading about these idiots.
Our profile isn't rising.
- Unless we fuck up.
- So don't fuck up.
I thought it might be time
to deliver the ring.
I can't hold on to it much longer.
[sighing] Okay.
Pay the sisters a visit.
Ask the widow about the cremation.
And give the other mother
her arts and crafts kit back.
- Okay, mons pubis.
- Yeah, you laugh.
- It's a real thing.
- [Bowen chuckles]
Hey, those shoes are gonna look great
on the local news.
[door buzzes, unlocks]
Like in the movies.
Who did this to you?
It's okay. It's fine.
It is not fucking fine.
Uh, okay, um...
Did you sleep at all?
[exhales]
How's the food?
- About how you'd expect.
- So, dog shit?
[both chuckle]
You know, Chloe would've been here,
I mean, you know, it's just--
It's complicated.
Michelle said Mom...
Chloe can, um, appeal the rule,
which is good.
They sent me a caseworker, a therapist.
Great.
Hey, that's good, right?
Well, you've been to therapy before,
haven't you?
[sighs] Couple of family sessions,
but then...
Well, it's good.
It's good.
To have someone to talk to, okay?
And it can be intimidating at first.
Um, but...
Oof.
If I'd started when I was your age,
you know, maybe...
[both chuckle softly]
You don't want to hold on
to secrets and stuff, okay?
It'll kill you.
It'll eat you up.
Okay? So, the most important thing
is you just show up,
get your ass in that chair.
[chuckles]
Okay.
Hey, um, do you mind not...
would you not tell...?
Hey...
I'm not gonna tell her.
It's a learning curve.
But, uh, it won't happen again.
I-I know what to do now.
[takes deep breath]
Are you... coming back every Tuesday?
I will be here.
As much as they let me, I will come.
[chuckles softly]
Okay.
[sighs]
[panting]
Oh, fuck off.
[sighs]
[pulsing, uneasy music playing]
[photographers clamoring]
- Hey.
- [Arty] Holding up okay?
- Yeah, I'm okay. Thanks.
- Good.
- [photographer] Chloe!
Chloe! Chloe!
[Arty] Get the fuck...
- Hey, get your hands off... Hey.
- [blow lands]
[indistinct chatter]
[Arty] Get the fuck out of here.
You're a motherfucking animal.
Hey, uh...
I'm sorry about outside.
Oh, it's okay, you know.
Thank you. Um...
- They're scary, those people.
- Yeah.
Asshole was lingering
around the lobby all morning,
but y-you don't need to see
things like that.
So I apologize.
No.
Not today.
God bless you. Uh...
Oh, I-I got your keys here.
- Yeah.
- Thanks.
[intriguing, percussive music playing]
♪ ♪
[inhales deeply]
[exhales]
[gentle, haunting music playing]
Much as I hated this thing,
you can't beat the view.
Remember that first spot we had on Eighth?
Above the cobbler/locksmith/barbershop?
[laughs] Yeah, that place was a front.
[laughs] Yeah, I never did get
a haircut there.
- Kitchen sink you could wash a goat in.
- [laughs]
Bedroom inexplicably had four doors.
I miss that place.
Oh, my God, the four doors. [laughs]
You look thin.
Do I?
You love when I say that.
Yeah, I do.
I haven't had much of an appetite.
They take their pound of flesh,
you serve it up.
Yeah, it's part of it.
Of course.
The bottomless pit
requires constant offerings,
and you give freely.
There's good in what I do.
What I give. What we give.
Not sure what good I was giving.
You think you would've been happy
if you'd have stayed at the D.A.'s office,
eating your wilted salad
from the diner over your desk
and making ten times less than me?
Clearly, you've done the math.
No, I wouldn't have been,
but being of service
rather than enabling
morally bankrupt scumbags?
Yeah, well, when you put it
like that... [chuckles]
A kept man or an empty one,
I wouldn't have been happy.
I had to get out.
We both did.
[camera shutter clicking]
Look at these assholes.
- [Chloe] Jesus Christ.
- [Adam] Make sure they get your good side.
They're both my good side.
You'd think they'd have got enough.
[Adam] You'll miss it when it stops.
[phone ringing]
[sighing]
Hello?
[Sanders] So,
this article...
I'm working on a response.
What Ethan needs is for you to keep quiet.
It's only gonna make it worse.
Well, for the moment,
it's put us in a good spot.
The court won't want to be a part
of this circus any longer than it has to.
Now, I'm waiting for an exact date,
- but it's likely the trial gets moved up.
- Up to when?
I don't know, could be as soon
as a few weeks.
Does that mean Ethan could come home?
As long as we all do our jobs,
so sit tight and lay low.
I'll text you when I hear.
[dramatic music playing]
[Chloe] Oh, my God.
[camera shutters clicking]
[sighs]
[photographer] Chloe! Chloe!
Chloe!
- [photographers clamoring]
- Hi, um, I'm Chloe Taylor. I live here.
Yeah, I recognize you.
Go ahead.
[♪ Brittany Howard sings "I Don't"]
♪ I don't, I don't...
Hi.
What-What's the,
what's the tomato smell in here?
I made gazpacho.
It's chilling in the fridge.
Okay, how is Ethan?
♪ Does anyone...
He was good. Yeah.
Same as yesterday but okay.
Okay.
Um, Michelle Sanders called
and said that the court
may want to move his date up
because they don't want to be
in the midst of all this.
- Amazing.
- It is, yes.
Also, um, Catherine has insisted
on our presence at hers tonight
- for the wake.
- Uh, Chloe--
I know. We can't get out of it, so let's
just, uh, pick something from my closet.
You can wear whatever you want.
[sighs] I have a dress.
Something black. Not too much skin.
Well, it's a good thing
I made the gazpacho.
We can bring it as a hostess gift.
Oh, please don't.
Okay, so... [sighs]
Who's gonna be at this thing?
Catherine said only people who knew
Adam, so a dozen max, I'd guess.
[sighs]
- [Nicky chuckles]
- What?
Nothing.
You look very... widow chic.
[scoffs] Thanks.
Is this appropriate enough?
Yes. You look f... You look really nice.
I've been wanting to get my hands
on this hair since I got here.
[Chloe chuckles]
It's so neat.
Well, I don't wake up like this.
- [laughs] No shit.
- [chuckles]
Listen...
Ethan is gonna start his therapy
with a caseworker this week.
He seemed a little nervous.
Well, you know, I guess, uh,
the best shrink
a correctional facility can buy.
Have you been to therapy?
Sure, along the way.
I do that, um,
Emotional Freedom Technique.
You know that tapping thing?
And how's that going for you?
Shut up.
[both laugh]
Oh.
What about Ethan?
Yeah, he went a couple times,
a family counseling session, but...
you know, just decided
he didn't-didn't need it.
Hmm. I just...
I would have thought, you know...
he'd been, seeing as...
- he's been through some shit.
- Yeah, when he was a kid.
Okay, I'm just relaying
what Ethan told me, and...
...you know, therapy doesn't make you
a weak person or whatever Adam...
- Hmm... okay.
- ...thought of it, which is--
Thank you. Thank you
for those wise words. [sighs]
You can stop right there.
Just, it takes a lot of work
to own your shit.
It's a... it's a process,
you know, and it's taken me
a long time, uh, to really--
Yeah, you know, it's always just, uh,
recovery porn with you people.
Isn't it? It's, uh...
my past and my, my problems
are so interesting?
I was there.
You don't remember everything.
Our childhood was not that bad.
You were just little for the worst of Dad.
[sighs] Your life
is shitty because it is built
on the bad decisions
that you have made, not Dad.
It's possible you don't know.
What?
What could I possibly not know?
He was an alcoholic, he got clean.
You never wondered why then?
Why'd he get clean then, Chlo?
I don't know, maybe he was trying
to, um, get his life together?
[laughs]
What father are you remembering?
Mom made him.
[sighs]
He got into bed with me, Chlo.
[laughing] What are you talking about?
He fell off the wagon,
and Mom didn't know,
but I did.
And he stumbled upstairs
drunker than usual one night.
And I was sleeping.
He came in, he thought I was Mom.
And he...
- he tried to put his dick in me, Chlo.
- Jesus Christ.
Nicky, don't talk about him like that.
It took me screaming and punching him
for him to realize who I was.
And then he begged me...
...not to tell Mom.
But I walked right down that hall,
and it's the wisest decision I ever made.
And Mom gave him an ultimatum.
And that's why she put locks
on the doors, Chloe.
That was why.
[sniffles]
Now?
You're gonna bring this up now?
As if we don't have
enough shit to deal with.
He d... No, no, he didn't think...
H-He didn't do that.
He-he-he would never have done that.
He would never have done that.
He didn't know it was you.
It was an accident.
[sniffles]
[doorbell rings]
[sighs deeply]
[sniffles]
Get the door.
Detective Bowen.
I almost didn't recognize you.
Ms. Taylor.
Ms. Macintosh.
I believe this belongs to you.
[Nicky scoffs]
Yeah.
Better all be here.
[Bowen] Oh, uh, and this.
Coroner's office sent this over.
We won't need it any longer
for the investigation.
Figured you'd want it back
as soon as possible.
[Chloe] Thank you.
They said, uh, you were anxious
to get the cremation done?
Called a number of times?
Yes, it was time.
We deal with the dead quickly
in my culture, too.
[Nicky] Is that all?
- Condolences--
- [Nicky] Good day.
His fucking culture.
All right.
You had him cremated?
It was what he wanted.
Come on, let's go.
We're gonna be late.
[gentle piano music playing inside]
[sighs]
[scoffs]
[knocks on door]
[sighs]
[door opens]
Hello.
Catherine, this is my sister Nicky.
Hi, uh...
Thank you for this to-do.
It's my pleasure.
It's good to meet you.
I'm sorry for everything
you're going through.
Gazpacho.
You don't have to heat it.
Well... [chuckles softly]
That looks great.
So do you.
Come on in.
[lively chatter]
Uh, you know what, just,
sorry, right off the bat,
I-I got to use the little ladies' room.
Powder room behind you.
[Nicky] Okay.
Oh.
Thank you. [chuckles]
What is Sid Evans doing here?
He's a reporter.
[Catherine] Mm, he wanted
to come show his support.
Completely off the record.
He gave me his word.
You know he's always had a thing for you.
Catherine, this is, this is just too much.
Chloe?
The board has decided
you're going to be taking
a temporary leave of absence
from The Real Thing.
What?
I tried pushing back, but I was overruled.
There won't be an official announcement
or press release,
just...
a couple of issues featuring guest editors
until you can...
manage your responsibilities again.
This is for the best.
Think how hard it was today
to get anything done.
Catherine, I am completely
capable of doing my job.
The decision has been made.
Now it's what you do with it.
Come.
They'll be wondering where we are.
[breathing shakily]
♪ ♪
[sighs]
Well, thank you very much for that.
And, um, appreciate you being here.
Would you excuse me, please?
Sorry, excuse me.
Chloe, oh, my God.
I am so sorry.
Oh, thank you so much, Afshin.
Adam and I were supposed
to play tennis today.
The alert just popped up on my calendar.
Oh, wow, well,
- reminders everywhere.
- Mm.
He really did enjoy
beating you every week.
[laughs]
Not every week.
- [Chloe] Excuse me, please.
- Sure.
[indistinct chatter]
[♪ "God Only Knows"]
[Bill] Oh, hello, my dear.
[Chloe] Hello.
Hi.
Nicky.
I'm Janie.
Catherine's daughter.
Okay.
- I'm s... [sighs]
- Oh.
I'm just so sorry...
for everything that you've been through.
May I offer you a martini?
Yeah, thank you.
Vodka or gin?
[server] These are gin.
Which do you prefer?
I like both.
But not together.
Don't go anywhere.
Do you like the threads?
Oh, I do.
I wore navy tonight
in homage to your husband.
You know better than I, the man
wore a simple blue suit
better than anyone else.
Mmm.
Yes, please.
Thank you...
Nate. Nicky.
See you, Nicky.
Wow.
Some vibes there, huh?
[chuckles] Well, wakes make people horny.
Ah, indeed.
[Bill] Tried to get Adam
to go to my tailor.
- He never would.
- [chuckles]
- And where's your husband tonight?
- [sighs]
His face.
It hasn't healed from the laser peel.
It's bad.
We're suing.
He sends his love, of course.
Oh, thank you.
[Janie] This is beautiful.
- I made it, actually.
- [gasps] No.
- Yeah.
- [chuckles softly]
- Made this, too.
- [gasps]
I made both of these, actually, yeah.
Aw, I love it.
Are these available?
Uh...
[chuckles]
I actually had
my biggest sales day ever
on my Etsy page today.
Oh.
- Mm.
- Got to...
- [Janie] Cheers.
- ...capitalize while I can, I guess.
Excuse me, Bill, I'm so sorry.
I need to check on my sister.
- Yeah, yeah. Yes, of course.
- I'll be right back.
[Jake] Sorry for your loss.
Hi.
- You okay?
- I'm fine.
Okay.
Now get the fuck away from me.
Okay?
[breathing deeply]
[laughs softly]
[breathing heavily]
[pensive music playing]
[phone chimes, buzzes]
[sighs]
[slow exhale]
[sniffles]
[Jake] So what'd they say? Any update?
Gentry assured me
they're quite pleased with our services.
Re-upped their retainer, in fact.
Three new stadiums in the Middle East.
They're gonna need a lot of hands.
[gentle piano music playing]
There you are. Come, let's get this done.
[indistinct chatter]
Thank you all for being here.
A small toast to Adam.
Well, yes, thank you all.
I do feel really fortunate...
for your love and support during this.
The last few days have been...
...terrible and confusing for our family.
How I wish I had Adam
to help me make sense of it all.
He was a...
...complicated man.
And I miss him terribly.
Would that he were here right now
trying to make us leave the party early.
[laughter]
[Chloe chuckles]
Cheers.
[gentle piano music playing]
Time to change 'em out.
My best friend.
- Nicky.
- Mm-hmm?
[whispering] Michelle Sanders texted.
They have set a trial date.
We should go.
Oh, really? Oh, does it start tonight?
Because they have
tiny tiramisu at this party.
What are you doing?
- Nicky, let's go home, please.
- You brought me here.
Now I'm staying.
We're celebrating Adam
and the great life he led.
With the people that...
knew him so well.
- Right?
- Right.
[Nicky sips drink]
[urgent music playing]
[Chloe] Can I bum one?
You doing okay?
No.
To be honest, I can't believe you're here.
You either.
Anything I say is gonna sound stupid,
which is why I'm out here.
[Chloe chuckles]
I'm sad for you all.
You know, I'm not hiding
my sister for my sake.
It's for him.
- For Adam?
- Ethan.
Ah.
It's that shit she put him through.
You want to talk about it off the record?
Or on.
[dark, mysterious music playing]
[bottles clinking]
[van door closes]
Howdy.
[atmospheric music playing]
That was a pretty fun wake.
[Nicky sighs]
[breathing heavily]
[Nicky giggles]
[sharp exhale]
[sighs]
Nothing.
[contemplative music playing]
[exhales]
[sets glass down]
[sighs]
[sets ring down]
[crickets chirping]
[van door opens]
[Nate] Hey. You sure you're good?
♪ ♪
[keys rattle]
[♪ America sings "A Horse with No Name"]
- [tires squealing]
- [Chloe gasps]
[Hank chuckles]
♪ It felt good...
What's the matter?
Come on.
[singing along] ♪ Na, na, na, na ♪
Yeah! ♪ Na-na ♪
♪ Na, na... ♪
[singing indistinctly]
[over radio] ♪ La, la, la-la-la, la, la ♪
♪ La, la, la, la-la-la-la ♪
[tires squealing]
[music echoing]
[sighs]
[latch clinks]
[water lapping]
[♪ M83 plays "Solitude"]
♪ Somewhere ♪
♪ back in time ♪
♪ I left a part of me,
I wanna see if you can try ♪
♪ to bring it back to me ♪
♪ You gotta go ♪
♪ where I cry ♪
♪ And take in all the tears,
I wanna see if you can try ♪
♪ Drink a little bit of me ♪
Jesus, Adam.
♪ No ♪
[hitching breaths]
♪ Just a little lonely ♪
♪ where I am ♪
[gasps]
♪ Take me back in time,
I wanna see if you can smile ♪
[line ringing]
♪ If I become a better man ♪
[phone buzzing]
♪ I need you ♪
♪ Now I know ♪
[Younger] It's her.
[chuckles]
♪ No ♪
- [gasps]
- [water splashes]
[mysterious music playing]
♪ ♪