But when the flesh
lusts against the spirit
and the spirit against the flesh,
the rational soul is supported
by the cross of Christ.
Nor does it, when seduced
by evil desires,
consent to evil doings,
for it is pierced
by the nails of continence
and the fear of God.
And, as at all times,
we must live worthily,
so at all times we must bear the cross,
which for each one
is rightly called his,
for it is born by each one...
I'm not feeling so good.
That's because you're hung over.
I can smell it.
We have supper.
She's been fasting all day.
I need your help.
And as a rule,
there is a greater danger
in the hidden betrayer
than in the open foe.
Is there a draft? I'll close it.
No, Father.
Are you with one of these two?
No.
Okay, turn around.
If you see me again
and I'm not smiling,
I don't think you're gonna like it.
Now get back in there.
Are you leaving?
Just to get some air.
You don't have to be polite.
I'm sorry. I didn't want
to lie to you in here.
I'm Father Gill.
I'm Peggy Olson.
- Katherine Olson's girl.
- Yes.
Yes, I'm having dinner at your sister's.
Are you a new priest?
I'm visiting.
So are you gonna come back in?
Yes.
Hello.
Good morning, Caroline.
Yes.
We're up.
Barbecue.
Right.
Caroline, we went over this.
Steaks.
And the kids can eat hot dogs.
Cancel.
I'm sorry. What?
I don't know.
Jell-O?
Do you want me to pick
something else up?
Cancel.
Caroline, hold on a sec.
I can't.
Caroline, I feel terrible about this,
but Don's not feeling well.
No. I'm sorry.
The 22nd?
Isn't that Easter?
Good.
Bye-bye.
What's with you?
I don't know.
I had an amazing dream.
You're always hogging the TV!
I don't like baby stuff.
Get out. We're... sleeping.
Get some Raisin Bran.
You can eat it in the den.
Out!
I should have locked the door.
Here's number 2, sir.
Thank you, Jeeves.
Why are we in the living room?
Because we live here.
What did I say about the stereo?
I wasn't touching it.
Bobby, I saw you do it.
- I didn't do it.
- Go watch TV, both of you.
I love this song.
His voice is like silk,
and you can really hear the words.
He makes everything
sound like Christmas.
In high school, I used to
love dancing to this song.
Come dance with me.
I thought we weren't
doing anything today.
Hurry. It's almost over.
I hate to think about your
reputation in high school.
Are you going to sit at the table?
Gerry, could you get it?
Jesus, Anita, I can't move.
Watch your language!
And I don't care if you have to lay there.
- Put your shoes on!
- Little Gerry, get my shoes!
Do you want me to get the door?
I can't reach my toes.
What am I supposed to do?
Hello, Father.
You're not leaving, are you?
Hello, Father. I'm sorry I'm late.
I went by Green-Wood to visit my son.
Well, I would love to meet him.
It's a cemetery.
Father, welcome.
Come, before it gets cold.
Hello, Father.
I'm sorry I missed Mass. My back is out.
He hasn't been feeling well,
but he did his part.
He watched the baby.
Well, I hope you feel better soon.
We all do.
I'm sorry. I gotta lay down.
Oh, please, please.
Oh, come.
Of course, Father.
Right this way.
We have you here.
Gerard! Mikey! Wash your hands!
They've disappeared.
Don't wait for them.
Father, would you
honor us and say grace?
Certainly. Why not?
O Lord, thank you
for this wonderful feast.
Thank you for these people
and this parish and their home.
That was beautiful.
Are you gonna say grace now?
Bless us, O Lord, and these thy gifts
we are about to receive from thy bounty,
and make us ever mindful
of the needs of others.
Through Christ our Lord.
Amen.
Okay.
Monsignor says you have
a beautiful singing voice.
And you play the harmonica?
The guitar.
I actually learned
how to play the mandolin
when I was in Rome.
And soccer.
Did you meet the Holy Father?
Not exactly.
It's kind of like being in Washington
and asking if you've met the president.
But you know
when he's in the building.
Aren't you gonna have one?
Should I?
Well, I'm not gonna drink by myself.
I'll get the sherry.
I'll get it, Ma.
I've always wanted to go to Rome.
Ah, yes, well,
Vatican City is one thing,
but then you realize you're in Italy.
Peggy works in Manhattan.
Oh, really?
What do you do, Peggy?
She works on Madison Avenue.
She comes up with the words
in advertisements.
They call it copywriting, Ma.
Father, I'm glad you're here.
I didn't know they knew what I did.
Stop it. No, you should see her work.
Lipstick, reducing programs,
feminine products.
Mom, not in front of Father.
She used to do her presentations for us.
She uses Latin.
I'm sorry to do this,
but I really should go.
Look at that.
Well, where are you headed?
I'll give you a lift. I have a car.
- To the Fourth Avenue BMT.
- Okay.
It is such an honor
to have you in our house.
And I'm sorry the chicken
was overcooked.
The chicken was perfect,
and you know that.
Go get the Brownie.
Let me wrap up some cake.
Thank you, but no, thank you, Anita.
You've all really made me homesick.
Father, would you mind?
Say "cheese."
- Cheese.
Brooks, have you made any decision
about our immediate future?
Believe it or not, Daddy,
Brooks has other interests
besides drinking.
That'll change.
Would you stop scaring them?
We're not scared.
Then how is it you've been engaged
for two months
and you're not running around
making wedding plans?
Because I told you.
We don't like the idea
of having a big wedding.
It doesn't have to be big.
We think it's silly.
You have to invite a bunch of strangers
to gawk at us
to somehow prove
our feelings for each other.
You know, it's embarrassing.
Brooks?
Whatever she wants.
Well, your mother wants a wedding.
Mommy had a wedding.
I did.
Wearing that dress,
my sister and my mother
fussing over me.
It was the best I ever looked in my life.
The Pierre.
I was drunk, and I didn't
have a glass of champagne.
Gliding around in your father's arms.
You know how good a dancer he is.
Dancing with Grandpa.
I don't want you to miss that.
What are you getting?
I'll have the mussels
with garlic if you do.
That's sweet.
Thank you for the ride, Father.
Peggy, wait.
Yes?
I want to ask you about something,
and it's personal.
Okay.
I have the honor of delivering
the sermon next Sunday.
It's Palm Sunday. That's a biggie.
I mean, you're on deck for Easter.
And, well...
you said you did presentations.
Can I run some things past you?
I don't know what I could tell you.
You must do this all the time.
Well, I've done it,
but your monsignor
is a tough act to follow.
I don't know that I'm your audience.
You were leaving,
and we ended up
having supper together,
and you're the only
person in this parish
that knows about public speaking.
This is how God works.
I find that if I'm prepared
and I have confidence
in what I'm selling,
that kills the butterflies.
That's good.
I'm prepared.
Do you have any other tips?
Well, pick somebody
and make eye contact with them.
You'd think it would make you nervous,
but it really focuses you.
Don't they have stuff that
you're supposed to talk about?
Yes, they have stuff.
Let's just say I'm covered
in the content department.
I can only speak for myself,
but the sermon is the only part of Mass
that's in English,
and it's very hard to tell sometimes.
Maybe be simpler?
Give us a chance of understanding.
Thank you for the ride.
I should go. I really do have to work.
Idle hands.
It's good to know you.
Have a great week.
I hate my feet.
I love your feet, Mommy.
Feet? I thought those were water skis.
Stop it.
Stop it! Stop it!
Stop it!
Great.
You broke it.
I didn't mean to.
You're being wild in the house.
It's late.
Everybody, brush your teeth
and go to bed.
I'm hungry.
You're going to bed.
We didn't have any dinner.
It's 7:30.
Okay. Come downstairs.
I'll make you some grilled cheese.
Go.
- Go. Go. Go.
- Come on.
And my wife says, "Duck and cover."
Well, look at this.
Marty, meet Vicky.
Hello, Marty.
- Hello.
- I've heard so much about you.
But you didn't tell me
about his wonderful head.
What about it?
Someone thinks a lot.
Well, look at that. It's love at first rub.
My head has been known
to make wishes come true.
Don't get up.
This is Marty Hasselbach,
from Gorton's.
Nice to meet you. Roger Sterling.
We were due to meet
tomorrow anyway.
- Love that frozen scrod.
- Thank you.
I'm Vicky, Marty's wife.
Aren't you a lucky man.
Yes, I am.
We were just discussing the male head.
Is that right?
I like the Yul Brynner look.
She does seem to.
I keep threatening
to shave him one morning.
Just hop in the shower
and take it all off.
Is that right?
How long have you two been married?
Five years.
Second time around. That explains it.
It's nice to meet you.
I hope to see you both tomorrow.
A pleasure.
Mr. Draper, Mrs. Barrett
is here at my desk.
No. Of course. Send her in.
Mrs. Barrett.
To what do I owe the pleasure?
May I take your coat?
No, thank you.
I'm not sure how they
do it in show business,
but around here
we have this nifty gadget
called an appointment book.
I was in the neighborhood.
What did Jimmy do now,
ask Eleanor Roosevelt
how fast her husband
ran the hundred-yard dash?
How are you?
Busy.
I have an idea for a television show.
Congratulations.
Is it too early to have a drink?
Let me call for some ice.
No need.
How do I make this happen?
Where do I go?
What is it?
Everyone loves Candid Camera, right?
Hidden camera situations.
Only Jimmy's the host,
and he's Jimmy, you know?
Not nice.
It's derivative, with a twist.
That's what they're looking for.
It's called Grin and Barrett.
That's cute.
I thought it up all by myself.
ABC's sick about losing Candid Camera.
But you'd have to get Jimmy
out of his contract with Utz.
I thought about that.
It's exclusive,
but they could come on as sponsors.
Show needs a national sponsor.
Utz won't do you any good.
You're a pessimist.
They could let him out.
They should want to keep Jimmy happy.
They don't care.
But they could be told
that their spots
would have more punch,
wherever they air,
if Jimmy's on a hit television show.
That is very good advice.
Will you sell the show for me?
I'm not interested in doing that.
But I can talk to the Schillings.
What's this?
I was thinking how I could avoid
becoming bored with you.
Bobbie. I have work.
Bullshit.
It's good.
But we should sell them
on the mascot first.
The jingle's going to be a cutie.
Hasselbach's at 3, right?
Is he bringing the missus?
Mary, that'll be all for now.
Roger...
there is a Mrs. Hasselbach,
and that's not her.
I see.
That makes sense.
I've got her number if you want it.
I've got lots of numbers.
No. That's okay.
Keep up the good work.
Daddy!
You need to shave.
Some people weren't so good today.
What happened?
Bobby broke the record player.
The repair call is going to be $18.
9 if you want to put it in your car
and drag it over there.
I don't.
When I asked him about it,
he said he didn't do it.
He lied to my face.
Where is he?
In his room.
Go on out.
Mommy says you broke the hi-fi.
I believe her.
Don't do that again.
I won't.
That's it?
I said to him,
"Wait till your father gets home,"
and that's what he gets...
"Go to sleep."
He knows he did something wrong.
First the shenanigans
with the washing machine,
and now the record player.
Don, you have to do something.
He needs a spanking.
How else is he gonna learn
the difference between
right and wrong?
That's not the way it works.
You think you'd be
the man you are today
if your father didn't hit you?
Can I get something to eat?
You left this by the bed.
I'll do it.
Draper residence.
Good. You're there. It's Duck.
Sunday morning.
Where else would I be?
Shel Keneally called me late last night.
American Airlines already scheduled
a bunch of pitches for this week.
Why are we on the calendar
for two weeks from now?
We're not anymore.
I got us Good Friday first thing.
Most of the team's already here.
The rest are on their way.
My hand!
Hello?
Let me look.
It hurts.
I walk out of the room
for ten seconds?
Mommy, make it stop.
He needs to go
to the emergency room.
That was Duck Phillips on the phone.
American Airlines
moved up their presentation.
- So?
- So I have to go in.
Damn it.
One child in the emergency room
is enough to deal with.
Take Sally.
Send Sally to Francine's.
It's Palm Sunday.
I am not about to impose
on Francine today.
I want to go with Daddy.
Hello, Father Gill.
Come in.
- Come in.
- Father, welcome.
I'm terribly sorry, Anita, Ms. Olson.
I can't stay.
- Oh, no.
- Oh, that's terrible.
We have Tom, Roberta Callahan,
Mrs. O'Neill, Mrs. Casey.
Yes, I'm afraid Mrs. Marchetti
has taken a turn for the worse.
I hope you'll forgive me.
Oh, that poor woman.
Let me fix you a paper plate.
Peggy didn't make it?
Oh, she's sick.
Oh. Well, could you give her this?
It is a copy of my sermon.
She helped me quite a bit,
and I would love for her to see it.
Peggy helped you write something?
Just some tips, really.
It was very good.
I felt like I was the only one
you were talking to.
Well, thank you.
Again, I'm sorry.
It's so nice he's taken an interest in her.
Come, let's eat.
Mr. Phillips and the others
are in the conference room.
I see you've brought a little helper.
Betty had her hands full today.
Sally, be good for Miss Holloway.
Keep her away from the paper cutter.
Friday morning,
the American Airlines folks
will join us at 10.
Roger will handle the introductions.
Mr. Cooper, Mr. Sterling,
Creative to the right,
Accounts to the left,
starting with myself, then the American
Airlines people, then Campbell.
Pete, you're next to our man Shel Keneally.
There will be one for each of them.
We can't get cordovan by Friday,
so we're going with maroon.
Campbell will run the show.
He has a list of every ad
we need in the presentation.
Art Department needs to make sure
that every image we use in a comp
is an airplane that American has.
No cutting and pasting
planes from other ads.
They may all look alike to us, but...
Why are you here?
I'm head of the Television Department.
We have 90 minutes to present.
I'll do the setup...
the history of American Airlines
up to and including the crash.
I'll tee up Creative
with what research says
travelers are waiting
to hear from American.
And then, Don, you do what you do.
Maybe you could give us a little peek.
I'm not ready to do that yet.
I say we show all three campaigns,
eliminate all possible objections.
Something for everybody.
Remember, this isn't the work
we have to run in the end.
This is about winning these guys over.
Creative.
In my office.
You have big ones.
My mommy has big ones, too.
And I'm gonna have
big ones when I grow up.
I don't care if we're
just selling a point of view,
but we have to commit to one thing.
They don't like wiggle room.
They like to see us
blowing up bridges behind us.
These are the boards
for the 60-second television spots.
Music you can talk over.
Stewardesses.
We're gonna bookend every spot
with the plane taking off and landing
up, down, no problems,
everything okay, every commercial.
Where's that list
Duck's buddy Shel gave us
with all the things that
make American different?
What's that?
The ad you asked for
to recruit stewardesses.
It equates what should
be a glamorous job
with being a waitress in a tin can.
Where's the bar of soap,
the ticket sleeves?
Who's doing the in-flight menu?
I think it's the best menu I've ever written.
This is in French.
How do I know it's right?
It's right.
Make up a chef.
Peggy, did you pick out
a china pattern yet?
Did you find the one
from the Queen Mary?
Yes. But there needs to be a decision
if we're doing anything to the logo.
I don't know.
We got a lot of bricks,
but I don't know
what the building looks like.
So how are you, Vicky?
I'm in a very good mood.
Well, I hate to sound remedial,
but I haven't done this
since I was in the Navy.
Been with a girl?
No. Not that.
Don't worry.
The prices may have changed,
but the menu's still the same.
Well, your invoice ran across my desk.
Look at you.
The menu hasn't changed.
Is it open for negotiation?
I don't want to ruin the magic.
How about double... plus carfare?
And I'll assume you live far away.
That'll be $100.
But I want everything I want.
Isn't that the perfect thing to say?
That's not so bad, is it?
I have to warn you,
I'm not in great health.
Don't believe what they say.
No one dies doing this.
Are you resting?
Everybody's resting.
No. I'm thinking.
Let's have a conversation.
Is that your maid?
No. She's my girlfriend.
Do you kiss her?
Sometimes.
Do you lay on top of her?
You know what, Sally?
Your daddy's gonna be angry
if I don't do my work.
Okay.
Just a minute, girls.
It's almost your turn.
You know, we'll get to go
anywhere American flies.
Familiarization.
We'll have to rent another floor.
We'll all have our own offices.
Do you realize we will get to pick out
the stewardesses?
Okay.
Son of a bitch.
Stupid little...
You there.
Chewing your cud.
It's one thing to be unladylike.
It's another to treat our office
like a subway platform.
Pack up your Wrigley's and go home.
How could it be my gum?
My gum's in my mouth.
This place is a zoo.
Thank you for getting him
out of here for the day.
Lose the gum, then get
yourself some dinner.
He won't remember firing you.
American Airlines is not about the past
any more than America is.
Ask not about Cuba.
Ask not about the bomb.
We're going to the moon.
Throw everything out.
Everything?
There is no such thing
as American history,
only a frontier.
That crash happened
to somebody else.
It's not about apologies
for what happened.
It's about those seven men
in the room on Friday
and what airline they are
going to be running.
So what does that mean?
Let's pretend we know
what 1963 looks like.
Jesus, Draper, make a decision.
What's that leave us with,
introductions?
If I can't mention the crash,
there's no preamble at all.
Let it go.
Our job is to bend down the branch.
Let him pick the fruit.
That champagne
is probably near frozen.
I'm meeting a friend.
You know what I really want?
Is there something we left out?
Have dinner with me?
I told you I'm meeting a friend.
I'll pay for his meeting, too.
You wouldn't think dinner
would be pushing it on the extras?
Have you been to Lutèce yet?
I have.
I think you'd like it.
I've got it.
It's great, but they're cheeky.
They started with this
prix fixe menu at lunch.
8.50 for lunch.
And they have these wines.
What kind of wine do you like?
I don't know. Red?
They're going to make you be
more specific than that.
We can walk, if you don't
mind a little rain.
You know what?
I love the sound of cabs
whooshing in the water.
Shall we?
Isn't this a nice town?
Absolutely.
She's here on a Sunday,
and I respect that,
but you know she's earning
more than all of us.
Come on.
Up.
Good night, ladies.
Thanks for baby-sitting.
I'm going home. Be good, Peaches.
Your sister wants to talk.
Hey, Pegs.
Okay.
It was good.
He gave us a copy
of his sermon to give to you.
Okay. So long.
It's nice that he can get to know her
without all her troubles.
She's such a beautiful young girl.
She does whatever she feels like
with no regard at all.
You're too easy on her.
You know that.
Is Gerry warming up the car?
Shel Keneally was fired this morning.
What?
The rest are on their way in.
What's going on?
It's over.
So why are they coming in?
Because they have to.
And we have to deliver a stillborn baby.
Mr. Phillips, the gentlemen are here
from American Airlines.
Send them in.
In the name of the Father, the Son,
and the Holy Spirit, amen.
Bless me, Father, for I have sinned.
It's been two weeks
since my last confession.
I took something
that didn't belong to me.
Go on.
I was in the Laundromat,
and I took some coins off the machine
and used them.
I took the Lord's name
in vain three times,
and...
and I am so angry, Father.
I am so angry at my little sister.
She's causing my mother so much pain.
She had a child out of wedlock.
She seduced a married man.
It's a terrible sin,
and she acts like it didn't even happen.
And I hate her for it.
And I feel so guilty about it.
But everyone keeps
falling all over themselves
trying to help her.
And she goes on
like nothing happened.
Nothing at all.
What about me, Father?
My troubles?
What about me being good?
For what?
I understand it's difficult.
You know it's not your place to judge.
God sees your goodness.
It doesn't feel that way, Father.
Try to trust God on this.
You will get your reward in heaven.
God loves you,
and he knows that you love your sister.
I do.
Say three Hail Marys
and two Our Fathers.
And try to forgive your sister.
She's not as strong as you are.
Would you like to make
your Act of Contrition?
O my God,
I am heartily sorry
for having offended thee.
I detest all my sins
because I dread the loss of heaven...
Cooper walked them to the elevator.
They acted impressed.
I just can't believe it.
Here. You should have this.
No regrets, fellas.
We were in it.
That's the important thing.
It's heartbreaking.
Still, good work, Don.
Come on.
We hired him to bring in new business,
not lose old business.
Don't you love the chase?
Sometimes it doesn't work out.
Those are the stakes.
But when it does work out...
it's like having that first cigarette.
Head gets all dizzy.
Your heart pounds, knees go weak.
Remember that?
Old business is just old business.
You're home early.
It's Good Friday.
How did it go?
It didn't.
Bobby, stop playing with the robot.
Do you want to talk about it?
No.
How was your day?
My father called. He's doing better.
He and William played golf yesterday.
William made a show of paying for it.
Bobby, what did I just say?
It was a accident.
You don't listen. Don, do something.
Is that what you wanted?
You take no responsibility
for anything that goes on in this house.
I pay the bills,
put clothes on your back,
your damn stables.
Don't you dare.
I'm here all day.
Alone with them, outnumbered.
What about Carla?
Doesn't she count?
It's not her job to raise our children!
I'm here, and then you come home
and get to be the hero.
You want me to bring home
what I got at the office today?
I'll put you through that window.
Brush your teeth. It's bedtime.
Bobby, it's not a good time.
I'm sorry.
It's okay.
Dads get mad sometimes.
Did your daddy get mad?
He did.
What did your daddy look like?
Like me.
But bigger.
What did he like to eat?
Ham.
And this candy.
It tasted like violets.
Had a beautiful purple
and silver package.
What did he do?
I told you. He was a farmer.
But he died.
A long time ago.
We have to get you a new daddy.
Come here.
You have nothing to say?
What do you want to hear?
Something.
Anything.
How about you're going
to help raise these children,
not be one?
Bets,
you do whatever you want.
It's not about what I do.
He's a little kid.
My father beat
the hell out of me.
All it did was
make me fantasize
about the day
I could murder him.
I didn't know that.
And I wasn't half
as good as Bobby.
Happy Easter, Peggy.
Hello, Father.
I read your sermon. I liked it.
It was very colloquial.
You were very helpful.
These kids.
For the little one.
Subtitled By J.R. Media Services, Inc.
Burbank, CA