[theme music playing]
[Flora, echoing] She hasn't moved.
[Miles, echoing]
Are you certain? I don't like this.
[Flora] Neither do I.
[Miles] We're not arguing, it's just…
It's more that I don't see
how this is part of the game.
[Flora] People shouldn't bleed in games.
Oh, see?
Here she comes.
[in clear voice]
Were you tucked away just now?
- [muffled moans]
- [Flora] Where did you go?
If you don't mind me asking.
But why not?
- [Dani crying]
- She's our friend.
[screams]
- [Dani screams]
- She's worried. Look.
[screaming]
[Miles] She can't even hear you.
I think she'd feel better
if you told her this yourselves.
[Dani continues moaning]
Come on. She's scared.
[panting and crying]
[panicked moaning]
[Dani whimpering]
What's the matter, Miles?
Like I said,
this feels wrong.
You know…
life is a bit funny in that way.
Sometimes,
right can seem wrong,
and wrong can seem right.
[Dani continues moaning]
But that's the difference
between children and adults.
Seeing the big picture.
Now, you can see it.
And…
I already know that.
Like the bird at school.
You see…
that felt wrong,
but it got you back home to Flora,
and she needed you home.
So, you did what you had to do
in order to keep Flora safe.
It's not the same.
Oh, heavens, no. No.
Helping someone be quiet
is not even a little bit
the same as the bird.
- But you've done nothing wrong, okay?
- [Dani panting]
[Peter] Both of you.
- Nothing wrong.
- [Miles] She's hurt.
[Peter] No, she's not hurt. She's just…
scared.
[Dani crying]
She doesn't know yet…
there's nothing to be scared of here.
Please, don't be frightened.
C-Can't you just tuck her away?
Somewhere nice,
till she feels a little bit better.
[Dani moaning softly]
Where would you like to go,
if you could pick anything?
- The best thing you can remember.
- It's not quite that simple, Flora.
Why not?
Well, she's never gone
dream-hopping before, has she?
I mean, it takes a little practice.
Remember?
She's very clever.
She'll learn fast.
Faster than me, I think.
[Rebecca] It's different, Flora.
It's not quite the same.
- [Hannah, echoing] Priceless heirlooms.
- It's… It...
Um…
- Well, I mean, it...
- [Hannah, echoing] Priceless heirlooms.
- They're not missing, they're stolen.
- [Rebecca] Well…
- Um, it's…
- [Dani moaning]
- [Hannah] They're not missing.
- I mean, um, it's…
- [Hannah] They're stolen.
- I…
- [Hannah] Priceless heirlooms.
- Becs, you're slipping.
Becs, Becs, you're slipping. Stay with me.
Becs! Becs!
[Dani breathing rapidly]
It's okay.
It's okay, kids. She's just, uh…
she's dream-hopping a little.
She'll be back.
The important thing is…
is we need to figure out
- what to do with our friend here.
- [muffled moaning]
I mean, she could get us
in a lot of trouble, couldn't she?
So, we need to find a way…
to help her…
but also…
maybe make it so
that she could dream-hop, too.
Wouldn't you want that for her?
For her to learn?
[Dani] No!
It isn't always very convenient,
and I don't like it much
when it happens unexpectedly,
but, the other times,
it's perfectly splendid.
- [crying]
- [melancholy music playing]
You'll like it.
But…
there are different keys, aren't there?
[knocking on door]
[loud knocking]
[Peter] That's Hannah, at the door.
Right, Miles,
I need you to say exactly what I tell you.
What?
- When she knocks again, I need you...
- Knocks?
Again, I need you to talk to her,
but don't open the door,
and you say exactly what I tell you.
I don't hear any.
Any knocking, I mean.
- [Peter] No.
- [pounding on door]
[Flora] He's hopping away.
- What should we do?
- [pounding continues]
[Flora] We never can tell,
just when you're going to be back.
[jarring musical crescendo]
No.
[woman] That's what you say to me.
All this time,
that's what you say.
And look at this.
Look at you.
You're... You're out?
I'm out.
How long this time?
[woman] Forever.
Well, I suppose they'd say I'm cured.
[chuckles softly]
They did.
They said I'm cured, free to go.
Wasn't much truly wrong to start with,
but here we are.
What do you want, Mum?
Just a little help.
Trying to get started fresh.
It's difficult.
And the doctors,
they don't give you anything.
Not even a note.
Nothing to say you're well.
Petie, I'm scared.
If I can't get my own place,
if I can't get my own job, well…
doesn't leave me a lot of options.
And where do I go if not your father?
He sent you, didn't he?
You know, he'd kill you if he could.
For what you did to him.
For what I did to him?
He says it all the time.
I just said I didn't want
to have to turn to your father.
After all he did?
Or to the streets. Where do I go?
Did you practice this together, did you?
I mean, where do I go?
To your father?
To the street?
To your boss?
You're shaking me down?
Lord Henry Wingrave, I presume.
[chuckles softly]
Amazing how far you've climbed.
He wound you up,
and now you're shaking me down.
I suppose those juvenile records,
he might not even know.
Sealed, aren't they?
How odd him not knowing.
I don't have any money, Mum.
- Oh, you're not a rich man, Petie?
- No.
Just work for one, do you?
- Forgive me if I misread.
- [jarring crescendo]
[Hannah] Priceless heirlooms.
They're not missing, they're stolen.
My apologies. Missing and stolen
are interchangeable in my speak.
But I'm afraid stolen heirlooms
are the least of it, ma'am.
What do you mean?
Well, Mr. Wingrave asked us
to make a full report,
and, uh, it appears that Mr. Quint
was quite the burglar,
and that, well,
I suppose he's been embezzling.
[scoffs] Of course he has.
[sighs]
Did he say anything at all
to you, Rebecca?
- Even the slightest hint.
- There a reason he'd confide in you?
[Rebecca] Well…
we-we were… I…
- I mean, I-I was...
- Mm. Got it.
So, did he?
I… um…
Rebecca, please. If you know anything,
anything at all, you have to tell him.
No, he…
He said…
[sighs] Well, he mentioned something
about having some money.
- [Hannah] Mm-hm.
- Just a little bit of money, maybe?
Quarter million pounds?
- What?
- No.
- He just said to pack a bag.
- Pack a bag?
Yes.
That we were going to America, together.
Sounds lovely.
All he said was that he had a plan,
and that we would live
in the States together.
- And this all made sense to you?
- I didn't know...
On a butler's wage?
- He isn't a butler.
- [scoffs] Didn't raise any alarms, then?
No.
Not like you're saying it now.
And you're certain he didn't say
where he got this money from?
- No.
- [constable] No, you're not certain?
- Or no, he didn't say?
- He didn't say.
Not even to his girlfriend?
Just pack a bag.
No explanation beyond that?
Nothing at all?
I can't help you.
[scoffs] I'd have thought he'd tell
his girlfriend
- if he gave a damn about her.
- No, he wouldn't...
If he loved her,
I'd think he'd tell her more.
- He wouldn't just...
- Maybe not, since he did leave you behind.
- He wouldn't run away!
- [jarring crescendo]
[crying]
- [breathing shakily]
- [fire crackling]
[Miles] You're right.
Miles, you should be in bed.
[Miles] I couldn't sleep. I don't…
I feel like
I might never sleep again, frankly.
I heard what he said,
the policeman, before he left.
Flora and I listened from the stairs.
It's nothing to worry about, okay?
Go back to bed.
You're right.
He didn't run away.
We told Hannah and the policeman,
but they didn't believe us.
Didn't believe what, Miles?
About the monster.
The monster that took him,
and it was awful,
and we thought he was…
But he's still here,
so it's actually all right.
He told me to tell you not to worry.
So, don't worry.
He's still here.
Miles?
[Rebecca pants]
- Miles!
- [jarring thud]
[Hannah] Why don't you use a mixer?
Save you some elbow grease.
[Owen] A mixer? Do I look like an amateur?
A mixer damages the gluten molecules,
Hannah, my dear.
[Hannah] Oh, would it?
- Not the gluten molecules.
- [Owen] Baking is just chemistry.
[Hannah] Oh, well, so is mopping floors.
One part bleach, two parts water,
and lots of lovely washing-up liquid
for the lemon scent, of course.
Seriously, just throw it
in a bloody mixer.
[Owen sighs]
What is that?
Dough.
Uncooked dough?
Brilliant, I'm starving.
Well, can't rush genius, Jamie.
See, a mixer would damage
the gluten molecules, and we mustn't.
God help us all if those gluten molecules
aren't tippety-top.
You having one of Owen's
cooking physics classes again?
Oh, yes, a fine lecture.
It's chemistry.
- Mm.
- [Jamie] Certainly is.
What's that?
Hi, Rebecca, love.
Lunch is gonna be late today.
Something about gluten atoms.
I'll let the children know.
Why don't you stay?
Sit with us and have a brew?
The kettle's still warm.
[Owen] Uh, kids can handle 15 minutes
by themselves.
[Rebecca] Um…
I'm not thirsty, thanks.
I think I'm going to get some air.
Feels quite warm today, doesn't it?
[footsteps receding]
- [Owen sniffs]
- [melancholy music playing]
[birds chirping]
How you doing, chick?
Here to gloat a little, Jamie?
Tell me you were right about him.
Not just a shite but a thief,
it turns out.
Is that what we're doing here, is it?
Not here to talk about him at all.
Someone should point out
that this is a moment for you.
A moment you have been waiting,
and waiting, and waiting for.
And it is finally here,
and you're too busy moping to even see it.
I thought I should speak to that.
Cause I'd want someone
to do the same for me.
What are you talking about?
Go and speak to our phantom boss.
Tell him you want that pupilage
you talked about.
All this drama?
Quint? The imposition of it all?
He could do right by you, right now.
Get you back on your barrister track.
Get you back
to whatever goal it was you had
before you even knew
what a Peter Quint was.
Well, that's…
Sorry to see you hurt so much.
You don't deserve it.
And I'm sorry to see it.
And if there is anything at all
that I can do to help,
please tell me.
I'd be happy to do so.
Thank you.
[Rebecca sighs]
[insects chirping softly]
[sighs] Hm.
Becs.
What…
- Where the hell have you been?
- Quiet, please.
You said you were coming back.
You said to pack a bag!
- They're gonna hear you, please.
- Good! They should hear me.
They should call the police
because you stole.
- I know. I just...
- You stole from them, and I…
My God, I said I would come away with you,
and you made me an accomplice.
You would have turned me
into a criminal, too,
and I would have been fucking clueless.
- It's not like that.
- You left.
- I didn't.
- Not even a note.
- I never... Mm.
- Never what?
You never loved me.
- Y... You never told me the truth.
- No, I never left you.
I was here,
this whole time,
but I... I couldn't…
[breathing deeply]
You couldn't see me, not right away.
I had to figure out a way to make it so…
So that you could see me.
Oh, you'll need to do better than that.
- Much better than that.
- Becs, don't come…
[scoffs] What is it?
- Afraid I'll hit you?
- No.
- You don't think you deserve it?
- Because you do, Peter...
- Please, just listen!
Just for one moment.
[Peter panting]
I never left you, Becs.
I won't.
I wouldn't leave without you,
and I-I won't leave without you now.
That's why I'm here.
I'm sorry.
I'm sorry we were apart, uh…
however long that was, I don't…
I don't even know
how long that was that…
What does that mean?
This is going to upset you.
Upset?
Oh, I'm much more than just upset.
Please, just…
hold out your hand.
What?
Why?
Just hold out your hand.
[Peter takes deep breath and sighs]
And please…
Please think…
What's the one thing…
the only thing…
that would ever keep me from you?
[melancholy music playing]
[swoosh]
[Rebecca gasping]
[whispers] I…
[Miles] May we be excused, Miss Jessel?
Miss Jessel?
[Hannah] Rebecca?
Are you still down here?
Are you all right?
Yes, um, I suppose.
- The children are asleep.
- Oh, I know. I know.
[Hannah sighs]
I'm worried for you, love.
I... I'm fine.
[Hannah] Hm.
Fractions, eh?
[chuckles]
Oh, yes.
[exhales]
Hated those when I was a little girl.
- Flora, um… She's quite good at them.
- [Hannah] Oh.
You know, uh…
a friend once told me something
about fractions, and…
grieving her breakup.
The maths of it.
How long it takes to grieve it.
Right, and what was that?
They said it's the length
of a relationship, halved.
- Halved?
- Mm.
To get over it.
The length of a relationship, halved,
which for you, well it…
it really isn't that long now, is it?
Well, not everything has a half-life,
does it?
[clock ticking quietly]
Quite right. [sighs]
[Rebecca, whispering] Peter.
[louder] Peter?
Gosh, it's been all I can do all day
not to just come up here.
Knowing you're up here
while I'm down there, it's just torture.
I know. I know.
I can see you in the classroom.
Couldn't risk it, you know,
'cause of the kids.
I've been thinking.
What if… [sighs]
What if we still did it?
Did what? [chuckles]
Went to America.
I know, just…
we do it anyway,
and… and people can think I'm some
batty old witch who talks to thin air,
- but at least we'd be together.
- [chuckles]
I can't leave Bly.
I can't get past the end of the drive.
I walk and I run, and the moment…
[sighs] The moment I reach
the edge of the property,
I'm right back here.
Inside. Right on the spot where it…
Will you tell me now?
How it happened?
No.
[ghostly whooshing]
You're right there.
You're right there,
and I can't even touch you.
[crying] I can't smell you,
I can't feel you. No, it's not fair!
- Shh.
- It's not fucking fair! [sobbing]
- You're here. I can hear you...
- Shh! You've got to be...
- [Rebecca] Quiet, Becs!
- [ominous crash]
[music box playing "O Willow Waly"]
Becs?
[Rebecca pants]
[gasping]
[jarring crescendo]
[Rebecca breathes heavily]
- Please.
- Peter?
- Oh, hell.
- What?
Wh-Where was I? What just happened?
I don't… I don't know.
[knocking on door]
What the hell?
What is that? Can you hear that?
[Rebecca] I-I was…
- All of a sudden, I-I was somewhere else.
- [pounding]
[Peter] What's that knocking?
What did you do to me?
What is that?
[pounding grows louder]
[jarring crescendo]
Oh, no.
That's what you say to me?
You're here, again.
And look at this.
Look at you.
- Look at this.
- No. No, enough.
Enough.
[breathing heavily]
Back.
Back. I have to go back.
Have to go back.
[jarring crescendo]
[music fades]
[footsteps approaching]
Hey, where have you been hiding?
Hiding?
You look better of late.
Did you speak to Henry?
Henry?
About working for him in London,
like we talked about.
How could I forget? Oh, yes.
I called him.
Thought you said you were gonna visit,
do it in person.
I changed my mind.
- Well?
- Well, what?
Well, what did he say?
Uh, just…
that he'll consider.
Consider?
For real?
Twat.
He owes it to you.
Are you okay?
Yeah.
[door closes]
[sighs]
[birds chirping]
[takes deep breath]
[haunting boom]
[grunts]
[somber music playing]
It didn't work.
No.
- [Hannah] Wait.
- [Flora giggles]
- [indistinct chatterand laughter]
- [Flora] Can I try doing it?
[storyteller]
Peter had not been back to find her.
He had left her at the boundary of Bly.
[Flora] Miles, stop it!
[storyteller] The boundary impossible
to walk through together.
[Flora] Miss Jessel!
Miles, stop!
[storyteller] And though she didn't
much like losing time being tucked away,
at least she had company there.
His company.
Peter?
Peter.
[lamp switch clicks]
[whispering] Becs.
Where the hell have you been?
- It's been almost a week.
- [in normal voice] I'm sorry, I…
I've been learning. I've been e...
exploring.
What? Where?
Here, at-at Bly.
I've seen things. I've seen, um…
You trust me?
I need you to trust me,
because I have a plan.
A plan that'll let us be together again.
And touch each other,
and… and-and taste each other.
So, um…
these little…
little hiccups when I'm inside...
I don't know if I like those,
being pushed away into a memory.
No, I know. I don't like them, either.
You always push me...
- Yeah, but I don't try to.
- I know.
But that's the thing, it's…
It's temporary.
It's just a blip.
But what if there was another way?
A way…
for us to be truly together,
fully together?
- How?
- Well, that's the thing. [chuckles]
It's like those other times, like those…
little blips,
but I think if-if it works, that…
If it works, it could last forever.
It would be the two of us…
sharing a life.
I don't understand, but how?
Well, it's simple.
I think a lot simpler than you think, but…
It just boils down to you.
It's up to you.
That's why those…
little blips never take.
That's why
I keep getting pushed out, because…
Because you didn't invite me in.
You just need to decide that it's forever.
Permanent.
Uh... I…
H-How would I even…
- What...
- I-I don't know, I…
I don't know e-exactly, but…
But I think it's just, well…
I think it's just you…
and me…
b-becoming us.
It's you.
It's me.
You'll take care of me, yes?
Of course.
And we'll be together?
We'll share it all, everything. Equals.
I promise.
I love you, Peter.
I love you, Becs.
[sighs shakily]
[Rebecca] It's you.
It's me.
It's us.
[inhales sharply]
[moaning]
[sighs deeply]
[jarring static]
- [music box playing "O Willow Waly"]
- [Rebecca] You all right?
[Peter] Yes, just, um…
Let me show you how beautiful you are.
- [shutter clicks]
- [camera whirring]
- Can I see?
- No.
- [laughing]
- [Rebecca] Come on.
- [shutter clicks]
- [camera whirring]
- [laughs]
- [Peter] Come here, come here.
Turn around. Come here.
[kiss]
- [shutter clicks]
- [camera whirring]
[Rebecca sighs]
[kiss]
[melancholy music playing]
I'm…
I'm tucked away again, aren't I?
- Yes.
- I…
I-I thought... I thought we'd be together.
But we are.
Peter.
[storyteller]
He had promised they'd be equals.
But she was safe,
tucked away in a memory of them,
where they could be together.
And he was here, alone.
And he had spent
too much of his life alone.
[water lapping]
[inhales and sighs deeply]
It's us, Becs.
- [water lapping quietly]
- [nocturnal chirping]
[emotional music playing]
[Rebecca gasps]
[muffled screams]
[water gurgling]
[unsettling music playing]
- [nocturnal chirping]
- [water gurgling]
[rain pattering]
[Rebecca sobbing hysterically]
No!
[screaming] No! [crying]
[sobbing continues]
Hey, Flora.
What are you...
[gasps] Fuck.
Okay.
You're okay.
You're all good.
- [ghost] No!
- [Rebecca] Whose is that?
[Peter]
Henry said this was yours, if you want it.
- Took a little convincing.
- [distant sobs]
I'm persuasive when I need to be.
[music box playing "O Willow Waly"]
- You can be convincing.
- [Peter chuckles softly]
[Peter] You know, fur like that,
you have to feel it on your skin.
You have to.
Once in your life.
There's nothing like it.
[Rebecca] No, no.
Not this one.
Not this one, please.
[cries]
Let me show you how beautiful you are.
[Rebecca] Oh, no.
Please, not this. Not this memory.
It's not a memory, Becs. I…
I just thought it would make you happy.
[Rebecca] But it was.
- [shutter clicks]
- [camera whirring]
I just kept getting tucked away.
I know.
- I know.
- [Rebecca] Because you hid.
You…
Y-You... You hid from me, a-after the lake.
You hid,
and-and I just keep coming back here.
[Peter]
Let me show you how beautiful you are.
- [shutter clicks]
- [camera whirring]
Let me show you how beautiful you are.
[shutter clicks]
Because you left.
So beautiful.
- [shutter clicks]
- [camera whirring]
[Rebecca sobs] You left.
After the water came into my lungs,
- you just left.
- So beautiful.
[sobbing] You just left me to do it alone.
This isn't what you said.
It's not what I agreed. I…
I-I didn't…
I didn't agree.
- Beautiful.
- I…
[shutter clicks]
- [camera whirring]
- Beautiful.
[melancholy music playing]
I had to.
[Rebecca] What?
[Peter] I'm so sorry.
But I had to, so that…
Well, so that we could be together.
Fucking son of a bitch!
[screaming] You fucking lied!
You're a fucking liar!
- I had to!
- [Rebecca] No!
- I'm sorry, but I had to.
- [Rebecca sobs]
And you'll have to, too.
How dare you!
- Look, you'll understand.
- [knocking on door]
When…
[knocking]
[sniffles]
When you... When you meet the others.
When you see
what happens to us here, Becs.
- [pounding on door]
- Please.
[pounding continues]
Now, I-I-I know,
I know that there's a way out.
You proved that. We've proved that
- there's a way for...
- [pounding]
How?
- Please, not now.
- How?
Not now.
How? How do I get out?
- I'm gonna show you. I'm...
- [pounding on door]
Damn it, I was right in the middle…
[pounding on door]
- [pounding growing louder]
- [unsettling music building]
[breathing heavily]
No.
And look at this.
Look at you.
Again, we have to do this?
I was in the middle of something,
something important.
I doubt that.
You know the others?
Well, they seem to go to lots places,
don't they?
Becs, the kids.
They get to hop around
into the warmest little memories,
the nicest little moments.
And I always end up here.
Is that so bad?
It's hell.
It's like I'm in hell.
Well, where else would you go?
At first, I thought…
[pensive music playing softly]
this-this isn't so bad. I mean, it…
could've been worse.
I mean, I could be back there at home,
with Dad.
I could've been tucked away
in one of those nights.
But then I started to realize
why this was worse than that.
Why this was hell.
Because I... I was a kid back then.
I didn't understand
what was happening to me.
I didn't know what it meant, and…
And you were there.
You were there
to tell me that it was okay.
That what he was doing…
was okay.
You said I was being silly.
That's what you said.
But I was innocent, wasn't I?
I didn't know any better.
But here, this time…
Well, I know better, don't I?
This time, seeing you
in that fucking doorway…
I've thought about every kid
that ever spent the night.
And how you knew what you knew,
and you didn't stop him.
[sobbing breaths]
Why didn't you stop him?
He'd kill you if he knew where you were.
You killed me, Mum.
You killed me asking me to do this. I…
I did what you wanted.
And it killed me.
I hope you know that,
late at night,
that you killed your own son.
Honey, I don't even know that you're dead.
But I was…
I was... I was right…
in the middle…
of something.
[Dani groaning]
Thank you. [sobbing] Thank you.
Flora? Flora, hurry.
- Please, hurry.
- [unsettling boom]
Please, keep going.
- [Peter] Stop it.
- Please.
- [Peter yelling] Stop right...
- There! Stop it, Flora.
- No, no, no. [muffled cries]
- She has to stay where she is.
Sorry! Sorry!
- [Dani] Flora.
- Sorry.
Is it?
The minute I'm gone,
you're spinning these kids up.
- You're taking...
- Advantage of their good intentions!
- [gasping breaths]
- Shameful.
You're supposed to warn me.
- I'm sorry, I had to.
- I don't like it when you don't warn me.
I know. I'm sorry, okay?
I'm sorry, I didn't mean to.
It won't be like that anymore, okay?
- I promise.
- [Dani sobbing softly]
I'll explain, but it won't…
[Rebecca] Peter?
How long was I…
Oh, you're back.
- Are you okay?
- [Dani moaning]
Oh, you're back.
I'm sorry.
No. No, no, no, it's okay.
It's okay. I slipped away, too.
But we're back now.
We're back.
And we're almost done.
We have to finish it now.
- No, no, but it's too soon.
- No, but it's right.
It's right.
A little longer, we…
We should give them a little longer.
We're out of time.
She'll take them. We're out of time.
[Miles] What are you talking about?
Well…
it's what we've been talking about
this whole time.
That…
- special thing, that…
- [Dani gasping]
…one last thing
we've been asking you kids.
The forever house.
[Peter] That's right.
It's time?
- It is.
- ["O Willow Waly" playing]
But why can't we just keep it
the way it is?
Those… Those little hiccups
aren't so bad.
I know, but it's just…
Well, Miss Jessel and I,
we just need a little more from you both.
It's like what we've talked about,
remember?
That special present
that will let Miss Jessel and I, well…
Well, let us be your friends.
Your best friends, forever.
And it's gonna save us.
It's gonna save us from…
well, you know what.
But I-I thought you said that...
I-I know what I said, Miles.
But we have to finish it now, okay?
We have to.
[Rebecca] Peter.
Maybe we can wait until…
Wait until what, Becs?
What? Until we fade away?
Until we look…
- Like this?
- [woman gasps]
[Dani yells]
'Cause that's what's gonna happen, Becs.
This is what will happen, Miles and Flora.
You don't want that
to happen to us, do you?
To Miss Jessel? To me?
No. No, of course not.
Because this is what happens
to everyone who dies here at Bly.
- [Dani screams]
- [Miles] It's fine.
- [woman cries out]
- [thud]
But not with your help.
[Peter] You…
You both can save us.
You're gonna help us break out
with that game we've talked about so much.
Jailbreak?
That's right, jailbreak.
I'm still not sure this is a good idea.
[Dani sobbing]
Miss Jessel,
do you promise this is a good idea?
Flora, I…
[gentle piano music playing]
Look, I know it's scary, but…
we're out of time.
And so, Miles, I need your help,
and Miss Jessel needs you, Flora.
Isn't that right?
It's easy.
You just have to…
think as hard as you can.
Think about you,
and me,
and then think us.
As hard as you can, just think… us.
- [Dani crying]
- [Peter] You have nothing to worry about.
Nothing at all,
'cause you're gonna be tucked away.
In the forever house, just like we said.
- With Mum and Dad?
- That's right.
With your loving Mum and Dad.
[Flora] You promise?
When we get tucked away,
we'll be tucked away with Mummy and Daddy?
That's right.
[Flora] We'll be with Mummy and Daddy,
and they won't fade, right?
That won't happen to them.
Because they died somewhere else.
They'll keep their faces, and so will you.
And it will be happy.
And then everyone will be just…
You promise?
We promise.
Now, both of you,
as hard as you can, think…
[breathing deeply]
Flora…
look at Miss Jessel,
and, Miles, look at me, and think us.
- [Dani moans]
- What about Miss Clayton?
- What will happen to her?
- Nothing bad.
Nothing bad, I promise you that.
See, Miss Clayton?
There's nothing to worry about.
I'm going to the forever house
with my mum,
and it's going to be just…
perfectly splendid.
[muffled] No!
Yeah, that's right.
- Go and see Miss Jessel.
- [Dani crying out]
I still don't feel...
No, no more pain.
No more sadness, ever, ever again.
No more school, no more bullies.
I'm gonna take all of that.
I'm gonna take it all.
Nothing sad will ever touch you,
ever again.
You just get your mum and your dad…
and a safe place.
With two people who love you so much.
So much.
That makes you
the luckiest man in the world.
The richest person.
I wi... I wish…
I wish I could be that rich.
So, have pity on me.
[Dani panting and sobbing]
Go on, be a good lad.
[Dani yelling] No! No!
It's you.
- [Dani whimpering]
- It's me.
It's us.
- [screams]
- [thud]
No!
[Dani screaming]
[Dani crying]
- No!
- It's us.
[thud]
[Dani screaming] No! No!
[sobbing]
[haunting echo]
Becs.
[panicked breathing]
Becs, is that you?
Oh, God. It's so strange, isn't it?
- It's so strange.
- [Dani whimpering]
We just…
Do you feel her?
I do, a little.
Miles is just, well…
He's just a little tickle now, isn't he?
Way at the bottom.
[Hannah, distantly] Dani! Children!
[Dani screams]
We've got to put that one away for good.
Becs, can I trust you to finish this one?
I'm still not sure why we have to.
[Dani moaning]
[Miles] Because she knows.
It's okay.
Just keep her quiet,
and I'll do it myself.
- [Hannah, distantly] Flora! Miles!
- [Dani screams]
- [Dani] No!
- Coming!
[Dani panicking]
I'll be back. Don't go anywhere.
[Hannah] Miles!
[Dani gasping]
Oh, there you are. Where is everyone?
Hannah, you beautiful, beautiful thing.
[scoffs]
I have a surprise for you.
Would you come with me?
All right, but where are we going?
I'll show you.
Come.
[Hannah] So, where... Where are we going?
[Miles] You know…
[nocturnal chirping]
I've been wondering
what makes you so special, I mean…
I know it's disorienting at first,
but y-you've…
- You really made it difficult, didn't you?
- Hm?
Walking around. Day to day.
Cleaning up and dreaming up new clothes.
Carrying on like nothing happened.
I thought you were just stubborn,
but it was more than that, wasn't it?
I asked the others.
They say it takes… a moment.
We're all on our own time,
it seems, but you.
You just kept on dreaming.
Then, I worked it out.
I realized who you reminded me of.
[chuckles] What are you talking about?
We're almost there. You'll see.
I was thinking about a cartoon
I used to watch when I was little.
- [Hannah] Oh, well…
- [Miles] Wile E. Coyote.
[Hannah chuckles] Hate to break it to you,
Master Miles, but you're still little.
[Miles chuckles]
Wile E. Coyote, remember those?
It would happen all the time.
He would run off a cliff.
Run straight off it.
And he'd keep on going.
That's you.
That's who you remind me of, Hannah.
You just went off that cliff,
and you just kept going.
Carrying on.
Cleaning the house,
dreaming up new outfits and earrings,
the whole thing.
- What on earth are you going on about?
- But the thing is…
when Wile E. Coyote looked down…
then he'd fall.
Only when he looked down.
You just need to look down, Hannah.
Then you can stop this charade.
Just fall already,
into whatever dream you like,
while your face melts away,
like some forgotten memory.
[inhales sharply]
Don't be ridiculous. Come on.
- Let's go inside.
- No.
I have gotten so sick of watching you,
strutting around like this.
No, you need to be put in your place.
You need to look down.
[breathes shakily]
[sobbing quietly] No, no, no, no, no, no.
[haunting echo]
[ominous music playing]
Meep, meep.
[music intensifying]
[Owen]
This is an opportunity to hone my skills.
In Paris, I was a sous-chef, which means
they only let me chop vegetables.
Here, I'll be putting
everything together myself.
It'll be a great learning experience.
You'll have two children to cook for.
I don't know
that's the type of experience you want.
Miles is seven, and… [chuckles]
…bloody picky.
Flora's five and a darling, but…
Miles is gone.
And Flora might be, too.
And there's nothing...
nothing I can do about it, because… [sobs]
Because I'm dead.
[Hannah sniffles] Oh, God.
[sobs] Oh, God.
Oh, God.
- [melancholy music playing]
- Oh…
[Dani breathing heavily]
[whimpering]
[breathing shakily]
How did I do?
You did very well.
- [panicked breaths]
- She told me to pretend.
He couldn't see her anymore.
So, she told me what to say.
Untie her, Flora. Quickly.
I still don't understand.
I thought we were playing a game.
- And I thought you needed my help.
- [Rebecca] No, Flora.
No one should ever need that much help.
Not from anyone else.
Miles?
It's too late.
It's too late, but not for her.
Get her away from here.
You get her as far away from this house
as you possibly can.
Go on. Quickly.
[panting]
Thank you.
[suspenseful music playing]
[ominous musical swell]
- [Flora] What about Miles?
- [Dani] It's okay, okay?
We gotta get out of here.
- [Flora] Where are we going?
- [Dani] I don't know, anywhere. Anywhere.
No! I don't like this game!
- [yells] I'm not leaving!
- Shh! Flora!
And you can't make me!
- Shh!
- [screaming] Miles!
- We gotta go!
- Miles, where are you?
[frightening music playing]
[Flora screams]
[closing theme song playing]