Blue Calamari is
still in the lead,
but Ample Parking is making strides,
and is now in fourth, third,
and holding second place, while
Blue Calamari is at a steady speed.
And down the stretch they come!
Ample Parking comes from behind.
And it's Ample Parking by a nose.
This is the last call for the third race.
You may still wager if you hurry.
Here's your information
on the race...
Out of the way.
Cripple coming through.
Sixth race at Golden Downs.
I'll take the two and the four.
Hey, that's my birthday.
February 4, 1963. Do you
think that's a good bet?
What's your birthday?
Take your time. Don't worry.
There's only 30 seconds to post.
Is there any way I can bet
on the six and the three also?
You know, for the year? All four horses.
Can I do that?
He wants a $2 exacta box, two,
four, six, three. Give him $24.
Your turn.
The ninth at Gulf stream Park.
$500 on the three horse,
Seminole Uprising to win.
Might as well burn your money.
I'll burn my winnings.
Bigger flame.
Same race, Termigator to win.
Sorry, race just closed.
Damn it.
She was 14-to-1, too.
Then fatass over there
just saved you money.
No way Seminole Uprising's...
I don't bet on the horses.
I bet on the jocks.
My rider's bulimic,
purges after his weigh-ins.
Leave a two-pound pile
at the starting gate,
shaves valuable time
off that final eighth.
Nice to have
inside information.
By a length.
The Burning Bush
and on the level is Candy,
right up on the inside
is Bowfinger...
And Termigator
pulling up against the rail.
Is anybody here a doctor?
Trying to cop a feel?
I took a CPR class at the Y.
That would be useful if she was having
a heart attack instead of a seizure.
Seizure? Hold her tongue down?
If you wanna get a finger bitten off.
Call an ambulance.
Methodist's three blocks down.
- I could drive her.
- Just make the call.
- What the hell is that?
- How should I know?
Tell the paramedics to take
her to Princeton-Plainsboro.
Her doctor's name is House.
And it's Termigator,
winning by two lengths.
Since when does House
hang out at OTB?
The man's an addict.
Right, addicted to pills,
not gambling.
It's the same thing.
Drug abuse, drinking, gambling.
They all fire up the same
pleasure centers in the brain.
An addict is an addict is an...
Gambling doesn't take away
his pain.
It does when I win.
Hot OTB babe has grand mal
and inexplicable bruising.
What up with that?
You were just standing there,
and she started to seize?
Spend as much time
around the real people as I do,
someone gets sick.
Her platelets are 89,
she's anemic.
And she has
a blood alcohol level of 0.13.
Hot OTB babe?
Obviously a working girl.
Probably an STD infection.
No fever. No infection.
Alcohol abuse explains it all.
Causes seizures and affects
her blood's ability to clot,
which causes bruising.
Start her on heparin,
she'll be fine by morning.
Except for the fact that the
bruises are not petechial,
which means it's not DIC.
So the bruises were caused
by trauma.
She probably got beat up
by her boyfriend. Or her pimp.
What's that called when you judge
someone before ever meeting them?
She's a regular at OTB.
Somehow, I don't see her holding down
a 9-to-5 and going to PTA meetings.
I was there.
I have a 9-to-3 job.
It could be SLE, familial
telangiectasias, or even Cushing's.
- Good. Start with those.
- Which one?
Cushing's. It explains
the seizure and the bruising.
Not the anemia.
So she doesn't eat
a lot of meat.
DIC brought on by alcohol
abuse is far more likely.
Do a full workup, H and P.
And lab her up, LP, MRI.
Did you just ever so subtly order
me to get her medical history?
Cuddy put me in charge
last week, so, yeah.
It was a pretend in charge, a formality
to get past the suits in legal.
Right, those licensing-board folk
love to play dress up and pretend.
Hey, no worries. I'll let you keep
your parking space.
You can have it. You'll also need
my handicap placard.
Bend over.
You make
a pretty convincing argument.
Chase killed that woman.
Now Foreman's in charge?
Yeah, we have
a pecking order here.
If Cameron kills somebody,
Chase takes over.
There's a flow chart
in the lobby.
For the next three weeks, you
answer directly to Dr. Foreman.
And I expect you here
for grand rounds at 9:00.
By the way,
I like sugar in my coffee.
If there's a screw up,
it's your screw up.
You won't have Dr. House
to fall back on.
"Do you wear a seat belt?" Is that
really relevant to a seizure?
Skip it.
How about,
"Were you vaccinated for polio?"
I think you gave me
the form intended for FDR.
You really like
Teeny Tiny Mo in the fifth?
I went 4-for-6 yesterday.
You want winners?
Cure me first.
"Are you generally satisfied
with your life?"
It does not ask that.
You know, I was gonna ask
what a respectable doctor
was doing at an OTB parlor.
Somehow that question
doesn't seem relevant anymore.
- What's your excuse?
- It turns me on.
Yeah? What else
turns you on? Drugs?
Casual sex? Rough sex?
Casual rough sex?
- I'm a doctor. I need to know.
- No sex.
Just moved here.
Haven't even found a job yet.
Don't know anybody.
Came here without a job.
That means you didn't move here, you
moved away from somewhere else.
Does that hurt? No.
Are you on any prescription meds?
Hormones? Prednisone?
I already answered that one. I think it
was question number 20-something.
Well, yeah. And I could
reach down and get it.
But that would kind of spoil
the whole cool move.
I'm not on any medications.
- Are you a vegetarian?
- No. Why?
Because you might have something
called Cushing's syndrome,
which basically means...
My pituitary
is overproducing ACTH,
which is causing my adrenal glands to push
too much cortisol into my bloodstream.
What a coincidence.
I'm a doctor, too.
Yeah, I had it last year.
They did brain surgery, removed
an adenoma from my pituitary.
What did you just say?
"You were right, House. Her pituitary
tumor regrew. It is Cushing's.
Uncanny how you do that."
Actually,
it was Cameron's idea.
No, Cameron had three ideas.
I chose one to encourage,
to nurture...
Yeah, you're all about
the nurturing.
Do you need a hug?
I don't see any regrowth.
You get her medical records
faxed over?
Work smart, not hard.
That's my philosophy, boss.
I'll take that as a no.
Anica, I need you
to stay completely still.
Sorry.
Still don't see anything.
Okay, so it's a microadenoma.
Too small to see.
So small, it's not even there.
Right. It's just a coincidence
that I predicted a rare condition
that she happened to have
a year ago.
Results from her LP back yet?
Didn't do an LP.
I knew what she had.
Go do the LP.
Okay, I need you to roll over on
your side, kiss your kneecaps.
Party time.
I thought it only took
one doctor to do this.
I'm observing.
She's here to make sure
I don't paralyze you.
You've done this before, right?
Successfully?
He's kidding.
He's an excellent doctor.
I'm going to numb
the area with some lidocaine,
and then we're off
to the races.
See what I did there?
I used horse-racing jargon to make
the patient feel more comfortable.
Okay, here we go.
Felt like bone. Does that hurt?
A little bit.
What are you doing?
Try rounding your back
a bit more.
You're perfect
just the way you are.
Oops, that was all me.
Might want to move down
one vertebra.
This is actually much harder
than I remember.
My chest feels a little tight.
Try taking a deep breath.
Dr. House, maybe I should
take it from here.
Eighth time's the charm.
You trying to piss off Foreman?
Just let...
BP's 240 over 140.
Turn that thing off, will you?
Take the needle out.
- Take the needle out!
- Okay.
It's a hypertensive crisis. Start
her on an IV lopressor drip.
Titrate to systolic less than 140.
She'll be fine.
Cameron. Meet me in my office.
At the risk of sounding
redundant and right, again,
she has Cushing's. Cushing's.
Right, the fact that you mangled
her LP has nothing to do with it.
Actually, it has
everything to do with it.
Cushing's plus stress
equals hypertensive crisis.
Smart move, sending the rookie.
Her initial symptoms could have
been caused by alcohol-induced DIC.
She had a hypertensive crisis
because it's been at least six hours
since she had her last drink.
She's detoxing.
The exact same moment that I'm
futilely trying to give her an LP?
Right. An invisible tumor on her
pituitary is much more likely.
What if the tumor
is somewhere else?
There could be an ACTH-secreting
tumor on her lung or pancreas.
It's awfully rare.
Not as rare
as an invisible tumor.
Why didn't they put you
in charge instead of Foreman?
Oh, yeah, you're the guy
that killed that woman.
Get a pan-man scan
before she dies a cortisol OD.
Fine. Do it.
But when you don't find anything,
put her on a Librium taper
for the withdrawal and get
her a bed in a rehab clinic.
Lungs look clean.
Her lymph nodes
are not enlarged.
Cuddy tapped Foreman
to run the department.
- I didn't even get asked.
- Neither did I.
- You were suspended.
- I was kidding.
It's the irony of women in charge.
They don't like other women in charge.
What? You think
it's something else?
You sabotaged yourself.
You went on a date with House.
You slept with me. Putting you
in charge of this department
is like a sexual harassment
suit waiting to happen.
Yeah, they're really worried
that I'm gonna create
a hostile work environment.
Maybe that's the problem.
Being in charge means
having to say no to House.
Would you hire you for that?
Anderson coming out strong.
What is he thinking?
He watched
what Tom Mants just did.
You ordered MRis
for the entire maternity ward?
I was in a crazy mood.
Good thing I got
a new boss to back me up.
Although, I think one of
those is actually necessary.
Better comb through
before you cancel them all.
What do you expect me to do,
House? Quit? Cry?
Actually, I expect you
to act like what you are.
My employee. My subordinate.
My bitch.
Well, since you asked nicely...
My God.
I can't believe I got more than a year
behind on my discharge summaries.
Got to get caught up.
Oh, no, wait.
I'm not authorized to sign
these anymore. Only you are.
Keep it coming.
I'm not gonna break.
Scan showed a mass
on her pancreas.
Looks malignant.
Probably inoperable.
I'd give her two months.
On the bright side,
it still means I was right.
Where's Dr. House?
Dr. Foreman's
overseeing your case.
He thought it'd be best
if I spoke with you.
We found a mass
in your pancreas.
It looks like cancer.
So something in my pancreas
caused me to have a seizure?
Probably.
But the bigger point is...
A one-year survival rate for
pancreatic cancer is less than 20%.
So what's the treatment?
We need to biopsy the mass to
see what we're dealing with,
and then we can
recommend options from there.
Sounds good.
I need your consent
to do the biopsy.
Thanks.
Wish me luck.
Good luck.
It was weird.
She barely reacted at all.
I've had people hug me
and people take a swing at me.
This was more like
she didn't even hear me.
Magnify three times.
House assisting.
That is funny.
Too bad Foreman's gonna die.
Good afternoon, I'm Dr. House.
I'm gonna be looking at your...
Perfect.
Excuse me.
Need Dr. Foreman in exam
room one for a consult.
So, when did this start?
Couple weeks ago.
I didn't want to get pregnant. Jake's not
into rubbers, so I got on the jelly.
You think I'm allergic
or something?
You have an infection.
I'm gonna need a sample.
I brought the jar.
No, I meant a sample of your...
Okay. We have
a neurological problem here.
There's something wrong
with my brain?
Oh, yeah.
Cover yourself up.
Got what I need.
What's up?
Smell this.
Smells like vaginosis,
but it's not really my call.
Great. I'll be sure to put a gold
star by your name on the board.
Anica's biopsy for pancreatic
cancer was negative.
Okay, I'm gonna give you
some antibiotics
and you probably shouldn't
have sex for a while.
How long?
On an evolutionary basis,
I'd recommend forever.
The mass in the pancreas is benign.
It's probably just scar tissue.
Good news. She's not sick at all.
Other than being an alcoholic.
The labs you sent yesterday put her
ACTH at 64 picograms per milliliter.
She's got Cushing's.
Something set it off.
It's gotta be in her brain. Set
her up for a venous sampling.
There is another possibility.
Chase, hold on.
How'd you get him trained
so fast? Electronic collar?
Got treats in your pocket?
She didn't even read the consent
form for the pancreatic biopsy.
Who reads those things?
Maybe she didn't read it because she knew
that there was nothing wrong with her.
There is another explanation
for the Cushing's.
Maybe she injected herself with the ACTH.
Her behavior suggests Munchausen's.
She's had four hospitalizations
in the last four months.
Well, being hospitalized a lot certainly
points to nothing being wrong with you.
She's had zero symptoms
since she got here.
The scarring on her pancreas
could be caused from injecting
herself with the benzene
and setting off the seizures.
She's had brain surgery.
You can fake a stomachache.
You can't fake a brain tumor.
You can fake an invisible one.
We should check her apartment.
Look for medications, syringes...
- Venous sampling's easier.
- And more dangerous.
- Not if you get caught breaking in.
- So don't get caught, House.
Why do you think Cuddy
picked Foreman over me?
Have I done something wrong
or is there...
Will it make you shut up if I told you
she wanted someone black?
How would you describe
my leadership skills?
Nonexistent.
Otherwise excellent.
There's more to being a leader
than being a jerk.
The world will never know.
No. No way. It just snowed.
Yesterday.
The streets are clear.
My car is right there.
There's construction on Elm.
Bike will be faster.
There's even books
in the bathroom.
Well, either she's very smart or
she has a severe fiber deficiency.
She's got an appointment with
her ophthalmologist on Tuesday
and an appointment with her
gynecologist on Thursday.
Multiple appointments
with multiple doctors.
Symptom of Munchausen's.
Or, just thinking
outside the box here,
she has a vagina
and trouble reading.
There's three pairs of reading glasses,
each with different prescriptions.
Which would be explained by a tumor
pressing on the optic nerve.
Because you're looking
for her to have a tumor.
And you're looking for...
A person with Munchausen's
syndrome drinks battery acid.
But they don't go to an ophthalmologist
to get their pupils dilated.
An ophthalmologist is a doctor.
Attention is attention.
How many hospitals have you contacted?
Has one doctor said she's crazy?
- It's not Munchausen's.
- It's not your call.
If you think
she's got Munchausen's,
then obviously you got
something to show the man.
A syringe in her apartment.
A bottle of ACTH.
Munchausen's patients are good
at covering their tracks.
Right. So, the fact that we found
nothing proves there's something.
Look at the pathology reports from
the surgery she had in Chicago.
They removed 30% of her pituitary.
They found no tumor.
It's possible
the surgeons just missed it.
In that kind of surgery, you're
just cutting and hoping...
Of course, we're both right.
Excellent solution,
everybody's happy.
Come on, step up, Foreman.
If you think I'm right, order me
to stick a needle in her brain.
If you think Cameron's right,
send the patient home.
Either she'll be fine,
or she'll die.
Do the venous sampling.
Get her consent.
Nice move, boss.
Way to cover your ass.
I just agreed with you.
Not because
you think I'm right,
you're just taking
the safe route. You're a wuss.
Don't worry,
your secret's safe with me.
Hey, Wilson,
guess what Foreman just did!
Hi.
This is a consent form to
stick a wire into your brain.
It's important for hospitals to
get these signed for procedures
that are
completely unnecessary.
- Then why are you doing it?
- Because you're mentally ill.
You injected yourself with ACTH to induce
Cushing's to get attention from doctors.
And so far, it's worked.
I'd like to see another doctor.
- I'm not giving you what you want?
- I don't want a bitch.
Just sign the forms, okay?
And I'll get out of here.
Hopefully for you, whatever you
injected yourself with won't wear off
before you get the fun of a caring and
concerned doctor cutting into your head.
You chose me to make House
miserable, didn't you?
Apparently, he's making you miserable.
That's impressive.
Find someone else.
No.
For the first time
in six years,
I'm getting copied on all
experimental tests and procedures.
Clinic hours have been
logged and completed.
You've given me four months
of House's dictations
so I can finally bill
insurance companies.
I only did that stuff to prove
he couldn't make me miserable.
Well, way to go.
Now everybody's getting
what they need, even House.
He gets to play mad scientist, and
this department runs smoothly.
So I'm stuck with this
for the next three weeks.
Maybe longer.
Would you be interested
if this wasn't just pretend?
What did Mommy say? I don't
get any candy in my stocking?
Patient being prepped
for the venous sampling?
Yeah, a mentally ill patient is right
on track for a pointless procedure.
Yeah, we get your objection.
Foreman. Are you sure?
That doesn't make any sense.
Check it again.
We gotta delay
the venous sampling.
Why? Her urine turning orange?
How would you know that?
Because
that's what rifampin does.
She's not on antibiotics.
But if a Munchausen's patient
thinks she's about to get busted,
she sees pills labeled "Dangerous,
might cause seizures",
she might grab a couple.
And if that label were accidentally
on a bottle of antibiotics,
and if that bottle were
accidentally left in her room...
- You set her up?
- Might have. It's Munchausen's.
All this, she did to herself.
I don't know what the hell
you're talking about.
I had a seizure. I'm sick.
I need your help.
Not from this department.
The half-life
of rifampin is three hours.
After that, you'll get your psych
referral and your discharge papers.
You know, just because you stick
your fingers down your throat
doesn't mean
the rest of us are screwed up.
I guess when cooperation fails,
you move on to hostility.
I didn't do this to myself.
100% commitment.
Sign of a good liar.
Also the sign of a sociopath.
What are you doing?
Correcting your last note.
We can't discharge her
if she's sick.
Anybody ever tell you,
you write like a girl?
What? You got some other explanation
for orange urine?
- It's Munchausen's.
- Correct, but not complete.
You just don't want to admit
that she skunked you.
At the end of The Boy Who Cried
Wolf, the wolf really does come.
Then he eats the sheep,
and the boy, and his parents.
- The wolf doesn't eat the parents.
- He does when I tell it.
You're not telling
the story now. I am.
Look, I checked her records.
All her hospitalizations
were for different things.
Brain tumor, fainting spells,
skin rashes, seizures.
She's had every
blood test known to man
and the results
are all over the map.
There's only one constant,
low HCT.
- The anemia's real.
- There's a million things
she could have taken
to have done that.
True, it could just be her MO.
She self-induces two illnesses. One
always changes, one never does.
Or maybe she has Munchausen's
and aplastic anemia,
which would mean,
without proper treatment,
she'll continue
to get sicker, weaker,
eventually she'll start
bleeding internally and die.
- She's not getting sicker.
- She will.
If her bone marrow was dying, the
entire blood panel would be affected.
- Her white count's normal.
- So far.
- We need to do a bone marrow biopsy.
- No. No more tests.
Look, you kick her to the curb
with a Munchausen's diagnosis
you're guaranteeing that no doctor
will ever listen to her again.
We do more tests, we'll only
be feeding her psychosis.
The more attention we give
her, the more she'll want.
What if she doesn't know
we're testing her?
House, you were wrong.
Live with it.
There's probably some blood
left over from previous tests.
Blood tests alone
can't confirm aplastic anemia.
Yes, I know. That's why I want
to do a bone marrow biopsy.
But blood tests could show
a systemic disease.
- A virus or a toxin could be the cause.
- Fine.
You want to test the extra blood?
Knock yourself out.
But the patient is off-limits.
And if the results
are positive, I get my biopsy?
It's the safe way to go.
I need all of these tests
and a PCR done on this sample.
You're gonna need more blood.
Patient's empty.
Then I can't do it.
You can try.
I can try to look like Salma Hayek,
that's not gonna make it happen.
You may not have Salma's ass,
but she doesn't have your eyes.
Yeah, right.
How soon you need it?
Dr. Wilson, can I talk to you
about something in confidence?
- Of course.
- It's about House.
Oh, then no.
Fine. I won't say anything.
Do you think there's any way House
would take me seriously as his boss?
Where is this coming from?
Did Cuddy say something?
We talked. She intimated.
And you want my advice
on how to usurp him?
It's very ancient Rome, you'll
need a toga, of course, a sword.
It's not a coup. I just want to figure
out some way we can work together.
I mean, I keep the team running from
an administrative point of view,
House doesn't have to
deal with the red tape.
It's a win-win.
I'm sure he'll see it that way.
Do you have any advice
on how to approach him?
- How to deal the guy?
- No.
But you won't tell him
we talked?
No.
There is no way
this is going to happen.
Epstein-Barr titers
are through the roof,
the most common viral cause
of aplastic anemia.
So what I'm saying is...
- Fetal hemoglobin's also elevated.
- Just a wee bit.
Could indicate...
You see that in sickle cell.
Not all sickle cell
patients are black.
None of her other blood panels showed
any sign of sickle cell, which means
either something's changed drastically
since yesterday, or this isn't her blood.
Of course it is.
Metaphorically.
Look, I couldn't do the tests.
I tried, but there wasn't
enough blood left over.
If you'd just let me
do the biopsy.
No way.
I just got back
from a suspension.
And if it wasn't for me,
you would've been fired.
Why don't you just
get the sample yourself?
Since when have you cared
what your boss said?
I don't care what anybody
says, I care what they do.
Right now Blackpoleon Blackaparte
has got the nurses on red alert.
I can't get into
the patient's room.
So, come on, I'll draw the
enemy fire, you outflank them
get in there,
get the bone marrow sample.
Can't.
Who you more afraid of?
I'm not afraid of Foreman,
I agree with him.
All the tests back him up.
All the tests
have not been done.
You do realize that Blackaparte's
reign is only temporary.
I also realize that no matter what I do,
you're still gonna treat me like crap.
"Crap" is a relative term.
I never even made it
to the room.
Nurses called the attending as
soon as a trocar was ordered.
You used her real name?
I just processed your
patient's discharge papers.
She's on her way out right now.
Wait up.
It's all right,
she's gonna stay.
- Wonderful.
- Oh, bite me.
I don't need to hear
the riot act again.
How'd you like
another medical test?
- What?
- Sit.
Why?
So you don't crack your skull
when you pass out.
Just do it.
You know what colchicine is?
No.
Well, don't feel bad.
It's for gout.
It's got nothing to do with anything
you've ever pretended to have.
- I'm not pretending to...
- Shut up.
Colchicine decimates
your white blood cells.
Leaves almost no trace.
It's great for faking
your way into hospitals.
- I didn't fake my way...
- Shut up.
You've been
doing this for years.
Don't worry,
it's probably not your fault.
When you were a kid,
you had a close relative
who had a chronic disease,
probably your sister.
And you saw all the attention she got
while you were left alone, ignored.
And it really,
seriously screwed you up.
- I do not have a relative...
- Shut up!
I'm trying to give you
what you want.
And save your life.
You have aplastic anemia.
What, are you trying
to scare me now?
It means you're not
just sick in the head.
Problem is,
the rest of you appears well.
So I gotta make you seem as
sick as you're supposed to be
by injecting you with a drug
that simulates the symptoms
that you actually have.
All you need to know is, you've
hit the Munchausen's jackpot.
I'm gonna give you a cocktail of
insulin for seizure and colchicine
to kill your white count.
This will absolutely confirm my
diagnosis of aplastic anemia.
There is one small catch.
If you've actually done something
to yourself to cause the anemia,
then I'm wrong.
And if I do what I plan to do,
then the treatment will kill
you instead of saving you.
So I need to know.
Have you been taking anything
besides the insulin, the ACTH,
and the pills
Cameron left in your room?
No.
Good. Give me your arm.
It was my mom.
She had MS.
She was in and out
of hospitals all the time.
People were always trying
to do things for her.
Bring her food, or brush her
hair, or make her happy.
People cared.
She died when I was 16.
Then there was no one.
Boo-hoo.
Where are you going?
I obviously can't be around
when it happens.
Well, what are you gonna do,
you're just gonna...
Relax, you know the drill.
People walk by here
all the time, you'll be fine.
So, barely out the door
and she has another seizure.
She must have somehow grabbed
insulin on the way out.
Once she's stable,
we need to get her out of here
before she does more damage
to herself.
We can't.
Her white count's down.
Sorry, I missed that.
Hearing's been off since
the Ricky Martin concert,
some cholo
kicked me in the head.
White count, hematocrit,
and platelets are all off.
Her bone marrow's shutting down.
She actually has aplastic anemia.
Say what?
All her other labs
show nothing that would...
Labs, shmabs. A good diagnostician
reads between the labs.
You were right.
Hey, we're not here
to play the blame game.
These things happen.
Sometimes doctors send people
out on the street to die
after other doctors
have warned them
that they're sending people
out on the street to die.
There's no way you could know.
I'll go give her the news.
Who are you?
I'm Dr. Foreman.
I'm in charge of your case.
You have aplastic anemia,
which means your bone
marrow has shut down.
Your body can't make
new blood anymore.
Are you sure?
I went back and checked your old records.
It makes sense.
The aplastic anemia's apparently
been developing for months.
I'm sorry, we should
have caught it earlier.
So.
It's not just the latest white count
that's leading you to feel this...
I know this is scary.
But a bone marrow transplant
could cure you.
A marrow transplant
could kill me.
The other option
is weekly blood transfusions,
injections of GCSF.
- It's a lifelong regimen.
- Yeah, I don't want that.
You sure?
I don't want to be cruel here,
but you've jumped through a lot of
hoops to get this sort of attention.
I just want to be healthy.
It's not so much fun
when you're actually sick.
No.
We'll check the registry.
See if there's a donor match.
Thank you.
We have to kill all the old bone marrow
before we give you the new stuff.
You'll have no immune system.
We'll keep you in a sterile
room for two weeks
to make sure everything's dead, then
we'll give you the donor marrow.
It'll take another couple
weeks until it takes hold.
You won't feel a thing.
If you get uncomfortable for any
reason and need to talk, don't yell.
Walls are
four inches thick, lead.
Use the microphone.
Are you ready?
Okay.
Where's Dr. House?
Turn it off!
- Now what?
- How long has she been in there?
Three minutes. What's going on?
She doesn't have
aplastic anemia.
- She has an infection.
- No.
Her white count would be through the roof.
Hers is on the floor.
Well, body does crazy things.
"Body does crazy things."
That explains everything!
She had no fever.
'Cause her self-inflicted Cushing's
suppressed her immune system.
Stopped her from having a
fever, hid the infection.
Clostridium perfringens
could cause the bruises,
the schistocytes, the anemia.
Explains everything
except the white count.
Augmentin is a lot safer than
destroying her immune system.
Why don't we try that?
You're taking the safe course?
What's going on?
There's lots of explanations
for a low white count.
Name one that fits her case.
Colchicine.
I figure that she'd gotten her
hands on it and self-medicated.
That's brilliant of her.
Take the exact medication that
would confirm your diagnosis.
People do crazy things.
You injected her against her
will just so you could be right?
- She consented.
- She's mentally ill!
But she smells oh-so-sweet.
She would've gotten sicker when
I said she was gonna get sicker
except Cameron
dosed her with antibiotics.
- Just hold this.
- Is everything okay?
Pull my finger.
Grapey.
You have a bacterium.
It's on all of us.
But the bruises you gave yourself with
the Cushing's made a lovely home.
Bacteria moved in,
parked their cars on the lawn.
There goes the neighborhood.
By neighborhood, I mean,
your internal organs.
So, should we put her
on the Augmentin, boss?
Or do you think she injected
herself with grapes?
I love the smell of pus
in the morning.
Smells like... victory.
If you were serious about the
offer, I'm serious about accepting.
I'd like to run the department. And you
said it yourself, things run smooth.
Except for the part where
House went behind your back
and KO'd the patient
with insulin and colchicine.
There was no reason
to suspect an infection.
Even House didn't think
it was an infection.
You would have done
the same thing I did.
And I'd be just as wrong.
What House did was insane.
But he saved her life.
He got lucky.
He got her to admit
she's got a problem.
She's agreed to outpatient treatment.
He gets lucky a lot.
Did you ever really intend
to give me this job,
or were you just trying to
stop me from stepping down?
Well, you've got
two more weeks in charge.
Hopefully the next case
will go better.
She should've died.
House is not a hero.
A person who has the guts
to break a bad rule,
they're a hero.
House doesn't break rules,
he ignores them.
He's not Rosa Parks,
he's an anarchist.
All he stands for is the right for
everyone to grab whatever they want
whenever they want.
You tell doctors that's okay,
your mortality rate
is gonna go through the roof.
Kind of digging this whole
Foreman-in-charge thing.
Give me those.
Frees me up to watch my soaps,
catch a movie in the afternoon,
have lunch with you.
Yeah, that's
a big change for you.
Now Cuddy's
on Foreman's ass, not mine.
You couldn't live with Foreman
as your boss.
Why not?
People can change, you know.
Your white count is way down.
We're going to need to admit you,
just to run a few more tests.
Whatever you think is best.
Last race at Belmont.
Put it all on the five
to win.