Hannah, you okay?
- Still can't sleep?
- I'm fine.
Can I do anything to help you?
Just go back to sleep.
I'm going to go get a glass of wine.
- I can keep you company.
- You have work in the morning.
Are you sure you don't want me to?
I'll be right back. Just sleep.
Hannah?
What did you do?
I just wanted to sleep.
I'm calling an ambulance.
You've seen one patient
in the last two hours.
Complicated case.
I'm a night owl.
Wilson's an early bird.
We're different species.
Move him into his own cage.
Who'll clean the droppings from mine?
Twenty-five-year-old female
with sleep issues.
I'm guessing she's...
What's the medical term? Upset!
These 25-year-old females,
they're usually completely rational.
They're rocks, really.
My theory seems to be
supported by the fact
that she swallowed
a bottle of sleeping pills.
Get her a shrink. I need some shut-eye.
She's a little bit more than upset.
She hasn't slept in ten days.
She's lying.
Without REM sleep,
your neurons start regenerating.
Your brain shuts down lobe by lobe.
She'd be insane after five days,
dead by ten.
Give me a little credit.
I know what gets you off.
She took the pills to sleep,
not to kill herself.
- Clever alibi.
- They didn't work.
She stayed awake, even though
she downed the whole bottle.
And the longest anyone's ever survived
without sleep is 11 days.
Which gives you about 22 hours.
- You stole my article.
- I wouldn't do that.
I wrote up the case where
we induced hypothermic cardiac arrest
in the terminal cancer girl.
I wrote my own. I didn't steal yours.
You knew I was writing one.
You gave me notes!
Got a case.
It can wait. You two finish.
Five bucks says someone loses an eye.
Fine, you're only putting off
the inevitable.
Twenty-five-year-old female
hasn't slept for ten days.
I assume the ER tried
giving her some sedatives.
We should up the dosage.
- Sedation isn't the same as sleep.
- Thanks for your insight.
For someone who hasn't slept
in ten days, sedation is a great start.
Sleep is an active process.
Reboots the system, restores the brain.
- Sedatives don't...
- The brain is being stressed.
We need to relieve that.
You've had my article on your desk
for the last four months.
I'm a very slow reader.
No fever, no white count,
means no infection.
Schizophrenia?
- No delusions.
- You read his.
Signed it. Didn't read it.
Aside from the sleeping pills,
tox screen was clean.
No cocaine, methamphetamines
or diet pills.
The only medication she's had recently
are steroids for poison ivy and
ibuprofen for a knee she hurt skiing.
Nothing that would cause
sleep disturbances.
- When did you get his article?
- About three weeks ago.
- Let's go back to the beginning.
- How far back?
Genesis.
God said, "Let there be light."
Sleep is initially controlled
by external light cues.
And if her brain can't interpret
those cues...
Optic nerve disease.
I'm sensing another article.
I'll go run the tests.
I'm injecting a dye which will
allow us to take a look at your retina
and your optic nerve.
- Everything's kind of blurry.
- Normal, because of the dye.
It's going to be that way
the next few hours.
- Need a hand?
- No.
Are we never going
to work together again?
I just don't see the need to make you
feel better by forgiving you.
I wasn't asking for forgiveness.
I was asking if you needed help.
It's unprofessional to be talking
about this in front of the patient.
Maybe that doesn't matter to you, but...
It doesn't matter.
She's not listening.
She's asleep.
Normal stage-one brain waves.
Maybe she's better?
Still blurry.
- You fell asleep.
- No, I didn't.
Negative
for optic nerve disease.
But she sleeps.
For, like, ten seconds.
Maximum one minute.
We also checked the ocular pressure.
It's normal.
And she doesn't know she sleeps.
The brain is often unaware
of stage one sleep.
The CT showed no tumors,
no clots, no seizure disorder.
So she sleeps.
She just can't stay asleep.
You going somewhere with this?
You know what keeps me awake at
night?
Monsters in the closet.
There's no monster in the closet.
We looked.
Well, it's certainly not showing up
on the scans.
Where's Cameron?
She felt I could deliver the news
on my own.
Oh, this is going to work out great.
Come on.
If you two guys can't play nice
together, I'm taking away your toys.
- I don't care whose fault this is.
- If you hadn't...
I especially don't care
if it was my fault.
Whatever this woman has,
it's not showing up on our tests.
Which means she's sick,
just not sick enough for us to see it.
- You want us to make her sicker?
- Yes.
I want to stress her body.
Specifically her brain.
Keep her awake.
Depriving her of even the few minutes
of sleep she does have, it's torture.
So is cutting people with knives,
but you can totally get away with that
if you have a doctor coat on.
Those few seconds of sleep are maybe
the only reason she's still alive.
The more symptoms we can force out
of her, the more tests we can do.
The more tests we do,
the more information we get,
the quicker we make a diagnosis.
See how much more fun it is
when you guys get along?
You two take the first four hours.
Hannah?
Hannah!
You fell asleep.
No, I didn't.
Your brain doesn't remember.
It was just a few seconds.
Is this really necessary?
The sooner we find out what's wrong, the
sooner she can get a real night's rest.
Hannah?
Hannah? Hannah.
Ow.
- What did you do that for?
- You fell asleep again.
- No, I didn't.
- We're sorry.
We have to do this.
We don't have to be cruel.
You know what happens when you're nice?
Nothing.
That's how you define nice?
Not stealing?
Doctors!
Did she fall asleep again?
- We've got rectal bleeding.
- What, all of you?
So the monster is peeking out
from under the bed.
Which either means
she has a clotting disorder
or she has a tumor in her colon.
- I'll do a colonoscopy.
- Who's keeping her awake now?
I figured once we found another
symptom, it really didn't matter.
- Yeah, he's got all the ideas.
- Who is with her?
Her partner's donating blood,
so she's with a nurse.
Probably singing her lullabies.
I want her awake.
You have to sedate a patient
to do a colonoscopy.
Why? Just because of the pain?
If you find a tumor in her colon,
you can knock her out.
If you don't, she stays awake.
Oh! God, it hurts!
- Can't you hurry?
- Trust me, you don't want me to hurry.
God, you're killing me!
Hold my hand.
Keep breathing, nice and steady.
How am I supposed to work with him?
Maybe we shouldn't be talking about this
right now?
Think I'm overreacting?
I need you to relax your anus.
We're not here. We're skiing.
It's Thanksgiving at Vail.
You want me to think about nearly
killing myself on a snowboard?
Come on, you never fell.
You were awesome.
Is that what you told him? I'm
hysterical and I need to relax my anus?
I told him... How many cases
do we work up in a year?
They're all weird. He could have
written up any one of them.
She's bleeding.
I can't breathe. I can't breathe.
Hold on.
We packed her nose to control the bleed
and started transfusing
two units of whole blood.
The pathology from the rectal bleed
showed traces of nasal epithelium.
So the butt bleed's just a nose bleed.
That much blood
is not a "just a" anything.
When two people fight this much,
you know what it means.
It's gotta be a massive sinus hemorrhage
that was draining down her throat
and out the back.
- The question isn't what, it's why.
- Oh, get a room.
Rat poison mixed with
some sort of neurogenic toxin
could cause bleeding
and sleep disturbances.
Do you have a specific type
of neurogenic toxin in mind,
or should we just start running
a thousand different tox screens?
Just pretend I'm not here.
I'll be reading.
It could also be
some type of coagulopathy.
Or it could be us.
Do you have any idea what it feels like
to have a six-foot-long hose
shoved into your large intestine?
No, but I now have a much greater
respect for whichever basketball player
you dated in college.
We've basically been torturing
this girl for the last eight hours.
We've been poking her foot,
not punching her face.
Extreme stress can cause
high blood pressure,
- which can cause bleeding.
- Wouldn't keep her awake for ten days.
What if the poison ivy
wasn't poison ivy?
She got the rash
that was diagnosed as poison ivy
around the same time
the insomnia started.
Rash plus nose bleed
plus sleep disturbance
equals Wegener's granulomatosis.
Start corticosteroid treatment.
- The poison ivy treatment was steroids.
- Much lower dosage.
Get her back on the juice
and triple the dose.
Get a cANCA and an upper airway biopsy
to confirm the Wegener's.
She has menstrual problems.
They're really bad.
The pain keeps her in bed all day.
Plus, she's super depressed.
She said, "Super depressed"?
She heard that birth control pills
can make her feel better.
She wants birth control pills
for her PMS.
I guess.
Judging by the redness
around your mom's nostrils
and the tissue she's got
conveniently stashed in her wristband,
I'd say her problem
is more likely a URI than a PMS.
A URI?
Upper respiratory infection. A cold.
I don't think so.
I also think she's got a problem
with a SAC.
SAC?
Thanks for playing.
Stupid American Child.
If you want the pill, all you have to do
is to walk into any health clinic
in Jersey, alone, and ask for it.
What exactly was your plan?
You're going to exchange
the birth control pills
for some over-the-counter
decongestants
and hope that your mom's cold
lasts another six years?
No.
- Is that for a cold?
- No, that's for your ovaries.
I assume you haven't had a stroke.
Have you ever had a blood clot?
- No.
- Super.
In three months when you need a refill,
take a bus to a free clinic.
Don't wait around hoping for Mom
to get another sniffle.
Not the sharpest chopstick
in the drawer, is she?
Was this just one of your experiments?
You just wanted to see how I'd react
to being screwed over by Foreman?
Nice idea, but no. This was just
good old-fashioned laziness.
I gotta hand it to Foreman, though.
He knew that you were a suck-up
and I don't give a crap.
He successfully exploited us both.
Right, we're both victims.
A simple heads up, that's all I needed.
Maybe between
your incredibly witty remarks
about anal sex and Cuddy's breasts,
you could have tipped me off.
Yeah, but then I'd have Foreman
pissed at me.
And as annoying as you could be,
at least I know
you're not gonna pop a cap in my ass.
Witty, huh?
You, on the other hand,
continue to be flabbergasted
every time someone actually acts
like a human being.
Foreman did what he did because
it worked out best that way for him.
That's what everyone does.
That is not the definition
of being human.
It's the definition of being an ass.
This will numb you up.
And this will keep your tongue
out of the way.
Don't worry. You shouldn't feel anything
except for a slight pulling.
So, do you think I was out of line?
That article would have sat on House's
desk for the next six years.
I could've told her.
You could have written it for her, too.
She knows House as well as any of us.
She should've known
she was waiting for him
to do something he was never gonna do.
Chase?
Hannah? You still with us?
- What's wrong with her eyes?
- It looks like REM.
- What's that?
- Rapid Eye Movements.
It's what your eyes do
when you're sleeping.
- But she's awake.
- Hannah!
Hannah, can you hear me?
Yeah, of course.
- Was she sitting up or lying down?
- Sitting up.
Then it wasn't REM.
Chase says her eyes were moving
the exact way...
You start her on the steroids?
- Not yet. We were still doing...
- Then she wasn't sleeping.
- How do you know?
- Because we haven't done anything yet.
She may be able to sleep with her
eyes open, but unless you also discover
she's got two extra teats
and hooves for feet,
there's no way she'd be able to maintain
enough muscle tensity
during REM sleep to sit upright.
It's a movement disorder,
which rules out Wegener's.
Where's Foreman?
- Keeping her awake.
- Good.
Rabies could cause muscle spasms,
malaise, anxiety and wakefulness.
Pretty unlikely she'd forget
being bitten by a crazed animal.
She could've been exposed
through an open wound.
- Does she have a dog?
- For less than a week.
She had an allergic reaction,
so they had to give it away.
Allergies.
Animal allergies seems unlikely,
but it's possible that...
- When?
- When what?
- When did she get rid of the dog?
- About a month ago.
Her girlfriend gave it to her
for her birthday.
Well, then, it's not allergies.
She's just leaving her girlfriend.
You... spoke to the dog?
If her birthday was a month ago,
she would have still been on steroids
for the poison ivy.
Those meds would have suppressed
any reaction
she might have had to the dog,
which means she lied about being
allergic. A dog's a commitment.
You pretend to be allergic because
you don't want to tell your girlfriend
that you're not planning
on being around that long.
So, I think we can move on
to options other than allergies.
We should still do
a scratch test.
- If she's allergic to one thing...
- She is not allergic.
Okay. Well, we could either base
our diagnosis
on your admittedly keen understanding
of lesbian relationships,
or we could do a scratch test.
Do a scratch test.
Are you still feeling
a lot of blood in your throat?
No, it's actually getting
a little better.
Good, maybe things are just starting
to improve on their own.
Just a few more.
- Want some water to wash your mouth?
- No, I'm okay.
Come on, that can't taste good.
I'm gonna get you a soda.
It's okay, isn't it?
You and Max seem to have a
really nice relationship.
- Yeah.
- She's very supportive.
When Max got you the dog,
did you lie about having
an allergic reaction?
No.
- Why?
- If you have preexisting conditions,
it's important we know, but
if you don't, it's just as important.
If I'm wasting my time doing this...
You're not going to tell her, are you?
It's none of my business.
She's a good person, and we've just
been together so long, I...
I'm tired of her.
It sounds terrible, doesn't it?
I guess it happens sometimes.
My back hurts.
Hannah, can you turn over?
- What's wrong?
- I'm not sure.
Oh, my God.
- She has massive internal bleeding.
- Did she have access to aspirin?
She'd have to take a hell of a lot.
Why not?
Considering her current mental state.
What about her mental state?
You were right about her
wanting to break up.
That just means I was right.
Doesn't mean she's suicidal.
A bottle of pills is what
landed her here in the first place.
Sleeping pills.
God knows why she'd want them.
What else could cause sleep disorder
and internal bleeding?
Drugs or alcohol could mess with
the sleeping and compromise the liver.
What are you doing here?
Who's keeping her awake?
Doesn't matter. Liver function tests
are through the sky.
Liver's not compromised. It's dead.
She doesn't need a diagnosis.
She needs a new liver.
She's not getting a new liver unless
we can figure out what's wrong with her.
Test for cirrhosis, 12 hours.
Test for hepatitis, eight.
Her liver's not gonna last another six.
So your advice is we just give up?
My advice is that we narrow our focus
to conditions that we can diagnose,
treat and cure in less than six hours.
And there's nothing on that list.
The girlfriend donated blood, right?
Yeah, so?
It means they're the same type.
You can't ask the person she's about
to dump to donate half her liver.
It does seem tacky, doesn't it?
I'm Dr House.
I'm in charge of your case.
What's going on?
How come no one
is keeping her awake anymore?
You're in acute liver failure.
We can continue the transfusions
and the lactulose,
but it's only a stopgap.
There's really nothing we can do
to stop the toxins
from building up in your bloodstream,
which means that, in a few hours,
you will lapse into a coma...
and you won't wake up.
I'm sorry.
That's it? You're giving up?
You're not going to try to figure out
what's doing this to her?
Well, even with the right diagnosis,
any treatment's gonna take longer
than the time she has left.
If it's her liver,
can't she get a transplant?
Wouldn't work without a diagnosis.
Whatever killed the first liver
would do the same to the second.
But it would give you more time
to make the diagnosis to get her better.
Well, it might give us
an extra day or two,
but no procurement agency
is gonna let a liver go to a patient
with an undiagnosed, preexisting...
Hannah and I have the same blood type.
Couldn't I be the donor?
Well, it is medically possible
for us to take a part of your...
Please, I don't care about the risks.
You're very lucky
to have such a devoted partner.
I just bought us 36 hours.
Differential diagnosis.
Which monster eats your liver,
screws up your sleep
and causes bleeding?
Does Max know Hannah plans to leave
her?
Didn't come up, so I guess no.
If she knew, there's no way
she'd go through with this.
And if you didn't have
a pathological need
to create a close, personal relationship
with every dying person you meet,
we would be blissfully ignorant
of any ethical dilemmas
and might actually be able to
concentrate on the differential.
The scratch test was negative.
It's rare, but any of the hepatitis
viruses could cause sleep disturbances
- and liver failure.
- No, PCRs were normal.
- We have an ethical dilemma.
- No, we don't. Continue.
What about splenic cancer
or Non-Hodgkin's lymphoma?
She's the right age.
It could explain the bleeding,
maybe the liver failure.
We're withholding information relevant
to her decision to risk her life.
- How is that not an ethical dilemma?
- It's not medical information.
- Who cares?
- The AMA.
Wilson's disease could explain the
liver and neurological symptoms.
It also causes bleeding disorders.
No Kayser-Fleischer rings in her eyes.
Rings don't have to be there
if there's neurological symptoms.
- This is immoral.
- Look, let's say you're right!
We tell, she changes her mind,
our patient dies. How is that moral?
What else?
Poisoned mushrooms
can cause liver failure,
sleep disturbances
and internal bleeding.
She's not shrooming. She's a sports nut.
Right, skiers never party.
She's doing this out of love,
and Max doesn't know...
It's only moral to save a person
if they love you?
That's kind of a selfish way
of looking at life.
I like Wilson's disease,
like cancer, love mushrooms.
Yeah, but we don't have the time
to test for any of it.
Before she can get the transplant,
we need to do about 80 procedures.
So, do those tests
and my tests at the same time.
Use the PET to look for cancer
and Wilson's.
While you endoscope her bile ducts,
scrape her stomach for mushroom spores.
One of you CT her liver,
while the other two
check protein CA-125 and CA-19.5.
Oh, yeah, anyone says anything to Max,
they're fired.
We have to.
We have to not,
because she's not our patient.
She's getting surgery.
She's someone's patient.
I think that's it. Great, thank you.
I need a little help.
Inexplicable rash on a patient's scrotum
you need me to look at?
Twenty-seven-year-old female
wants to donate half her liver
- to her dying girlfriend.
- That's very generous.
This the sleepless girl? What's she got?
Liver failure.
Sort of figured that out when you said
she needed a new liver.
- You don't have a diagnosis?
- The transplant buys me time.
Let's just skip the part
where I say this is insane.
It was her idea.
If she wants to be an idiot,
it's her call. You don't need me.
Have one of your team
walk her through the process.
The donor and the donee
sort of have opposing interests, right?
We can't really advise them both.
You're concerned
about the ethics of this?
What's going on?
- What do you know?
- Nothing medically relevant.
But you know something,
and it is relevant.
If I can't tell her,
I can't really tell you, can I?
I mean, if you're advising her.
I assume this information
is in the medical file.
- In my patient's confidential file.
- This hospital's file.
You can either satisfy your curiosity,
or you can remain ignorant,
do nothing ethically wrong, and
my patient doesn't die in three hours.
These tests and the counseling
normally happen over weeks,
sometimes months.
It's okay.
Well, the most important part
we're skipping is time.
Time for you to change your mind.
I don't wanna change my mind.
Not now, but, with time and perspective,
maybe we learn things...
If we had the time, we'd take the time,
but we don't.
So can you get this over with?
Either I sign off on this,
or it doesn't happen.
So I need you to listen to me,
because there's a chance
that you will die on that table.
I just want me and Hannah
to be able to lie in bed together
as old ladies,
compare scars.
I need you to lie on your side
and hold your knees.
I'm going to check
for vascular abnormalities
that might prevent us
from doing the transplant.
At the same time,
I'm also checking for mushroom spores
- to see if that's the underlying...
- I don't do mushrooms.
If you lie about your love life,
maybe you lie about drugs. Open.
Aren't you at all concerned about
what Max is going through right now?
They're shoving a tube up her rectum,
then they're going to swab her stomach
just like I'm doing.
It's going to hurt just like this hurts.
Which is nothing at all like the risk
she's taking on the table.
And you don't love her, do you?
I'm not leaving her because I don't...
I'm not talking about the leaving.
I'm talking about this.
If you care for her at all,
you won't let her do this blind.
- You'd really tell?
- Yeah.
You'd die?
I take it you've seen that.
Seen it, digested it, watched it
blow up my entire department.
- Did you read Cameron's version?
- I didn't read either.
It was good.
- Better than Foreman's?
- Maybe.
He was more analytical
about the diagnostic procedures.
She concentrated more on the
ethical dilemmas of informed consent.
How any patient can really be informed
without a medical degree.
Same old party lines.
- Foreman should have told her.
- Oh, shoulda, woulda, coulda.
If you allow this sort of thing
in your department,
you're basically saying it's okay.
No, I'm saying that I don't care
what they do
as long as my life isn't interrupted by
pointless conversations like this one.
They won't trust each other,
and they won't trust you.
They shouldn't.
Deception like this
is just one step removed
from actively sabotaging one another.
Then what would you do?
I could be the kindest,
gentlest boss in the world,
and Foreman would still have done
what he did, because that's who he is.
We can only hope that Cameron
has learned something.
Right,
because you're all about the teaching.
Our children are the future.
Hey.
Cuddy cleared Max for surgery.
She's okay to go.
- How's our patient?
- She's also cleared.
I don't care about the prep.
I care about the diagnostic tests.
Looks negative for Wilson's disease.
We'll know for sure in an hour.
- Blood proteins are normal. It's not...
- Where's Cameron?
Taking a sample of the bile duct.
Surgeries are supposed to start
in about 15 minutes.
She had a chance to get one last...
Hannah and Max will be in the same
room.
You wanted us to do
as much as we can before...
They're both awake with Cameron.
Maybe we should give these two
a minute together before the surgery.
You ready, honey?
- Max.
- It's okay, I'm right here.
- I need you to know something.
- I know.
I love you, too.
- I don't know how to say this.
- Good Lord!
- You can tell me anything.
- She hasn't slept in 11 days!
You people trying to torture her?
Ding, ding, let's go.
- I told you...
- I didn't say a word to Max.
This is exactly why you got screwed
with Foreman.
You're looking for people
to do the right thing.
She hasn't slept.
Her judgment is compromised
due to inactivity
in her prefrontal cortex.
Oh, she could have the best prefrontal
cortex in the history of mankind,
but given the choice
of life versus death,
those bad, bad people
are going to choose life.
Then why'd you sedate her?
If she wasn't going to tell,
if she was never going to do the right
thing, why bother knocking her out?
This isn't about them. If she talks,
if she does the decent thing,
then you don't get to solve your puzzle,
your game's over, you lose.
Yeah, I wanna save her.
I'm morally bankrupt.
How's it going?
They're about to remove Hannah's liver.
All right, I'm good to go.
You can start removing Max's liver.
You wanna let me in on what
the big secret is between these two?
You read Foreman's article?
It was good.
He basically stole it from me.
- So?
- You're on his side?
Sides? No, this isn't dodgeball.
What am I supposed to do,
just sit back and take it?
No, write another article.
Kick ass until you're sitting behind
some big, expensive desk,
and someone from Johns Hopkins calls
and says,
"We're thinking about hiring
Eric Foreman as our head of Neurology."
And you can say whatever you want.
Lovely. Revenge as motive for success.
Well, it doesn't have to be the motive,
but it sure tastes good.
- She's in VF. I've got no pulse.
- She's arresting.
I am so relieved
you two are here.
Without you looking out,
they'd be playing foosball down there.
- Max's heart stopped.
- Your patient is on the other side.
Now get yourself upstairs
and figure out what Hannah has,
or Max has risked her life for nothing.
Charging.
Clear.
We're okay.
Max's cardiac arrest was caused
by hypoxia from hypoventilation.
They restarted her heart,
and the right lobe of her liver was
successfully transplanted into Hannah.
Now, where were we
before we were so rudely interrupted
by the liver transplant?
Dopa decarboxylase
was processed normally,
and the ceruloplasmin
and copper levels were normal.
So, no Wilson's disease.
Gastric content was negative for spores,
so no mushroom toxicity.
And initial tests
were negative for cancer.
- Which cancer were you looking for?
- Any of them.
We ran blood tests
for ovarian, lung and lymphomas.
Not gonna tell you much.
Her blood was taken after she
was given immunosuppressants.
They fight rejection.
They also mess up our ability
to get any clear readings.
Great battles kick up a lot of dirt.
Obscure the battlefield
so generals can't see what's going on.
So, what are your orders, General
House?
Sound the retreat.
How you feeling?
Is Max okay?
She's still unconscious,
but her vitals look good.
We need to stop
all the immunosuppressant drugs
which are protecting your new liver.
But if you stop the drugs, I'll die.
You're dead anyway if we don't
figure out what caused all this.
By removing any outside influences,
it'll help us see
what's really going on with your body.
So you did all this
to buy me a couple of days,
and now you're taking one back?
Will it hurt?
As your body goes into
acute organ rejection,
your liver will begin to swell,
and that'll put pressure on...
Yeah, it'll hurt.
But we can knock you out.
No, if Max wakes up,
I want to talk to her.
She's been taking the decongestants,
but she's not getting better.
- She also says...
- What?
Her boobs are bigger.
How could you get them mixed up?
They come in a little wheel. They
don't look anything like decongestants.
Oh, God. The cashier
put them both in the same bag.
I thought I gave her the right ones.
No, you gave her the wrong pills.
You speak Mandarin?
I can count to ten,
ask to go to the bathroom and...
I'm not pregnant.
We haven't even done it yet!
Okay,
I'm going to leave you two alone now.
I'm sure you got a lot to talk about.
Fever is 106.
She's in full rejection mode.
Is that supposed to surprise me?
Her white count is normal.
Normal is not normal.
She's been on steroids.
The transplant team gave her
a cocktail of immunosuppressants.
She hasn't slept in over a week.
Her white count should be in the tank.
Looks like the problem
is some sort of infection.
Probably caused
the hypotension, shocked the liver.
We should start
broad-spectrum antibiotics.
Yeah, you might want to add
some chicken soup.
It'd be just as useless,
but it's got chicken.
We need to know exactly what kind
of infection we're dealing with.
What infection causes sleep disturbance,
bleeding, a movement disorder,
organ failure
and an abnormally normal white count.
- What about tularemia?
- Chest was clear.
Tularemia doesn't cause
movement disorders.
- It would if she developed meningitis.
- There was no ulcerations on the skin.
With the bleeding,
it looks more like leptospirosis.
Without conjunctivitis
and elevated creatinine?
What about typhoid
or some kind of relapsing fever?
Makes sense, if we were in the Sudan.
Are you sure she hasn't
been out of the country?
She hasn't even been out of the state
in at least a year. Neither has Max.
Maybe she lied.
- You talk to her friends, neighbors?
- You don't know?
Come on, if you don't stay
up-to-date on my notes,
where's your next article
gonna come from?
Talked to the dog?
We're not as up on foreign languages
as you are.
- Has the dog been traveling?
- It came from a breeder.
- Where?
- I don't know.
Place called Blue Barrel Kennels.
They only had the thing
for, like, two days.
Blue barrel is a kind of cactus.
You see many cacti in Jersey?
Wanna see a magic trick?
Oh, no. Where'd it go? Where'd it go?
Is it here?
No. What about here?
There it is.
Oh, that doesn't look anything
like a nose.
That wasn't there this morning.
- Get that to the lab and call the CDC.
- Tell them what?
That we have a patient with the plague.
- The black plague?
- Looks that way.
Plague is carried by rodents, not dogs.
Where there's dogs, there's fleas.
If they hail from the Southwest,
then those fleas
can't tell the difference
between prairie dogs and puppy dogs.
A small percentage of plague cases
present with sleep disturbance.
Imagine an idyllic river of bacteria.
Okay, it's not idyllic for her,
but it serves my purposes.
The steroids and immunosuppressants
acted like a big honking dam
across the river. Physics 101.
Put a dam up in front of a raging river,
the river rises.
By stopping the immunosuppressants,
we blew up the dam,
and a 100-foot wall of bacteria
flooded her lymph nodes.
We better find out
where that dog is now.
After you restart
the immunosuppressants,
and fill her up to the eyeballs
with streptomycin sulfate,
gentamicin and tetracycline.
Use a garden hose if we've got one.
Get yourselves
some prophylactic treatments as well.
I've got the plague?
Don't worry, it's treatable.
Being a bitch, though,
nothing we can do about that.
You weren't in your room.
The surgeon said I'd heal faster
if I walk.
I got this far, needed a rest.
What you did was crazy,
but it was pretty amazing, too.
Yeah. I'm a hero.
She's been planning to leave me.
Really?
She told a friend.
The friend let it slip.
You knew, and you gave up
half your liver anyway?
She can't leave me now.
You really want her to stay
out of guilt?
That's not gonna make
either of you happy.
You don't know that.
I love her.
I just want her to stay.
I don't own House's cases.
You had just as much right as I did
to write it up.
You should have told me, but
I should have handled it better, too.
If we want this not to get in the way
of our friendship,
I think we both have to apologize
and put it behind us.
I like you, really.
We have a good time working together.
But 10 years from now,
we're not gonna be hanging out
and having dinners.
Maybe we'll exchange Christmas cards,
say hi,
give a hug if we're at
the same conference.
We're not friends. We're colleagues.
And I don't have anything
to apologize for.