Jasper, hold still.
Stop squirming, hold still.
What did he do now?
He got in another fight and I can't
get his nose to stop bleeding.
You have to apply
much more pressure than that.
You had to do this today.
I got office hours, I'm supposed
to have dinner with the Dean.
You just can't lash out
whenever you get angry.
He said I smelled like
a monkey.
Well, you do. You can't
refuse to take a bath
and then hit kids
who tell you that you smell. Damn.
Don't you think
we should call 911?
This isn't his first
nosebleed. He'll be fine.
- Daddy!
- Hey! Lucy Goosey!
I'm playing doctor.
So am I. Can you
go back and play?
- When was this fight?
- Over ten minutes ago.
I feel dizzy.
Maybe you should
make that call.
Okay.
Daddy, look, I can help.
No, no, that's great, honey.
Can you just please leave Daddy alone?
One of my kids is bleeding
profusely from the nose. Please hurry.
They're sending an ambulance.
Call them back. He'll be fine.
How you feeling, bud?
You light-headed?
Lucy.
Oh, my God.
Lucy? Are you okay? Lucy? Lucy?
Lucy? Lucy, are you okay?
Lucy! Lucy!
Oh, for God's sake.
Stop. Don't move.
The way the soft evening
light catches your eyes.
The gentle caress of dusk
on your hair
as you turn around and leave my office
without giving me that file.
Restrictive pericarditis.
Boring.
She's in kindergarten.
Less boring. Or Grandma's
been held back a few years.
It's calcified
and she's hypertensive.
- Better get her into surgery.
- She already is in surgery.
Tricky procedure.
It's gonna take all night.
Sleep tight.
No congenital defects,
no health problems,
but her heart is
strangling itself.
Fascinating.
Since the pathology on the pericardium
won't be back
until after they remove it.
Get started on her blood. You can test
for viral infections, bacterial...
Round up the usual suspects.
Amyloidosis, sarcoidosis,
hemochromatosis.
Heck, go wild.
Do all the -osises.
All taken care of. Sleep tight.
This thing is already
all around her heart.
It gets into the muscle,
she's dead.
Best bet's Coxsackie virus,
Parvovirus B19, CMV.
Bacterial infection's more likely to
turn constrictive. It could be TB.
Right, forgot about the part
where she did time in a Russian gulag.
Her hematocrit's elevated.
A few extra red blood cells
means nothing.
She's probably just dehydrated.
Yes, and I could assume three or four
things to fit my theory, too.
She's sick! She obviously hasn't
been drinking enough...
Enough!
I take it you two aren't sleeping
together anymore?
We do what House said,
we test for everything.
Good, then I can go home.
Since when does
we not include you?
Well, House is gonna
call us idiots, anyway.
Might as well be
a well-rested idiot.
You guys are idiots.
Why? Because we stayed up all night
doing exactly what you told us to do?
No, because you stayed up all night
doing exactly what I told you to do
and have nothing
to show for it.
We eliminated dozens
of wrong answers.
I asked you what two plus two equals and
a day later you tell me, "Not 25."
Pathology report
just got filed.
They found granulomas
in Lucy's pericardium.
Indicates a fungal infection.
Nice work.
He went home.
Work smart, not hard.
Find out which fungus.
Biopsy a lymph node.
Take employee of the month
with you.
- I would rather Foreman...
- I know.
I don't want any more shots.
Jasper.
Look at me, Goosey.
Squeeze my hand, okay?
This will tell us why you're sick, so
that we can make you all better.
Where would she pick up
a fungus?
Anywhere moist. Around a pool,
locker room, public shower...
She doesn't have any gym
or swim classes.
She doesn't even like to play
with kids outside.
You haven't taken any trips?
Gone anywhere new?
It's been hard to get away
since their mom...
Our mom is dead.
- I'm sorry.
- Last year. Brain cancer.
You're gonna stick that thing
in her arm?
Cool!
The cool part is
your sister won't feel a thing.
Nice necklace.
- Thanks.
- You like video games?
Love them.
That should do it. You okay?
I want my bunny.
Are you being silly?
I didn't know
which one to take.
What do you mean?
What's happening?
So. What does
the double vision tell us?
Slit lamp revealed the eye's
anterior chamber is swollen.
Uveitis. Means it's not a post-op effect
and it's not neurological.
It's not fungal, either.
Lymph node biopsy was clean.
So, we're back to square one.
One and a half. We've eliminated
two more conditions.
Yes. Two plus two doesn't
equal 12 or 16, either.
Vision issues plus screwy heart equals
some type of autoimmune.
Lupus and Kawasaki's are
the most common in a six-year-old.
Yeah, tough to find a six-year-old who
doesn't have Lupus or Kawasaki's...
Did you look at her knees?
Those knobby things in the middle
of her legs. Any scars or scabs?
What does that
have to do with...
Well, most six-year-olds
hurt themselves a lot.
Crash their bikes,
climb trees, bungee jump...
Dad says she doesn't like
to run around outside.
'Cause running around
outside hurts.
She didn't mention anything...
Most six-year-olds are not familiar with
the phrase, "My joints feel inflamed."
So, two plus two equals...
Juvenile rheumatoid arthritis.
We're checking her ANA to confirm and
giving her steroids to fix her vision.
Some idiot gave me two tickets
for a play tonight.
Saved his life.
Apparently worth $186.
Sorry, had to take a leak.
Oh, I didn't know
you were seeing a patient.
It's an exam room.
What did you think I was doing?
What you usually do.
Hiding from Cuddy.
Well, it'd be stupid to do it in here.
There's a patient in here.
You been drinking more?
No, I haven't.
Guy's peeing all the time.
Play. Interested?
Sure. You want me
to pick you up?
- Well, I'm not going.
- You said two tickets.
You thought this was a date?
Any other symptoms?
My stomach hurts.
I have back pain
and muscle aches,
I feel dizzy and I have trouble
concentrating sometimes in class.
I really should...
You want the tickets or not?
- Why don't you want to go with me?
- It's a play.
Dudes only go to plays
if they're dragged by women
they're hoping to see naked.
So, why are you
giving them to me?
Maybe there's someone
you wanna see naked.
All right.
- Any fever?
- No.
Anything in your pee
other than pee?
No.
I'm going to need
a urine sample.
No!
Yeah, that last one
wasn't a question.
- You might have diabetes...
- I can't pee in public.
We have bathrooms.
I can't pee
in public bathrooms.
Where can you pee?
I only live
a few miles from here.
I thought arthritis
was for old people.
JRA is an autoimmune disease.
Her body's attacking itself,
causing inflammation in the joints,
her eyes, and her heart.
Is it treatable?
It can be crippling, but it can also
go into complete remission.
Well, the good thing is
we caught it early.
Gives her the best chance
to have a positive outcome.
Dad.
Don't get up, Goosey.
Your stitches.
She's having a stroke.
The stroke was caused by a clot
in her middle cerebral artery.
Started her on tPA.
Should dissolve the clot
and hopefully prevent brain damage,
but we won't know for sure
until she regains consciousness.
Or she has another stroke.
Arthritis, heart disease.
Why can't this kid act her age?
JRA doesn't affect the blood. That means
the clot's a symptom of something else.
It's a symptom of polycythemia.
She's fully hydrated and her blood's
still thicker than pancake batter.
Well, thick blood
explains the stroke.
It could also have caused
an autoimmune response,
which would explain
the JRA kicking into gear.
But what explains
the thick blood?
Lack of oxygen forces the body
to overproduce red cells.
What explains
the lack of oxygen?
Carbon monoxide fumes,
cigarette smoke.
I doubt our patient's a smoker.
- Dad could be.
- He's not.
- He says he's not.
- Hey!
Don't make me turn the hose
on you two.
Chase is right.
You two go check the house,
see if Dad's a closet Marlboro Man.
You're intentionally
punishing us.
By making you do your job?
Does seem kind of cruel, doesn't it?
Take along a carbon monoxide
detector to check for leaks,
and, you, start her on hydroxyurea to
control her red blood cell production.
Dig out a Merck Manual,
Medieval edition.
Tell you how to drain
a pint or two so she doesn't clot again.
Dr. Cameron!
I got you flowers
for helping my sister.
That's so sweet.
Does your dad know
you're down here?
Yes.
"Congratulations
on your bundle of joy."
Something you forgot
to tell me?
You should take these back
to where you found them.
- Okay.
- Excuse me?
Can you make sure these flowers
and this kid both get back
to where they belong?
Sure.
- Thanks.
- Let's go. Come on.
Wait.
So, you're just
draining blood from her?
You're not testing it?
You're not fixing it?
Your daughter's vascular system
is engorged with blood.
Draining some reduces
the chances of another stroke.
We're also starting her on a drug that
suppresses the production of red cells
so we don't have to
keep doing this.
Good chance
she'll make a full recovery.
She hasn't spoken yet.
Give her time.
This your boy?
- Where have you been?
- Exploring. See ya.
Thank you.
You know you can't just
run off without telling me.
Okay. Can I have $2?
Oven's a long shot.
They'd smell the gas
long before anyone got sick.
Yeah, right. House loves it
when we skip something
'cause it's a long shot.
Why did you take the flower?
- Why did you kiss him?
- He did something sweet.
He stole flowers.
He's eight.
You're trying to
make me jealous.
Yeah, I want you to
profess your love for me. Oh, wait.
You already did that and it caused me
to end our relationship.
You're enabling a thief
and a delinquent!
Letters from school. Fights, detentions,
a parent conference...
Oh, I know, I know.
Bad boys, hard to resist.
It's a crush. It's harmless.
- It's never harmless.
- So I'm learning.
So, this is us now?
We snipe at each other?
I'm not sniping,
I'm looking for a vent.
Her room's directly above the garage.
There's all sorts
of CO sources down there.
I found a vent.
I think there's
something in it.
This isn't right.
You dumped me.
You don't get to be mad.
We had a really good thing.
You broke the rules. I'm angry.
I'll get over it.
She's being abused.
A bloody T-shirt doesn't
equal abuse. Kids get hurt all the time.
That amount of blood?
Oh, crap.
You two are agreeing again.
Her father's overwhelmed.
Hectic job,
his wife passed away last year, he could
easily be taking it out on the kids.
Or she had a nosebleed
and grabbed a T-shirt.
She's so ashamed of a nosebleed
she has to hide the evidence
in a vent under her bed?
She's socially isolated, the brother's
always in trouble, it's classic signs.
But no physical signs.
No marks on her body,
no bruises at all.
What if it's sexual?
We should call Social Services.
Well, this sucks.
Either it's abuse,
or it's not abuse,
which means either it's a symptom
or it's completely irrelevant.
Either way, we got to waste half a day
figuring out which.
Full physical exam.
Look for bruises we may have missed,
check her mouth and do a vaginal exam.
We can't do a vaginal exam
on a six-year-old
without the dad's consent.
And if he's abusing her,
he'll never say yes.
"Never" is just "reven"
spelled backwards.
Have you been abusing
your daughter?
What? Why would you...
We found this hidden in a vent
under her bed.
I don't know anything about this.
Maybe she had a bloody nose?
We need to examine her
for abuse.
You can't really think I...
Maybe you,
maybe the school bully,
maybe the creepy neighbor.
I'm guessing you're not paying as much
attention as you should be.
Do you even know
where your son is right now?
Yeah, he was here just...
Here a minute ago.
She isn't being abused.
Unfortunately, that answer
doesn't help me.
If you have abused her,
- you're obviously gonna lie about it.
- I'm not lying!
- We need to do a vaginal exam.
- No.
She may be dying,
she still can't talk and you're gonna
waste your time with this?
Either you consent and we waste a few
hours doing the exam, or you refuse
and I call Social Services and they
waste three days doing an investigation
which ends with them
doing the exam anyway.
Okay. I'm gonna look
inside your mouth. Open wide.
I need to look at your chest
and your back next, okay?
I know you can't talk,
so stop me if you get scared.
Before you came here, did anyone
hurt you? Make you bleed?
I need to look
in your vagina now. Do you understand?
I'm a doctor, so it's okay.
All right?
Bend your knees,
keep your ankles together
and just let your knees fall
to the side, okay?
Oh, my God.
She has cuts all over her genital area,
like slices.
Some are almost healed,
but some are new.
She could be doing it
to herself.
She's a little young
to be cutting.
for a stroke.
Depression accounts for the cuts,
molestation accounts for the depression.
But do the cuts account
for all that blood?
They weren't deep enough.
So she's getting cut,
but that's not the source of the blood?
The other obvious source
is forcible penetration.
The obvious source
of the blood, not the cuts.
There was no tearing,
there's no evidence at all.
So we have no explanation
for the cuts or the blood.
Where is he?
What if our original
assumption was wrong?
Meaning what?
We found a T-shirt covered with blood
hidden in a heating vent.
How do we know it's even hers?
Her dad identified it.
Not the shirt, the blood.
Are those
the urine test results?
- Yes.
- And...
- I'm going to ask you for some blood.
- Why?
To see if your answer will be,
"I can't bleed in public."
This wasn't your urine, was it?
Why would I give you
someone else's urine?
The usual reason is
because you're on steroids.
I'm not an athlete.
Second favorite reason is
because you're on drugs.
- I'm not.
- I am.
Third favorite reason
is you have insurance
but your
friend Eggs Benedict doesn't.
So, Eggs describes a list of symptoms
and you repeat them to a doctor,
which is particularly stupid
because this is a free clinic.
Need you, now.
My work here is done.
Am I okay? Is it diabetes?
No, you're pregnant.
Six-year-old abuse victim and you
haven't called Social Services?
She might've been abused?
That's horrifying.
Why are you wearing
extra concealer under your eyes?
The law's clear. You suspect abuse,
you call the authorities.
You don't proceed as usual while the
possible abuser sits by her bedside.
Dad consented to the exam
which means it's not the dad.
How late were you
out last night?
It's always the dad
and I don't have a curfew.
Panty hamster
get a spin on its wheel?
I went to a play.
House, you are going back to your
office. You are picking up your phone,
calling Social Services and you are
reporting suspected abuse.
Do you understand?
What play?
You're trying to have sex
with Cuddy.
- Fries?
- You took her to a play.
You only take women
to plays because...
No, you only take women to plays for
that reason. That's your theory.
Okay. Then why did you
take her to a play?
She's a friend.
A friend with a squish mitten.
It is possible to have a friend
of the opposite sex without...
Blasphemer!
She's not a friend of the opposite sex,
she's a different species.
She's an administrator.
She's going to eat your head
after she's done.
Yes, I slept with her.
- Seriously?
- No.
Yes, you did.
Yes, I did.
- Seriously?
- No.
You've got a problem, House.
We just tested the blood
on Lucy's T-shirt,
it's full of endometrial cells.
So it's not her blood.
We tested that, too. It is.
Your six-year-old patient?
It's menstrual blood.
She's started puberty.
How can someone start puberty before
they even start the first grade?
She was in diapers
two years ago.
For some reason her body
has too much sex hormone.
It caused her
reproductive system to get confused,
start operating prematurely.
We need to find out the source
of the hormones and cut it off.
She's so young.
I haven't even
talked to her about sex.
I doubt she even knows
what a period is.
Girls talk to their moms
about that.
You're gonna be okay, Goosey.
I love you.
I
Want
juice.
She got her period
and didn't know what it was.
She was scared and confused.
A friend told her to put a T-shirt
in her underwear.
When she started
growing pubic hair,
she snuck Daddy's razor
and tried to shave it off.
Apparently forgot to sneak
the shaving cream.
Tumor's most likely.
A pituitary adenoma would send her
hormone level sky-high.
In Puerto Rico, in the '70s, there was
an epidemic of kids growing breasts
because of estrogen
in the poultry.
If it was in the food, it would be an
epidemic. We've got one kid.
She's six, she's tiny, she lives
on chicken fingers and milk.
Dad doesn't look like
the type to read labels,
he's probably buying stuff
packed full of hormones.
Excellent argument.
It's a tumor.
There's all sorts of environmental
sources. Pesticides, soy products.
Some shampoos are basically a placenta
in a bottle.
If the tumor's not in her brain,
it's in her reproductive tract.
Get an MRI.
- Can I at least...
- Waste your time?
Wouldn't recognize you
if you didn't.
Frontal cortex is clean,
moving caudally.
For the record,
Cameron's the one who broke it off.
Not interested.
No masses in the hypothalamus.
I wanted more.
She didn't share my feelings.
I feel like
I'm in a similar position.
Pituitary's clean.
You're an idiot.
Either she's lying or she's actually
emotionally detached.
Which one sounds more
like Cameron to you?
Neither.
You have to choose one.
There's a bright spot
on her left ovary.
Looks like a solid tumor.
They printed my letter.
You were right.
Of course I was.
What are we talking about?
- They printed my letter.
- Great.
Cuddy.
- You want to see her naked?
- No, no, no.
She wants to see me naked.
She sent me flowers.
Just thanking you for the play.
See, some people feel
an emotion called gratitude.
- There's a card.
- I suspected.
It explains how you knew
who they were from.
"Let's do it again.
Soon. XX, Lisa."
Xs are the kisses, right?
No, I think they're the hugs.
I think Os are the kisses.
No, no. The Xs are
definitely the kisses.
"Soon" is its own sentence.
I gotta go!
I'll miss you.
You were a good friend.
They printed my letter.
How was the play, Mrs. Lincoln?
What's up with Wilson?
He's just a little freaked.
Why?
I sent him flowers.
Jasper, you're not
supposed to be up here.
Is that other doctor
your boyfriend?
No.
Your dad's probably looking
for you.
He's got enough to
worry about right now.
Do you like him?
He's a friend.
Do you like him, like him?
We should get you
back to your dad.
Let me put this down
and I'll take you there.
I could be your boyfriend.
I think that wouldn't be fair
to the girls your own age.
- He seems like a tool.
- He's not. And that's rude.
I'm taking you back
to your father.
The mass is small.
About a centimeter across.
Firing the biopsy needle.
You nick an artery?
No.
She's in V tach. No pulse.
- Charging 50.
- Clear.
Clear.
Arrhythmia must have been
a reaction to the hydroxyurea.
We have to stop
the drug therapy.
Her bone marrow will just go back to
overproducing blood cells,
she'll keep having strokes
and we'll have to keep bleeding her.
Forever.
We resect the tumor, hormone levels go
back to normal, her symptoms go away.
Great plan, except for the fact
that her tumor's not a tumor.
It's a benign cyst.
If it's not a tumor, that just leaves
an environmental source.
I'm feeling another late night.
I'm gonna leave you two alone.
- You're kidding me, right?
- What?
The answer's right there.
It's just a question of finding it.
You don't need me for that.
Don't get the mochaccino
they screwed up
and put hot chocolate in the dispenser.
Thank you.
You were right.
The eight-year-old kid grabbed my ass.
I shouldn't have
encouraged him.
Well, I was a boy once.
I know how they think.
You were a pervert at eight?
Maybe eleven.
I didn't realize
you were gonna get hurt.
I'm sorry I misled you.
You didn't.
You have feelings for me.
You come back to me
again and again.
- For sex. It's a simple physical...
- Come on.
You have feelings for puppies
and patients that you barely know.
But when it comes to a guy
that you've worked with for three years,
had sex with,
spent the night with...
You telling me
you feel nothing?
Absolutely nothing?
Get away from her! Don't touch her!
I'll kill you if you touch her!
- Jasper!
- Get him off!
He's biting me. Get him off!
What is he gonna do?
He stopped and looked at him
from the top rope!
But now he's scaling... No way!
Somebody better be dying.
Lucy's big brother's got a crush on me,
so he bit the crap out of Chase.
And I care because...
Just thought you might
want to know when one of your employees
gets attacked by a sociopath.
Bees or monkeys, yes.
Sociopaths, no.
He doesn't have sense enough
to know he was pinned.
He's not a man,
he is a monster!
No way!
We've got to take
another look at this...
That might be what he needed.
Unable to somehow kick out of a...
- Hello?
- He's not a sociopath.
How do you know?
He's acting logically.
He's got a crush on you.
He's being aggressive about it.
Not just regular aggressive,
he's out-of-his-mind-on-hormones
aggressive.
You think he's...
Better figure out what's killing the
girl, because her brother's got it, too.
Jasper's got
a hundred times more testosterone
than a healthy eight-year-old.
But we scanned his brain
and reproductive tract,
no hormone secreting tumors.
I'm not surprised.
What's more likely?
Brother and sister get the same type
of tumor at exactly the same time,
or they both play
in the same toxic sandbox?
Yes, you would think that if for some
reason you were completely unaware
of the fact we spent the entire night
testing everything from that home.
It was all negative.
You went home?
Good for you. Delegate.
We're not his subordinates.
Making it all the more
impressive.
What if it's genetic?
Well, anyone else think it's
more than a coincidence
these kids have symptoms that
could be caused by a brain tumor
which is exactly
what killed their mom?
You just said
there were no tumors.
We scanned both their brains.
They looked clean.
So did their mom's,
until it didn't.
It can't be genetic.
Mom had none of the same symptoms.
Yes, she did, if the symptoms
were pubic hair and menstruation.
That's ridiculous. If menstruation
is a symptom of brain cancer
then I should be
on chemo right now.
That's ridiculous. You're way
too skinny to be menstruating.
What if the mom
had other problems?
Symptoms her doctors ignored on account
of the fact she was already dying?
Pull all her medical records.
Find any similarities
to our patients.
And punch the little brat on the nose
so he doesn't have a stroke
like his sister.
I'm not sick.
Just trying to
keep you that way.
I want Dr. Cameron to do mine.
Trust me, you don't want her
cutting you right now.
So Jasper's
behavioral issues...
They could be a function
of the increased testosterone.
Hopefully, he'll be a delight
as soon as we figure this out.
My tummy hurts.
It hurts!
No, it doesn't.
Don't be such a baby.
My tummy hurts!
- Where in your tummy?
- It hurts!
It hurts!
Stomach pain is from
a cyst in her pancreas.
I found two more in her
kidneys and one in her lung.
They weren't there
48 hours ago.
Hormones are making
her body go haywire.
She gets one in her brain
or heart, she's dead.
No pressure, though.
Her mom was perfectly healthy
until she got cancer.
She had none of the symptoms
the kids have.
It's not genetic,
it's not environmental.
It's gotta be
a pituitary adenoma.
Yes! That would make
complete sense if they had one.
Just because we haven't found anything
on the scan doesn't mean it's not there.
We should remove
her pituitary gland.
Two siblings, same condition.
It's gotta be genetic
or environmental.
We add in the same time
and we're back to just environmental.
Yes, and that would make complete sense
if there was anything
in her environment.
Just because we haven't
found anything yet...
She's been out of her environment for
four days and she's still getting worse.
I'm getting
the father's consent.
No!
We have no evidence.
This is your process, House.
You asked us
what two plus two is.
We've eliminated every number
except for four.
She needs brain surgery.
The ovaries produce
sex hormones
in response to a signal
from the pituitary gland.
Since we know the ovaries are fine,
the most likely cause...
"Most likely" means she wants to root
around inside your little girl's brain
without any guarantee
that it'll work.
That's why she's holding off
on doing your son.
Dr. House knows that unfortunately we've
ruled out every other option.
We need to resect
Lucy's pituitary before...
Who else visits these kids?
They don't have
any family in town.
You got a girlfriend?
- No one visits.
- School?
They don't go to the same school.
House, I've covered...
- Nanny?
- They don't have one.
They go to after-school daycare
but none of the other kids are sick.
Yet.
It took your son twice as long
to develop symptoms as your daughter.
Maybe the other kids
are just slow.
We wait
and your daughter may die.
She does this,
your daughter will need
hormone replacement therapy
for the rest of her life.
The treatments are extremely effective.
She should lead
a relatively normal life.
And isn't that
every parent's dream?
To have a kid grow up to be
relatively normal?
My husband died of thyroid cancer
that metastasized to his brain.
I've been there.
I know how terrifying
this can be.
And I am telling you this is your best
chance to save your daughter's life.
You did not just play
the dead husband card.
My wife died.
Because she signed a consent form that
I didn't want her to sign.
Died.
Thank you.
How did you know?
Know what?
That the other kids
weren't sick?
You've been here for four days.
I just...
I would have heard.
Right.
Do you have hair
on your special place?
Miss Janie!
Can I help you?
I'm a doctor.
Two of your kids are sick
and I need to know why.
You think they got sick here?
I think
you're dating their dad.
He told you?
No.
And I don't really care
why he didn't.
I just need to know how often you go
to their house and what you bring.
- I don't.
- Shampoos, fancy soaps...
- Kids get in your bag.
- I've never been to their house.
They just lost their mom
and we thought it was too soon.
Why are you staring at me?
Lip wax?
I just had it done over lunch.
- Mani-pedi?
- No.
Just the wax.
Women get a wax as a part of a whole
self-indulgent beauty ritual.
Pedicures, steam,
cucumber masks.
No one runs out at lunch
just to get a lip wax,
unless you woke up looking
like Yosemite Sam.
You're an ass.
- Cameron.
- It's always the dad.
Excess facial hair in women.
It's a clear sign of hormonal imbalance.
Exactly what
the little kiddies have.
Is there something wrong
at the daycare center?
There's something wrong
in your pants.
She's a lot younger
than I am. I
use a
male enhancement cream
to keep up with her.
What does this
have to do with...
Never occurred to you
to get a prescription
instead of some penis-pumper
loaded with testosterone?
I keep it at the gym.
I apply it daily in the shower
just like it says on the bottle.
It's never been in my home,
it's obviously never been near the kids.
But you have.
We've been through that,
I'm not a pervert or a pedophile!
Thirty percent of our waste
is excreted through our skin.
That sounds high.
It's why you stink
after eating garlic.
Jack waters his beanstalk
every day for a week
he's oozing bean curd
out of his pores for a month.
Every time
you gave the little tykes a hug,
you gave them a dose of testosterone.
Small for you, but more than
their little bodies can handle.
So...
I did this to them?
Just holding their hands?
Uh-huh.
If I stop using it?
You'll be floppy,
they'll be fine.
Give it back!
He'll still be eight.
You okay?
Yeah, I think so.
- Talk to Cuddy?
- No, not yet.
I don't know what to say.
Just be straight with her.
I'm not sure what that is.
I can't stop
thinking about her.
In what way?
Maybe she's right. Maybe...
Maybe this is worth exploring.
Are you sure that she feels...
She sent me flowers.
How do I do this?
What do I say?
Cameron would tell you
to say how you feel.
Me? I'd get her drunk.
I'm not gonna say anything.
I'm just gonna walk into her office
and I'm gonna kiss her.
That's a bold move.
Cuddy likes bold.
Yeah, you're right, if you spoke,
you'd just say something stupid.
Yeah, I mean I'll either
get a girlfriend or get fired.
Okay.
Yeah. Okay.
You! You! You!
You were gonna let me do that?
You made a compelling argument.
You sent those flowers to me!
Yes! Because you
took her to a play.
And because, actually, you do wanna
march down there and kiss her.
No! I don't.
Yes, you do.
You're right.
Seriously?
No.
You're a jerk.
- Night, Wilson.
- Night, House.
They're beautiful.
I thought about what you said.
And
I really don't want
a relationship with you.
I know.
I also know you like flowers.
I don't get the whole
May-December thing.
Give him a break.
May-October at worst.
Well, why can't it be
October-October?
May is when
things start to get hot.
If that guy wasn't trying
so hard
to keep up
with a woman half his age,
he wouldn't have
almost killed both his kids.
Guy gets a little
something-something,
couple of kids
have to die... Circle of life.
So many people,
so much energy and drama
just trying to find someone who's almost
never the right person anyway.
It just shouldn't be so hard.
I got tickets to a play.