Here you go.
That fried crap
will kill you. See?
Good night.
Time to make the donuts.
- Hands in the air! Right now!
- Get them up!
Move out here. Get up!
Move out here! Let's go!
- Move it.
- Put them up!
Purses and wallets
on the counter, right now.
Yo! Your watches, your jewelry!
Take it all off!
- Yeah, all right.
- Keep the girl. Keep the girl.
Yeah.
We're moving to
the back room. Let's go!
- Go! Let's go!
- Move it!
Go on! Not you.
Hey! Hey, wait a minute.
She's staying right here.
You're not going to do this.
Whoa, whoa, kid.
No, Jeremy. Please, just do
what they say. Please!
Okay. Okay. Yeah. Move!
Son of a bitch!
You thought I was
going to let you hurt my wife?
Hey! Hey, sir. Your wife!
What did he do to her?
Nothing.
Tracy!
Twenty-year-old married
African-American female.
Couldn't breathe.
Anaphylaxis-like throat swelling.
- Children?
- You think pregnancy would explain...
Explains the marriage.
Who the hell
gets married at 20?
I'm guessing, people in love?
Show me a 20-year-old
who's not in love.
You get married at 20,
you're going to be shocked
at who you're living with at 30.
It's not allergies.
Negative on the skin test.
Four days of antihistamines
and steroids.
- Who's he talking to?
- What?
It's got an ass.
Technically, that makes it a "who."
New nurse in pedes.
Wendy something.
Swelling just started
to go down...
You seen her here before?
A couple times. I tried following
her home, but she gave me the slip.
Swelling's...
You think that's funny?
Ask him about the time
he sabotaged my cane.
Are you serious?
There was a point to it.
Wendy, this is House.
Something about not getting too uppity
with normal folks who walk good.
You're everything I'd heard.
Nice to meet you.
Why so rude?
You've sprinted through
three bad marriages
into an affair with a dying patient.
Now a naughty nurse?
How many more failed relationships are
we both gonna have to deal with
before you learn to
love yourself?
And I mean that
in the literal way.
It's amazing how you can not only know
it's a relationship,
but that it's a bad relationship,
based on nothing but nothing.
I know you.
I'm not with her,
not even trying.
You're lying to me.
That's interesting.
Well, as long as
it's interesting.
- Swelling is...
- Why is she hanging out here?
Anyone interested in what happened
with the swelling?
She's in pedes.
That's the next wing over.
If you're wondering
if Wilson's dating her, ask Wilson.
Clearly he did, and Wilson denied it.
And House doesn't believe it.
That's gotta hurt. That's why it pays
to have more than one friend, House.
If he's not hitting that,
why is she here?
Because I'm hitting that
and it's totally hot.
Swelling took four days
to resolve.
Patient has unexplained
intense abdominal pains.
So explain them.
Wake me when they've done
an exploratory laparotomy.
Anybody know her?
Know her story?
Up and at 'em.
They did a laparotomy.
Liver, bowel, gall bladder,
appendix, all clean.
Belly pain plus
throat swelling.
She was in some sort of assault, right?
Simple neck trauma.
It says no one touched her neck, and if
they did, it would resolve by now.
Didn't need to touch her.
Some guy coughed on her, right?
He's in jail and
he's completely healthy,
except for the broken head
he got from the beating he took.
There's pot on her tox screen.
Salmonella from the pot
would explain the stomach pains.
It's a stretch.
She'd have a fever.
She's on steroids for the swelling,
therefore no fever.
And the smoking
explains the throat.
Sorry, take it back.
That's a stretch.
Got a better idea?
Then stretch away.
Start her on fluoroquinolone
for the salmonella.
I was waiting
two hours out there.
Fascinating.
Have you considered a career
as a memoirist?
Let's see it.
You don't introduce yourself?
Sorry, I thought
you were waiting two hours.
Didn't know you wanted to chat.
Hi, I'm Greg.
How about that local sports team?
It's not an infection.
How can you tell without...
You want me to touch you?
It's your private place.
You're chewing nicotine gum,
which causes dehydration,
which causes wear and tear.
Try a lubricant,
or foreplay if you're cheap.
Just take a swab
and get it tested, okay?
Sorry, I already met this month's quota
of useless tests for stubborn idiots.
You're rude.
Wow. You're like a
detective or something.
And you're smart
and you're funny.
But you are bitter
and you're lonely,
so you treat everyone around
like they're idiots,
and you get away with it
'cause of your cane.
Please stop. It's hard to
write through the haze of bitter tears.
But you're not actually
getting away with it.
Last nurse you made fun of, she probably
slipped some crap into your coffee.
Yeah, I asked for
decrapinated coffee.
Treat people like jerks,
you get treated like a jerk.
Thank you.
Bend over.
- You kidding me?
- If you have an infection,
you'd have a fever.
But you're chewing
nicotine gum,
which messes with the weather
in your mouth,
so I need to
vacation elsewhere.
And wait till I put
the thermometer in.
You break it, you bought it.
Leaving early today.
Do you ever get that thing
where you're sure you forgot something,
but you can't figure out what?
Guess it can't be
that important.
Salmonella is a bacterial infection
that you can get from pot plants.
It causes stomach pain.
And my throat?
The thinking is it's
an inflammatory reaction to the smoking.
How much would you need to smoke
for your throat to go nuts like that?
Most cases, a lot.
We don't smoke a lot.
Let's just start the treatment.
You think we're liars,
as well as druggies?
Actually, I'm wondering if you'd mind
getting her a cup of ice chips.
You're not gonna get
any different answer from her.
No, no. He can stay.
No offense, but this place is scary.
I feel better when he's around.
Tracy, I need to talk to you.
We don't do a lot of drugs.
I need to know
your answers aren't being pressured.
Look, if you think the antibiotics are a
good idea, you can give them to me.
Okay. Worst-case scenario,
it'll help us rule out a few things.
He's a good guy.
He just has a hard time
holding in his emotions.
You don't have to
apologize for me.
That mean you're
going to do it for yourself?
I got nothing to apologize for.
He's young.
Itchy.
Allergic reaction
to the fluoroquinolone.
We should switch to
a different antibiotic.
Why?
We can't treat the salmonella unless...
Salmonella? That was a total stretch.
Oh, man, why does that
sound so familiar?
You think it's 'cause
I said it an hour ago?
Then it was a dumb thing
to say. Now it's smart.
She's got the rash, so we know
she's unusually susceptible
to allergic reactions,
so that's what brought her in.
Probably the peanut butter
in her sandwich.
Stick test was negative
for peanuts.
That's because you foolishly tested her
while she was lying down.
- Exercise-based anaphylaxis?
- I think that requires exercise.
When her throat closed,
they'd just got done eating.
Not even competitive eating.
And getting robbed.
That always gets my heart rate up.
Give her the same food
she ate at the diner
and stick her on the treadmill.
Better yet, put a gun to her head,
threaten to rape her.
You don't think
I'm going to get a response?
No.
You're on. Fifty bucks.
I'm not betting
on a patient's...
A hundred bucks. If you say so.
Tracy, I'm increasing
the speed a little.
My stomach really hurts.
Jeremy, you out there?
Talk to... Talk...
You're doing great.
Isn't this enough?
We're not getting
any allergic response yet.
Shut it off.
We don't complete the test,
my boss will just come down here
and do it himself.
You do not want that.
She's in pain. Look at her.
I don't want to have to
ask you to leave.
You're gonna ask me to leave?
Are you kidding me? This is my wife!
You guys aren't helping her.
You're just hurting her. What?
You guys have all this equipment here,
and you're not doing anything!
You guys can't even
figure out what's...
God, it hurts.
- Where?
- In my stomach. And my chest.
- Oh, God!
- It's Foreman. Get me a wheelchair.
He's as sick as she is now.
I told you it wouldn't work.
It worked on the wrong patient.
We could spend all day
arguing right or wrong.
Give me the 100 bucks.
We didn't bet.
We could spend all day
arguing whether we bet or not.
Give me the 100 bucks.
Come on, Foreman, pay up. He won.
Or we could just never finish the DDX.
Husband's test showed no MI, no
aortic dissection. It's not his heart.
It's just nonspecific
chest and abdominal pain.
So, psychosomatic?
Panic attack?
Pain persisted after
he got lorazepam and morphine.
Whose locker is that?
Mine.
Chest, stomach, throat.
- What does it all mean?
- We're in the nurses' locker room.
I know that.
Oh, that is so annoying.
Wilson's girlfriend's
left her stuff in my locker again.
Great. I hadn't committed
any felonies yet today.
Relax. You know who
they're going to blame.
House, you want to mess
with Wilson, no problem.
But you got no reason
to screw around with...
Can we get back to the medicine?
Okay.
Why assume one disease?
His chest, her throat.
So it's just a coincidence that they've
both got crippling stomach pains?
Wow, they really are a great couple.
So much in common.
One blue shoe.
What do you think that means?
It means you're insane.
Wilson's not dating her.
You feeling luckier?
It doesn't matter
what I answer.
Two hundred it is.
If they're married and caught
the same disease, then it means they...
Brochure to a jazz festival
in the Poconos this weekend.
Wilson likes jazz.
Foreman, pay the man.
Four, five, six novels, no music.
What does that mean?
She's literate.
It means she spends
her leisure time reading, not listening.
She'd only want to go and watch jazz
if the other person wanted to go.
She has a martyr complex,
issues of inferiority.
Married couple, same disease.
They either got it from each other
or in the same place.
Infectious or environmental?
What we have to do is check out
parasites, viruses, bacteria, fungi,
prions, radiation, toxins, chemicals.
Or it's Internet porn-related.
I'll check the Internet.
You guys cover the rest of the stuff.
If they can live here without killing
each other, they must really be in love.
It's tiny.
How come it's taking you
so long to search it?
Box of condoms in his jacket.
I know you're poor now,
but buy your own.
She's on the pill.
Why would he need condoms?
No, no, no. Put that back.
Why?
We show that to House, he'll just
call the guy a cheating bastard.
Look how he is with Wilson.
He'd be right. Could be an STD.
One that doesn't give them
any symptoms in their sexual organs?
- They never mentioned anything.
- Maybe they're embarrassed.
What else could it be?
You think they just like the sexy feel
of latex against their genitals?
Maybe the wife
just wants to be extra-cautious.
- Come on. You really believe that?
- Yeah.
Good. Then I'm sure
you'll have no problem convincing House.
That cheating bastard!
He loves her.
Right, I bet he told you
that she's the love of his life.
People lie. I get it.
But they don't go up against two armed
gunmen to save someone unless they...
There's a reason that we don't let kids
vote or drink or work in salt mines.
They're idiots.
Twenty-year-olds
fall in and out of love more often
than they change their oil filters,
which they should do
more often.
Sorry. Ridiculous of me
to draw a conclusion
based on actually
observing them.
I should have just depended on
your misanthropic view of human nature.
Gonorrhea explains
all their symptoms.
Fitzhugh-Curtis syndrome
for her belly pain,
costochondritis and bladder infection
for his chest and abdominal pain.
Good.
Now go rub their lying,
cheating privates with a cotton swab.
Why would you want to
look at our...
Is this because of the condoms?
You found them in his jacket,
figured he was hiding something from me.
I thought I was pregnant last month.
It kind of freaked me out.
I'm way too young to have kids.
So you just wanted
to be extra-cautious?
Wish one of us had figured that out,
stuck to his guns.
We've still gotta
check you both.
She's the only girlfriend
I've ever had.
- She's the love of...
- Please don't say it.
I can't say I love my wife?
We're still going to test you.
What is it? I'm white?
Yeah, that's it.
Jer, I wish you would stop it.
You're really embarrassing.
Everybody thinks they're so liberal,
but I see how they look at us.
White and black,
especially black.
I'm sorry, Trace,
but it's true.
Great. Prove us all wrong.
Stupid...
No scarring, no purulent discharge,
and the NAATs were negative.
- They don't have an STD.
- What's that you say?
You've got a problem
with interracial couples?
Thank you, Chase. No!
Have any of your shorties
ever been whities?
I'm not sure I understand
your ghetto slang, Dr. House.
How many black women
have you dated, by the way?
I don't care about color, as long as
they can help me breed a superior race.
Yeah, my exes have usually
been black. So what?
It's not a racial thing. It's cultural.
I have more in common with them.
Like I assume you only date
emotionally stunted bigots.
Sorry, you're right.
That kind of prejudice is totally fine.
The abdominal pain's getting worse.
We've had to up their morphine twice.
Take the wife off the steroids.
She spikes a fever,
we'll know it's an infection.
She doesn't,
it's environmental.
He got off easy.
I almost gave him a colonoscopy.
That was one of the stupidest things
you have ever done,
and there is heavy
competition for...
What are you doing?
You only ate
half your breakfast.
Feeling a little sick
this morning?
I'm not pregnant.
They burnt my omelet.
You need to apologize
to this guy.
I am a man of principle.
I don't care how much time and money
it costs you to defend me.
He wants to kill you.
No empty coffee cups.
Off the caffeine. Good for baby.
Cups are in the other wastebasket.
Baby's in your mind.
You can berate patients
all you want.
Shoving objects into
their rectums is assault.
Pay attention to me.
Sorry, that would make
it harder to ignore you.
Can't ignore that rapidly
expanding first-trimester ass, though.
Sometimes an ass
is just an ass.
You are not always right, House.
Apologize to the guy.
- What are you doing here?
- Stay away from my son.
How did you find us?
Stay away from that girl.
Please! Please! Please!
You leave him alone!
- What happened?
- She's dreaming. She started yelling.
- You're breaking Jeremy's arm. Please!
- No one's hurting him.
Baby, it's me. It's Jeremy.
Tracy, Tracy.
She's okay. Baby, it was just
a bad dream. Everything's okay.
Tracy. Tracy?
It was an acute delirium.
Well, she's talking, right?
I mean, she's coming out of it.
No, she's not really talking,
just making sounds.
Okay. When's she
gonna come out?
Jeremy, she's in a coma.
So her vitals
are pretty stable,
but her response to stimuli
is getting weaker,
which means the coma's
getting worse.
Her brain is slowly
shutting down.
Can I see her?
We're getting some more images
to check for masses or infections.
I'll increase your morphine.
Her hallucination.
If you knew what it was,
would that make any difference?
Medically, I mean.
Not usually.
Some cases, the form of
a hallucination can tell us
what part of the brain
is being hit.
I think it was about my dad.
Your dad was breaking your arm?
He was a drunk,
pill-popping racist.
He caught me sneaking
into her house when we were 13.
She lived next door.
He broke my arm
and threatened her.
We ran off when we were 16.
You still in touch with him?
He killed himself
a couple years ago.
Oh, it's not medical. I just thought
blacks were the racist ones.
Some generalized
edema throughout,
and areas of increased signal
here, here, here and here.
Damn, all over her brain stem.
Could be plaques,
maybe hyperdensities from the edema.
Or tumors or anything.
We add brain involvement to the chest,
stomach, throat, what do we got?
Didn't spike a fever
when we took her off the steroids,
- so it's not an infection.
- Leaving environmental.
What flavor?
Environmental doesn't make sense,
either.
If it was a toxin,
we'd see it in their livers.
None of the neighbors
are sick, no coworkers.
They both got it.
That means infection or environmental,
and since it's not an infection...
What if they
didn't both get it?
Maybe we got our basic assumption
wrong and it's two different diseases.
Maybe we didn't and
it's sarcoidosis.
Sarcoidosis isn't infectious
or environmental.
Tell that to the clusters
of sarcoidosis cases.
Firefighters and residents
of pine tar forests?
I did see these two putting out
that blaze in the Pine Barrens.
If sarcoidosis has
two environmental causes,
it has environmental causes.
We just don't know all
of them yet. Husband's chest.
He has slightly enlarged
hilar lymph nodes.
Sarcoidosis explains
almost all of their symptoms,
including her getting worse
off the steroids.
Doesn't explain
his throat swelling.
That's what "almost" means.
90% of sarcoidosis cases
have lung scarring.
- Oh, 90?
- Oh, "almost"?
Fine.
Consult a specialist.
If this is more
dating advice...
Love to gossip,
but I got work to do.
Is this sarcoidosis?
It's pretty nonspecific.
It could be granulomas,
could be plaques. What's this?
Oh! Oh! You stole
Wendy's personnel file?
In a way, aren't we all guilty
of bribing the janitor
to take her file and
give it to me?
Yes, I take my share
of the blame, but society's...
First of all,
I'm not dating her.
She is so wrong for you.
You know she filed a form so the
hospital would take extra withholding?
- Who does that?
- She's much too cautious for me.
Point taken.
I'll start dating her
so I can break up with her
and start dating a stripper.
You're a miserable jerk
who can't stand to be alone.
I didn't try to break up your marriages.
You did that yourself.
My marriages were so crappy,
I was spending all my time with you.
Your real fear is me having
a good relationship.
Yes, it keeps me up at night.
That and the Loch Ness monster,
global warming, evolution
and other fictional concepts.
Although, big romantic weekend
in the Poconos could change everything.
You don't... No.
I don't think it's sarcoidosis.
He says it's sarcoidosis.
Start them both
on methotrexate.
And if you're wrong?
If Wilson's wrong,
we'll biopsy her just to be sure.
Her brain stem?
Brain damage is
not only possible, it's likely.
Good point. Let's biopsy
something safer, like her shoes.
The husband. He'd have to give consent.
He can't right now.
Why? Does this guy write
with his stomach?
He has a conflict of interest.
It's not his brain we're cutting open,
but he still gets all the benefit.
He'd do it
just to save himself.
Or save her.
She's the love of his life,
remember?
He never said that.
She needs a guardian ad litem.
I can't let you do this.
Well, how are you going
to stop me? Call Cuddy?
Cameron's right.
There's a conflict.
No, there isn't.
Not unless one of them
wants to die a horrible, painful death.
I'm sure the guardian
will figure that out.
In a couple days.
Will the guardian convince the disease
to hold off eating her brain
until we can get
the legalities worked out?
I just don't want some
plaintiff's lawyer owning my hospital.
Legalities help.
Speaking of which,
did you get your thermometer back yet?
We had a nice chat.
Did you know he's a Rotarian?
Listen, she'll die
without the biopsy.
I need to cover the hospital's ass.
You're too biased.
I send you in there,
you'll steamroll over him.
Something goes wrong, he'll sue us for
not disclosing the risks.
Then have Wilson
talk to the husband.
Wilson kills people left and right.
No one ever sues him.
Fine, but only if you apologize
to the clinic guy.
No. Probably better
to just let that couple die.
I don't care if you mean it.
Just do it.
Unfortunately, we don't see
any way around a biopsy.
We'll do all we can
to minimize any damage.
No.
The methotrexate isn't showing
any effects yet.
You could both be...
She's brilliant.
All A's in college
while working full-time.
I can't do that to her.
And if you both die,
you think she'd want that?
Do it on me instead.
- It's not in your brain.
- It will be.
It's the same disease, right?
Do it then.
She could die
before you show the symptoms.
Then stop treating me.
Great job. Why didn't you just
shoot him in the head?
Hold on. That gives me an idea.
You know what could save this couple?
Lots of misdirected sarcasm.
They're dead! Yelling at you
might prevent you from screwing up...
I didn't screw up.
I did my job.
Your job was
to get me the biopsy.
No, it was to present
the patient with his options.
Two options,
biopsy or no biopsy.
He chose a third, no treatment.
How do you even do that?
Remember when you used to just weave
elaborate conspiracy theories
about my love life?
Those were such good times.
How much morphine
is the husband on?
We can't increase it any more.
His respirations are depressed.
Increase it?
Drugs cloud people's judgment.
Cold-turkey the sucker.
No.
Good point.
Did I ask you guys
to follow me?
No, which made us nervous.
He'll catch on if he notices
he's off the morphine drip.
Shoot him up with one of
these puppies instead.
No!
You do understand
it's not really a puppy.
It's naloxone.
An opiate blocker? He'll feel like
he's swallowing a bonfire.
That's pretty unethical,
even for you.
How is that unethical?
It'll lead to a diagnosis.
It's leading to
the torture of the husband
on the off-chance he'll allow
a procedure on another person.
Which will lead to a diagnosis.
Didn't I just say that?
Give it up.
Foreman and Cameron are too ethical,
and I'm too scared of getting sued.
Fine. Now, I'm just going to
find someplace safe to hide this
so I won't be tempted
to use it.
You're not doing it, either.
What, are you going
to run for it?
If they die now, they'll never be able
to grow old and tired of each other.
We can't baby-sit
House all day.
Tell Cuddy to put a nurse
by his room.
Damn it!
Atropine? What happened to...
He knew we'd stop him.
He stuck both of them in his pocket.
That's actually pretty clever.
Guess I can't use
that trick again, huh?
My stomach!
It was a pretty smart plan,
Jerry, but I'm onto you.
There's only one good reason
to kill the biopsy.
You poisoned your wife, and you don't
want the coppers to get wise.
No!
Oh, all right. Then you're just a moron.
Biopsy me!
Only if this thing hits
your brain, you moron.
And I can't stress
that "moron" part enough.
You're killing your wife.
She is the love of my life.
Careful. When she's dead
and you're on wife number two,
you're gonna feel real guilty
about saying that.
Feel that? Get used to it.
Pain's going to get
a lot worse.
No, it won't.
Morphine just isn't working
right now for some reason.
I'm putting you on a tranquilizer
in the meantime. It'll work again soon.
Want to bet?
I don't care about the pain.
I need to be in pain,
because I have to get worse.
It means you can do
the biopsy on me.
Dude, she's in a coma.
Who are you trying to impress?
I'd die for her.
Give up. Or are we going to wait for him
to get all grown up and cynical?
I was just going to call you.
I need a court order
to biopsy this woman's brain.
Speaking of litigation...
Michael Tritter,
you know Dr. House.
You guys can talk here.
I don't want to sue you.
Good.
I want to beat
the crap out of you.
- Less good.
- And I'll tell you why.
You're a bully,
and bullies,
they don't back down
until they run into someone
stronger and meaner.
But you'll accept an apology?
Yes.
Not really a recipe
for sincerity.
I'm not looking for sincerity.
I'm looking for humiliation,
something that will make you think twice
before you treat
the next patient like crap.
Here's what's going to happen.
You go brag to your friends
about how you made
the big, nasty doctor poop in his pants.
I get Cuddy off my back
by telling her that I humiliated myself.
Here's the catch.
We're both going to be lying.
I'm not apologizing.
If anything,
you deserved a bigger thermometer.
- What's wrong?
- Jeremy's worse.
And that's what's right.
Cut the stubborn jerk's
head open and take a slice.
It's not his brain.
Lactic acid's up to 39.
His intestines are rotting.
This isn't sarcoidosis.
Then he'll get his wish.
He's dying, just not in a way
that's going to help his wife.
Coma's worse.
She's losing response to stimuli.
He's vomiting blood
and his lactic acid's 45.
- He's got to have ischemic bowel.
- So what?
Well, let's see. Lack of blood flow's
causing his guts to die,
which will cause him to die,
unless we cut out a few feet of
small intestine and reattach the ends.
I don't know,
seems worth a mention.
Why does he have it?
What does it tell us?
Small-cell vasculitis?
Good. Now let's hear it again,
but this time with a more environmental
or infectious feeling.
Or, like I said before, it might not be
environmental or infectious.
He has vasculitis,
she has porphyria.
Belly pain plus hallucination,
classic symptoms.
It could even cause a coma.
Fine. Start her on
hematin for porphyria.
What about him?
Take out the dead bowel.
It's all we can do.
And biopsy it.
If Foreman's right, it might save him.
If Foreman's wrong, the dead bowel
might save both of them.
Bowel's not dead.
Unless he's been tossing down frosty
cans of lactic acid, bowel is dead.
What we're looking for
is a reason it's dead.
Bowel's not dead.
Just general swelling and edema.
High lactate was probably from stress.
We just sliced him open
from chest to pubic bone for nothing.
Nothing's something.
Forget the ischemia.
Add the edema and swelling.
Probably from cutting him open.
Probably, not definitely.
Okay, back to the beginning.
What did we talk about?
Anything. I want to hear it all again.
Allergies.
Doesn't fit at all now.
STDs. Maybe we
got the wrong one.
What about syphilis?
- Neurological symptoms.
- He wasn't cheating on her.
Yeah, love of his life.
Don't you have to wait till he's dead
before you make
that determination?
She's his only girlfriend ever.
They grew up next door,
ran off together as teenagers.
Sarcoidosis. We only ruled it out
because we thought he had ischemic...
- Why did they run off?
- What difference does...
Kids talk about running off.
How many do it?
What was the reason?
They were trying to escape
his evil, pill-popping, racist dad.
You would've liked him.
We should do another...
How do you know
the dad was racist?
He beat up his son for dating
a black girl. I extrapolated from that.
You see racism everywhere.
Maybe he just didn't
like this black girl.
It's not sarcoid.
We would have seen granulomas in his...
She has pretty eyes.
Forget infectious.
Forget environmental.
Defective DNA is keeping them
from making a critical protein,
hence the fluid build-up.
Hits the throat, stomach,
chest and brain.
Angioedema?
Hereditary angioedema.
Symptoms fit perfectly.
It's an incredibly rare disease.
They both would have to have a parent...
Is it a coincidence
that your sister has great hair,
or that these two
have green eyes?
You're not saying...
They're not brother and sister.
God, no. That would be sick.
Half brother and sister.
Different moms.
Dad must have had
an affair with her mom.
That's why he flipped out
when the kids started dating.
He had it himself.
Probably why the pills.
We won't know for sure...
Testing for HAE or paternity
is going to take a day.
She doesn't have a day.
Start treating and see what happens.
Any change?
Her response to stimuli
is still just as weak.
I almost hope
she stays in a coma.
That's sweet, Cameron.
I'd like to avoid shattering
both of their lives.
You don't think
dying will do that?
It's just her oximeter.
Tracy.
She's awake.
Oh, God, baby.
It's gonna be okay.
Awesome. Can I tell them?
We've obviously got to
let them know what's wrong.
But the cause,
the brother-sister thing...
Good plan. We just gotta keep them away
from doctors, the Internet
and anyone who's
not a total moron.
Tell them.
Yesterday he was willing to die
to save her.
We've gotta give him time to recover.
He might be a little vexed
that you kept letting him
hump his sister in the meantime.
Tell them.
Look, unless their dad was also
the product of an incestuous union,
the chances of serious
complications are minimal.
Noble of you to take that risk.
Tell them, or I will.
So we just need
to take these pills?
Twice a day.
Angioedema is very treatable.
You'll be fine.
So, what? We, like,
caught this from each other?
No, it's a condition
you've both always had.
The onset of symptoms are
sometimes caused by stress or trauma.
The incident at the diner.
So we got it as kids?
It's a genetic disease.
It's not...
There's no good reason
two unrelated people would get it.
We think you guys
should take a DNA test.
How can we be related?
We think you have the same dad.
We won't know for sure
until we do the test.
Oh, God!
Your father.
No. No, this can't be true.
Yeah. Yeah, Jer, I'm lighter.
You know, I'm lighter
than both my parents.
And our eyes. Everyone always talks
about how we have the same eyes.
You're not really siblings.
We have the same father!
You didn't fight in
the backseat on car trips.
You didn't change
each other's diapers.
You guys just met
and fell in love.
The way you feel,
that hasn't changed.
Hey, Foreman, can you wear the beeper
for a couple of hours this weekend?
What?
We just destroyed
two people's lives.
So I'm not allowed to
run errands anymore?
I'd like to see some sign
that it affects you,
or that you recognize
it affects other people.
So are you going to wear
the beeper or not?
Sorry, I can't.
You just want to punish me.
I'm busy.
With what?
Going out of town.
Where are you going?
Foreman, you're not missing
a blue shoe, are you?
Come...
You can't bet when you know
the answer beforehand.
We could spend all day
arguing whether you can bet
when you know
the answer beforehand.
Give me the 200 bucks.
What?
- Hey.
You okay?
I was just wondering,
do you really like jazz?
I love it.
Are you lying?
I'm lying.
I want to spend time with you.
Is that so terrible?
No.
Maybe we shouldn't walk out together.
If people see us leaving...
Everybody's got to
find out sometime.
Let me just meet you
at your place.
She got her own room.
She just needs some time alone.
Do you want me to
hang out here a bit?
If you've come to return
the thermometer, don't bother.
I've moved on.
If you'd actually read my chart,
you'd have known that I'm a cop.
You were going 40 in a 25 zone.
Oh, come on.
This isn't because I was speeding,
this is because I'm Latino.
License, registration,
proof of insurance.
Sorry, cool jacket.
Only pockets for important stuff.
That's a shame.
A 50 buck ticket?
Is that your way of
beating me up,
or is that just the price
for sticking something in you?
You took a pill
while you were examining a patient.
That's serious
addictive behavior.
I'm betting that
you're holding right now.
I wasn't weaving.
I'm not drunk.
- You've got no reason to...
- Pupils dilated.
Appear to be under
the influence of a narcotic.
Would you mind turning around, please,
and putting your hands behind your head?
Does that polite crap
ever work on people?
Most people realize
there's only one answer.
You got a prescription?
I'm a cripple who
works in a hospital.
You don't think
I can get a valid prescription?
Arrogant son of a bitch
like you?
I'm going to bet
you didn't bother.
You are under arrest
for possession of narcotics.
You have the right
to remain silent,
which you should take advantage of
for once in your life.
If you give up the right
to remain silent,
anything you say
can and will be used against you...