Mom!
I'm thirsty.
I just gave you water.
I want juice.
It's bedtime.
Close your eyes
and go to sleep.
Mom!
What do you want, Clance?
Oh. Hi, Dad.
Go to bed.
Can I turn the TV on?
TV's only for the daytime.
That was the deal.
I'll keep the volume down.
I just like the light.
Go to bed.
Dad, what if...
What if they come
to get me again?
Nobody is coming to get you,
okay? Go to bed now.
Come on, Clancy.
It's time to get up.
If you plan to
be out at the shore today,
you are in for a treat.
We're looking at mostly sunny skies up
and down the Jersey coast...
I guess he's already up.
That's a first.
Well, I'll see
if he needs breakfast.
Hey, Clance, you hungry?
Hon, he's not down here.
You sure?
Clancy?
Clancy? Where are you?
- Sweetie, are you hiding?
- Clancy?
Where is he?
Clancy!
You're gonna be in big trouble
when I find you.
Honey, come out right now,
wherever you are. This is not funny.
Clance?
Clancy?
Where's the sweat and the BO?
You've taken such pride
in bathing us all in your musk.
I showered at home.
And yet you're
earlier than usual.
Is this an intervention?
It's a little late,
since I'm not using drugs anymore.
I am, however,
still hooked on phonics.
If you did your morning run
and showered at home,
you'd be later than usual.
Thought of you in the shower.
How's your leg?
You seem to be favoring your left side.
I was hanging down
my right pant leg yesterday,
makes all the difference
in the world.
You've taken the stairs
every day.
Do I need a restraining order?
You slack on your rehab,
the muscle will weaken,
and your leg will hurt again.
Looks like the ketamine
treatment might not stick.
Or maybe we've made him depressed
because we're lying to him,
telling him
he got that case wrong.
We didn't hurt him.
The pain isn't...
He gets depressed,
he stops exercising.
He stops exercising,
the muscle atrophies.
The muscle atrophies,
the pain returns.
Maybe he stopped exercising because the
giant hole in his leg actually hurts.
The ketamine
could work perfectly,
and he would still be back on his cane,
popping Vicodin again.
You can't tell him.
He got lucky. There was no medical...
He was right.
We tell him he was right,
and we're feeding his addiction.
Without Vicodin,
he's only got one to focus on.
Well, he's not gonna
OD on puzzles.
No, it's not gonna hurt him,
but he could just as easily
have killed that patient.
We have a tiny window of time here where
House may be healthy enough to change,
and based on that limp,
the window's closing fast.
Kid is a product
of an in vitro fertilization pregnancy,
had all his vaccinations,
fractured his right ulna at age three,
chicken pox at age five...
He ever get his feelings hurt?
I'll need to know that, too.
You are "0" for one since you came back.
We just wanna make sure that...
Rectal bleeding plus
alien-abduction fantasies.
Most likely sexual abuse.
Penetration causes the bleed.
Trauma causes the fantasy.
ER ran a rape kit, found no evidence
of tearing, semen or pubic hairs.
I think we should
talk to the kid.
Why? In case
he's telling the truth?
You're a believer, aren't you?
Well, I'm just not
arrogant enough to think
that of the 50 billion galaxies,
100 billion stars per galaxy
and 10 million billion planets
in the universe,
that we're the only ones
with life.
No, but I'm guessing we're the only ones
who like shoving things
through our back doors.
There is new research indicating a link
between neurological problems
and bleeding disorders.
Perfect, especially
if there were neurological problems.
What part of hallucinating
an alien abduction isn't neurological?
It wasn't a hallucination.
What? You think the kid...
He's having nightmares.
Nightmares aren't a symptom of anything
other than wanting to sleep with Mommy,
which just leaves us
with one symptom, the bloody tuchus,
which can easily explained
by a GI problem or bleeding disorder.
Check his coags with a PT,
PTT and bleeding time,
and prep him for endoscopies
from above and below.
I'm gonna make
a tiny nick in your forearm, okay?
Then I'm gonna time how long
it takes for you to stop bleeding.
Now, this is gonna sting a little,
so you might wanna look the other way.
Are those windows locked?
Those windows don't even open.
They're just here to let sunshine in.
Good, 'cause they know
I'm here.
Clancy, don't bother
the doctor with this stuff.
No, it's okay.
How do they know you're here?
They put a chip in my neck
so they can keep track of me.
I can feel it back there.
Clancy, you know
there is nothing back there.
There is.
Let me see. Lean forwards.
And they have this other thing, and they
put it in between these two ribs,
always on this side,
and then they move it around my insides.
It hurts.
You know what, Clancy?
I think I might have
found the chip back there,
and I think I might be able
to get it out.
- Really?
- Mmm-hmm.
Okay, lean forwards.
Now hold very still, okay?
Got it.
I'm seven, not three.
All you did was pinch my neck.
Sorry.
His alien-abduction story,
the level of detail is...
Well, I don't know
where he gets it from.
The parents say he doesn't watch sci-fi.
He doesn't read comic books...
Great. You do any
of that medical stuff we talked about?
Upper and lower endoscopies
were clean.
So it's a simple
bleeding disorder.
No, blood tests are all normal,
and he clotted in six minutes.
So it's a simple bleeding disorder,
and you screwed up the test.
I didn't screw up the test.
So it's a UFO.
Unidentified Flowing Orifice.
Either you screwed up the test, or
I screwed up my analysis of this case.
If you screwed up,
I don't have to cry myself to sleep.
It's a simple bleeding disorder.
Foreman, redo the test.
How could I screw up
a simple bleeding-time test?
Maybe you were abducted,
lost time.
Kid's got a bleeding disorder.
Sure?
I had to stop the bleeding
myself after 25 minutes.
So you're saying
Chase did screw up.
Or Foreman screwed up.
Big hand points to minutes.
Maybe you got it mixed up.
Oh, snap.
Foreman's playing the dozens.
You're at a huge cultural
disadvantage here, Chase.
Take a couple of minutes
to think of a witty retort.
So we have contradicting
bleeding-time tests.
If we run labs
to check his clotting factors,
we can confirm which one's right.
Yeah, testing. Nice idea.
Way better than trying
to guess which doctor's incompetent.
Looks better
in the paperwork, too.
Hey, Foreman, your mama's so fat,
when her beeper goes off,
people think she's backing up.
Where's Clancy?
He's asleep. He's...
House, Clancy's gone missing.
Oh, no! You take Alpha Centauri,
Foreman can look on Tatooine,
and Cameron can set up
an intergalactic checkpoint.
Let's pray he hasn't gone
into hyperdrive. We'll never catch him.
Clancy?
I had to go where there are no windows
so I could get the chip out.
God.
I can feel it.
I just can't grab it.
Clancy, stop. There is no chip.
We're gonna clean you up,
and we're gonna go back to your room.
You can't do things like this.
Your parents...
Results came back.
The lab cannot identify the metal.
Said it might not
even be terrestrial.
Really?
No, you idiot, it's titanium,
like from a surgical pin,
like the kind the kid had inserted
into his broken arm four years ago.
Nice medical history.
That pin was removed
six months...
So a little piece broke off
during removal.
Titanium is used to build nuclear subs.
Pieces don't just break off.
Tell that to the guys
on the Kursk.
And how exactly did it get from his arm
to the back of his neck?
Body attacks
any foreign object.
Inflammatory reaction could erode it
into a vein. Fragment gets a free ride.
To his lungs maybe,
not his neck.
Yeah, an alien chip
makes more sense.
The real mystery is
that you didn't actually screw up.
You okay?
Fine. Tripped.
Kid carved a hole
in the back of his neck.
Apparently didn't bleed
to death. Now that's weird.
He clotted on his own?
Sure did.
So first there was no bleeding disorder.
Then there was. Now there's not again.
Which is impossible.
Or Foreman screwed up.
Two out of three tests
agree with my findings.
Lucky for us,
the fourth test will be the charm.
So you're just gonna
keep cutting him? Until what?
This test is different.
We'll draw some blood, and see if
any clotting factors are low or missing.
- But why haven't the other tests...
- We've got three results.
They haven't been consistent.
One of them must be wrong.
Or two of them.
Is it possible the problem isn't
his blood? It's just psychological?
I mean,
he almost killed himself.
He wasn't trying
to hurt himself.
No, he was just looking
for an alien tracking device.
I have time for one more.
Can't blame you
for spending extra time down here.
I heard the Artist
Formerly Known as Gimp is back upstairs.
Oh, Dr. Cuddy wants that one.
She's busy. I'll take it.
Oh, my God! You're...
You're okay!
Have we met?
I was one of your doctors.
You were in a vegetative state
when you left here last week.
Addison's disease.
All I needed was cortisol,
and my brain turned on like a switch.
This is amazing!
Surprised you didn't know.
How would I know?
Not quite my old self yet.
Baby steps,
the doctors tell me. Now...
With rehab, you'll do great.
What hospital did you go to?
- How would I...
- I wanna have sex with my wife,
and I was hoping that
maybe you could...
Viagra? You're here for Viagra?
A bucketful would be nice.
Dr. Cuddy.
Hi.
It's completely unethical.
He was reckless with a patient.
- He was right.
- But he didn't know that.
He needs at least
some glimmer of humility.
Why does he need that?
Because other people have that? Why does
he need to be like other people?
He needs to be less reckless.
Well, you did it.
He's dismissing symptoms, looking
for easy solutions. He's in pain.
- How much pain?
- Why?
You know this is
affecting him, don't you?
Telling him that he got his last case
right won't do anything to help him.
- It'll make him less depressed.
- Which might not help his leg.
But you don't know.
Just let me run a PET scan
on his parietal thalamic area
to see if it's sensing pain.
If it is, the ketamine
isn't working anymore,
and he's headed for a huge crash.
If it's not, the leg pain is my fault,
and I will tell him the truth.
Too tight?
My parents think I'm crazy.
No, they don't.
They're just worried
about you. That's all.
I'm not weird.
It's just that weird things
keep happening to me.
Slight pinch.
If you make me better, do you think
the aliens will leave me alone?
I don't think they're gonna be
bothering you for much longer.
Are you lying again?
No.
We figure this out,
everything's gonna be okay.
Still with us?
Let's go.
Pulmonary edema,
stage-two hypertensive crisis.
What is happening?
Wait outside.
Get him oxygen, and start him
on an IV drip of sodium nitroprusside.
Get them outside!
He's in ICU, systolic is
hovering around 170.
I left instructions to lower it slowly
so we don't risk
hypoperfusing his organs.
Trade-off being that leaving his
blood pressure that high risks stroke,
MI and blindness.
I'm open to suggestions.
Solve the case. Kidneys could explain...
Kidneys are clean.
Tell me
he's a mutant-human hybrid.
It is a bleeding disorder.
Clancy tested positive
for Von Willebrand's.
I didn't screw up.
How could he clot on his own
two out of three times?
Maybe he cheated.
Right. Kids always cheat
on their bleeding-time tests.
She was being metaphorical.
She's trying to sound like me.
I have no idea what you meant, but
I could smell what The Rock was cooking.
I meant, he's clotting right now,
and he's in hypertensive crisis.
Maybe the two are related.
What if he was hypertensive
the other two times that he clotted?
Hypertensive crisis
can activate clotting factors.
Even someone low on Von Willebrand's
could theoretically clot.
And the first time Clancy clotted,
he was all worked up
recounting his alien abduction.
He could've easily been hypertensive.
I get worked up when I cut microchip
tracking implants out of my neck.
Sounds like a cheat to me.
Yeah, we get it.
Okay, what's the differential
for a seven-year-old boy
suffering multiple
hypertensive crises?
We think the problem is
in your son's heart.
We need to do a procedure
called a transesophageal echo.
Okay, and that will
fix his heart?
That will tell us where the problem
is, hopefully. Then we can fix him.
Listen, this isn't
really part of my job,
but he's worried that
you think he's crazy.
Well, isn't he?
There are still plenty of other
explanations for what's going on.
It's important he knows
you believe in him, even if you don't.
It's clean.
His heart isn't the problem.
Why don't I have a high-def
in my office? I'm a department head.
- There are no structural defects.
- Valves are intact.
Tissue characterization is impossible
when the pixels are the size of Legos.
See, this is what
I'm talking about.
Foreman, you gotta
steal this thing for me.
Let me ring up
one of the homies.
The clearer the image, the clearer it is
that there are no masses,
no clots, no tears.
The problem's gotta be
somewhere else.
We're gonna need a bigger boat.
You're wrong, House.
Think he'll make us break into the IMAX
before he admits it?
- There.
- Where?
Right there.
Left side, no movement.
Well, don't freeze it.
Something's not moving.
How do you see something not move
if nothing's moving?
I need a laser pointer.
- We don't have a laser pointer.
- Well, why not?
Who's gonna take us seriously
if we don't have a laser pointer?
Right here.
A few thousand myocytes
not beating with the rest.
So you've found an arrhythmia?
That's not an arrhythmia.
That's a no-rhythmia.
Myocytes contract.
These aren't moving at all.
Go get me those myocytes.
I wanna talk to them in my office.
How's the kid doing?
Heart nearly exploded.
Still beating, though.
Most of it, anyway.
Why do they bother
putting age restrictions on these things
when all you have to do
is click, "Yes, I am 18?"
Even a 17-year-old
can figure that out.
What's going on with the leg?
First, tell me
what's going on with the boobs.
- If you're feeling pain...
- They're firmer.
It's called an underwire.
I wanna get a PET scan
of your brain.
I think it's hormones.
As long as there's
no increased activity in the thalamus...
Looks to me like those puppies
are going into the dairy business.
Then the pain can be good.
It could be muscle regenerating.
After you workout, you get sore.
Pain doesn't mean the ketamine failed.
Guess I should be saying, "Mazel tov."
Who gets to pass out the cigars?
I'm not pregnant.
I need to get a PET scan of your brain.
- Boy or girl? You got a name?
- I'm not pregnant.
- My leg doesn't hurt.
- You're in denial.
No, I'm not!
Oh, you got me.
If I thought that my leg
was deteriorating,
don't you think
I'd want to take steps to prevent that?
Okay.
Gotta go.
Here's Clancy's DNA.
And here's the DNA from that piece
of his heart we just biopsied.
That is impossible.
Run it again.
We already did
and once more after that.
The genes from Clancy's
myocytes don't match the genes
from the rest of his body.
Alien DNA.
Anybody watch any X-Files
that inspired an explanation?
There are ways DNA can become mutated.
Extreme UV radiation.
That much sun, he'd be dying with
a healthy bronze glow.
Nitrous acid
or ethidium-bromide exposure.
First, Daddy was a rapist.
Now he's a chemist.
Various species of fungus
have been proven mutagenic.
Not unless the kid's
been eating barrels of celery
or living in Indonesia or both.
- Is your leg hurting?
- Is that question helping?
- You're leaning.
- You're sitting.
- You're evading.
- My head's hurting.
Please, someone, give me a plausible,
terrestrial explanation
for this kid's alien DNA.
We could search his home for toxins,
fungals and radiation.
Who cares what caused it?
A kid comes in with strep,
we don't conduct a search to see which
classmate he got it from. We cure it.
We know he's got the stuff inside him.
Let's get a scalpel and cut it out.
Where do we cut?
Chances are, it's not just in his heart.
Well, we got lucky with the heart.
Myocytes contract.
We could see that
these weren't working.
I don't know how the hell
we're gonna find it anywhere else.
What if we take the heart cells
with the bad DNA, and we tag them?
Can you phrase that
in the form of a metaphor?
It's the same way
we search for cancer.
The bad DNA creates a unique protein
on the surface of the affected cells.
We create an antibody
that recognizes only that protein,
we flush it throughout his system,
and the similar cells light up
like light bulbs.
Okay, let's do that.
You have to tell him.
He said he wasn't in any pain.
- He's lying.
- Of course he's lying.
We need another plan.
Don't talk about it that way.
What way?
"Plan."
It sounds like we're conspiring
against him.
- I'm gonna tell him.
- No, you're not.
Then come up with a cunning plan
and fast.
She's not nearly as delightful
as she thinks she is.
What's this machine do?
Makes a lot of noise,
and it's gonna help us figure out
what's wrong with you.
You think House
has lost a step?
He's fine.
There. Clump of affected cells
in the bone marrow of the femur.
Explains the
intermittent-bleeding disorder.
'Cause I don't need to subject myself
to House's torture if there's no upside.
I'm telling you, he's fine.
We missed some
affected cells in his heart.
Explains the continuing
hypertensive issues.
You said the last case
really threw him, and now suddenly...
I was wrong.
So you changed your mind. Why?
His brilliant ideas
on this case have all been yours.
There's the reason for him
needing glasses.
Apparently, it's a symptom.
It means the condition predates...
You don't change your mind
without a reason. Now, what do you know?
House didn't blow
the last case.
Cuddy cured the guy
using House's idea.
Cuddy and Wilson
are trying to teach him some humility.
Scan is complete. Three hot spots,
but nothing in his brain.
House's original theory was right.
It is not neurological.
Is he going to be able to walk?
His leg should be
functional after some rehab.
"Functional"?
What does that mean?
He'll be able to walk,
but not run? He'll have a limp?
If everything goes well,
he'll walk. He'll run.
He'll probably be
even stronger than he is now.
When we close him up,
we'll move over to his other leg,
snake a catheter up through
the femoral artery and into his heart.
Once the affected areas are removed,
is normal tissue
ill step back in, do its job.
He should have no more problems
with his blood pressure.
After confirming those areas are clear,
we'll start the final procedure.
We're gonna insert
a needle through the pupil
and get rid of the
abnormal cells in the retina.
Close your right eye.
Can you see my face?
Yeah, it's clear.
You can throw away your glasses.
We got it all.
Get some sleep.
You're going home tomorrow.
Thank you.
Do you wanna go for a run?
What do you want?
I want you to run.
When did you become an enabler?
I'm enabling you to exercise.
Vicodin blocks the pain,
you get through your rehab,
muscle strength increases,
and pain decreases.
I'd rather not become dependent
on pain pills to get through my day.
You're just like
any other patient,
running away from knowledge
that won't make you happy.
I'm as happy as a pig in poop.
You're scared
the ketamine treatment's wearing off,
that it was just
a torturous window to the good life.
What part of "poop"
didn't you understand?
How can you be so sure
it isn't just a sore muscle?
It's my leg.
We've known each other a long time.
You're not always right, House.
You've proven that lately.
What's happening to him?
- He's seizing. I need clonazepam.
- I thought you got it all.
Yeah, yell at me. That'll fix your kid.
Obviously, we missed some foreign
tissue. There's something still in him.
The hallucinations and seizures
indicate problems in the temporal lobe.
Sorry, House, it is neurological.
Looks like you're wrong again.
We didn't miss anything.
Brain scan was completely clean.
Our tag must not have penetrated
the blood-brain barrier.
Don't use an IV this time.
Get it right into the brain.
No cells are lighting up. His brain
is clean. It is not neurological.
His symptoms are neurological.
His condition has to be neurological.
His scan was clean twice.
It's not there.
What if it is there,
but didn't show up on the scan?
What if the tag
just doesn't work in his brain?
Brain cells are structurally different,
express a different protein.
So how do we find it?
Where are we going?
I am going to think.
Send the kid home.
What do you mean?
Make sure his blood pressure's
stabilized, and send him home.
What, like nothing ever happened?
We cured his bleeding disorder,
removed all the damaged cells
we could find.
We don't know that we fixed anything.
It's only been a day.
Maybe these symptoms come and go
like the blood disorder.
It's more probable that his
remaining symptoms are
just a nightmare.
He had a convulsion.
May be epilepsy.
May be psychological. May be nothing.
If the kid gets sick again,
it'll give us another clue.
We can start searching again.
If he doesn't, doesn't matter.
Send him home.
House.
You're just giving up
on this kid?
You gotta know when to stop.
You don't stop. You never stop.
You just keep on going until you
come up with something so insane
that it's usually right.
Except on my last case.
Don't be pathetic.
Just forget the last case.
This kid obviously
has something wrong with him.
When did you develop
such strong opinions about my patients?
Last week, you were convinced
my patient wasn't sick.
Now you're convinced
this one is.
This one is a young boy.
His parents are desperate.
Just get together with your team,
spend a few extra hours...
Well, I guess we could amputate his left
leg. That's where we found most of it.
Maybe we should just
remove his affected eye completely.
If you have reason
to believe that that might help...
I'm not gonna start
lopping off body parts,
but it's interesting
that you give me the green light.
I just want you
to do something.
You've been overly supportive
this entire week.
Either you're hormonal,
or you're guilt-ridden,
and it's too early in the pregnancy
for this to be hormonal.
- I'm not pregnant.
- Then what did you do wrong?
He had Addison's.
Your last patient. You were right.
I gave him one shot of cortisol
and he woke up like Rip van Winkle.
Oh, your mommy is in such trouble.
She's such a liar.
That's why you don't have a daddy.
That's why she had to...
How does one person
end up with two different sets of DNA?
We've been through this.
Our assumptions are faulty.
We've confirmed two different sets
of DNA. We re-ran the sequence.
I didn't say the lab work was faulty.
I said our assumptions were faulty.
We assumed he's a person.
Of course. The aliens didn't
just visit him. They replaced him.
You're being silly. What if he's
not a person? What if he's two persons?
- I'm not getting the metaphor.
- No metaphor.
Chase, you said the mom
used in vitro fertilization, right?
Yeah, they had trouble conceiving.
Kid was right all along.
He was implanted with something,
back when he was young.
I mean really young,
like 12-cells young.
In vitro increases
the likelihood of twinning.
But he doesn't have a twin.
Not walking around.
But in vitro fertilization
costs around 25 grand a pop,
so doctors implant two to six embryos
to make sure you get your money's worth.
Problem is, there's not always
enough bedrooms for all the kiddies.
Two brothers get stuck sharing.
There's no bunk beds,
so they cuddle up to keep warm,
and they never untangle.
He's two people in one.
It's called chimerism.
Unfortunately, his brother's
like a bad doubles partner.
The guy just takes up space,
gets in the way.
Clancy's body thinks that
he's gonna put away the easy winners.
His brother just keeps
swatting balls into the net.
We gotta get him off the court.
So does that mean that you can find
the bad cells in his brain or not?
Sure, abandon the metaphor. Fine.
Clancy thinks differently
than his brother because he thinks.
If we induce an alien abduction...
Wait. What the hell
are you talking about?
The foreign DNA has got to
be in a portion of your son's brain
that makes him believe
that he's being abducted.
If we stimulate those neurons
with an electric probe,
we can trick your son's brain
into hallucinating.
Your son's neurons will light up,
and his brother's cells will stay dark.
Those are the ones we cut out.
You're talking about
brain surgery.
I'm talking about really cool brain
surgery. One of your sons will die,
but the taller one
won't be so annoying anymore.
So I have a twin?
Not really. What's on the card?
A light bulb.
Start us out at 10.
I'm not doing that.
That was all me, kid. Sorry.
You're in motor function.
Try two centimeters back.
He lives inside me?
Sort of.
That tickles.
Stop tickling my feet.
You're in sensory.
You're getting closer.
What do you see on this one?
Moon and stars.
So I am kind of weird?
We're all kind of weird.
No!
- Clancy?
- We got something.
- What do you see?
- The light.
Here they come, I think.
Brain waves indicate a mild
hallucination. Neurons are lighting up.
- Any dark spots?
- Area's too fuzzy.
Hallucination isn't strong enough.
Turn up the juice.
His blood pressure's already
160 over 110. Any higher...
Riding the short bus is better
than not breathing. Take us to 100.
Area's still too fuzzy
to make any kind of distinction.
- Crank it up higher.
- You've already exceeded
the preset maximum.
Next step's brain damage.
They're gonna get you.
They're coming through the walls.
They're gonna take you, torture you.
You'll never see your parents again.
Clancy? Can you hear me?
Clancy?
You got them.
Yep.
We got them all.
Close him up.
Everything's gonna be normal again.
You believe what
Cuddy tried to pull?
What now?
She lied to me.
She cured my patient with my diagnosis,
then lied to me about it.
That doesn't sound like her.
You're right.
Does sound like you, though.
What exactly did Cuddy tell you?
Nothing that your body language
isn't telling me right now.
So what was the plan?
I'd feel so humbled by missing a case
that I'd reevaluate my entire life,
question the nature of truth
and goodness and become Cameron?
Something like that.
More that if we told you the truth,
that you solved a case
based on absolutely no medical proof,
you'd think you were God.
And I was worried
your wings would melt.
God doesn't limp.