Previously on From...
[Sara] I hear their voices.
They said it was
the only way to go home.
Sara, just tell me
what you did.
[Sara]
I left the door open.
[Weeping]
Are you living in town
or Colony House?
-Town.
-Julie.
Colony House.
Why are you doing this?
[Fatima] What's wrong?
I think maybe
I-I made a mistake.
[Fatima] Julie, there are
no mistakes, just choices,
and you chose what was right
for you, and that matters.
Come on,
try it out!
[Kenny] Every single one
of these pins
is a different resident
who drove in
from a different location.
That is fucking impossible.
I don't just sit around,
accepting the world as it is!
-[Static hisses on radio]
-Someone is doing this,
and I'm not gonna rest
until I figure out how!
[Father] I wish you had
the luxury of grief,
but you don't, Boyd.
These people need you.
You need to be the one
to lead these people home.
'Cause if you don't?
She died for nothing.
What are you doing here?
You promised you'd stay home.
If I didn't show up,
they would have wondered why.
-It'll be okay.
-Sara...
I promise.
Do you wanna help me bring
over the rest of the food?
Yeah!
[Jim]
I just feel so... broken.
We're gonna figure it
out together.
Don't worry.
Whatcha got there?
Sweet potatoes.
Ooh!
Nice family.
[Gasping breaths]
[Ethan] Sara!
[Boyd] Hey.
Oh! Oh, no, no, no.
Okay, grab her,
grab her arm, grab her arm!
Hold on, hold on!
[Goats bleating]
Hey, Alma. Come on.
There you go, Alma,
a fresh batch just for you.
Hey!
Make sure you share this time.
Nathan! Nathan!
It's your sister!
Something happened at the diner.
They're taking her
to the clinic.
I really am feeling much better.
I still think you should spend
the night for observation, okay?
Do I have to?
It's just,
with things like this,
it's best not to
take any chances, you know?
I can have someone
go get Nathan.
He can stay with you.
No. He worries.
If he comes by,
could you...
just tell him I'm sleeping.
Yeah, no problem.
[Door opening, closing]
I'll, uh...
I'll be right back, okay?
Hey. How's she doing?
I mean, fine,
given the circumstances.
Has this happened before?
Well, I mean,
not according to Sara.
And unless there's an MRI
machine tucked around somewhere,
there's no way to really
know what's going on.
-Yeah.
-I'm, uh...
I'm gonna keep her overnight
and see if anything changes.
Okay. You sure you're ready
for that?
Look, I don't know
how that door got open,
but I'm not gonna
let those things
take this place
away from me.
They've already taken
too much already.
Yeah. They sure have.
Hey, can I ask
you a question?
These seizures - first,
the Matthews kid, now Sara.
You think it's possible
to have a physical
reaction to this place?
Maybe something you
might normally diagnose
as one thing on the outside,
but here it's...
Look, Boyd, if you asked me
this six months ago,
I would have said anything that
we've seen here was impossible.
But the truth is, I...
Okay, how long has
this been going on for?
Long enough that it's got me
asking stupid questions.
-Boyd...
-I'm fine.
Come by tomorrow.
I want to take a look at it.
No need.
I already know what it is.
Nathan's here.
[Sighing]
She doesn't want to see him.
Yeah, I don't... I don't know.
Um, okay.
Go take care of your patient.
I got this, okay?
And I'm good.
Whoa, whoa, whoa! Whoa!
Is she okay?
She's fine.
She's sleeping.
I wanna see her.
And you will, tomorrow.
Kristi's gonna sit
with her tonight
and make sure
everything is okay.
No, no. I-I need
to see her now, please.
You will. Hey, hey.
Is there anything else going on
that we should know about?
Anything that might help Kristi
figure out what's wrong?
No. I'm just worried,
that's all.
She's my little sister.
Right. Look,
this is Kristi's first
night back since... right?
We don't want
to be going in there
and making tonight more
stressful than it already is.
Sara's in good hands.
Okay?
Go home.
Get some sleep.
You'll see her in the morning.
Yeah.
Okay?
Is Sara gonna be okay?
Well, yeah,
she's down at the clinic.
They're gonna take
good care of her. Don't worry.
You remember Kristi?
The nice lady
who took care of your leg?
She's gonna patch up Sara
the same way she patched you up.
In the meantime,
we are gonna
play a little game.
For you.
Well, we said we're gonna
figure it out, right?
Let's figure it out.
Follow me.
[Exhales]
We're gonna do some
problem-solving,
and the way
you problem solve
is by asking questions.
You ask every question
that might apply,
no matter how crazy,
no matter how unlikely.
You put it up on a board,
you get it out in front of you
so that you can identify
everything you know
and everything you don't.
It'll be like telling
a story.
Right, buddy?
Question number one.
[Ethan] Dad!
What? You never wanted
to write on a wall?
There.
That's where we begin.
♪
["Que Sera, Sera [Whatever Will
Be, Will be]" plays]
♪
♪ When I was
just a little boy♪
♪ I asked my father♪
♪ "What will I be?"♪
♪ "Will I be handsome?"♪
♪ "Will I be rich?"♪
♪ Here's what he said to me♪
♪ "Que sera, sera"♪
♪ "Whatever will be, will be"♪
♪ "The future's
Not ours to see"♪
♪ "Que sera, sera"♪
♪ "What will be, will be"♪
♪ Now
I have children of my own♪
♪ They ask their father♪
♪ "What will I be?♪
"Will I be pretty?"♪
♪ "Will I be rich?"♪
♪ I tell them tenderly♪
♪ "Que sera, sera"♪
♪ "Whatever will be, will be"♪
♪ "The future's
Not ours to see"♪
♪ "Que sera, sera"♪
♪ "What will be, will be"♪
[Crickets chirping]
[Gasping breaths]
Hey.
I can't sleep.
Uh, yeah, me neither.
I thought you'd like some tea?
Do you want some?
Sure.
You and Kenny make
a really cute couple.
Oh, uh, no,
we're just...
We're just friends.
Why?
He's really sweet,
and he loves you.
It's complicated.
How?
Well, 'cause I...
[Sighing]
...have somebody at home.
At least I think she's...
still... waiting.
What's her name?
Mariel.
-Were you married?
-Engaged.
I wonder sometimes,
actually all the time, uh,
what it must be like for her,
thinking I, uh, abandoned her.
Um, how about you?
Do you have
anybody back at home?
No.
I... I was with someone,
but he wasn't...
It's better that
he's not around anymore.
It's just me and Nathan now.
He's all
I've got in the world.
Before we got
stuck here, I, um...
Things weren't
really very good for me.
Nathan was
the one who saved me.
Can I ask you something?
Yeah. Sure.
If there was
something you could do,
something that would
let you see Mariel again...
something that would let
everyone here go home,
even if it was something bad,
would you do it?
Wait,
what are you talking about?
I wonder sometimes...
about this place,
what it means...
why we're here.
If someone came up to you
right now and said,
"Do this one bad thing
and everyone
gets to go home,"
would you do it?
Well, we're...
we're speaking
hypothetically, right?
Yeah.
Okay.
Of course.
[Chuckles]
Okay.
Uh...
I mean...
Yeah, I'd, um...
I'd do anything
to see her again and...
And hey, I mean,
if that meant everybody else
got to go home too,
then, I think
that's a lot of good
for one bad thing.
Yeah.
Hmm.
[Exhales]
Tell me you
figured it out.
Oh, I-I did.
And the answer is 12.
[Chuckles]
Okay.
All right,
let's go over this again.
Everyone enters from different
parts of the country,
on different roads,
in different places,
and they all, presumably,
see the same tree,
same crows.
Jim, Jim...
everyone here has asked the same
question over and over again.
How does writing
them on the wall
going to make
any difference?
Because...
There are plenty of things in
the world that don't make sense.
Yeah.
Something here
is missing.
We just can't see it yet.
But we will.
Well, there's a question
we haven't asked.
No.
Why not?
Because it's crazy.
[Sighing]
I don't want
to know the answer.
You sure you're not hungry?
I was gonna make some oatmeal.
I'm not really hungry.
Thank you
for last night, though.
It's been a long time
since I've had a girls' night.
Yeah, uh, me too.
I mean, hey, no need to wait
for a medical emergency
if you ever wanna
do it again.
Oh, your brother's back.
Uh, he's very persistent.
Yeah, he is.
Are you... are you
sure you're okay?
Yeah, yeah, it's fine.
He just... he cares a lot.
Yeah.
I'll see you later.
You're up bright
and early.
Sara, we need
to talk.
About what?
I'm so sorry I worried you.
I didn't mean to.
It's fine. I just need
to know what happened.
I was just...
I was standing
in the diner one minute
and the next,
I was on the floor.
I don't really remember
much other than that.
Why are you suddenly acting
like everything's okay?
I need to get
to the diner.
Mrs. Liu is
gonna be worried.
Sara!
I'm okay, I promise.
I love you so much.
Knock, knock.
You awake in there?
Yeah, come on in.
Whatcha doing?
I'm making a list.
Of?
All the people
that are probably
wondering where
we are right now.
Oh.
I mean, it's gotta be
worse for them, right?
Not knowing.
Just...
I made one too.
Pretty sure everybody here
did at one time or another.
Who's on yours?
My grandparents
and my friends.
Boyfriend?
No.
Girlfriend?
No, there's
nobody like that.
I guess that's a good thing
though, right?
Just one less person sitting
around losing their minds,
wondering where you are.
[Exhales] Okay.
That's enough of that.
We need some fun, stat.
Get dressed and meet me
downstairs in five?
Why?
You'll see.
[Sighs]
[Metallic clanking]
Hey.
No more work
this morning.
She's, uh,
making the list.
I think it's time we
show her the Brundles.
Just a fucking idiot.
That's special relativity.
Uh... Klein.
Hardy's.
Klein. Hardy's.
Einstein-Podolsky-Rosen.
[Trudy] Where are you
going with that?
Sorry?
Is that a radio?
Uh... yeah.
Sort of.
Why are you carrying it around?
[Sighing]
Because it helps me think.
I'm sorry, I...
You're even cuter
when you're awake.
Excuse me?
I watched you when
you were sleeping.
I'm Trudy.
Okay.
Too bad you chose the town.
I would've rode you
like an alabaster dragon.
Bye!
[Door opening]
Morning, Sheriff.
I stopped by the diner, let my
mom know that Sara was okay,
and she made those
bread things that you like,
so I picked up
a couple of those.
Uh, Sheriff?
I'm gonna need you to
hold down the fort for a bit.
Is everything okay?
Everything's fine.
I'm gonna visit my wife.
It's been a while.
Okay?
Yeah, sure.
[Door opening, closing]
[Jade] What the hell?
You guys built a bar
in this fucking place?
Yeah.
You end up in a place like this,
you ask yourself,
what do the people need?
Turns out it's not a fucking gas
station, so I figured...
[Chattering]
Hey, you okay?
What?
Are... you... okay?
No, no, I'm not... okay.
Are you okay?
Great.
Here, drink this.
It'll help you feel better.
What the fuck?
How are you...
Why are you all
just sitting here?
[Gags]
Holy fuck!
What is this shit?
Just consider it your
poor man's potato vodka.
[Groans]
You're one of the guys
from the two cars, huh?
[Groans]
Your, uh, friend, uh...
friend got, uh...
Yeah. Yeah.
Look, if it's
any consolation, it...
It gets easier, man,
it really does.
[Scoffs]
Gets easier,
that's rich.
That is fucking rich.
You know, you guys are...
you're like rats in a maze,
sitting there, contentedly...
nibbling on your cheese.
This is a paradox.
That's the problem.
[Breathes deeply]
The immediate question is,
how do we get home, right?
How do we get out?
How do we get out of here?
'Cause unless we
know where "here" is,
we can't get outta here.
It's like... it's like... this,
it's like, uh,
hitting a bull's-eye with
your eyes closed, right?
You're just throwing 'em blind!
You don't even fucking know
where the fucking target is!
Maybe it's over here!
I don't know!
Maybe it just, like,
went that way!
-Whoa, whoa, whoa! Come on!
-[Jade] Throwing it!
Settle down.
Eventually, you just
get tired, you give up.
You accept that
you can't just get out,
'cause you have
no fucking idea
where you're
trying to get out of.
So, you sit around drinking
your acidic potato piss water
that you call vodka.
Yeah.
So, let me guess,
you're gonna be the guy
who figures it all out.
You're goddamn right I am.
People like me,
we design the maze,
we place the cheese.
I don't know what
you did before you got here,
but I just sold a company
for an obscene amount of money
based on a quantum
computing algorithm
with the potential to...
[Sighs]
I'm not supposed to be here.
I'm supposed to be
celebrating right now at...
Look, the point is
we can't get out of here
unless we know where "here" is.
Right? To solve the paradox, you
gotta understand the paradox.
You gotta identify it.
You gotta frame it.
-Schrodinger's cat.
-What?
Schrodinger's cat,
that... that's the paradox.
You put the cat in the box
and you close the box.
As long as you never
open it again...
The cat is theoretically alive
and dead at the same time.
I know what
Schrodinger's cat is.
Okay, so,
we're the cat.
This place here
is the box, right?
So, all those people
we left behind back home?
Well, they're all
sitting around wondering
if we're alive or dead.
So, to them, we're both
things at the same time.
I taught
Intro to Philosophy at USC.
Hmm.
Look, uh, I don't know
a fuckin' thing about computers,
I'll be the first
to admit that.
But that, uh...
that radio you brought in,
well, if you're
so goddamn smart,
why don't you figure out how
to get it broadcasting, huh?
And I'll tell you what,
if the cat
turns on the radio,
you can be goddamn sure that
the people outside the box
are at least gonna
know it's still alive.
Huh.
♪
Are you sure
this doesn't hurt?
It's just a little sore.
Hm.
What's wrong?
Nothing.
It's...
[Sighing] It's just...
It's just healing
so fast.
Is that bad?
No. No.
Um, actually,
it's very good.
I think this place is special.
I know it tries
to hurt people,
but maybe it tries
to help people too.
Maybe that can be one of
the questions on the wall.
What would that be?
Is there anyone
trying to help?
[Chuckles]
[Kissing noise]
That's a great question.
[Jim] Ethan!
You have a visitor!
Oh.
Let's see who that is.
[Ethan] Sara!
How's my
favorite customer?
We drew on the walls.
I see that.
We never draw on
the walls at home.
[Chuckles]
How are you feeling?
Much better, thank you.
Good. Uh, did Kristi
figure out what happened?
Not yet. It's...
It's just one of
those things, I guess.
[Tabitha] Yeah.
[Ethan] There's
a playground outside.
Wanna see?
Hey, honey, Sara just
came out of the hospital.
Sure.
Okay.
Yeah.
[Stammers]
It's okay, really. Yeah.
-Come on!
-Be careful.
This one's my favorite.
♪
Hello?
Father Khatri?
♪
[Laughing]
[Ellis]
Welcome to the Brundles!
[Laughing]
Whoo!
[Julie] Oh, God!
Oh!
[Chuckling]
[Sighing contentedly]
See?
If you close your eyes
and just listen,
it's almost like being
anywhere else in the world.
How do you do that?
Do what?
How do you act
like this place doesn't...
You're always so positive.
I guess it all just depends on
how you choose to look at it.
What do you mean?
Well, I didn't come to
the U.S. until I was 11.
I grew up in
a small village in Iran
with my parents
and two older brothers.
My father, he was
a very outspoken cleric,
which wasn't always the most
popular thing to be at the time.
One day, it was my birthday.
Actually, we were getting
ready to go see my uncle.
These men showed up.
They were angry, shouting.
I remember my mother
told me to hide.
But I was so confused
because we were just laughing.
My father had told
this story about...
He was a really
good storyteller.
I think that's what made him
such an effective preacher.
Anyway, I could tell
my mother was afraid.
My brothers had run to the door
and now they were shouting too,
and my mother just kept
saying "Hide, hide."
But I just stood there,
I couldn't move,
because it was all so strange.
I mean, we were just laughing
so hard, you know?
It was gonna be
the best birthday ever.
The sun was so bright
coming in through the door
that my father
became a silhouette
when they dragged him outside.
And then, there was this pop,
like a firecracker,
and the silhouette fell down.
Oh, my God.
The point is,
there are always going to
be monsters in the world.
It doesn't matter
where you are.
But I promised myself
I would never let them
scare the life out of me.
-Oh, hey, hi.
-Hi!
Ah, yeah, you just
look too dry. Come here!
Oh, no, no, no!
No, no, no, no!
[Ellis] Come on. Come on.
Come on. Yup, we're goin'!
We're goin'! Hey!
[Fatima]
Julie, come on!
Come on!
[Metal squeaking]
That's the most like himself
I've seen Ethan
since the accident.
[Metal squeaking]
How long have you lived here?
Just a few months.
Mom and Dad are trying to
figure out where we are
so we can all go home.
That's what
the Cromenockle would do.
What's a Cromenockle?
[Tabitha]
She's a sweet girl.
Hey, honey.
Don't make her sit there.
Those things are filthy.
It's okay.
It's... it's actually kinda fun.
Sara said we can go see the
goats and chickens at the barn.
Really?
My brother, he tends to all
the animals for the town.
I thought it might
be fun to show Ethan.
It's just down the street.
Do you want to go?
I'm gonna tell Dad we're going.
[Sara]
I can take him.
I don't want to
take you guys away
from anything
that you're doing.
We're not doing anything.
Hey, Jim,
I'll be right back.
Okay.
[Birds chirping]
Hey, babe.
It's been a while.
Things have been...
they've been a little
crazy past few days.
Those, uh, things...
they, uh...
they got into the house
where the little girl lived,
got into the clinic.
You know, we were doing
pretty good for a while there,
keeping everything together.
It was almost
starting to feel like...
[Clears throat]
Uh...
I started getting tremors
in my hand a few weeks back,
same way it started with my Dad,
which means the clock
is officially ticking.
But, see, uh...
I have this crazy idea
that might actually work,
and-and if it does,
then I might be able to find
a way to get these people home,
to get Ellis home.
Of course if it doesn't,
if I'm wrong or if I fail,
then, uh...
then I'm leaving these people
in a worse-off position
than they already are.
You were always the one...
[Chuckles]
You made all the hard calls.
"Sometimes you got
to swing big, baby."
[Laughs]
'Member that?
God, you had...
[Laughs]
[Stammers] I do this
and that's about as big
a swing as I can take.
And, um...
And look, I know,
I know, I always said
that I don't believe in signs
or any of that stuff, but...
I could really use
one right now, okay?
'Cause, babe,
I'm standing at the plate,
and I'll swing if you
tell me to swing. I just...
Babe, I just need
a little help here.
Come on.
I need a sign.
[Birds chirping]
Father Khatri?
Nathan.
Have you come up here much?
No, not really.
It's strange,
don't you think?
A place like this...
could exist in
a place like this?
Um...
I was wondering,
what are the rules?
When it comes to confession,
if I tell you something,
does it stay between
the two of us?
Anything you tell me
stays between us and God.
What if it's bad?
What if it's really bad?
That one's name
is Alma.
Hi, Alma.
[Tabitha chuckles]
Oh, this is so much fun.
Thank you.
It's my pleasure.
Really,
he's a little sweetheart.
Yeah.
You have
a really nice family.
Hmm.
It's okay to be sad,
you know?
And it's okay
to be afraid.
Yeah, it seems the one thing
that everyone
in this town agrees on.
Really, though,
you'd be surprised
how quickly
all this becomes normal.
I don't want this
to become normal.
I just want
to go back home.
Me too.
At least we have
the talismans, though.
Father Khatri
always talks about
how much worse
it was for people.
They'd just hide
in places after dark,
hoping the monsters
wouldn't find them.
Those hiding places
are all over town.
It's really good
to know about them,
just in case you ever
get stuck outside after dark.
Yeah, I guess.
There's one in the barn.
I can show you where it is.
Really?
Yeah, it's just...
It's right inside.
Uh, yeah.
Honey, uh, I'll be right back,
okay? Don't move.
[Sara] This way.
Nathan, you should've
come to me much sooner.
I didn't...
Wait, wait.
What's gonna happen to her?
[Stammers] I don't want
her to go in the box.
You gave your word.
And I intend to keep it.
But right now, we have to worry
about the people of the town.
She'll be at the diner.
Okay. Come on.
Let's go.
♪
People used to spend
the night in here?
What are you doing?
Sara!
-Sorry, Tabitha.
-[Tabitha] Open up!
I'm sorry.
I'm doing this for you.
I'm doing this
for all of us.
Why are you sorry?
Just open the door, please!
-I'm sorry.
-[Tabitha] Sara!
Sara! Sara!
Go get your sister.
Father Khatri!
Hey, I've got kind of
a weird question for you.
If, uh...
If someone asked for a sign,
how would they know
what they were looking for?
Sara?
Looking for your sister?
Yeah.
She's not here.
I saw her heading
towards the barn
with that Matthews lady
and her boy.
[Goats bleating]
Where's my mom?
She'll be right out.
Come here.
I need to tell you something.
Sara!
Ethan! Sara!
I really like you.
And what's about to happen,
it's gonna save everyone,
just like in one
of your stories.
You're gonna be the hero.
Where's my Mom?
I want my Mom!
-We're doing this for her!
-[Nathan] Sara!
-Sara, what are you doing?
-This is how we go home.
Let him go.
They told me,
this was the last one,
then everyone gets to go home!
Ethan! Sara!
-[Grunts]
-[Nathan] Ethan, run!
[Screams]
No! Let me go!
You don't understand!
Oh, my God, Ethan! Ethan!
-[Gasps]
-[Sara] Nathan?
Nathan?
Nathan!
[Gasps]
No!
No, Nathan!
-Nathan.
-[Sara] Nathan, please!
Nathan!
Nathan! Nathan!
Nathan! No!
My God, please!
Please, Nath...
You guys are right.
It's not all bad here.
[Giggles]
You know, I was thinking,
when we get back to the house...
-[Ethan] Julie!
-What?
[Sobbing]
Hey. Ethan?
-[Ellis] Hey.
-[Ethan] Julie!
Hey, hey, hey.
What's wrong?
-Where's Mom and Dad?
-[Crying]
Hey, what's wrong?
It's okay. Don't cry.
Come here. Come here.
Come here. It's okay. Shh.
[Voices screaming]
Oh, my God! Oh, my God!
Oh, my God! Ethan!
Tabitha!
Ethan!
[Banging]
[Tabitha] Help me!
Please help me!
Help me out here, please!
[Jim] Tabitha!
Tabitha!
Jim! Jim, over here!
You okay?
Where... where's Ethan?
-What?
-Where's Ethan?!
Go and find him!
[Indistinct chatter]
[Jim]
Ethan! Ethan!
Jim!
-[Julie] Mom!
-Jim, where's Ethan!?
-[Julie] Dad!
-I don't know.
-Where's Ethan?
-[Julie] Mom!
Oh, my God! Ethan.
-Oh, my God!
-[Ellis] Here you go.
Oh, my God!
Come here, come here.
[Gasps]
♪
[Breathing heavily]
-I was too late.
-Hold on.
-I'm sorry.
-Hey.
Jim. Tabitha.
[Sighing]
-How is he?
-He's fine. He's fine.
-We're gonna go home.
-[Jim] You go on ahead, okay?
-Come on, Jules.
-I'll catch up.
Where is she?
Uh, she, uh...
She ran off into the woods.
And?
And if she comes back before
dark, then we'll handle it.
And if she doesn't?
If she doesn't,
then it's handled.
She came into my house.
She played with my kid.
I know.
Look, if there's
anything that we can do...
The fuck is
wrong with you people?
You talk like this place
is fucking Mayberry!
One big family,
is that what you said?
Are you fucking kidding me?
♪
Where did you find him?
Um, we were
just coming back...
Well, it doesn't
really matter.
But he was running up the hill
towards the Colony House.
You did good, Julie.
Can you take him upstairs
for a minute?
'Kay.
[Tabitha]
You wanna go upstairs?
Hmm?
Come on, bug!
Let's go read
the "Cromawhatsit."
[Ethan]
It's The Cromenockle.
Oh, yeah, sure.
That's what I said -
the "Cromawhatsit."
Come on. All right.
Just take it slow.
You're good.
Yeah. You got this.
[Door closing]
I need something
to write with.
[Clears throat]
Ask every question, right?
That's right.
♪
[Door creaking open]
Mind if I sit?
Yeah.
No. I mean,
yeah, you can sit.
I understood.
She just kept
asking these questions,
like...
what I would do to go home.
[Boyd] Mm.
I just had...
[Stammers]
It didn't cross
my mind that, um...
Listen. Listen to me.
This is not your fault.
I spent the entire night
with her,
and it was just nice
to sit and...
talk and...
[Chuckles]
...have a good time, and...
that scalpel she used,
she took it from my clinic.
So, if...
it's not my fault,
then who...
Whose is it?
You did not bring us here.
You did not put whatever
thought she had in her head.
You're just trying to
do the best you can.
And a few nights ago, hey, look,
you saved a little boy's life,
and you're gonna save more lives
before this is all done.
Hey, hey.
Look.
I need you
to do me a favor.
Cut yourself
some slack. Okay?
["If I Had a Boat"
by Lyle Lovett playing]
[Soft guitar playing]
I'll be damned.
What?
♪ And if I had a boat♪
What is it?
♪ I'd go out on the ocean♪
♪ And if I had a pony♪
I just got my sign.
♪ I'd ride him on my boat♪
♪ And we could all together♪
♪ Go out on the ocean♪
♪ I said, me upon
My pony on my boat♪
♪ Now, if I were Roy Rogers♪
♪ I'd sure enough be single♪
♪ I couldn't bring myself
To marrying old Dale♪
Well, it'd just
Be me and Trigger♪
♪ We'd go riding
Through them movies♪
♪ Then we'd buy a boat♪
♪ And on the sea, we'd sail♪
♪ And if I had a boat♪
♪ I'd go out on the ocean♪
♪ I said, me up
On my pony on my boat♪
♪ Now mystery
masked man was smart♪
♪ He got himself a Tonto♪
♪ 'Cause Tonto did
The dirty work for free♪
♪ But Tonto, he was smarter♪
♪ And one day said,
"Kemosabe"♪
♪ "Well, kiss my ass
I bought a boat♪
♪ "I'm going out to sea"♪
♪ And if I had a boat♪
♪ I'd go out on the ocean♪
♪ I said, me upon
my pony on my boat♪