Previously on From...
I feel like I'm hanging
on by a thread here.
Those things, they never run.
They know there's only
so many places we can go.
I think we're running out of
spaces on the board, Sheriff.
I wish you had the luxury of
grief, but you don't, Boyd.
These people need you.
You need to be the one
to lead these people home.
'Cause if you don't,
she died for nothing.
Come on.
Started getting tremors
in my hand a few weeks back,
which means the clock
is officially ticking,
but I have this crazy idea
that might actually work and...
And if it does,
I might be able to find a way
to get these people home.
Something here is missing.
We just can't see it yet.
I need something to write with.
Ask every question, right?
I don't just sit around
fucking accepting the world
as it is!
Someone is doing this,
and I'm not gonna rest
until I figure out how.
Jade!
I really like you,
and what's about to happen,
it's gonna save everyone.
Where's my mom?
I want my mom!
You're doing this for her!
Let him go.
They told me this
was the last one,
then everyone gets to go home!
- Ethan, run!
- No!
You don't understand!
- Nathan!
- Nathan.
Nathan, please!
Where is she?
She ran off into the woods.
And?
And if she comes back before
dark, then we'll handle it.
And if she doesn't?
If she doesn't,
then it's handled.
Chaos and faith,
that is the duality
of our existence,
from the moment we first arrive,
and not simply
here in this town...
...but in this world,
in this life.
From the moment
we open our newborn eyes,
we are faced with a chaos we
cannot even begin to understand.
And how do we respond?
What is the very
first sound we make?
We cry out.
We plead for answers,
before we even have words to
give voice to the questions.
That's how we begin our
journey through this world -
terrified,
confused.
And so, we search,
and we strive,
and we stumble
through the chaos.
We spend our lives looking
for signs that somewhere,
somehow there's a meaning,
a purpose to it all.
And then, one day,
we find our faith.
Our faith that we are
each here in this world,
in this place,
as part of God's
mysterious plan.
In our faith, we understand
the chaos is the meaning.
It is in our struggle,
in our search,
that we find our purpose.
"Trust in the Lord
with all thine heart
and lean not unto thine
own understanding."
- Amen.
It's always... it's always nice
to see new faces.
Yeah, I'm, um...
I just came by to give you this.
We've been packing up
the other family's stuff.
I figured
they were yours.
Yeah.
How's Ethan doing?
Well, he's, um...
He's scared
and confused.
He doesn't understand why
Sara would try to hurt him.
Mm.
Has anyone seen her?
Not since she ran
off into the woods.
Mm.
I ran after her, but...
my knees aren't quite what
they used to be, I'm afraid.
Do you think
she's still alive?
It's unlikely
she survived the night.
Those Bible passages, did you...
Did you write
those from memory?
Yeah.
Word for word.
It tends to stick.
Um, what did you really come
here to ask me, Tabitha?
How do you know
any of this is real?
I mean...
It sounds crazy,
but are we dead? Are we alive?
I...
Would it matter?
I mean, for argument's sake,
let's say we're dead,
and we're all stuck here
together in some strange,
tormented purgatory.
What would be different?
We'd still be stuck.
We'd still be searching
for a way to go home.
All that would change is
the home we're searching for.
Yeah.
I mean, I'm guessing
I'm not the first person
to come to you
with that question.
Well, let's just say
I've had plenty of chances
to work on my answer.
Yeah.
But if it's any
consolation to you,
you were already here
when your vehicle crashed.
You're alive, Tabitha.
Your family's alive.
So you can scratch that
question off your list.
Yeah.
Bye.
We need to talk.
You all right?
Yeah, it...
I'm having a hard time wrapping
my brain around it, I guess.
I mean, it's Sara, you know?
She was always
so thoughtful, so nice.
- How's your mom taking it?
- It's hard.
You know, Sara was kind of like
the daughter she never had.
I been thinking about
what you said the other day,
about running out
of room on the board.
I was upset.
Well, it doesn't
mean you're wrong.
Something's changing here.
It's like...
like something's slipping away.
The other night, the talisman
worked out in the RV,
same way it does in the houses.
And?
And I've been thinking
that the only reason
we haven't pushed
further into the forest
is we didn't know
whether the talisman
would protect us out there the
same way it does in the town.
So...
I'm putting
together some supplies.
I'm gonna take the talisman
and go out in the forest
and I'm gonna see...
Hey!
Hey, hey, hey, hey!
Kenny, what...
Hey! You don't walk away
when I'm talking to you!
Are you going alone?
Yeah.
And how far are you going?
As far as it'll take me.
I'm doin' this
to find a way out,
find a way home.
Isn't that the point?
Make sure we
all get home?
Honestly?
I'm not sure there
is a point anymore.
But if you're in that much
of a hurry to fuckin' die,
you should just go and do it.
Okay?
I got everything packed up.
It's ready to go to storage.
Oh, okay.
What are you up to?
Look.
There's no wire in here.
What?
In the cord.
When you want
to splice a wire,
you gotta strip away the coating
to get at the wire inside.
But there's no wire.
This is...
You know,
it's not actually a wire.
And the plug?
Look.
The outlets,
none of it makes any sense.
I mean, these lamps,
they shouldn't work.
Hello!
Ah, you, uh,
rollercoaster guy,
- I need your help.
- You don't knock?
I'm sorry, would you like me
to take off my shoes too?
You noticed the wire thing too,
huh? Fucking weird, right?
You're that asshole
that almost killed us.
Okay, look, first of all,
I wasn't driving.
Second, my best friend,
who I've known since fourth
grade, is dead. All right?
He's not walking around with
A little boo-boo on his leg.
So, how about we
just call that one even, okay?
Now, you guys wanna play house
or do you wanna go home?
Because I have an idea.
Did you know there's
not a single copy
of the Bible in town?
I mean, in our little
traveler's library in the diner,
there's at least a dozen Robert
Ludlum and Judy Blume novels,
yet...
not a single copy of
the world's most popular book.
I imagine you wonder
why you're here.
You've done such
unspeakable things.
And by the rules of the town,
you should be in the box.
Nathan told me
about the voices.
It's okay.
Sara, what if I
were to tell you
that despite the horrible
things you've done,
you can still help
the people of this town?
You could still
do something good.
I think Nathan would
like that, don't you?
Yeah?
Good.
Those are pretty.
Right?
You have a good eye,
Miss Matthews.
Oh, I just found
them like this.
Like what?
Arranged like this.
They were on the porch
on the side of the house.
Huh.
Well, it seems we have a phantom
florist running around.
Come on. It's laundry day.
Come on.
Ow!
Motherfucker! Come on!
Ugh.
These people are ding-dongs.
They stripped the car.
They leave behind the only
parts that actually matter.
They're not all ding-dongs.
Battery's gone.
Huh?
I said,
the battery is gone.
That means we gotta
go back to town.
Wait, just as soon
as I get this cable here.
Goddamn it, come on.
Why all the way out here?
We literally could've gotten
wiring from any car in town.
My friend, this is
a top-of-the-line Audi Q5.
Parts sourced from...
You really wanna pin our hopes
to some peasant model jalopy?
Yep.
You got all that?
Whoo!
We're doing it!
Science!
Good morning.
Uh, I'm dropping
these off for storage.
Hey.
Honey, she's not here.
She's not gonna hurt you.
Promise?
Yeah, I promise.
Come on.
Where should I...?
Wow.
Look at all this stuff.
Hey.
Don't touch anything.
Why?
Because this... this used to
belong to other people.
The people
who lived here?
Mm-hmm.
Oh.
It's like the cavern
of the lonely dragon.
Yeah?
When the Cromenockle was
lost in the rainbow sky,
she found a cavern where
the lonely dragon lived,
and it was full of stuff
that nobody wanted.
But for the lonely dragon,
all the stuff was treasure.
And guess what.
What?
In one of the
big piles of stuff,
there was the map
of the rainbow sky.
So, the lonely dragon
gave it to the Cromenockle
and then she
wasn't lost anymore.
So maybe we'll
find a map in here.
Yeah, maybe we will.
Mom?
Yeah.
What's wrong?
Nothing.
Yeah, this is it,
this one, right here.
Oh, this'll
never work.
Of course,
it's going to work.
No, it's not
nearly tall enough.
It won't have
the signal strength.
Yeah, listen, we can
deal with that, okay?
This is just a test run.
Look, you're an engineer, right?
Amusement parks?
Yeah.
Okay. So, I guess that
means one of us built
a multi-million-dollar
software company
and the other does, what,
safety tests on the teacup ride?
You know what?
Do it yourself.
Huh? Wait, no, no! Hey, look.
I'm sorry, okay? I'm sorry.
People tell me I'm not great
when it comes to
talking to people.
You have no idea
what it's like
being smarter
than everyone you know.
Listen, okay, look,
the truth is...
I could really
use your help.
Yeah, you could.
This antenna,
it has to go up high.
That is the highest tree that I
could find, but I... I can't.
I get vertigo.
So, you brought me
out here to climb a tree?
Yeah.
Listen,
you don't like me.
All right? That's fine.
But if there's even
the slightest chance
this could work,
don't you want to know for sure?
Yeah. Yeah, I do.
Okay.
All right.
Pass me up the cable?
Kristi, you here?
Sheriff Boyd?
Kristi, hey.
I-I was just, uh...
I didn't see
you upstairs, so...
Everything okay?
I know you and Kenny are close,
and I was just, uh...
How's he doing?
Well, I mean...
I think he's...
been having a hard time since...
Right, right.
And I-I think he's
trying really hard
to be this person that he
thinks people need him to be,
if that makes sense?
Yeah.
Being your deputy and...
and I know
a big thing for him
is he doesn't want
to let you down.
I know. And I'm really trying
not to push him too hard.
The truth is, he needs
to be ready to lead.
Can I be honest
with you?
Please.
I get that you want to
prepare him for the worst,
get him ready to take your
place in case something ever...
But right now,
he's really hurting,
and I don't think
he needs a sheriff.
I think he needs a dad.
Goddamn it.
I'm sorry, I...
No, no, no.
It's...
It's not you. It's me.
If you don't learn
from your mistakes,
you're doomed to
repeat them, right?
I really didn't mean to...
- You didn't.
- No apology.
Thank you, Kristi.
People think the
Bible's a fixed object -
something written,
completed.
But how can
the story be finished
if all the players
remain on stage?
We call it
"the Good Book", but...
Did you know it's actually
comprised of 73 books?
Did you know that?
Matthew, Mark,
Romans, Corinthians.
Seventy-three books.
All filled with tales
of miracle and wonder.
But there's also
darkness in the Bible.
Gruesome, horrible things.
You know, since...
Since the night I arrived,
there seems to be a question
I keep coming back to.
Seventy-three books.
What if we,
the people of this town,
are living the book
that has yet to be written?
What if this is Book 74?
And, Sara,
what if we were chosen?
For what?
I don't know.
Which is why I need you to
tell me about these voices.
Please.
When's Dad coming home?
Soon, honey.
I don't think
he will be much longer.
What's wrong?
Nothing. I'm just...
Just admiring this piece
of lonely dragon's treasure.
It's pretty.
Yeah.
Why does that light
keep turning off?
I don't know.
How about you
and I have an adventure?
What kind of adventure?
Mm, some sort of,
um, treasure hunt.
Really?
Mm-hmm.
Yeah, the game's
gonna be called,
"Where does
the light come from?"
Sounds good?
- Yeah.
- Let's do it.
Let's go. Okay,
we will need some tools, right?
Mm-hmm.
Ooh, I found your tool!
Let's see if I've...
found my tool.
Okay.
Let's move this.
Come on, honey.
I need you to push. Help me.
Okeydokey.
Now, this is your tool.
This is my tool. Ready?
Mom!
You're doin' great!
Here we go.
Hey, I'm snagged somewhere.
Can you see where it's caught?
Uh, no, not really.
Just, uh, give it a shake,
see if you can wiggle it free.
Yeah, that's it.
- You got it?
- Yup.
All right.
Okay.
How you doing up there?
Doing good.
Fuck!
Oh, Jesus.
No, no, no! No!
No, no, no! No, no!
No, no!
Hey. Hey.
Jade, wh...
Jade, Jade, right here.
Right here.
Listen, whatever it is,
it's not real. Okay?
There's nothing there.
Jade, I'm going
to help you up.
Come here.
You okay? Huh?
Just get your
fucking hands off me!
What did you see?
Just fuck off, all right?
They said they wanted to help.
That they'd been here
a long time
and they'd been waiting
for someone to come
who would hear them,
someone who could help them.
Help them do what?
Help them escape.
Help them go home.
They said they were
just like us.
But why?
Why did you believe them?
Because...
they told me things,
things they couldn't know.
They told me those
two cars were coming
and to stand out near the edge
of town and I would see.
They said it happened before,
that two cars came
on the same day
and everyone died.
They said it was because of the
people in the cars, but if...
...if I did what they said,
that we'd be safe,
we'd get to go home.
Okay. How?
How would we get to go home?
- I don't know.
- Okay.
Do you still believe that
they were telling the truth?
They promised...
that Nathan would be okay.
They-they promised,
and now, now he's...
Sara.
Sara, listen to me.
Come here.
Listen to me.
Listen to me, Sara.
If these voices are real,
if something here is
communicating with you,
then that means you're
connected to this place
in a way that
no one else here is,
and that makes you
incredibly valuable.
Do you understand?
But we need proof.
We need to be able
to go to Sheriff Boyd
and tell him with absolute
certainty that you...
That I'm not crazy.
No, the voices,
that these voices are not simply
the product of a troubled mind.
So, Sara, I need...
Ow!
- Sara?
- Ow.
- What?
- Ow. No!
What?
- Sara.
- No! No!
- What?
- No, no, no!
- Please! Ah, no, no!
What?
- Sara, what is it?
- Ah, no!
What?
I need... I need...
Need what?
Paper.
They want me to
show you something.
Hello?
Is anybody out there?
Is anybody there?
I don't want any tea!
You realize I have no
idea what you're saying.
Fine.
It's good.
Thanks.
I keep seeing it.
I-I keep...
I keep having these, uh...
Hey, where are you going?
Hello?
Where'd you go?
Holy shit.
This is all the, uh...
Wow. Oh, wait, wait!
Hold on.
Slow down, Tian.
I got this.
What...
What are you looking for?
What is that?
It's a yearbook.
1972?
How many people...?
Okay.
Well, I mean, could you tell me
what you're looking for?
Shh.
What's that?
Hmm?
Oh, what the fuck?
Please...
I can't...
I don't...
What is this?
They said...
They said they watched you
on the day you got here.
They said they
watched you bury the bag
and that this is proof
that they're real.
Do you know what that means?
Oh!
Ah! Here we go.
Okay.
Yeah.
That's it.
There we go.
Hey.
Sheriff Boyd.
Ladies.
Hi!
Fuck!
Come in.
Hey.
I was, uh, going through my
things back at the station,
and I realized I haven't thrown
a ball around in a while.
Come on outside.
You can help an old man
knock the rust off.
I'm good.
Hey, I ever tell
you, uh,
I played first base
back in college.
No.
Yeah, I was
pretty good too.
Had a couple scouts
kicking around.
Here I am,
18 years old, thinkin',
"Man, I might
be going to the show,"
"be the next Willie McCovey."
What happened?
Oh, you know...
life had other plans.
Life always seems
to have other plans.
I'm sick, Kenny.
What do you...?
Have you talked
to Kristi about it?
Not that kind of sick.
My father was diagnosed
with Parkinson's
when he was around my age.
It's not supposed
to be hereditary.
The doctors all
swore up and down
how extremely rare
that would be.
Wrong time to win
the lottery, I guess.
But how do you know that...?
How do you know?
I mean,
it could be anything, right?
It is what it is.
Look...
this thing is already
chipping away at me.
And eventually, I'm gonna get
to the point where I can't...
I'm not gonna be able to protect
these people anymore.
So I gotta find us a way out
while I still can.
You understand?
The only way
I can do this
is because I know these people
are gonna be in good hands
when I'm gone.
There's a lot of folks
in this town
who are alive today
because of you.
And I know your dad
isn't around to say it,
but I promise you...
he's so goddamn proud of you.
I'm proud of you.
But if you tell me
right now
that you are not ready
for me to go,
that you need more time,
then I ain't
going nowhere.
Okay?
Well, we doing
this or what?
Doing it.
Hey? Anybody here?
We might be onto something
with this radio.
We're gonna have to get it
higher up, but it could...
What the fuck?
Hi, Dad.
Hey, kiddo.
What you up to?
We're on an adventure.
There's a lot of dirt,
so mom said I should
bring some outside.
Uh-huh.
And where is your mother?
In the basement.
Tabitha?
Hey. Hey.
How'd things go?
Good.
Yeah?
We got some static, so...
Yeah, well,
that's wonderful, right?
Yeah, it's a start.
What you doing?
It's like you
said this morning,
it has to come from somewhere,
right? The electricity.
There's no power lines,
and all the wires,
all the cords, they just...
they just go down,
straight down.
It's so weird.
Okay. Uh, sorry, can you...
not dig for a moment?
Yes.
What's going on?
Okay.
Do you remember
the bracelet I made you?
The what?
The bracelet I made you
after our first few dates,
from, uh, the laces of
your father's boots.
Yeah, of course, I remember.
Okay. Remember,
you lost it at the hospital
the night Julie was born.
Okay.
Turn around.
Look what's sitting there.
Okay, I still don't get it.
You're saying
you found a bracelet
that's similar to
the one you gave...
No, no, no, no.
It's not similar.
That is the bracelet.
Those are the laces
from your father's boots!
No, those were generic
rawhide laces,
the same you'd find on any boot.
No, no, no, no, no, no.
Look. Look at this.
Look at this.
What?
This was an accident.
I made this.
I was so afraid I ruined it,
but then, when I gave it to you,
you said, "Accidents... "
"Accidents are the best part."
Yes. Why?
Ah, because it makes
it one of a kind.
Exactly.
It's impossible.
Jim, everything
about this is impossible.
That doesn't
make any sense.
Those wires
don't make sense.
We may not be able to
find out how this got here,
but we can find out
where those wires go.
Give me the shovel.
Where's yours?
First base.
I don't need no glove.
Are you sure?
Because I got some heat.
Just throw the damn ball.
You're gonna regret this.
I hear a lot of talking,
but I'm not...
Here comes the heat.
I think, uh...
Think maybe I'll carve us a bat.
That way, when you get back,
we can do this right.
When I get back, huh?
Yeah, when you get back.
Yeah.
They're so beautiful.
I'm so glad you like them.
When can I come inside?