-[LAUGHTER]
-You know the saying,
"Walk a mile in a man's shoes"?
I mean, think about that.
The perspective that gives you.
Well, I took it to heart, put on
a pair of my husband's shoes,
and, my God, were they comfortable.
I get it now, why men rule the world
no high heels.
They can walk faster,
and their backs don't hurt.
I'm divorcing my husband,
but I am keeping the fucking shoes.
Thank you, everybody.
I'm Mrs. Maisel.
I'm on the road the next few days,
but, unlike your innocence, I'll be back.
-Good night!
-[CHEERING, APPLAUSE]
-[MUSIC PLAYING]
-Great set.
Hey, thanks.
I can never tell if they're
talking about the boobs
-or the comedy.
-That guy was a dancer in Pal Joey.
He wasn't talking about your boobs.
-Hi.
-Hi there.
-Uh, what is she doing?
-I don't know.
Ooh. It's a pen.
-Oh, she wants your autograph.
-Really?
Wow.
This is really cool.
How's it look?
Lose the heart.
Really? Doesn't make it stand out?
No, it makes it look like
a third grader signed it.
Okay. [CLEARS THROAT]
Here.
And thanks.
Thank you.
I just signed my first autograph.
-And check this out.
-Hmm.
Our first road itinerary.
Let's go over it.
Not necessary, I know it by heart.
Days one and two, D.C.
Day three, Philly.
Day four, Harrisburg.
Day five, back home for the
gig at the new club on 23rd.
Oh. Okay.
I mean, I typed it up all fancy.
One for each of us.
Even fixed my "S" key.
-But you don't need it.
-No, no, no, let me see it.
-I'll just use it as toilet paper.
-Let me see it.
-You spelled "itinerary" wrong.
-Damn.
It's impressive.
Just remember the most important part:
day one, tomorrow,
depart New York City 1:30 p.m. sharp.
-Got it?
-I will not be late.
Okay, I got Montana,
North Carolina, Utah,
-Wisconsin…
-We'll do this later, Jackie.
Do what? What is this?
The plates for you to switch on the car.
Why are we switching
the plates on the car?
Well, it… it's technically stolen.
There's nothing technical about it.
It's fucking stolen.
I like Utah. They'll think you're Mormon
and leave you alone.
I mean, no one talks to Mormons
unless they have to.
-You said it's your mother's car.
-It is.
You stole your mother's car?
Hey, she stole my childhood.
I think we're even.
What if we're pulled over
and they run our plates?
-I'll handle it.
-Great plan.
We'll just cross our fingers
and hope for the best.
It's how I live my life
just sort of half-assed
and completely random.
I want no part of this, okay?
Fine. Have no part of it.
Take Wyoming.
SUSIE: Wyoming? Why?
Wyoming's full of cowboys
and tough hombres,
and cops are less likely to pull us over
'cause they won't want to mess with us.
Plus, it's got a horse,
and I like the horse.
I had a feeling that was it.
So, 1:30 tomorrow.
1:30. See ya, partner.
Pew, pew. [BLOWS]
Lose Wyoming.
["OOMP WADDLE DICKIE DUCK" PLAYING]
♪ Dickie the duck went
out walking one day ♪
♪ He wanted some ducks
to come over and play ♪
♪ He quack, quack, quack,
quacked as he waddled along ♪
You tire of Chopin?
No, I like Chopin very much.
What are you doing?
Working. Or trying to.
You do know that's Ethan's record.
Hence the references to
"Ducky Waddles ha ha ha."
-[MUSIC STOPS]
-Don't you have some dirty jokes
-to go tell?
-Told 'em.
So, whatcha doin'?
Our Bell Labs speech synthesis team
is going to be the first in the world
to teach a computer to sing.
But I need to find
precisely the right song.
It has to have a simple melody
with a maximum one-octave range
and, ideally, very few
diphthongs in the lyrics.
Ethan's records are perfect.
You're not gonna want that one.
It's just barnyard sounds.
Oh.
I signed my first autograph tonight.
A complete stranger asked
you to put your signature down
on a piece of paper and you did it?
Yes. She was very excited, too.
Well, of course she was.
Now she can forge your
signature on a check.
It was a really good show tonight.
You know, when you saw me at the Concord,
it wasn't exactly my regular act, Papa.
I saw you, and… I got nervous.
You made me nervous.
And that made you vulgar?
No. I just…
I have a gig in the city when I get back.
Nearby. Nice club.
Maybe you'd like to come.
-It's too far.
-Nearby is too far?
I mean I'm very busy.
I just think if you saw
me at a normal gig,
you might feel better about it.
Don't worry about me.
How about Mama? How's she feeling?
Marry Benjamin, and
everything will be fine.
I don't know if I'm
going to marry Benjamin.
Marry somebody, and
everything will be fine.
-Okay.
-To be clear,
I mean marry somebody at city hall.
I'm not going to pay for fake snow
and papier-mâché reindeer again.
$400 for embroidered yarmulkes
that say "Midge and Joel forever."
Explain that to an orphan.
If I see one, I will.
I'm sorry, Papa.
I know that all this stuff
with me, with Noah…
Miriam, please,
I have no time to concern myself
with my children's feckless behavior.
I'm a man of science,
engaged in complex research
at the highest levels
on incredibly important
scientific matters.
BOY: ♪ I went to the bathroom by myself ♪
ADULTS: ♪ Big, big boy went by himself ♪
BOY: ♪ I took some paper ♪
♪ Wiped myself ♪
ADULTS: ♪ Wiped his bottom by himself ♪
There's a fair amount
that works in this one.
Unfortunately, computers
don't use the bathroom.
Yet.
BOY: ♪ I went to the bathroom ♪
-♪ By myself ♪
-♪ Big… ♪
I have no idea what to get.
I haven't been out of the house
in a month.
Archie's mother keeps sending us
corned beef and cabbage.
The whole apartment building
smells like Downtown Dublin.
Well, order as much as you want.
It's all on me.
This is a purely
guilt-motivated "I'm sorry" lunch.
I love your quaint Jewish traditions.
-Ooh, who's that?
-Oscar Udenosky.
-Is he famous?
-He's a dentist.
Oh. I thought he was famous.
What's kishka?
Jewish haggis.
No, thank you. Oh, who's that?
-Bertha Frisk.
-Is she famous?
She's the bingo queen of St. Mary's.
Does that count?
I thought there were going
to be famous people here.
It is called the Stage Deli,
not the Boring Everyone
Normal Eats Here Deli.
Couldn't get all those
letters on the sign.
I was hoping it would be
like when Lucy went to the Brown Derby
and saw William Holden and got so nervous
she buttered her hand
instead of her bread.
I can see a dentist at Lindy's.
I need some excitement.
Excitement. Okay.
Oh.
See that guy over there in the gray suit?
Marty Segal.
Yesterday, he scored his first Copa gig.
-Big, big deal.
-Huh.
He just spilled coffee on his suit.
Does the Copa know about that?
That may be his opening bit.
Gregory Peck came in once.
-He did?
-Came in
and ate lunch. Right over there.
No. Are you lying? Never mind.
Don't care. I love Gregory Peck.
Congratulations on the Copa.
Put some club soda on that, Marty.
What can I get for you two?
Oh, shoot. I haven't finished looking.
Allow me.
Verla, my dear friend Imogene here
will have the hot pastrami Reuben on rye,
chicken in a pot, potato knish,
matzo ball soup, cheese Danish,
a lime rickey, and a couple of
black-and-whites for dessert.
-And some Bromo-Seltzer to go?
-You bet.
Coming right up.
That's exactly what Gregory Peck ordered.
No. Are you lying? Never mind.
Don't care. This is so exciting.
-Hey, Midge.
-Hey, Eugene.
How'd the Florida gig go?
I did ten minutes on bad shellfish.
The place went nuts.
Oh, you never told me
Grace Kelly was your friend.
Easy, boy. Those tits are just temporary.
-[GASPS]
-Oh, sorry.
Congratulations.
What?
[WHISPERS]: I can't believe what you said.
In a restaurant.
Oh, he's a comic.
Th… That's just how we talk.
It's just I've never heard you…
Oh, my. He looked at my…
He didn't mean anything
by it except that your boobs
are enormous. And they are. Mazel tov.
Oh, my God. A man looked at my…
I should tell Archie.
Should I tell Archie?
Deep breaths, honey.
And I have never heard
you talk like that before.
-I'm sorry.
-Midge,
you cannot do that at my shower.
If my mother heard you say T-I-T-S,
she would…
well, she might not do anything
because she won't know
what you're talking about,
-but please don't.
-Imogene,
I promise, I am throwing the
most beautiful baby shower
in the world for my very best friend.
And, I promise, I will be
on my very best behavior.
Okay. Okay.
So, did Gregory Peck
really eat over there?
And Cary Grant joined him for dessert.
[BELL DINGS]
This car is unkempt, to say the least.
Hey, lady, I could use another hand.
I have to make sure nothing back
here gets crushed and wrinkled.
Who knows if they have
irons where we're headed?
Ah! Motherfucker!
Fuck my mother!
Hey, what the hell?
Oh. Did you need that?
That's my shit.
-It is? In that?
-Yes.
Just because it's not wrapped
in a pink box like some party cake
doesn't make it garbage.
Why didn't you bring a suitcase?
I don't have one.
What do you use for vacations?
-My imagination?
-Sorry,
I thought your stuff was packed
in the little suitcase in the back.
Ah. The suitcase thing's a tape recorder.
I'm gonna tape all your road sets
so we can study 'em when we get back.
-That's a great idea.
-Thanks.
Here's another one.
Stop sounding so surprised
when I have a great idea.
Now, please, just hold the plate up.
-The screw won't go in.
-No way.
I have two priors.
I can't risk another arrest.
Never mind.
Just go over your set for tonight.
Oh, I have been.
Do you think I can do the bit
about Eisenhower's penis in D.C.
or will the Secret Service not like it?
-I could say "sausage."
-Eh, they'll know you mean "penis."
Maybe I'll say "penis" but
not "Eisenhower's penis."
I'll put "Eisenhower's
penis" in the Philadelphia set.
I think Eisenhower's penis is a
slam dunk wherever you put it.
Okay.
America, here we come.
Great. Lift your ass.
-I'm sorry?
-You got to lift your ass
-or the car won't start.
-Are you kidding me?
-No.
-Why?
Am I a mechanic?
Just pick it up so we can go.
I do a version of this
-in my Helena Rubinstein class.
-[ENGINE STARTS]
Good for the thighs.
-Can I put my butt down now?
-Almost.
-The car's moving.
-Few more seconds.
You're just screwing
with me now, aren't you?
Yep. The Eisenhower penis tour has begun.
-Mm.
-[HONKS HORN]
♪ I'm gonna ♪
♪ Live till I die ♪
♪ I'm gonna laugh 'stead of cry ♪
♪ I'm gonna take the town
and turn it upside down ♪
♪ I'm gonna live, live, live till I die ♪
♪ They're gonna say ♪
Is Senator Kennedy running
for president, do we think?
-[SCATTERED AGREEMENT]
-It's up to Jackie.
You know she wears
the pants in that family.
-[LAUGHTER]
-And she wears them well. Seriously,
have you seen how easily
that woman wears linen pants?
Linen. The material that wrinkles
while you're ironing it.
I believe the Kennedys
will stand up for Americans.
Because, really, if Jackie
sits down for ten seconds,
that whole outfit goes to shit.
-[LAUGHTER]
-I hope he runs,
because he'll restore the science funding
that Eisenhower cut.
Science is big in my family
because my father works at Bell Labs.
And I was very excited
when he got this job.
The greatest scientific minds
in the world all in one building,
solving the world's problems.
I came home the other
day and found him listening
to my four-year-old's record,
a song about teaching
yourself how to wipe your ass
-after going to the bathroom.
-[LAUGHTER]
He told me he's listening
to it because at work,
they're trying to teach
a computer to sing.
And I believed him at the time,
but now I'm wondering:
does my father not know
how to go to the bathroom?
-[LAUGHTER]
-And if that's true, who taught me?
Because my mother never goes
to the bathroom. Or eats. Or…
Fire!
Fire in the kitchen! Everybody out!
-To the exits, now! Go, go!
-What? Why?
What… What's going on?
CLUB MANAGER: There's a fire.
Everybody out.
Move to the exits, now! Go!
Okay, folks, I guess
everybody's supposed to leave.
-SUSIE: No! Keep talking!
-Are you not hearing me?
-There's a fire in the kitchen!
-Well, of course there is.
It's how you fuckin' cook things.
I'm Mrs. Maisel. Thank you. Good night.
If you catch on fire,
stop, drop and roll.
You have water in that kitchen?
You can put fire out with water.
-You know that, right?
-Susie, please. I've got
a lot of flammable product in my hair.
We'll die if we just stand here.
-So you die on stage. What a way to go.
-Move!
Aw, come on, it hasn't
even hit this room yet.
It will.
[DOOR UNLOCKING]
-Huh.
-I told you it wasn't gonna be The Ritz.
It's fine.
Big enough. Clean-ish.
Drawers open.
Lights light.
There's the parking lot,
so we can watch the car.
Hi, car.
It's good. Guess we share the dresser.
How many drawers do
you think you'll need?
[SIGHS]
Looks like one.
Then I'll make do with the other five.
Hey, you put coins in the TV.
Are you not having fun?
I just wanted you to finish your set.
I know. I was on fire.
And then the place was, too.
-Maybe I set the fire.
-On the bright side,
the guy paid us the whole take.
Plus we got out before
the building collapsed.
So, go ahead and shower.
I know you want to.
I will.
As soon as the guy brings up my bags.
-What guy?
-The guy who checked us in.
You think Vlad the Impaler in the lobby
is bringing up your bags?
-Yes.
-Based on what?
Based on the fact that I
said, "Just the two, thanks,"
and he nodded like he
was gonna bring them up.
No, he nodded like he was
gonna go through your luggage
and whack off with your
girdle stretched over his face.
-So no one's bringing up my bags?
-No. It's a motel.
You want 'em, you go get 'em.
Right. Okay.
-Do not look at me.
-Fine. I'm gonna go down
to get the bags and carry them up myself.
After all, this trip is
about trying new things
and expanding my horizons.
It's bags, not a threesome
with Marilyn Monroe and Arthur Miller.
No, but it's steep stairs; no elevator.
Here, take this.
Sure you don't want to come?
Mm.
Only you can expand your horizons, Miriam.
New things!
Fuckin' weirdo.
This is like being back in
college, sharing a room.
-Or a slumber party.
-Or jail.
You ever have slumber
parties when you were a kid?
If you count everyone falling
asleep in the same room
'cause they were too drunk
to get up a slumber party.
We used to play with a Ouija board
and try to contact Valentino.
One time the lights flickered.
It was scary. But fun.
One time my cousin
came into my room at night
and got on top of me.
I jabbed my finger into his eye,
and he was blind for a week.
It was scary. But fun.
-We could watch TV.
-Meh. This late,
it's just the test pattern
with the Indian chief.
Just shut the lights off,
and we'll both be snoring
like buzz saws any minute.
-Oh.
-What?
-You snore?
-How would I know? I'm sleeping.
Well, has anyone ever told you you do?
What kind of a sick fuck's
gonna come into my room,
listen to me sleep,
then tell me about it?
So no one you've ever shared
a bed with has let you know?
-Did you ask your cousin?
-Really?
The reason your husband left you?
You wouldn't let him get any sleep.
[MIDGE CLEARS THROAT]
[TAKES DEEP BREATH]
Hey, remember when that
really old lady was yelling
"Take me, I'm on fire!" at the fireman?
Yeah.
Then the fireman threw
that blanket over her.
For a minute I thought
he was gonna do it.
SUSIE: Give the old bird her dying wish.
MIDGE [BREATHILY]:
"Take me, I'm on fire."
Hmm. You should put that
shit in your set tomorrow.
I'm opening with it. Did she die?
-Nah.
-Maybe in the act she'll die.
I think I can keep that funny.
Night, Susie.
Mm.
-Hey, Susie.
-What?
She wanted to slide down his pole.
Go to sleep.
[CHUCKLES] Pole's funny.
[MIDGE CHUCKLES]
MIDGE: He's sleeping okay there?
-JOEL: Like a rock. He's doing great.
-Let me say hi.
Hey, Ethan. It's Mommy.
Want to say hi?
No. She has to ring it.
-He doesn't want to talk to me?
-Sure he does.
He just wants you to call
back so the phone'll ring
-especially for him.
-Okay.
Guess Mommy's made of coins. One sec.
-What's wrong?
-Nothing.
-It's something. What is it?
-Leg hurts.
-What'd you do?
-Why is this my fault?
[PHONE RINGS]
Hi, Mommy.
Hi, sweetie. How… Hello?
Ethan?
[PHONE RINGS]
-Hi.
-What happened?
Well, he doesn't really
like talking on the phone.
He just loves answering it.
-He's forgotten me.
-No, he hasn't.
Two days, I've been gone. Two days.
He's a kid. I'll tell him you miss him.
And you can call collect, Midge.
That would have been a good
idea about three dollars ago.
Wait, are you short?
You got enough money for the trip?
Sure. I just don't carry
it all around in quarters.
It makes my thighs look lumpy.
-Where are you two?
-Gas station.
How's Susie's car? Does it run okay?
Purrs like a really old, angry kitten.
-And she's a decent driver?
-We go places and we get there.
Does she know how to change a tire?
I'd assume so.
-Ask her.
-Joel.
Where'd you stay in DC?
I'm not sure I have enough coins
to get through all three centuries
-of the Spanish Inquisition.
-You know what?
-Is she there?
-Susie?
Yeah. Put her on. I can give her
some pointers on changing a tire.
Okay. Joel wants to know
if you can change a tire.
What?
Ugh.
[SINGSONG] Hello.
Yes, I can change a stupid tire.
Now, listen, and you listen good.
I swear to motherfucking
God, if anything happens
to Midge on this trip,
I'm gonna fucking kill you.
I don't care that
you're a girl, or short,
I will rip your head off and
use it to play catch with my kid.
She's the mother of my children.
If you fuck this up,
I want you to think of the worst
possible thing that could ever
happen to you, and I want you
to triple it and add a hobbling.
You got it? Now
apply the wheel wedges,
remove the hubcaps,
loosen the lug nuts, jack up the car
and change the fucking tire.
Or call a goddamn cab.
Put Midge back on the phone.
Thanks for the tip.
Great guy.
Too bad you kids couldn't work it out.
I should go.
We have to get all the way to Philly.
Where are you staying when you get there?
-I don't know. Some motel.
-Uh-huh. Put Susie on again.
Too late. She limped off. Really quickly.
Just be careful, okay? Will you? Please?
Yes. And kiss Ethan and Esther for me.
Show them a picture if you have to.
I will.
-Bye.
Hey, scoot over. Let's get going.
I got to take a break from
driving; it's killing my leg.
-Meaning…
-You drive.
-I don't know how to drive.
-What?
-I grew up in the city.
-How the hell do you plan a road trip
with somebody and forget to
mention that you can't drive?
I did plan to learn a few years ago.
Oh, well, that's a relief.
For a second there,
I thought maybe you didn't
plan to learn a few years ago.
I even bought pink driving gloves.
I brought them with me.
Because we were gonna be in a car.
-You can wear them if you want.
-[SIGHS]: Jesus Christ.
Sorry.
Ass up.
[ENGINE STARTS]
[METALLIC CLATTERING]
Hey! Occupied!
Aren't I supposed to
have a real dressing room?
Or at least a door with a lock?
Yeah, well, I guess I got a little busy
making sure the place
had, you know, a stage
-and a place for an audience.
-A manager's supposed to request
things like a dressing
room with a door that locks.
I'm a total idiot.
What do you want me to say?
Usually you show up to
a gig in your show dress.
I forgot you'd need a place to change.
My fault.
-Learning lessons.
-Fine.
-Knock, asshole!
-There's someone in here, asshole!
-It's me, Dante!
-Booker.
MIDGE/SUSIE: Sorry!
DANTE: Your girl is on.
-Uh, we need a minute.
-And a lock for the door.
DANTE: Crowd is restless. Get a move on.
-Zip me. Hurry.
-How is the crowd?
-DANTE: Good.
-Crowd's good.
-How do I look?
-Like you're ready to take Philly.
DANTE: Hey, everybody.
Straight from the Big Apple…
-Sorry about the room.
-Sorry I yelled about the room.
-Let's do this.
-Give a big Philly welcome to…
Mrs. Maisel!
[SCATTERED APPLAUSE]
Well, hello, Philadelphia!
Wow.
You said the crowd was good.
They are good.
There's just not that many of them.
MIDGE: I'm Mrs. Maisel.
-Motherfucker.
-MIDGE: So, the
first joke I was gonna
tell you guys tonight
has one of those "has
anyone here ever" thingies.
But I realize the odds that anyone here
has ever actually done the thing
I was gonna ask if you had done
are pretty darn low.
Just mathematically.
Unless it was something
like: Has anyone here
-ever gotten alcohol poisoning?
-[LAUGHTER]
In which case the odds
get pretty good again.
Because it's Philly.
I think there were
more people in the room
-when my son was born.
-[LAUGHTER]
Maybe also when he was conceived.
Ma'am, the… the tag is
sticking out of your dress.
[DOGS BARKING, SIREN WAILING IN DISTANCE]
[DOOR UNLOCKING]
-Jesus.
-Oh, my.
What a shithole.
[INDISTINCT SHOUTING NEARBY]
[MIDGE GASPS]
What's the matter?
I'm kind of digging the suspense here.
Well, hello.
[TOILET FLUSHES]
Am I a fucking manager or what?
I'll never unsee that. The sheer size.
Go to bed. Dream of puppies.
Well, hello.
-What now?
-Nothing.
Just a lot of things to
say hello to in this room.
-What?
-Teeth.
-Teeth?
-False teeth?
-Real teeth.
-Baby teeth?
-Large teeth.
Adult teeth.
Or teeth from a really big baby.
Maybe a… I got nothing.
I don't think I'll unpack tonight.
Or use the bathroom. Or lie down.
Or sit down. Or shut my eyes.
-Miriam.
-Hello.
You're on tour. You got to sleep.
-Just keep your clothes on.
-I don't need sleep.
I can't sleep, anyway, because of your…
'Cause of my what?
What are you doing? Don't touch that.
You need to hear something.
I don't want to hear your DC gigs.
It's not my DC gigs.
I was going to wait
until we got home, but…
[SUSIE SNORING ON TAPE]
What is that?
-That's you.
-Bullshit.
-Hold on.
-[SNORING GROWS LOUDER]
-Jesus Christ.
-I'm sorry.
I recorded you when you
were sleeping last night.
First of all, don't ever,
ever touch the tape recorder. Hear me?
-And "B," that's the most sadistic…
-[ON TAPE] Tom Collins.
-Wait, what'd I just say there?
-I think it was "Tom Collins."
-Didn't know you liked gin.
-[SNORING CONTINUES]
Tom Collins was my teddy bear.
-Oh. Sweet.
-Turn it off.
I will. I just think you
should hear one more thing.
[GRUNTING, SNORTING]
[SNORING STOPS]
Did I die?
-Maybe. You really need to see a doctor.
-[SNORING RESUMES]
You need to learn some
manners, you know that?
-I was just trying to help.
-Don't help me. Write that down.
Look, I know it's embarrassing,
but when I was little,
my mother used to wake me
up when I made unseemly noises
to train me to be a ladylike sleeper.
For when I got married.
-She recorded you?
-No. She sat on the edge of my bed
and shook me when I made a noise.
Wow.
Freak doesn't fall far from the tree.
-One day you might thank me, Susie.
-Yeah?
Well, you taped over the D.C.
gigs, so thanks for that.
Hope you remember your
American Revolution joke
word-for-word, 'cause it's gone.
You're really gonna
stand there all night?
It works for Francis the Talking Mule.
Suit yourself.
I'm sleeping in your bed, then.
Mine's taken.
-MIDGE: Good night.
-SUSIE: Fuck you.
Starving.
Bathroom. Fix.
-Counter. Eat.
-Coffee.
Fuck.
Come on.
Don't look.
Mmm.
[SIGHS]
Hey, you have any idea
what these weird bumps are?
-I mean, is this, like, a local thing?
-I'm 16.
I didn't ask if you'd ever been blown.
I asked about this.
I give.
You didn't get me any coffee.
Coffee, please.
Yeah, he's not coming back.
Probably on his way to therapy.
I knew it was bad, but when
I looked in a mirror… God.
Why didn't you tell
me I looked like shit?
I have my own problems, missy.
Oh, my God, your face.
-No kidding, my face.
-What happened?
-What's it look like? Something bit me.
-It was the bed.
You laid on the bed.
Thank God I didn't lay on the bed.
What have you got in
there that can fix this?
Nothing.
You have 500 things in that case.
-You got nothing for bites?
-I could do
some mascara for you.
Maybe a little eyeliner.
-How's that gonna help?
-It'll make your eyes look bigger,
and that'll draw attention
away from the rest of your face.
Hey, I have that all organized.
Yeah, this shit's got "skin" right there.
That'll make your welts
look ten years younger.
There's more now.
Shit, they're still hatching.
Shit. This bite has a bite on it.
I'm sorry.
I'm going to the drugstore to
see if there's someone there
who can help me more than you,
like a blind-mute baby with no arms.
[LINE RINGING]
ABE [OVER PHONE]: Hello?
OPERATOR: Collect call from Miriam Maisel
for Abe or Rose Weissman.
Do you accept the charges?
I don't know. What are my options?
-MIDGE: Take the call.
-I'll take the call.
-OPERATOR: Go ahead, please.
-Hello, Papa.
Skip the niceties. What do you need?
MIDGE: I'm just calling to check in.
-How's the baby?
-ABE: She's drooling.
-She's defecating.
-Does she miss me?
I think unless she can
fit you in her mouth,
you are of no consequence to her at all.
-Anything else?
-You're in a mood.
-Well, your mother has pulled a fast one.
-What now?
She's throwing some sort
of soiree and forgot to tell me.
Or you forgot to listen.
ABE: Now there's tables and chairs.
-They've taken over my study.
-Maybe it's her garden club?
It's been ages since she's hosted them.
There's flowers and tables and streamers.
Streamers usually indicate music.
They drink some wine
and talk about stamens.
-It'll be over in an hour.
-She's not even here.
She just left me like
this to fend for myself.
-So where's the baby?
-Glassware?
She got rental glassware.
Papa.
The baby's with Rose
at the beauty parlor.
-I just said that.
-You didn't, actually.
Miriam, I have to go.
I just heard the words "potato salad."
There's only so much a man
can take in his own house.
This stuff does not help at all.
You're supposed to blow on it.
[BLOWING]
-Are they gone?
-No.
Then get the fuck away from me.
Okay. I have to go change.
["TRAVELIN' MAN" BY RICKY NELSON PLAYING]
♪ I'm a travelin' man ♪
♪ I've made a lot of
stops all over the world… ♪
Aren't you supposed to keep
both hands on the wheel?
Thought you didn't know how to drive.
I know how not to drive.
-[THUNDER RUMBLING]
-Was that thunder?
-I didn't hear anything.
-I definitely heard a rumble,
and I didn't bring my rain mac
because you said not to, Susie.
I didn't tell you not
to bring your rain mac
'cause I don't know what a rain mac is.
It's a fashionable cover
to keep you dry, and I left it
at home because you said
the weather was gonna be good.
-I repeated what the paper said.
-I would've brought my rain mac,
I would've brought my
galoshes, I would've brought…
-Potato salad.
-What?
Stop the car. Stop the car.
I can't just stop the car.
Pull over. Pull over.
[LINE RINGING]
-[PHONE RINGING]
-WOMEN: Aw.
Oh, yay, more booties.
Thanks, Nancy.
Bring more napkins.
-They're going through a lot of them.
-Yes, ma'am.
IMOGENE: Good, a bonnet and booties.
WOMEN: Aw.
Mr. Bemis works at a bank,
but all he wants is time alone
to read his precious books.
It's his passion.
-I love books.
-Anyway…
Why is no one answering the phone?
His wife's a shrew, so he can't
read at home. She won't let him.
And he wears these really
thick reading glasses, you see?
Anyway, he finally decides
to hide out in the bank vault.
All right, I'll answer it.
DON: What's this program called?
ABE: The Twilight Zone.
-ARCHIE: Never heard of it.
-ABE: It's new.
-Hello?
-MIDGE [DISTORTED]: Hello?
ABE: While our man is in
the vault, there's a nuclear war.
-They drop the H-bomb.
-ROSE: Hello?
-Wow.
-[CHUCKLES] Didn't see that comin'.
Neither did he.
But there's another twist.
I love twists.
Miriam, is that you?
-I can barely hear you.
-Miriam's on the phone?
I forgot about the baby shower.
-Did you? I hadn't noticed.
-MIDGE: Oh, God.
I am so sorry.
I… I must've gotten the dates mixed up.
I've been so busy
getting ready for the tour,
and then Papa said "potato salad."
I'm so sorry. It's today.
-ROSE: Where are you?
-MIDGE: A pay phone
-in Pennsylvania.
-She's not gonna make it?
-ROSE: Apparently not.
-Wait.
Wait, it's still happening without me?
You're right. We should reschedule.
I'm sure Imogene can cross her legs
-and hold it in.
-She's not coming?
-I'm sure there's a good reason.
-ARCHIE: Can you tell Imogene?
I'll wait here behind the table.
And Donny.
-MIDGE: Put Papa on.
-Abe?
Hold on, let me finish this.
So, Mr. Bemis is the sole survivor
because he was in the vault,
and for the first time, he's lonely.
Burgess Meredith plays
this with a lot of pathos.
But then he finds
the ruins of the library.
-ROSE: Abe.
-ABE: Mr. Bemis is overjoyed at the sight
of all the books with all
the time in the world to read.
-But then…
-Does he break his glasses?
And there's no one to fix 'em.
You made a big deal
about his glasses before.
Is that right? [CHUCKLES] That's great.
-Hello?
-Papa, why didn't you tell me
they were setting up
for Imogene's shower?
I did.
You said it was the garden club.
No, you said it was the garden club.
-Put me on speakerphone, please.
-Why?
Take me to the living room
and put me on speakerphone.
MIDGE: Hello? Am I on?
It's working. Explain yourself.
Hi, everyone.
-ALL: Hi.
-Imogene, can you hear me okay?
-Yes, Midge.
-You sound far away.
I'm not. You are.
Honey, I am so sorry.
I'm here in Pennsylvania,
and I'm stuck, and I have no excuse.
-And I want everyone to hear it.
-DRIVER: Whoa.
I am a terrible person,
but I want you all to know
-I am sorry, and I love my friend Imogene.
-[HORSE NEIGHS]
You're not a terrible person, Midge.
MIDGE: I am. I am terrible,
and I just have to live with that.
-But I hope you liked the cupcakes.
-IMOGENE: I did.
And the little sugar babies on top.
A little creepy eating
babies, but delicious.
MIDGE: Good.
Oh, your present.
Imogene, you should get your present.
-That's okay.
-No, it's in my bedroom,
but I didn't have a
chance to wrap it yet.
There's a Bendel's bag. Run and get it.
-She's not supposed to run.
-No, I didn't mean she should run.
I'll get it when you're back.
Take a picture for me, Archie?
I didn't bring my camera.
MIDGE: Borrow my father's.
Uh, well, I guess I
shouldn't hold up the party any longer.
Everybody go back to having fun.
Bye, Midge.
And, Midge, it's beautiful.
I'm glad. Bye, everyone.
ALL: Bye.
[THUNDER RUMBLING]
Hey! Hey! What are you doing?
-There's a storm.
-So what?
She has a gig here tonight.
This is Mrs. Maisel.
-You're the singer?
-No.
-She's the comedian.
-Well, sorry.
No one's showing up in this weather.
There's a 50% chance the roof'll cave in.
Call me. We'll rebook for next week.
Sure, we're in Harrisburg all the time.
Can't get enough of that Civil War Museum.
Hey!
-Crap.
-Susie.
-What?
-It's raining.
[SUSIE GROANS]
How does he know no one's coming?
He's an idiot. That's how he knows.
He knows nothing.
Well, then let's stop
dealing with idiots.
Everyone in this idiotic
business is an idiot.
You ever meet someone in show business
who's not an idiot,
then they're an asshole.
It's a business of idiots and assholes.
I could've gone to the shower.
Goddamn it.
Let's go.
-[IGNITION SPUTTERING]
-Oh, come on.
You ever read the Book of Job?
My mom read it to me
every year on my birthday.
-You can put your ass down now.
-Why?
This car isn't going anywhere.
Great.
Well, motel's probably foul, anyway.
This was a big screwup, Susie.
Hey, I didn't force that
guy to close his club.
I didn't break the wiper,
and I definitely didn't make it rain.
So what now?
Walk to the motel?
Sure.
Although we are out of money.
[THUNDER RUMBLING]
[CAR HORNS HONKING]
We'd have beaten the traffic if you knew
how to read a stinkin' map.
We'd have beaten the traffic
if you had woken us up earlier.
What am I, a fucking rooster?
-[HORN HONKS]
-[MAN SHOUTING]
What do you want me to do, asshole?
Half of Jersey is parked in front of me!
God, it's like I have a twin
who's a middle-aged whore.
Hey. I need it to see.
We're gonna die in this tunnel.
Good. Something to look forward to.
No time to shower. What do I do?
You're a comic, not Miss America.
Just go on stage looking like shit.
Oh, so now I look like shit?
What, are we married all of a sudden?
You're my manager, you're
supposed to care how I look.
Wait, wait, Miriam. Look, look.
We're out of Jersey.
-We are?
-That's the line; we crossed the line.
-We're in New York.
We're in New York. We're in New York.
Take that, assholes!
We are back in New York City!
-WOMAN: Shut up!
-[MAN SHOUTING]
Mm.
We will die of old age in this tunnel.
At least place of death
won't be New Jersey.
♪♪
-You, where's Ricky?
-Manager?
-Yes, yes.
-By the bar.
It's a two dollar cover tonight.
-We're talent!
-The what?
I'm… I'm one of the comedians tonight.
Mrs. Maisel?
We got caught in this horrible traffic,
almost ran out of gas
in the Holland Tunnel.
Is there a place where I can…
-Stop talking. Move.
-Hey.
Susie Myerson. Mrs. Maisel.
You're late!
We got stuck in the Holland Tunnel.
-Hey.
-Maisel. Talent.
-Drink.
-I need a mirror.
You look great.
-I should change.
-No time.
-Get right to the good stuff.
-Mm-hmm.
Hit 'em hard and fast.
Good? [GRUNTS]
Tits up.
Hey there, ladies and gentlemen.
What the fuck am I doing? Go.
Just fucking clap.
Magda Goebbels, ladies and gentlemen.
Poisoned her dogs
and all six of her children
in honor of the Fuhrer,
but now hiding in Manhattan
and giving stand-up
comedy management a go.
Thank you, Magda.
So, how ya doing?
How am I doing?
How do I look like I'm doing?
I'm fucking exhausted. And sore.
And late…
I don't mean "my time of the month."
Although I'd prefer an
unplanned pregnancy
-to the day I just had.
-[LAUGHTER]
We almost ran out of
gas in the Holland Tunnel.
That would've been fun.
As if people coming from Jersey
need something else to be angry about.
So I can't tell you how
good it is to be back
-[SUSIE SNORING ON TAPE]
-Shit.
Shit!
[SNORING CONTINUES]
Shit.
-Professional comedy.
-[LAUGHTER]
I'm really glad to be back
in New York City, my home.
Where I have so many friends…
who hate me.
So much family…
who are disappointed in me.
Where my children live…
until they abandon me.
That's why New York is so great, though.
Everyone you care about can despise you
and you can still find a bagel so good,
nothing else matters.
Who needs love when you've got lox?
They both stink but only one tastes good.
[LAUGHTER]
Ladies and gentlemen, fellow assholes,
you've been awfully nice to come home to.
I'm Mrs. Maisel.
Thank you and good night.
[CHEERING AND APPLAUSE]
Hey, what were those weird animal noises
on the tape recorder?
Can we just settle up?
It's been a rough fucking week.
Yeah, we all had a rough week.
Thanks for auditioning;
I'll pay ya next time.
Whoa, whoa, whoa.
This wasn't an audition.
Are we ready to go?
Please say we're ready to go.
-He's not paying us.
-What?
Prick Rick. He's not paying us.
He has to pay us. We have a contract.
We don't have a contract.
Why don't we have a contract?
Because you're doing comedy,
not rezoning the building.
He owes us money.
And I really, really need to shower.
-Yeah. No shit.
-Fuck you.
Wait here.
Hey, tough guy, you pay the
guys and you don't pay the girls?
Listen, you were late,
and no one was drinking.
How do you think we make our money?
-Everybody was drinking.
-And it wasn't a bar deal.
Next time. Go home.
-Clean up.
-Hey.
-Stay here.
-Susie, wait.
We are not leaving without our money.
Stay here and watch the tape recorder.
Shit.
-Susie?
-SUSIE [MUFFLED]: Hey.
[DOORKNOB RATTLING]
Susie, where are you?
-I'm in the janitor's closet.
-Did you get the money?
Oh, yeah, I'm in here
counting it right now.
-Really?
-No. What's wrong with you?
I'm tired, that's what's wrong with me.
How did you get in there?
That psycho shoved me in.
Unlock the door.
I… I think you need a key.
I'm gonna kick his nuts so hard
they're gonna be popping out of his nose.
-I'm calling the police.
-What are you, an idiot?
You don't call cops
to come to a nightclub.
Just give me a minute to think.
That wasn't a minute.
Ow! Fuck!
I did the gig.
We were late, but I killed.
And the asshole just won't pay us.
Because he's an asshole.
And I kicked a door and I
can't leave without Susie.
So I'm stuck.
And I stink, and I scuffed my shoe,
and I broke my toe and I
want my goddamn money.
-What's this asshole's name?
-Susie.
I know Susie; I meant the other asshole.
-Ricky.
-Ricky!
Hey, Ricky!
-MIDGE: That's him.
-What's this?
-You locked her manager in a closet?
-What?
No. It was a joke.
Lighten up.
We're in the comedy business, man.
-Let her out.
-Sheesh.
No sense of humor.
-JOEL: Are you all right?
-Yeah.
-Did he do that?
-What? This?
-Oh, no. The bed ate me. See…
-I don't want to know.
Now pay them.
-She was late.
-Ten minutes.
Doesn't matter. Pay her what you owe her.
So you're her manager.
I'm her manager, Ricky. You know that.
-So who are you?
-JOEL: What's it matter?
I like to know who I'm talking to.
-JOEL: I'm her husband.
-Her husband?
Well, why the fuck don't you keep her…
MIDGE: Joel.
Wherever that sentence was going,
it was gonna end up like that anyway.
A whole new light, pal.
Now pay her what you owe her.
Fine.
You're lucky I don't sue you.
MAN: Hey, your nose is bleeding.
I miss something here?
-You the owner?
-Yeah.
You let guys like that run your business?
-He's my sister's kid.
-Family's nice.
Doesn't mean he can run your business.
Get some people working
for you who respect the talent.
That's talent.
She could put this shithole
on the map someday.
Wake the fuck up.
Yeah, and you also have to
buy your janitor a new plunger.
The one in there is old
and sad and lost its suction.
Sure.
-Is it all there?
-Yup.
Nice doing business with you.
MIDGE: You got to teach
me how to do that one day.
I'm gonna grab a cab home.
You want me to drop you?
No. I started this road trip with Susie
and I kind of want to finish it with her.
Thank you, Joel.
Any time.
You didn't have to call him.
Unfortunately, sometimes to
make things work in a man's world,
you need a man.
That's just the way it is, Susie.
I would have found a
way to take care of it.
You may be some kind of
damsel in distress, but I'm not.
No, you were a damsel in di-closet.
Someday.
Yeah. Someday.
Your commission.
Thanks.
You're counting it? Really?
Force of habit.
What the…
[FOOTSTEPS APPROACHING]
How was Pennsylvania?
-Mama, what happened?
-What happened?
There was a baby shower.
Did you forget again?
Should we have you
checked out by a doctor?
But it was yesterday.
-I mean, where's Zelda?
-Zelda?
Oh, no. It's your mess.
Good night.
["SOMEDAY" BY THE STROKES PLAYING]
♪♪
♪ In many ways ♪
♪ Still miss the good old days ♪
♪ Someday, someday ♪
♪ Yeah, it hurts to say ♪
♪ But I want you to stay ♪
♪ Sometimes, sometimes ♪
♪ When we was young ♪
♪ Oh, man, did we have fun ♪
♪ Always, always ♪
♪ Promises ♪
♪ They break before they're made ♪
♪ Sometimes, sometimes ♪
♪ Oh, my ex says I'm lacking in depth ♪
♪ I will do my best ♪
♪ You say you want to stay by my side ♪
♪ Darling, your head's not right ♪
♪ I say, alone we stand ♪
♪ Together, we fall apart ♪
♪ Yeah, I think I'll be all right ♪
♪ I'm working so I won't
have to try so hard ♪
♪ Tables, they turn sometimes ♪
♪ Oh, someday ♪
♪♪
♪ Now, I ain't wasting no more time ♪
♪ Ooh ♪
♪ Trying, trying ♪