♪♪
[ETHAN HUMMING MELODIC TUNE]
[SIGHS]
ETHAN: Boom, boom, boom, boom.
Boom, boom, boom, boom.
[WATCH TICKING]
[SIGHS]
[HUMMING]
♪♪
ABE: Ethan, no!
These are not toys.
-They look like toys.
-They're not.
Go. Go. Get. Get. Go.
How is this a toy?
♪♪
ROSE: That's everything.
Thank you, Stewart.
MIDGE: Yes, thanks, guys.
Once again, you're our heroes.
Ah, the ever elusive cabana jackets.
How many should we bring?
-Two each.
-Or three.
I've got one more coming from Saks.
It's chinoiserie. You're gonna love it.
Ooh. Bikinis.
You're doing the beauty
contest again, I assume.
I believe my public demands it.
So this year, should I go classy?
Your Doris Day.
-Or risqué?
-Your Mamie Van Doren.
Will any other girl bother to compete?
I wouldn't.
Bring them both, just to be sure.
ABE: You can't bring everything!
Next is clamdiggers.
It's the Catskills; you can't
have too many clamdiggers.
ABE: Yes, you can.
What about picnic dresses?
We each have four.
-Should I bring them all?
-There may be four picnics.
Or you can wear the same picnic
dress to more than one picnic.
-Oh, Abe.
-[LAUGHS] Papa, you're too much.
Ladies, we've been over this.
The trailer has 163 cubic feet of space.
Do you understand?
There's finite capacity.
-Beach robes?
-We never wear them.
-I'll bring them anyway.
-Okay.
D… Did you see what just happened there?
Papa, please do not micromanage this.
We have a system.
Your system is to bring
everything you own.
I'm not bringing this.
It's too late to change
the luggage we've chosen.
I've made precisely scaled models.
Your little toys.
-They're not toys.
-They're cute.
They're cute, yes, but they're not toys.
And right now, after much effort,
all our tiny luggage
fits in our tiny trailer.
He's adorable when he
talks about these things.
Papa, we will do our best
to stick to 160 cubic feet.
-I promise.
-Good.
This way, I can create a plan
so that my boy Jimmy at the resort knows
how to load it back up
at the end of our stay.
You got Jimmy as your
boy again this year?
I thought he couldn't come back.
Yeah, he thought he was doing
an internship at a big law firm,
but I made a couple of
calls, and now he's not.
Abe, you did not spoil
that young man's future
just so he can be your
boy again in the Catskills.
What? No.
I called and found out he didn't get it.
I was heartbroken for him.
I wouldn't do that to Jimmy.
I love Jimmy.
-Mm-hmm.
-A little too much.
-Scale down, please.
-We're scaling. Go.
-Yes, go, Abe.
-I'm supposed to have lunch with a friend.
-Okay if I scoot?
-ABE: Ethan, no!
-Do not play with these toys.
-Sure, go. We'll finish later.
ABE: I didn't mean toys.
They're not toys.
-I won't be long. Thank you, Zelda.
-ABE: It was a misnomer.
You know what a misnomer is.
No, no. Don't play dumb.
These club owners
call me back in a flash.
Sometimes I hear 'em
yell, "Take a message,"
and when they hear it's me
on the phone, they take the call.
-That's respect.
-For me. I mean, look at me.
-They're respecting me.
-I'm looking at you.
Alone, I am a spittoon;
with you, I'm a somebody.
That's not true, Susie. They respect you
because they fear you;
you're great at what you do.
Mm, half of them respect me, maybe.
The other half want to get in your pants.
-Oh, stop.
-It's gonna happen. I mean, look at you.
It's like a dollop of
whipped cream grew a head.
Just don't undercut
yourself; that's all I'm saying.
So you called this lunch.
What do you want to talk about?
I just wanted to touch base
before I go to the Catskills.
-We leave tomorrow.
-Cool.
God, it's gonna be so
nice to have a break.
This past year has been tough.
They're leaving.
Hurry, hurry.
We're switching tables, Verla!
Oh, here.
-What's this?
-Gigs.
My typewriter lost its "S."
That's why it says "Aturday," "Unday."
You went to college;
you can figure it out.
These are all in the next two weeks.
-So?
-I'm going to the Catskills.
-Yeah, you said.
-So I can't do these.
I'm going to the Catskills.
First one's not till a week after next.
But I'm going to the Catskills.
Yeah, your record's skippin', missy.
Get to the point.
I'm going to the
Catskills for two months.
-Wha…
-Geez, I almost did a spit take.
Almost? That was a fucking spit take.
You're going to the
Catskills for two months?
I told you a million times I
was going to the Catskills.
Yeah, but I figured
it was five days, tops,
not two fucking months.
I think you got the
guy in back of me, too.
What the hell do you do
up there for two months?
-Lots of things.
-What things?
You look at a tree, you go to bed,
you get up, you look at a tree.
You gonna do that for
two straight months?
What the fuck is going on up there?
There's activities.
We go boating, we sunbathe.
What do you do for the summer?
I stay here. And I sweat.
And I smell like a bum.
And I'm miserable,
and I want to kill people.
And I do that till it gets cold.
But the whole city empties out in summer.
Why the hell are we having
lunch if not to figure out
our game plan for the next two months?
I don't know, I just…
wanted to say goodbye.
Say goodbye, like we're friends?
-Yes.
-Oh, my God.
How many times do I have to say this?
We are coworkers, not friends.
Want some proof?
Look, no friendship ring. Case closed.
-Okay, okay.
-And I would like you
to start treating me more professionally.
Like keeping me in the loop.
I mean, two months away
is gonna kill our momentum.
A heads-up would've been nice.
I'm sorry.
I thought I gave you a heads-up.
-Yeah, yeah.
-WAITRESS: There you go, ladies.
-What is that?
-Nothing.
Miriam.
What is it?
It's a ring.
-Holy fuck.
-But it is not a friendship ring.
Eat your sandwich.
It's just a ring I saw at the store.
It was on sale.
I thought you would like it.
-Two months.
-Plus, I get a 20% discount.
-It's not that big a deal.
-Eat, eat.
-Is it gold or silver?
-What?
The ring, is it gold or silver?
Silver.
You don't seem like a gold person.
I'll take a look at it.
Later.
I can take it back.
Two months.
♪♪
Everything's gonna fit!
My miniatures were spot on.
-I still got it!
-ROSE: Good for you, Abe!
Let's go. We want to beat the traffic.
Such a beautiful day for a drive.
MIDGE: Where's the baby?
ROSE: I've got the baby, Miriam.
-Hurry, Mommy!
-Don't run, Ethan.
Goodbye, Zelda. We'll miss you.
I'll miss you, too, Miss Miriam.
We're going to the Catskills!
♪ Let's take a trip in a trailer ♪
♪ No need to come back at all ♪
♪ Oh, let's take a powder ♪
♪ To Boston for chowder ♪
♪ Let's get away from it all ♪
[LAUGHTER]
-♪ Let's go again to Niagara ♪
-♪ Do-do-do ♪
♪ This time we'll look at the falls ♪
-♪ Do-do-do-do-do ♪
-♪ Oh, let's get away ♪
♪ From it all… ♪
-[PAULY CHUCKLING]
-♪ Let's get away from it all. ♪
-Mr. Weissman!
-[CAR DOORS CLOSING]
Oh, you look thin.
Hello, Pauly. How have you been?
Can't complain. Ladies!
-Welcome back to Steiner Mountain Resort.
-[ABE SIGHS]
-Your home away from home.
-Hi, Pauly.
-Oh, good to see you, Pauly.
-[ABE CHUCKLES]
It's your 27th year in a row, I believe.
Your stats are correct, dear sir.
Oh, smell that mountain air.
Invigorating.
There's plenty more where that came from.
Oh, here's Kent.
He'll be your kid camp coordinator.
His name's actually David,
but we wanted to keep the K-sound thing.
-Uh-huh.
-Hi, everybody.
-Hi, Kent.
-Hi, Ethan.
It's potty and playtime. You ready to go?
-Yeah!
-[LAUGHTER]
We'll take him from here. Let's go!
-Come on inside, gang.
-Bye, Mommy!
-Let's get you all settled in.
-All right.
KENT: Run, everybody, run!
[KIDS SCREAMING PLAYFULLY]
-[LIVELY CHATTER]
-[PHONES RINGING]
I'm assuming you worked
up a thirst on your journey,
-Mr. Weissman?
-That I did.
Our signature Steiner tomato juice.
Homemade and frosted to perfection.
I've been hankering for it since August.
-Ah.
-Mm.
[SIGHS] It's the very taste of vacation.
-Ah.
-Mr. Weissman.
We have you in your
usual cottage by the lake.
If I could just get you to
sign a couple of forms for me.
Ooh, with blood or a pen?
[LAUGHTER]
Mr. Weissman, you should be on the stage.
-A pen will do.
-Ah.
And keep the pen.
MIDGE: Three-legged race.
-You're on.
-Goodbye, ladies.
-Hello, Midge.
-Gabi. Good to see you.
-How are the kids?
-Happy and healthy.
And how far along in the process are you?
-The process?
-With him.
-Joel?
-[GROWLS]
Oh, well, it's all kind of new,
and we're still figuring it out.
He'll actually be up here later today.
-Really?
-Yeah.
Why?
Well, the kids are
his, and he likes them,
so he'll be coming back
and forth from the city.
How modern.
So I'll see you two ladies at the salon?
-Yes, you will.
-Mm-hmm.
Goodbye, Gabi.
Oh, God. Is this what it's gonna be?
[GROANS]: Grr.
-There you go.
-PAULY: Okay.
Now that you're all signed
in, let me introduce you
to your boy for the summer, Mr. Weissman.
Oh, well, no introduction necessary.
-I raised Jimmy from a pup.
-Oh, it's not Jimmy.
This is Samuel.
He's one of my best young boys.
What happened to Jimmy?
Good news. There were some stumbles,
but he was finally accepted
to the internship he wanted.
-Isn't that great?
-But I…
Good for Jimmy.
I'm at your service, Mr. Weissman.
Your hand is wet.
MALE ANNOUNCER
[OVER PA]: Attention, guests.
Just a reminder that
orientation in the main hall
is one hour away. See you there.
You know the way, friends.
Bring everything in the trailer,
and there's a couple
of things in the trunk.
There's a baby in the
backseat, Mr. Weissman.
Bring that, too!
SAMUEL: Right.
ABE: Ah, that beautiful lake!
[DOOR CREAKS]
-Good morning.
-Ah, gentlemen.
-I'll take this one.
-I'm right here, Mr. Weissman.
MIDGE: Whew!
It needs to air out a little.
ABE: Come on, guys. Hustle, hustle.
ROSE: All the furniture's
in the wrong place.
-MIDGE: We'll move it around.
-ABE: I left a diagram
-for them last time.
-Well, they know how we like it.
-It should've been ready.
-MIDGE: Those go to
the second bedroom! The one on the left.
ABE: The screen door needs adjusting.
SAMUEL: I can do that for you, sir.
ABE: Or someone from the proper
department can fix this, Jimmy.
-It needs to be done right.
-MIDGE: Sorry, I meant right, not left.
-Right. Right.
-SAMUEL: Right. Right.
ROSE: Abe, make sure the
windows are open upstairs.
-ABE: Right, got it.
-MIDGE: There's no room for this.
ROSE: Just wedge it in, then
move that piece over here.
No, no, don't put it on the couch.
ABE: There's new carpeting on the stairs.
MIDGE: Put it back, guys.
We've got to figure this out.
ROSE: I've already figured this out.
MIDGE: You just put
the couch on the chair.
ROSE: This is more
luggage than last year.
It's way more.
ABE: Oh, beautiful day.
ROSE: The luggage is
piling up in the kitchen.
MIDGE: Oh, watch the lamp!
Watch the lamp!
-Was this tree here last year?
-SAMUEL: Which tree?
-I think it was there, Papa.
-ABE: I don't remember
-this big tree being there.
-ROSE: Oh, there's an extra chair in here.
SAMUEL: Can I help you
with the tree, Mr. Weissman?
ABE: How could you
possibly help me with the tree?
Explain yourself.
MIDGE: Ah, I forgot Esther's doll.
-ROSE: Which one?
-Betsy Wetsy. I knew I forgot something.
ROSE: We'll have Jimmy
run out for a new doll.
MIDGE: That'll wet itself?
It has to wet itself.
ABE: What's the couch doing outside?
-ROSE: It's just temporary!
-ELIANA: Oh, Midge.
-ABE: It'll get dirty out here.
-Oh, sorry about Joel, Midge.
MIDGE: It's okay, Eliana.
-Are you devastated?
-Fresh tomato juice, sir?
You were getting luggage; now
you're bringing me tomato juice?
ELIANA: Oh, good, good, you
should move on. Such a cad.
MIDGE: There's one too
many cooks in the kitchen.
ROSE: There's a cook in the kitchen?
-Watch out!
-ABE: Oh!
[GLASS BREAKS]
-ABE: Jimmy!
-ROSE: There's tomato juice everywhere!
-SAMUEL: I'll get a mop!
-Oh, Abe.
-MIDGE: Where's the towel?
-We need some help here.
ABE: And he forgot the baby.
Jimmy, bring a mop and the baby.
-MIDGE: Why is the couch outside?
-ROSE: I don't know.
I think the layout in there works.
I think it works, too.
And I think it's exactly the
way it was when we got here.
-But I think we've proven that it's right.
-Mm.
-All situated, ladies?
-Yes, Pauly, thank you.
Abe's upstairs. I'll get him for you.
Abe!
Actually, I'm here to talk to Miriam.
-Mind if I sit?
-No. Pauly, please.
MALE ANNOUNCER [OVER PA]: Carl Finger.
Paging Carl Finger.
Not an emergency, but not
not an emergency, either.
Now, orientation is in a few minutes,
-so I don't want to keep you long.
-Sure. What's up?
[CLEARS THROAT] It's about
the swimsuit competition.
-Mm, the Mrs. Steiner Pageant?
-What about it?
We're all aware of your record, Miriam.
What a feat: eight wins in a
row in three different categories.
And you get lovelier every
year, just like your mother.
-Oh.
-But this year, I think we have
a new and exciting proposition for you.
-Fun. What is it?
-Sash girl.
Sash girl?
But the sash girl doesn't compete.
She just hands the sash to the winner.
-That's right.
-But what if I win?
I hand the sash to myself?
The photograph will look ridiculous.
Look, you've competed as a teen,
as an ingénue, and in
the Mrs. Steiner Pageant
these past four years, but
this year, we're hard-pressed
to make the argument that
you are any of those things.
Not after the recent
change in your situation.
But I'm technically still married.
Yes, but the Mrs. Steiner
Swimsuit Pageant winner
is always accompanied by her husband.
And having him there with you…
might cast a pall.
-I see.
-But of course we want you there,
and that's why we'd like
you to enjoy the honor
of handing the sash
to this year's winner.
But what about the weird old lady
who always hands out the sash?
That would be my grandmother.
Sorry. Won't she be disappointed?
-She passed.
-So I guess she won't mind.
I appreciate your understanding.
And on the bright side,
you're free to load up
on rice pudding tonight.
[CHUCKLES] See you at orientation.
Hershey?
I just got kicked out of
the swimsuit pageant.
That does it.
You're definitely wearing
the Mamie Van Doren.
ANNOUNCER [OVER PA]:
Paging Leon Zigglestein.
Please come get your
wallet at the front desk.
Mr. Leon Zigglestein.
-[LIVELY CHATTER]
-Ah.
PAULY: Let's all grab seats, everybody.
We'll begin here in a minute.
Miriam Maisel.
Alya Feinburg, good to see you.
-You, too.
-And how's Marv?
Uh, I can't get him off the links.
A widow to golf, and yet so young.
I thought we should touch
base about this thing with Joel.
-All right.
-The four of us have spent
so much time together
up here, playing charades,
the bowling team,
all the stuff friends do.
-Yes?
-Well, Marv and I
[WHISPERS]: discussed it,
and we were pretty much in agreement that
he's actually a better friend
of Joel's than I am of yours.
-Okay. I get it.
-So…
We'll still run into each other.
Buffet line, bathroom.
-I'm glad you understand.
-Mm-hmm.
So are you changing your name?
-To Zippy Maisel.
-Really?
-No.
-You're fun.
-Just not as fun as Joel.
-Bye.
PAULY: All right, here we go.
-Good afternoon, my beauties!
-CROWD: Hi, Pauly!
Now, most of you know
me, but for those who don't,
I'm Pauly Auerbach, just
beginning my 18th fabulous year
as your Steiner executive director.
And, oh, boy, I'm gonna
have a heart attack
from all the exciting activities
we got planned for you this season!
[CROWD CHEERING]
Now, each of you
will find a Steiner
newsletter under your seat,
Issue Number One for 1959.
And if you think you
notice a fun new font,
you're not wrong. Good eye.
Oh, finally!
I hated the old font, hated it.
PAULY: In it is a map of the property,
some things you need
to know, and of course
a list of upcoming
activities for the week.
And here's hoping
that our returning guests
will take all you
newcomers under their wing
to give them the lay of the land,
and to show them what's
mud and what's bear bleep.
[LAUGHTER]
Now, there is a young man here
that a lot of you already know and love,
our entertainment
director, Buzz Goldberg.
Come on up and take the mic, Buzz.
Hello, Steinerites!
How's everybody doing?
[CROWD CHEERING]
You all may not have met
me, but you know what I do:
-I manufacture fun.
-[CROWD MURMURS EXCITEDLY]
And it seems like I could
whip up a little right now.
-What do you say?
-[CHEERING]
Hey, now, what are all these
employees doing standing around?
Get on up here and help me lead the group
in the "Steiner Resort Welcome Song."
[CROWD WHOOPING]
[PLAYS NOTE]
One, two, three, four.
[TO "CAROLINA IN THE MORNING"]
♪ Nothing could be finer ♪
♪ Than to spend the day
at Steiner in the summer ♪
Ah, you remember it!
♪ Nothing much convinces
like the taste of Steiner blintzes ♪
♪ In the summer ♪
Just the girls now.
♪ Play all day and dance all night ♪
-Now the boys.
-♪ All us happy Israelites… ♪
[JOSH CONTINUES HOLDING NOTE]
Oh, boy.
Looks like we have a note challenge.
-CROWD: Note challenge!
-The resort record
for holding that last note is 42 seconds.
Let's see how he does, folks.
[CONTINUES HOLDING NOTE]
I hit some traffic.
Did I miss the bear shit joke?
-Yes, you did.
-Ah, hell.
This guy's an amateur.
-♪ …ites. ♪
-[CROWD CHEERS]
Ah, not a record,
but a heck of an effort.
-Good try, Josh.
-[APPLAUSE]
-[CHUCKLES]
-[PLAYS NOTE]
♪ So skip the luxury liner ♪
♪ To enjoy a schvitz at
Steiner in the summer ♪
ALL [CHANTING]: Steiner! Steiner!
-Steiner!
-[FEET STOMPING RHYTHMICALLY]
We're finer! Finer! Finer!
-How's it going here since you arrived?
-Steiner. Steiner.
-Fine, I guess.
-[CROWD CONTINUES CHANTING]
-Anybody mention anything about…
-Us? Oh, yeah.
Me, too.
I was here ten minutes, and I
got corralled by three people.
I've gotten it all day.
They even kicked me
out of the swimsuit pageant
'cause I'm no longer a missus.
-What?
-I get to be sash girl.
But sash girl just hands out the sash.
Pauly has spoken.
Steiner!
Good job! Applaud yourselves, everyone!
[CROWD CHEERING]
Anything I can get for you, Mr. Weissman?
PAULY: Thank you, Buzz. Great job.
You'll never be Jimmy.
PAULY: Now, friends, last
year there was some kvetching
that the resort was short on
certain recreation equipment.
Well, listen to me and
listen to me carefully.
This year, there will be more hula hoops.
-WOMAN: Yeah!
-There will be
-more floaties.
-[WHOOPING, CLAPPING]
And there will be more balls!
[CROWD CHEERING]
JOEL: Nothing to see here, Asher!
PAULY: On a happier note,
let's wish all our
newlyweds mazel tov, yes?
Some of whom met right
here at Steiner Mountain Resort
and made a blessed, lifelong commitment.
Are you kidding me?
There's Izzy and Enid Schulburg.
Neil and Phyllis Cohen.
And Allie and Taavi Applebaum,
who met playing shuffleboard.
To all our happy couples,
may you have life, luck,
and lots of little Steinerites!
[APPLAUSE]
What are you doing?
Hey, Steiner guests,
can I get your attention?
Sorry, Pauly. This'll just take a second.
Most of you know me. Joel Maisel.
And an awful lot of you are staring at me.
And Midge.
Now, you know what happened to us.
We're separated, okay?
But we're still close.
Our families are close.
And we love our kids,
and they both love us,
so everything's fine.
Really, there's nothing to stare at here.
You can still be friends with me, or not.
And you can still be
friends with Midge, or not.
It's up to you.
And, Pauly, shame on
you for not letting Midge
in the Mrs. Steiner Swimsuit Pageant.
She's eight years a
champion and a huge draw,
and every $25 award she won,
she donated to an
orphans home in the Bronx.
So this year, thanks to you,
some orphans are going hungry.
[CROWD MURMURS]
So we're clear? Yes?
-[MAN COUGHS]
-Good.
So, have fun, everybody.
See you dockside.
PAULY: Always expect the unexpected
here at Steiner Mountain Resort.
Well, you know what I always say.
Abi gezunt!
-Everybody! Abi?
-CROWD: Gezunt!
PAULY: Well, that's all that's
on the docket, everybody.
[APPLAUSE]
So enjoy your summer, enjoy your stay,
because before you
know it, it'll be over.
I'll see you tonight.
MALE ANNOUNCER:
Steinerites, the pool is now open.
Remember, we have our
salon appointments later.
-I will be there.
-Mm-hmm.
-So what building are you in?
-Hmm?
What building?
Are you north side, south side?
-Oh, shit.
-What?
-I don't have a room.
-You don't have a room?
I'm always in the cottage
with you and your parents,
so it didn't even occur
to me to book one.
Still getting used to
some things, I guess.
Well, go see if they
have something available.
I heard people talking.
There's a gigantic waiting list.
Such an idiot. Guess I'll go back.
Don't go back. You just got here.
I could throw myself
on the mercy of Pauly,
but I don't think he's my
closest friend right now.
Look, just stay on our sun
porch till you figure it out.
Really?
Ethan can sleep out there with you.
He'll love it.
Will your parents love it?
They'll be fine. I'll make it fine.
Okay. Thanks.
MALE ANNOUNCER
[OVER PA]: Attention, guests.
Tonight's vodka and latke mixer will be
in the rec room at 8 p.m.
The ladies just headed out to the salon.
Yeah, Rose told me that
was where they were heading.
Abe… I promise I won't be in your way.
I'll store my stuff under the staircase.
You'll never see it.
You'll hardly know I'm here.
It's fine, Joel.
Sorry, with everything going on,
booking a room just slipped my mind.
Ah, it's fine, really.
A room will open up soon enough.
Anything else?
Look, Joel, up here in the mountains,
I do… different kinds of things.
You drink a lot of tomato juice.
Not just the tomato juice.
I have a morning routine.
Every day, before the sun's
up, when everyone's asleep,
I do my special outdoor calisthenics.
I didn't know that.
And I wear special clothing.
And now that you're down here,
you're bound to see me when I head out.
-Special clothing?
-A romper, Joel.
-I wear a romper.
-What's a romper?
It's a one-piece exercise outfit.
Oh.
Very tight-fitting, and
no one has seen me in it,
not even Rose.
But now, you may see me in it.
You should be prepared.
Okay.
Anything else?
I'm wondering if I should
put it on and show it to you.
-Oh, no, Abe, no.
-Just so we can get beyond it.
I really don't think that's necessary.
-You haven't seen it.
-I sleep very deeply.
Really, don't even think about me.
Okay. I'll try not to.
[SLURPS LOUDLY]
MALE ANNOUNCER [OVER PA]:
Ladies, Chef Seymour Silver invites you
to join him in the trailside lounge
at 2:15 for a garniture demonstration.
That's 2:15 in the trailside lounge.
You know, he hypnotized her
at the mesmerism show last year,
and to this day, she
still clucks like a chicken
-when you clap your hands.
-No.
-[MIDGE LAUGHS]
-All that clucking at orientation,
that was Lottie Friedman.
I'll give her this, she
clucks on the beat.
[LAUGHTER]
Oh, you see Saul over there?
-ROSE: Oh, dear.
-EDIE: You know, his wife died.
Yes, a tragedy.
Well, she's not dead three months
when he turns around
and marries her kid sister.
Joanie?
But the man is still on
the prowl; look at him.
At the "End of Summer" soirée last year,
he danced with Leah Bernstein.
And when he pressed up against her,
she could feel his excitement.
Oh, kind of wishing you hadn't said that.
It may have been a pocketknife.
[CHUCKLES]: Yes, a pocketknife!
Well, I'll see you two tonight.
My God, you look like sisters.
-If only. See you tonight, Edie.
-Bye, Edie.
Let's get you to the dryers, ladies.
Mama, thanks for letting Joel
stay with us for a few nights.
He got stuck, and I
want him to see the kids.
Oh, it was fine.
I'll get you some lemonade.
It was very nice what
he did at the orientation.
Surprisingly manly.
Let's hope it stops all this silliness.
From your lips.
Relationships should be private.
-Don't you think?
-Amen.
So, are you dating?
-What?
-Are you dating?
What's your dating life? I know nothing.
I guess my dating life
doesn't get to be private.
You're just out late so
often, what else would it be?
Well, as a matter of fact,
yes, I am dating a little bit.
Anyone I know?
Anyone from the neighborhood?
No, I'm kind of just getting around.
I mean, not "getting around."
It's just that I'm not being
geographically snobby.
-You know?
-I guess.
I'm kind of hitting all five boroughs.
Well, that doesn't seem right.
Don't your friends have
anyone to set you up with?
-Nope.
-Not even that little blonde thing
that talks all high and chirpy?
Imogene.
Nope, all her friends are Gentiles.
Oh. Well, tell me about these
Jewish men you're seeing,
like that man that gave you the fur coat.
-Fur coat?
-You wore it to synagogue last year.
-What is he, a furrier?
-No, a trapper.
But it was a short-lived thing.
He was a little Paul Bunyan for my taste.
-You dated a trapper?
-And a cab driver.
-You didn't.
-And a carny.
I actually met the carny, oddly enough,
because the date with
the cab driver was so awful
I told him to let me out of the car,
and we were in Coney
Island, and I got out,
and there was the carny.
-My God.
-So he and I had a drink.
And it was nice. And he introduced me
to his sister, Koo Koo the Bird Girl,
but I thought, "Where could this go?"
Koo Koo was nice, but
I don't want to end up
living in a circus tent.
-Is this a joke?
-It's the truth.
Are you intimate with any of these men?
Oh, no, it hasn't gotten that far.
-But, Miriam, when…
-Mm, sorry, Mama.
If I don't start now,
my hair will never dry,
and I'll be late picking
up Esther from the sitter.
Pick it up, Goldie.
I'm glad we talked, though.
It's been weighing on me.
Okay, but I'm gonna keep
on the lookout for you. Okay?
[DRYER WHIRRING]
What?
[LOUDER] I'm gonna be
on the lookout for a man.
Fine.
♪♪
♪ The way you hold your knife ♪
♪ The way we danced till 3:00 ♪
♪ The way you changed my life ♪
♪ No, no, they can't
take that away from me ♪
♪ No, they can't take that away… ♪
What are you doing, Papa?
Yes, Abe, please tell me
you didn't bring homework.
This is my Catskills
alcohol-consumption index.
I drink more up here,
but I've devised a system
to keep from getting tipsy.
Takes into account food
consumption, time frame,
total alcohol intake.
Here, verify this for me.
Drink number one: a Napoleon, 7:30.
Napoleon reported for duty at 7:30.
Check.
Drink number two: a Tom Collins, 8:15.
Tom Collins made the list at 8:15.
Now it's 9:15,
and I'm just finishing my gin rickey
with absolutely no
sign of "abbleebliation."
I'm sorry. No sign of what?
"Abeebalation."
Why is that so hard to say?
Because you are totally "abeebalated."
♪ Can't take that away ♪
♪ From me ♪
[APPLAUSE]
Ken Washington and his
Swinging Lamplighters, everybody.
Making their ninth annual appearance
-at Steiner Mountain Resort.
-[APPLAUSE]
Hope everybody enjoyed
the sheet cake for dessert.
I know I did.
I didn't think it tasted
like sheet at all.
[LAUGHTER]
-So corny.
-And how.
[LAUGHING] That's hysterical.
So, now put on your dancing shoes
and get ready to swing
with Ken and the band.
Ken, what do you say, daddio?
Do what you do so well.
[CHEERING]
[WHISTLE BLOWING]
Hold it. Hey, hold it.
Ken starts playing
and folks start dancing?
[CHUCKLES] It's too easy, no?
No, tradition calls
for having a little fun
with the first dance, right, everybody?
-Dance challenge.
-Get up, get up, get up.
-BUZZ: That's right.
It's time for a dance challenge.
And here is your
challenge: You don't dance
unless you find a partner that has
-wait for it…
-[WOMAN LAUGHS]
wait for it
-wait for it…
-ABE: Tell us already, farty!
[QUIET LAUGHTER]
Uh, here it is:
Your dance partner must have
first and last initials
that match your own.
-Otherwise, you don't dance.
-[CROWD EXCLAIMING]
An "Initial Dance."
-BUZZ: Are you ready?
-Yes!
Then let the Initial Dance begin!
[LIVELY DANCE MUSIC BEGINS]
-Ooh, M.M.
-M.M.
Marvin Mueller.
No, Mitzi Mossberg
has already grabbed him.
Ooh, damn. Who else, who else?
Menashe Morgenstein. Where's he?
-Oh, on a kibbutz.
-Fucker.
-Dance with Sheldon Babiatz.
-No, not the concept, Papa.
Shoot, they're going fast.
Ooh, Marty Micklestein, 12 o'clock.
His name's not Marty, it's Buddy.
No, his name's Marty, but
everybody calls him Buddy.
That's why he's still available. Go, go!
Damn you, Molly Mencher.
Ah! Michael Mussbaum, right?
-It's Nussbaum.
-[GROANS]
Morty Mermelstein.
-Oh, excuse me. Coming through.
-[WOMAN LAUGHS]
Ah! Sorry, Malca.
Okay, Morty, let's see what you got.
BUZZ: Gorgeous, everybody.
Now let's mix it up a little.
Guys, cut in and dance with
the beauty of your choice.
It was a pleasure, Morty.
-Whoa! Too close?
-[GRUNTS]
Uh, any closer, I'd be
on the other side of you.
Yeah.
So, did you hear I married Aunt Joan?
My kids call her Aunt Joan.
I just call her Joan.
-Mazel tov, Saul.
-[CHUCKLES]
Oh, hey, Feivish.
-What's wrong?
-Do you know Marnie?
The cutie from Canarsie? Sure.
She won't even look at
me no matter what I do.
-And what are you doing?
-Nothing.
Oh, Feivish. What am I gonna do with you?
Talk to her? Be the go-between?
It's a big mitzvah to make a shidduch.
-Let me see what I can do.
-Thanks, Miriam.
Oh. [CHUCKLES]
-[SQUEALS]
-Oh, look at you.
-You're a dervish.
-Mr. Fuchtwanger.
Back for another
go-around at Steiner, huh?
What's the Steiner Daily Newsletter
without its resident gossip columnist?
-Mm.
-You ready? Blind item.
-Hit me with it.
-What doyenne of Brooklyn Heights
still bears the scars of
recent breast augmentation?
-No idea.
-Nellie Abromowitz.
It was a blind item.
You weren't supposed to say.
I'm such a bitch!
Oh, been there, done that. Sorry, Morty.
Ooh, Marnie, you know
Feivish Feldstein, right?
-A little.
-He likes you, a lot.
-He never looks at me.
-He's young and shy
and a little stupid, but he's sweet,
and he's pining for you,
and right now he's propped
against a pillar pretending
not to stare at you.
-Give him a shot?
-Here goes nothing.
-[LAUGHTER, LIVELY CHATTER]
-[DANCE MUSIC CONTINUES]
[WOMEN WHOOPING]
Ooh, kiddo, your palms really do get wet.
Could you do me a favor, Mrs. Maisel?
Could you put in a good
word for me with your father?
-I'll do what I can, Samuel.
-Just tell him
that the scuff on his suitcase was there
before I picked it up, I swear.
-I will.
-I checked it against the miniatures.
-I'll do what I can.
-Thank you, ma'am.
Ooh, that makes me sound old.
-Ooh, some pocketknife.
-Just heard you'd been banned
from the swimsuit pageant, Miriam.
Word travels fast.
Golly, I'm gonna miss
seeing you in your bikini.
Time to go back to Aunt Joan, Saul.
[MUSIC ENDS]
-Oh.
-Hi.
-Well, hello there.
-[SLOW DANCE MUSIC BEGINS]
Thought we'd confuse
the hell out of everybody.
Let's do it.
♪ I stand at your gate ♪
♪ And the song that I
sing is of moonlight ♪
♪ I stand and I wait ♪
♪ For the touch of your hand ♪
♪ In the June night ♪
♪ The roses are sighing ♪
♪ A moonlight serenade… ♪
ABE [SLURRING]: ♪ He always sings ♪
♪ Raggedy music to
the cattle as he swings… ♪
I'm in no condition to drive.
[CHUCKLES] Luckily, you don't
have to drive tonight, Abe.
The state of New York
will thank us for that.
♪ Back and forward in
the saddle on his horse ♪
-♪ A pretty good horse ♪
-[WHISPERS] Thanks, Midge.
♪ With syncopated gait… ♪
-[CRICKETS CHIRPING]
-[BIRDS CALLING]
[DOOR CLOSES]
[FOOTSTEPS APPROACHING]
["CHICKEN FAT" BY ROBERT PRESTON PLAYING]
♪ Touch down every morning, ten times ♪
♪ Not just now and then ♪
♪ Give that chicken
fat back to the chicken ♪
♪ And don't be chicken again ♪
♪ No, don't be chicken again ♪
♪ Ready ♪
-♪ Touch down, up, down ♪
-♪ Touch down every morning ♪
-♪ Ten times, hut, four ♪
-♪ Not just now and then ♪
-♪ Hut, five, hut ♪
-♪ Give that chicken fat ♪
-♪ Six, hut ♪
-♪ Back to the chicken ♪
-♪ Seven, hut, eight ♪
-♪ And don't be chicken again ♪
-♪ Hut, nine, hut ♪
-♪ No, don't be chicken a… ♪
♪ Beautiful girl ♪
♪ You're a lovely picture ♪
♪ You're a gorgeous mixture ♪
♪ Of all that lies ♪
♪ Under the big, blue skies ♪
♪ My heart cries ♪
♪ Beautiful girl ♪
♪ You're a dazzling eyeful… ♪
It's a competitive
field this year, people.
Every bathing beauty before
you is a potential winner,
but only one walks
away with the $25 prize.
Each husband as proud as the next.
Each contestant beautifully
representing Steiner Resort.
[SCATTERED APPLAUSE]
And this year, the
winner of the Mrs. Steiner
Swimsuit Pageant is…
-Talia Goldstein.
-[CROWD CHEERING]
Oh, my gosh! Oh, my gosh!
♪ Beautiful girl. ♪
-[CAMERA CLICKS]
-Wrong girl.
Thanks for coming, everyone.
Don't forget, the Miss Ingénue
Pageant happens at 3:00.
When we say the scenery's lovely here,
we're not kidding. [CHUCKLES]
-See you then.
-[APPLAUSE]
A bunch of us are gonna sunbathe, Miriam.
Want to join?
Sure. Just let me grab my magazines.
I left 'em all in the car.
-See you in a bit.
-Mm-hmm.
-Hi, Frieda. Nice to see you.
-Hey, Midge.
-Susie?
-What the fuck are you wearing?
What the hell are you doing here?
My question first.
It's my Mamie Van Doren.
You constantly astonish me.
I repeat, what are you doing here?
Well, my star/only
client decides to go off
and spend the fucking
summer up in the land
of canoes and knishes,
and I couldn't just let
things stop, so I came up
to look for a gig for you up here
on the off chance… [GRUNTS]
[COUGHS] I ate a bug.
-Happens a lot.
-[GROANS]
It's in my throat. It's still moving.
Susie, I can't play gigs up here, okay?
Everybody knows me.
[COUGHS] Don't worry, there's
hundreds of places up here.
A lot of them are shit,
but some of them have
pretty good rooms;
that's what I'm aiming for.
But how would I do this?
I'm here on vacation.
[RASPS] You'll slip out,
just like you've been doing
for most of the year… no big deal.
Oh. Well… you got any leads?
[SIGHS] Friends at the Stage
Deli are lending a hand.
It's not easy breaking
through, but I'm trying.
-What is that?
-Ah.
It's my ticket in, sister.
My magic pass to this godforsaken place.
-How so?
-All I have to do is
walk around holding this thing,
everyone thinks I work here.
-It's genius.
-But how will you eat?
-Where are you staying?
-Let me worry about that.
You just wait for my call. Be ready.
-I'll be ready.
-And if I don't book you,
at the very least, I'll have made…
[GROANS] Shit! I ate another bug.
-Go get something to drink.
-Ah!
It's mating with the other one.
-Really, a little bit of water.
-God, I hate nature.
-[DRYERS WHIRRING]
-IDA: They never found the body.
EDIE: They did too
find Glenn Miller's body.
-IDA: No!
-Yeah!
He was still holding his trombone.
[CONVERSATION CONTINUES QUIETLY]
IDA: Did you see that
Tony Curtis said that
kissing Marilyn Monroe
was like kissing Hitler?
Kissing Hitler?
How would Tony Curtis know
what kissing Hitler was like?
I don't know. He said it, not me.
He had such thin lips.
-Tony Curtis?
-Adolf Hitler.
His lips were almost nonexistent.
Maybe that's why he was
so angry, do you think?
I don't like thinking about
that man; he was awful.
Speaking of awful, did you see
Gladys has a hair appointment on Tuesday?
But her husband's a weekender.
He won't be here till Friday.
Oh? Who's she getting all
dolled up for if not for him?
She's been playing an
awful lot of tennis lately.
-The tennis pro?
-You said it, not me.
I'm getting tired of people
hopping around from bed to bed.
Tony Curtis, Gladys Lipschitz.
Stay in one place. It's exhausting.
Oh, please.
If my son would just stay with a girl
for more than two dates, I'd plotz.
-Benjamin?
-No one is good enough for him.
Lovely girls from good families.
They cook. They're sweet as pie.
They don't laugh too
loud or talk too loud.
"They're too normal," he says.
"They're boring."
Boring? What's that?
All my friends have grandchildren,
and here I am with
nothing on the horizon.
And he's such a catch.
A doctor, handsome.
He's so handsome.
But he says he wants someone interesting,
someone unique… get this, someone weird.
Weird!
I've got the perfect girl for him.
Mink is the ultimate way for your husband
to say, "I love you."
It's the most popular
fur and will last for years.
Very durable.
Raccoon fur is similar
to mink in that it's durable,
and the color scheme is
unique and stands out in a crowd.
Note this, ladies: it is better to buy
a luxurious raccoon
than a poor-quality mink.
Now, let's talk about coordinating muffs.
Your grandmother called them "mufflers,"
but, ladies, this is not
your grandmother's muff.
♪♪
[WOMEN LAUGHING QUIETLY]
-[WORKERS CHATTERING]
-[DISHES CLINKING]
-Hey!
-Yeah?
Don't be picking off my plates.
Employee mess is around the corner.
-Grab what you want.
-Thanks.
♪♪
[LIVELY CHATTER NEARBY]
[DOOR CREAKS]
[WOMEN LAUGHING, CHATTERING]
[CHATTER STOPS]
You in plumbing?
-Uh, yeah.
-Need a bunk?
-Yes, I do.
-That one's free.
-Huh?
-Yeah.
Long day?
Uh, plunged my ass off.
[BIRDS CALLING]
[BIRDS CHIRPING]
Okay, well, I thought spotting
that rose-breasted grosbeak
would be the highlight of
our day, but I was wrong.
That's the Bicknell thrush.
And, folks, this is a rare opportunity
to hear its beautiful morning song.
Let's listen.
[BIRDS CHIRPING]
[QUIETLY] He's an accomplished surgeon.
Lenox Hill.
First in his class at Johns Hopkins.
Had his choice of residencies
at any hospital he chose.
He's already invented
new surgical techniques
that have become the worldwide standard,
which is a remarkable
feat for such a young man.
He's widely published
in medical journals.
Now, I know he sounds a little oddball
on the surface, but he's just eclectic.
That's often a symbol of accomplishment.
John Quincy Adams
kept an alligator as a pet.
And Benjamin Franklin
took naked air baths.
Did you know that?
I wonder if Ida's son
was named after him.
Oh, that's his name, Benjamin.
Do you like the name Benjamin?
He's never rented.
He originally lived in Sutton Place
had a beautiful view of the bridge.
But as close as it was to his practice,
he still found it to be too far.
His patients are everything to him,
so he sold the place at a loss.
Can you imagine that?
He bought a duplex just
a block from the hospital.
It has views, but not of the bridge.
So they went out about two hours ago?
Yes, they do this every day.
They swim, they leave all their stuff.
This is my sister's purse.
She doesn't go anywhere
without her purse.
Look, they could've swum
to another spot on the lake
and are taking their time to walk back.
-Not without telling me.
-Or…
Kyle, get to the office,
find Pauly, and fill him in.
-We need boats on the water. Go!
-On it!
Tell them to call
every resort on the lake
within a five-mile radius!
This is a red flag alert.
-[WHISTLE BLOWS]
-[PEOPLE MURMURING]
He loves the opera.
I know, I know, you're
not the biggest opera fan.
But the spectacle alone is entertaining,
so you should give it a chance.
The sets are sensational.
And, yes, sopranos can be very annoying,
but the orchestra is wonderful.
He loves Puccini.
MALE ANNOUNCER [OVER PA]: Red flag alert.
-I repeat, red flag alert.
-[ALARM WAILING IN DISTANCE]
Joel
you saw me in my romper, didn't you?
Yeah.
BENJAMIN: Fifteen two, fifteen four,
fifteen six and a pair is eight.
Not your lucky day, Golda.
-Benjamin, right?
-I'm sorry?
-Ida's son?
-That's the rumor.
-Get up.
-What?
We are going to do something together.
The sooner the better. Get up.
-I'm a million steps behind.
-I'm Miriam Maisel.
You say that like I should know it.
Most people do know me here.
Eight swimsuit sashes?
Top-seeded badminton champ?
22 straight years in the Steiner
Fire Safety Captain's Club?
-Nothing?
-I'm just trying not to laugh here.
What's going on is not funny.
Now, we have to do
something together to satisfy
my mother's insatiable desire
for us to meet before I
tie her to a concrete post
and throw her in the lake.
Is she dead before
you tie her to the post,
or do you tie her to the post
alive and dump her in like that?
-She's alive.
-There'll be screaming.
Not with the gag in her mouth.
-You've thought this through.
-Stand. Start walking.
I'll admit my mother's mentioned you.
Our mothers have been
scheming to set us up for days,
and it will not stop until they
see us doing something together.
So we'll do something,
tell them we gave it a shot,
nothing came of it, and
I can get back to my life.
-And you want to do it now?
-Right now.
You're not missing a meeting
of the Steiner Fire Safety Corporal Club?
Captain, captain.
And we don't meet till Thursday.
-It's raining.
-It'll pass.
-If it doesn't?
-We melt.
Okay. I'm convinced. What do we do?
-Boating? Really?
-Yes. Yes.
Let me guess, you're a charter member
of the Aquatic Maritime
Gunwale Anchor Schooner Society
-nine years running.
-It's what we're doing.
BENJAMIN: I'm not a big fan of water.
But I like the public nature of it.
It's private, yet on display.
-Everyone will see us.
-Can't argue with logic.
My new friend Benjamin
and I would like a boat, please.
You got it.
No standing, no rocking,
no rowing past the buoys.
Thank you, Josh.
Yes, thank you, Josh.
[MIDGE CLEARS THROAT]
One, two, three.
Happy boating!
Be safe.
♪♪
Perfect. Everyone's already watching us.
Even with the pétanque
championships going on,
we're still a pull.
-Well?
-Yes?
-Are you going to row?
-No. Are you?
-No. The boy rows.
-I don't row.
What do you mean, you don't row?
Everybody rows.
-Then go ahead and row.
-The boy rows.
-Not this boy.
-Pick up that oar.
It was your idea to get into a rowboat.
-Really? That tone?
I might as well be rowing with my mother.
Well, you could've
suggested something else.
I'm just going along for the ride here.
I was perfectly happy playing
cribbage with the bubbes.
-[LAUGHTER]
-[BAND PLAYING LIVELY MUSIC]
It's getting sillier.
-What is that?
-The Steiner Daily Newsletter.
But we've got to at least
look like we're talking.
-We are talking.
-You're reading.
I am trying to stay informed,
and I am loving this new font.
Well, read something and
I'll pretend that I'm enjoying it.
"Arthur Rossman would like
to thank all the fellow guests
who consoled him on the
death of his beloved dog Mogul."
[LAUGHS]
You are sick.
Well, read something
light that I can laugh at.
"There will be a twilight gathering
of Holocaust survivors tonight in…"
Just shut up.
This is going very well.
You're supposed to row.
-I know.
-I don't row.
That's why you didn't get very far.
-I know.
-She never asked if I could row.
Well, Benjamin, thank you
for the very, very little you did
to get my mother off my back.
-Don't mention it.
-Are you getting out?
I'm quite comfortable here, actually.
SAMUEL: I think the angle's fine, sir.
ABE: Almost, but not quite.
Rotate it five degrees counterclockwise.
-Yes, sir.
-ROSE: What's that, Abe?
My new drinking index.
I blew some of the timelines before,
but this one is going to work.
So ten degrees is five
degrees in your world?
What world do you live in, Jimmy?
SAMUEL: But if it's
close enough, I can always
help you reposition it any
time during the fireworks.
[SIGHS] And miss which
fireworks while we're doing that?
The crackly dragon eggs?
The… The weeping willows?
The gorgeous crescendo of chrysanthemums?
-Which ones?
-I'm sorry, I'll get it right.
-With my help, you'll get it right.
-Hello, Joel.
Oh, hey. You joining us?
Got a spot on the blanket.
Nah, I'm a little tired.
Probably just gonna turn in.
-Your new room working out?
-Yeah, it's great.
Again, thanks for letting
me stay like that, Rose.
-It was really nice.
-No problem.
Good night.
ABE: Fold it up. Let's just start over.
We'll start over. Get another blanket.
All right.
So, I saw you two from the shore.
Who? Me and Benjamin?
-What happened?
-I did what I could.
I mean, why in the world
wouldn't he pick up a damn oar?
He just refused.
-So rude.
I must say, I was unimpressed.
-How could you not be?
-Oof.
ABE: Ah, forget it.
-[CRICKETS CHIRPING]
-[BIRDS CALLING]
[LAUGHTER, CHATTER]
-Papa?
-Yes?
You're snockered.
-I'm fine.
-No, Abe, you're drunk.
Your calculations were off again.
[SLURRING]: Give me another pickle.
The brine in the pickle
counteracts the alcohol.
You've had ten pickles, Abe.
Your pickles aren't working.
-[LAUGHS]
-Why are you laughing?
'Cause it's funny.
I'm having my lawyer
contact the chief counsel
at Claussen Pickles.
There will be a lawsuit.
[BOTH LAUGH]
-Are you both laughing?
-No.
That should be not laughing.
-[FIREWORKS WHISTLING, POPPING]
-[CROWD GASPING]
Oh, Abe, you're missing the fireworks.
Oh, just describe them to me.
MIDGE: Well, there was,
like, a big display of flowers,
multicolored, and they
danced across the sky.
Ah, that's a chrysanthemum.
I love the chrysanthemums.
[BOTH LAUGH]
And now there's another
sparkly thing going off.
-[BOTH LAUGH]
-Oh.
-Oh…
-[FIREWORKS CONTINUE]
♪ Send me photographs and souvenirs ♪
♪ Just remember ♪
♪ When a dream appears ♪
♪ You belong to me ♪
♪ I'll be ♪
♪ So alone without… ♪
[FIREWORKS CONTINUE]
BENJAMIN: Got a light?
Sure.
Thanks.
Not in a sociable mood tonight, huh?
-Guess not.
-Me, neither.
I've never really understood fireworks.
We used to love them.
I mean, I did.
Now they're just…
-Lights in the sky.
You think… What?
You think we're ever really forgiven
for the mistakes we've made?
Who do you want doing the forgiving? God?
People.
People never forgive.
Not in my experience.
They say they do, but they don't.
I'm not even sure
forgiveness really matters.
Why wouldn't it matter?
Well, what is it, forgiveness?
It doesn't mean anything.
I mean, you still did
what you did, right?
Nothing's changed.
Forgiveness is a mindset.
Synapses in your brain
telling you to think differently
about something that's already happened.
It's amorphous. It's not really there.
And if it's not really there, what is it?
God, I hope that's not true.
Every day, I feel like I'm getting kicked
in the head a little.
I know I deserve it, but I sure
would like it to end someday.
Just do what I do, stay away from people.
If you're not around them,
there are no mistakes to be made.
That's not the answer.
You know that.
You need people.
To bum a light.
That's about it, though.
Nah.
You'll change your mind someday.
Just wait.
You'll see.
[CROWD EXCLAIMING IN DISTANCE]
[FIREWORKS CONTINUE]
["ROCK THE BOAT" BY THE
HUES CORPORATION PLAYING]
♪ So I'd like to know
where you got the notion ♪
♪ Said I'd like to know
-♪ To rock the boat ♪
-♪ Don't rock the boat, baby ♪
-♪ Rock the boat ♪
-♪ Don't tip the boat over ♪
-♪ Don't rock the boat, baby ♪
♪ Rock the boat ♪
♪ Ever since our voyage of love began ♪
♪ Your touch has thrilled
me like the rush of the wind ♪
♪ And your arms have held
me safe from a rolling sea ♪
♪ There's always been a quiet
place to harbor you and me ♪
♪ Our love is like a ship on the ocean ♪
♪ We've been sailing with a cargo ♪
♪ Full of love and devotion ♪
♪ So I'd like to know
where you got the notion ♪
♪ Said I'd like to know
♪ So I'd like to know
where you got the notion ♪
♪ Said I'd like to know
-♪ To rock the boat ♪
-♪ Don't rock the boat, baby ♪
-♪ Rock the boat ♪
-♪ Don't tip the boat over ♪
-♪ Don't rock the boat, baby ♪
-♪ Rock the boat ♪
-♪ Don't tip the boat over ♪
-♪ Ooh-hoo-hoo ♪
-♪ Rock the boat ♪
-♪ Rock on with your bad self ♪
♪ Rock the boat ♪
♪ Rock on with your bad self ♪
-♪ Rock the boat ♪
-♪ Rock on with your bad self ♪
♪ Rock the boat, rock the boat ♪
♪ Rock the boat ♪
♪ Rock the boat, rock the boat. ♪