- You could have as little
as six months to live.
"A Leap of Faith" is about
the patients
other doctors have given up on.
And I love you, Benita.
- That is not how I wanted
you to find out.
- You don't cross those lines!
- Tomorrow I'm going
into a 14-hour surgery.
They're gonna replace
half of my chest.
What are you doing?
- Would you like
to have dinner with me?
My place, 10:30?
- That works.
- Life is good
when you believe
good things can happen.
- Where's Chris Lyles?
- He passed away last night.
- What?
- Dr. Macchiarini is asking
what happened
with your trials.
Any mistakes could
slow down our progress.
Make sure that doesn't happen.
- I want to know you
better than anyone.
- Arresto?
- You got arrested?
- Speed limits are just
suggestions to me.
What if we could
continue like this
at home in Barcelona?
- We found a priest
for the wedding.
- ThePope is gonna marry you?
- Pope Francis will
be traveling
to South America this summer,
not Italy, not your wedding.
You've always had
great instincts.
Maybe you should trust them.
- Padraic, I need you
to look into someone for me.
The name is Paolo Macchiarini.
* *
- You were right.
The Vatican is not happy
that Jorge agreed
to marry two divorcées
in the church.
- Our wedding's in three weeks.
- I know.
I thought I could
change things on my own.
I thought I--
honestly, I don't know
what I thought.
- Okay.
Y-you do realize
this isn't about the Pope
though, right?
You--you're hiding things
from me.
- I know you want
to know everything.
But it's not easy for me.
I have been alone too long.
I'm trying to create something,
and all I have is me.
And each time I come close,
there's always someone fighting
against it,
trying to stop me, so I--
I don't share.
I'm not used to it.
I don't know how.
I--I stay alone.
And it's very difficult
to let that go.
- I didn't even know
you felt that way.
- How would you?
I mean, honestly,
sometimes I think
I cannot trust anyone
but myself.
And you.
* *
I'm just trying to make
this wedding perfect.
- I never asked you to do that.
- But I wanted to.
I wanted to because I know
how difficult it is for you
to give up your life here,
your job.
I didn't want to add more
to your worry.
Honestly, I didn't want
to give you a reason
to change your mind.
But the church, the reception,
nothing else has to change.
All I can hope is when you walk
out of that church,
when you listen
to those bells ringing,
that you will be happy.
* *
- Excuse me.
Where is Dr. Macchiarini?
- Oh, Dr. Svensson.
They are all
at the press conference
in the lecture hall.
- Oh.
Okay.
- Today is a very special day
for all of us here
at Karolinska.
Today, our "Lancet" paper
was ranked
among the top ten
most important studies
on regenerative research.
However, I would like
to remind us
that we're all here because
of the courage of one man,
Andemariam Beyene.
Andemariam was handed
a death sentence
before he came to us
here in Stockholm.
But today,
six months after his surgery,
he is cancer-free...
And he's been able to return
to Iceland, to his family...
Where I believe that he's
nearly completed his doctoral
in geothermal engineering.
Am I correct, Andemariam?
- Yes.
His breath,
and therefore his life,
has been restored.
Ande, you are a living proof
of what these transplants
can achieve.
And we're just at the beginning
of this technology,
so you can all imagine
what we can do
for so many patients like him
around the world.
Ande, thank you very much.
And thank you all
for being here.
* *
- Thank you.
Thank you.
Yeah, but--Ana, Ana.
Do you have five minutes?
- Of course.
- Yes? Okay.
Uh, let's go this way.
Let's go to my office.
- Okay.
- Thank you.
- Quite the turnout
for the event.
- Hm.
- So, uh, six months,
no additional surgeries,
no tangible advancements
in the technology.
I would say your research
is stagnating.
- I would argue
it's just the opposite.
We have a successful operation,
a published article,
an additional surgery
from which we can draw
a great deal of conclusions.
But the most important thing
that we've learned
is that we cannot execute
our research here,
not with your team,
not in your facilities.
- I beg your pardon?
- It's only the fault
of the regulations
here in Sweden.
We're shackled
by compassionate use.
Our patients here
are just too sick.
I have contacts in Russia...
- Oh.
- Who have offered us
a campus to conduct
additional research.
In Krasnodar, we can work
with full autonomy,
and any progress
that we see there
can be used to gain approval
for patient trials
back at Karolinska.
It only benefits our work here.
- Well, that is quite an ask,
to have Karolinska
hand you over
to Russia, of all people.
- It's not an ask.
It is an opportunity.
And it's not me
who you will be handing over.
I was hoping
to have Dr. Lasbrey
set up and run a lab there.
If Mr. Beyene showed us
one thing,
it's that there is
a pervasive need here.
Now we just have
to take the opportunity
that has been presented to us.
- Yes, well,
quite an opportunity.
* *
- Okay, tomato.
Okay. Two more.
Cheese.
- Cheese.
- Good morning.
both: Good morning.
- Wow. Maybe I should
sleep in more often, huh?
- Can I wear my hair in braids?
- No, we don't have time
for that, tesoro.
- You heard him.
I think your hair looks
really cute though.
Do you have your homework?
Oh.
Oh, God.
- What is it?
- Oh, we've been having
these issues
with our materials,
and it's causing
these costly delays.
It's a nightmare.
But if you want,
we can have dinner tonight,
and I can explain to you
every boring detail.
- It's a date.
- And you?
What is my superstar producer
going to do with her first days
of freedom from the newsroom?
- Hmm.
I think I'll probably
finish packing here,
and then hopefully
a whole lot of nothing.
- Perfecto.
- Hey.
All right, you got your phone?
Keys?
Lunch.
Love.
both: Mwah.
- Bye, Mom.
- Bye.
- Okay. Bye, my love.
What is that?
- What's what?
- That ringing.
Hey, Lizzi, is that your phone?
- No.
- Oh.
- Oh, mine.
My work phone.
Okay.
Okay, now we need to go.
* *
Get my keys.
- Bye.
- See you tonight, okay?
- Bye, guys.
- Bye, Mom.
* *
- So you're looking
for Dr. Macchiarini's
2008 pig study, yeah?
- Yes.
- Uh, you know,
the Bristol paper's online.
- Well, I'm looking
for raw data, eh,
notes, raw datasets,
any other trials that might
have gone unpublished.
I--I'm hoping
to cross-reference
for my own research here.
So...
- Sure, uh, just need to get
a sign-off
from the higher-ups.
Me boss is a bit
of a sheephead
about that kind of stuff.
- Uh, I'm one of the authors
of the follow-up study
in "The Lancet."
- Ah.
- So, uh, I, uh--
- Fine, but I-I'll still
have to get
Dr. Macchiarini to authorize.
- Oh. Oh, Dr. Macchiarini?
- Yeah.
- Ah.
Well, I'm requesting directly
from him.
Eh, he asked me
to give you a call.
- Okay, let me see
what I can find for you, mate.
- Thank you.
- Mr. Beyene, hello.
It's great to see you
in person again.
- I thought I was coming here
for a checkup.
But they told me
to bring a suit.
Now I understand.
* *
How could they say those things
when I feel like this?
- We'd like to do an endoscopy
just to confirm
your airway is looking
exactly the way it should.
- Where is Dr. Macchiarini?
- He's in an interview
at the moment, but--
- My wife begged me
not to come.
- I understand you're anxious.
You're tired.
The lingering symptoms
are expected,
but always taxing on the body.
- Ande, you had
six months to live.
Now you're sitting here
with your entire future
ahead of you.
This was a success
for all of us.
- Why don't you get some rest?
It's been a long day.
* *
- Thank you.
Thank you.
- Are you ready?
- I'm ready.
- Mrs. Lyles.
I'm so sorry about Chris.
He was very special.
- Thank you.
- I know this isn't
the best time
to burden you
with more paperwork,
but, uh, this is
an autopsy request.
I can help walk you through it
if you'd like.
- The other doctor said
an autopsy wasn't necessary.
- It's elective.
As the next of kin, you have
the right to request one.
- Why would we request one?
Was there something wrong
with the procedure?
- No, it's not that.
There are some battles
you simply can't win.
This is just for your own
peace of mind.
- Dr. Macchiarini fought
for my son
when all the other
doctors gave up.
We knew the risks.
We trust him.
- So did Chris.
He believed in this medicine,
the research.
I think he would have
wanted this.
- So you're saying this is good
for Dr. Macchiarini's work?
Wh-why didn't he ask for it?
- Like I said,
it's your choice.
My job is just to make sure
you know what the choices are.
* *
- Buongiorno. Hotel Gandolfo.
- Ciao.
Uh, I'm--I'm calling
about the Macchiarini wedding
on the 15th.
I just wanted to confirm
our reservation
for the reception hall.
- Of course. One moment.
- Thank you.
- Macchiarini, you say?
- Mm-hmm.
- Uh, I'm very sorry, signora,
but I have
no Macchiarini wedding.
- No, no, no, no, th--
no, th-that can't be right.
We're--we're supposed to have
the entire place booked out.
- I see here Dr. Macchiarini
has booked with us before,
but, uh, no wedding.
- You have reached
the Bonaparte Luxury Resort.
Please leave a message.
- Hi. Uh, my name
is Benita Alexander.
I'm calling about my honeymoon.
- No, signorina.
Is it perhaps
- under another name?
- We're sorry.
You have reached a number...
- No.
Um, can--can I speak
to the chef directly?
Madame,
the chef has never catered
a wedding in his life.
- Asshole.
- Macchiarini? No. No.
No, no, no.
We--we should have rooms
reserved, including suites.
Yes, we should have
rooms reserved, including--
Ciao.
Uh, I am--
I'm calling about the--
- Macchiarini? No. No.
- The Macchiarini wedding.
No, no, no. No.
* *
- Hi! Ah!
- Hello.
- Welcome. Come on in.
- Oh, hey, here.
This is 80 proof.
I know you don't like
the fruity stuff.
- Wow. Thank you.
That's very kind,
especially for you.
- He even wore a jacket
over his Springsteen T-shirt.
- Mm.
- Mm-hmm.
- Oh, this is my, uh...
- Márjá.
- For God's sake, Nathan.
I'm Wilma, welcome.
- That press conference today
was a fucking circus.
Uh, shit, sorry.
- You were there?
I--I didn't see you.
- I skipped it.
All I'm saying is that
it's ridiculous
how they paraded him around
in front of the cameras
like that.
- This was delicious, Anders.
- Thank you.
- Skal.
- Skal?
Skal?
- Skal.
- So how did
the two of you meet?
- I tend a bar
near the hospital.
- Ah. You're the one.
- I don't usually date the men
who come into the bar,
especially doctors.
Most are arrogant assholes.
- He's arrogant,
just not an asshole.
- Sometimes I'm an asshole.
- And Nate mentioned
you're a lawyer.
- Yes, I am--well, was.
I stepped down
after Axel was born.
We wanted one of us
to be here with him.
And somehow the rats won out
over the law.
- Ah.
- Mm.
- Oh, playtime.
That's my cue.
- Oh.
No, no, no, no, no, no,
you sit.
- No, no--
- I'll take it. I'll take it.
Yeah, you sit. You sit.
- Are you sure?
- Yep.
- Okay.
- You have boring
medical stuff to talk about.
- Um, may I join you?
- Uh, yes.
I'm better company anyway.
- Mm, that is true.
- I'll do the dishes.
- Great.
- I know that Macchiarini's
magic plastic had something
to do
with Christopher Lyles' death.
- You know this how?
- That press conference today,
it was an infomercial.
Lyles died, and Karolinska
is covering their ass.
I know how I sound,
but I--I'm not the only one.
There is a Belgian researcher,
Dr. Doris Dufort.
She has a blog
called "Phase IV."
She wrote a peer response
to your paper in "The Lancet."
- Mm. Mm-hmm.
- You've read it?
- No, uh, I don't entertain
fringe theories
from a rival in the field.
Doris Dufort is a troll.
- What about
your trial results?
Anything come up there?
That's a loaded silence.
I haven't released them, Nate.
I'm still compiling my report.
- That's bullshit.
I know you've got
a lot on the line.
You know, more--more
than I could ever understand,
but I--I know you.
I know that look on your face,
and I know you haven't said
a word all night
to contradict me.
Just promise me
that if you find anything,
you'll let me know.
* *
- Okay, we're
in the larynx now.
Okay, Ande, I'm going to push
through the vestibular fold.
- So you're gonna feel a little
pressure as I go in, okay?
- All right.
Yeah.
The stitches look good.
They look very good.
- You're doing beautifully,
Mr. Beyene.
- Okay, I see--I see some
inflammation at the top here,
but you've been traveling,
so that's not unusual.
- Okay, let's give you--
let's give you a little break.
Okay, I think that we're
all finished here.
Everything looks as it should.
- Do you want to retrieve
any samples
from towards the bronchi?
- No, no, no,
that's not necessary.
I'm satisfied.
But we're gonna give you
some antibiotics for that
inflammation, all right?
Good job, Ande.
I will check on you later.
Okay?
- Okay.
- Thank you.
- Well done.
- Dr. Lasbrey,
so we're not gonna biopsy?
I don't follow.
- The doctor said to leave it.
That's all you need to follow.
* *
- You only sent research
for bronchus testing.
I need trials
for the biosynthetic tracheas.
- That's what the lab sent up.
Well--
These data tables
are incomplete.
They are redacted.
There is no real
information here.
- If you want,
I can talk to me boss.
- No. Th-thanks.
Thank you.
* *
- Hi.
- Hey, I just sent something
over to you.
Should be in your inbox.
- Okay.
Yep, got it.
- If it's an American school,
why do they make us
speak Spanish?
- It's probably not
what you were hoping to find.
- Uh, I--I have to run,
but I'll call you back.
Okay, bye.
- Hi.
Hey.
Hi.
- Who was that?
- Uh, it was Luke about
my final wedding dress fitting.
- What? Can I take a peek?
- No, no.
- Why not?
- Sorry.
- Ugh.
Tsk. Such a cruel tradition.
- Did you finish your homework?
- Almost.
- Why don't you go finish
your homework before bed?
- Okay.
- Buenos noches, papá.
- Buenas noches, tesoro.
Ah, that's so cute.
- You look exhausted.
- Oh, yeah.
- Was Lizzi a lot today?
Oh, God.
No, she was great.
It's this thing
that doesn't stop.
I definitely will
have to go back.
- Back where?
- To Russia.
The problems at the lab, it--
you understand, right?
- Yeah. Of course, yeah.
* *
Hey, I have a--an idea.
What if we have
chilled champagne
waiting for guests in the suite
when they arrive
for the wedding?
- Oh. Yeah, lovely.
That's nice.
- Yeah?
- Yeah, yeah, yeah.
- Is there someone
I should contact
at the hotel or...
- No, no, no, no.
It's okay. I--I got that.
Leave that with me.
I already pay the--
the final deposit for the--
for the reception hall.
You're gonna love it.
It's beautiful.
- Do you have
an early flight tomorrow?
- Yeah, I do.
- Yeah.
Why don't you go get some rest?
- I'm never too tired for you.
Huh? You want me
to go to sleep alone?
* *
What are you doing
out here in the dark?
* *
Russia's going to be
the longest
few days of my life.
- Yeah.
But I'm gonna have this place
pretty much entirely packed up
by the time you get back.
You don't want to be late.
- I love you.
* *
Fuck.
- Paolo was arraigned
for extortion.
- He made up some bullshit
excuse about the arrest.
I mean, this guy--
this guy was in Italy.
- His name is Matteo Peralta.
Says here he's a plaintiff,
a widower.
He lost his wife.
And there were other charges--
embezzlement, deception,
extortion by multiple patients.
These are felonies.
- He--he lied to my face
so easily.
- Is he in the apartment
right now?
- No.
He's on his way to Russia.
- I did a background check
and criminal history.
I looked into
his personal history myself.
How--how did I miss
all of this?
- Our vetting is good,
but this?
This is designed to be missed.
The charges were dropped.
- I'm packing up my life
to move to Barcelona.
I gave notice on my lease.
I pulled Lizzi out of school.
I gave up my fucking job.
- What are you gonna do?
- I have to go to Luke's
for my wedding dress fitting
right now.
- Are you gonna tell Luke?
- I have to, right?
* *
- Hey.
- Why are we meeting
like spies?
Okay, uh, Christopher Lyles'
mother came to see me.
She said you pressured her
into performing an autopsy.
- It was
my professional opinion--
- Yeah, well, it seems
they weren't interested
in your professional
opinion, Nate.
And yet, you offered it.
Look, an autopsy is not going
to bring their loved one back.
You should have let them
just mourn in peace.
- Shouldn't that involve
knowing
why they're mourning
in the first place?
- Okay, look, Nate,
you are an excellent surgeon.
You--you care
about your patients
more than anyone
I have ever seen.
But really, just...
leave the dirty politics
to lesser men.
You went behind
Macchiarini's back.
- When Chris died,
Macchiarini was already
out of the country.
We don't know which way
his back was turned.
- I get it.
Every time we open a cadaver,
we're exposing this institution
to possible litigation.
- Okay, Christopher Lyles
was terminal.
Litigation didn't even
cross my mind.
My job is to steer clear
of bad optics.
- So our patient died,
it's unclear why...
- I'm sorry, unclear to who?
- And you're concerned
about a stain
on Macchiarini's reputation?
- Okay, I mean bad optics
for you, Nate.
Paolo's reputation
is impeccable.
And these claims are unfounded.
Some people could see
these maneuverings
as something incendiary.
Like a personal rivalry.
Professional jealousy.
Just watch your step, Doctor.
Please.
- We've had some success with
these cadaveric donor organs.
Although survival
in the body is short-term,
there's evidence
of gas exchange
and vascular perfusion
after transplantation.
- For how long?
- Two hours.
It was a milestone.
Follow me.
Take a seat, Dr. Svensson.
Oh, thank you.
- I must admit, I was wary
when you first
reached out to me.
Your name is
on "The Lancet" paper.
Naturally, I questioned
your motivations.
- You could say
I'm the one taking the risk.
I could be fired
for coming to you--
breaching an ethical wall,
crossing enemy lines.
- Some ethical walls are meant
to be breached,
especially in service
of the truth.
- I read your blog,
your response
to our article about, um--
- Andemariam Beyene's
transplant.
- I'm currently running trials
to support the results.
- Your paper was published
before you completed
your study?
So you come to me,
an act of scientific espionage.
I must say, I like your style,
Dr. Svensson.
- I--I also requested research
from Dr. Macchiarini's
previous work in Bristol,
but, uh,
I couldn't find anything.
- No. You wouldn't, would you?
Nothing but a stone wall.
I had the same
funny feeling as you
way back in 2008,
before anybody had
grand designs.
Those are for you.
* *
Go on.
Too late to turn back now.
Dr. Macchiarini is setting
a very dangerous precedent,
making this kind of
experimental surgery elective.
- N-no, we haven't.
It is only approved
for compassionate use.
- For now.
* *
- Yesim?
Hi. I'm Dr. Gamelli.
Uh, I'll be doing
your intake today.
So...you're here from Turkey.
Well, it's very brave to come
all this way on your own.
- I've been to 12 countries,
but never to Sweden.
I'm worried more for my father.
He's meeting me here
in a couple days,
but he's traveling on his own,
and his English is not so good.
- Well, how about his Swedish?
- Even worse.
- I'm sure he'll do fine.
You're here
for a consultation, I see.
Your trachea was injured
during an operation?
- My hands, they sweated a lot.
My doctors back home,
they tried to fix it,
but something went wrong
with the--
- What they tried to do
is a very risky
surgical procedure.
- After this,
they couldn't help,
so they recommended
Dr. Macchiarini.
He's the best in the world.
- There's my lovely
young patient.
So good to finally meet you
in person, Yesim.
Welcome to Karolinska.
This is Dr. Lasbrey.
- Hi.
- Thank you, Dr. Gamelli.
* *
It really pains me to see
someone as young,
as beautiful as you are
suffering like this.
We are all so very happy
that you're here with us today.
We're also very lucky
that the talented
Dr. Lasbrey is with us
for one last procedure.
* *
- Hi.
- I'm just taking
the hem up a little bit.
- What is it?
- I promised Paolo
I wouldn't say anything, but...
the Pope agreed
to give me and Michael
Holy Communion at the wedding.
- What?
- I know.
After all the shit
our families put us through
when we got married.
My mom, she refused to come.
- No, I--I remember that--
- And now
the freaking Pope giving--
giving her little boy
Communion?
For her to see that now,
it's just--
Paolo's just--
he's really special, Benita.
* *
Okay.
You ready?
* *
Axel, Axel.
Axel!
Ugh!
Axel.
Sweetie, I know you're upset.
I'm coming in now.
We'll just skip to quiet time,
okay?
- Okay.
- Well, have fun with Aubrey.
I'll see you in the morning.
Love you.
Good night.
* *
Paolo?
- Do you trust me?
- Oh.
Oh, God.
What are you doing?
- It's a surprise.
- Are you ready?
- You're supposed
to be in Russia.
- They delayed my flight.
And I have a beautiful idea.
Let's get married right here.
Friends and family
or just the two of us.
Tomorrow if you want.
Let's do it.
- Was that your plan all along?
When everything eventually
fell apart, we would just--
we would get married
up here on my rooftop?
- I would marry you
under a bridge if I had to.
What's going on?
- Paolo, I called everywhere.
No one knows anything
about our wedding--
nothing.
- Is that what this is about?
Benita, we have
important guests
that require discretion.
Our wedding was supposed
to be confidential.
What did you expect
to find out without me?
What's going on?
- You're lying to me.
- Why would I lie to you?
- And I trusted you
with my daughter.
I was getting ready to uproot
my entire fucking life
for a lie?
* *
- I made a few mistakes,
and you're still punishing me.
- No, no, no, no, I--
- I thought we were past that.
- I looked into everything.
I looked into you.
- You looked into me?
- Yeah.
- Why would you look into me?
- Why me, Paolo?
Why me?
I'm a journalist.
You had to know at some point,
I was gonna start
asking questions.
- Yeah.
That's what I love about you.
- That man in Italy had
a wife...
- Oh, God.
- Who was your patient.
He wasn't mafia.
He wasn't some stranger.
- Please, Benita.
- He wasn't an enemy.
- Please.
- What did you do to them?
- Baby, don't do this.
* *
There are certain things
I didn't want
to have to tell you.
You're giving me no choice.
Benita, my work, what I do,
is tied to governments,
heads of state,
oligarchs.
I've been forced to treat
some very bad people.
And you don't want to go
digging in there, Benita,
because it's dangerous.
It is dangerous for me.
It is dangerous for you.
It is dangerous for Lizzi.
What I'm trying to do
is to protect you.
- Paolo.
Paolo.
You need to leave.
* *
- All of his work,
his--his grant, his everything,
it's all based on a lie.
- They performed trials
with donors, cadavers,
but never
with the biosynthetic tracheas.
- So those pigs
from that first presentation,
they were really
just happy fucking pigs?
- In my rat trials,
there were no evidence
of stem cell growth.
Once the implants went
into the bodies, just--
- Detachment, infection,
fungus.
- All leading
to collapse of the airways.
No cartilage tissue,
no regenerated blood supply.
- "It's like magic."
That's what he said,
how the tracheas work.
And it is.
It's all smoke and mirrors.
- Hm.
My trials failed.
They were doomed to fail.
- Because he never did
any trials in the first place.
- Nate...
the patients are the trials.
He's experimenting on people.
* *
- * He looked
right through me *
* Yeah *
* *
* "Come on home, girl,"
he said with a smile *
* "You don't have to love me
yet, let's get high awhile *
* "But try to understand *
* "Try to understand *
* "Try, try,
try to understand *
* I'm a magic man" *
* *
* Winter nights,
we sang in tune *
* Played inside
the months of moon *
* Never think of never *
* Let this spell
last forever *
* Well, summer lover
passed to fall *
* Tried to realize it all *
* Mama says she worried *
* Growing up in a hurry *
* Yeah *
* *
* "Come on home, girl,"
Mama cried on the phone *
* "Too soon to lose
my baby yet *
* My girl should be at home" *
* But try to understand *
* Try to understand *
* Try, try,
try to understand *
* He's a magic man, Mama *
* Ah, he's a magic man *
* *
* "Come on home, girl,"
he said with a smile *
* "I cast my spell of love
on you *
* A woman from a child" *
* But try to understand,
try to understand *
* Oh, oh, oh *
* Try, try, try
to understand *
* He's a magic man *