How is fishing competitive?
Man versus fish?
-No.
-Morning.
Man versus man.
The weighing, the measuring.
Got to respect anything
that rewards you for siIence.
Come on.
Morning, aII.
My mother aIways said
good news couId wait.
But I spent an hour and a haIf
on the phone Iast night
with my new best friend Victor
at the New York Times.
Gonna get a paper route?
No, they're doing
some Iiterary profiIe on hip agencies.
Hep.
After an hour of
invading the detaiIs of my Iife...
You shouIdn't start it with the Mayflower.
Anyway, I toId him to get in touch with you.
He wants to see what we've been up to.
I'II have Joan put it together.
And don't worry about an interview.
He seemed to be
onIy interested in taIking to me.
SterIing CampbeII Draper Pryce.
May I heIp you?
And this one.
That'II do it.
Peggy reaIIy got buried with Heinz.
Yes, they are mostIy Mr. Ginsberg.
Look at aII the great work
you've done as creative director.
Look at aII these voices, aII this taIent.
You reaIIy shouId put the Ietter in there.
ShouId I? That was a year ago.
As far as the worId knows,
it wasn't reaIIy an ad.
It's something to taIk about.
We're stiII suffering for it.
Might as weII get something out of it.
Leave 'em.
See? Because pIaying with a pro
makes you worse.
Makes you seIf-conscious.
Look, J.C., you goIf with me,
you're gonna win every time.
No, because I'm terribIe.
Okay.
Get Max Rosenberg on the phone.
I thought your taiIor was ItaIian.
I met him at the Javits fundraiser.
He's got a piece of business.
It's a Jewish wine.
Why not bring it up at new business?
Why?
Don't you think we're capabIe
of doing this on our own?
Mr. CampbeII is very good for our business,
but this requires your finesse
and, frankIy, your Semitic wife.
Bert, how do you not know
I'm getting a divorce?
Not Mona, Jane.
Jane and I are getting divorced.
AIready?
How Jewish are they?
You know, FiddIer on the Roof,
audience or cast?
The company is Manischewitz.
Max wiII know.
You can't bIink.
Try to keep your eyes open
so the sting from the air comes in.
Like this.
Daddy, don't forget the coIored penciIs.
Whining is not gonna get you anything.
I'm crying because I need them so badIy
for my famiIy tree project.
-Dinner's at 7:00?
-You're gonna work aII day?
It's 3:30.
-Bye, boys.
-Bye-bye.
How'd you do that?
Just keep 'em wide open and think about
something that makes you sad.
They're probabIy tying their shoes.
That's what it aIways is.
I can't sit here aII day.
I thought you couId park anywhere.
Betty, I'm not an ambuIance.
We're doubIe-parked.
What do you think you're doing, paI?
Okay. Jesus.
Just go get 'em. I'II circIe.
The doorman said you were downstairs.
-Where's Megan?
-I don't know. In the bathroom.
Hurry up, get everybody.
Bobby, Gene, Mom's here.
Come on.
We were waiting.
And they buzzed you.
Henry's doubIe-parked.
I'm sorry. I've Iost track of the time.
Don's Iate.
This is quite an apartment.
Thank you.
I think you've seen most of it.
-Bobby, come on.
-I'II go get them.
Daddy was supposed to bring
the coIored penciIs.
I'II buy you some. Let's go.
Okay, goodbye.
Bye.
This is irritating.
I'II see you in two weeks.
Goodbye.
A traiI of Sno BaIIs Ieading to bigger saIes.
A frozen machine
that makes money for vendors.
Now, if it's for the customers, the kids,
do they get to work the machine?
Find out.
A snowman
on the beach.
A Sno BaII's chance in heII.
They don't meIt.
They're refreshing for the damned.
They're sinfuI.
The Sno BaII is the sin
that gets you into heII.
They're sinfuIIy deIicious.
Jesus, not bad.
Just put Gene to bed. I'II be right up.
Everyone Ioves the cartoons
in The New Yorker.
And I thought we couId do that kind
with the guy crawIing across the Sahara
dying of thirst,
the Iong beard, the tattered shirt.
OnIy there's four guys,
and each one has
a thought bubbIe above him.
"Water, water,
"water, Sno BaII."
-What's the Iine?
-Doesn't need one.
WeII, if you want to
stay with the New Yorkerthing,
maybe some kind of cryptic joke.
-I aIready have the joke.
-Okay. Your turn.
As much as I hate
foIIowing another comedian,
Sno BaII, because it's for kids,
demands a big, Ioud joke.
"Hit me in the face with a Sno BaII"
is the tag.
And the picture is someone
getting hit in the face with a snowbaII.
Not the drink, an actuaI
round, white, messy snowbaII.
And when I say someone, I mean a cop,
schooI teacher with gIasses,
businessman, Indian chief.
Anybody kids hate. And maybe a pig.
Why a pig?
I don't know, but everybody Iaughed.
Great, so that's a way to go.
I agree.
AIso, Sno BaII comes with its own sIogan
because when you think of a snowbaII,
there's a 90 % chance
you think of its chance in heII.
Right. That's true.
So I picture this deviI
with a mischievous smiIe on his face,
sipping a Sno BaII
in front of the fIames of heII.
The cup is beading with condensation.
And in your head you hear his voice,
"Yes, even me."
That's actuaIIy good.
I'm gIad I couId surprise you.
No, it's just damn impressive
you couId not write for so Iong
and come back with that.
It's good to know.
Thank you.
-It's great.
-I'm working on the Iine.
I'II do the rest of it.
That's the easiest part to change.
So Iet's run with both of these.
May I?
Judy SteckIer, haIf-pound Ioss.
That's so good. We both had a good week.
I don't know what happened.
I just wasn't that hungry this week.
Stop it. You're here. You came.
This meeting can start
to define what is a good week
and a bad week in our Iives.
But there are good weeks and bad weeks
for thin peopIe, too.
Coming to Weight Watchers
is not just a chance
to feeI better about yourseIf.
It's a chance to share so that if, for exampIe,
you're someone Iike me,
you don't stuff yourseIf
just to keep from teIIing
your famiIy your probIems.
How was your week, everybody?
Betty?
WeII, I had a bad week out there
after having a good week in here.
CouId you stand up, sweetheart?
I, you know, had
a very trying experience.
I was in an unfamiIiar pIace and I saw...
FeIt a Iot of things I wish I hadn't.
And I Iost a haIf a pound.
And I feeI Iike I shouId
pat myseIf on the back
because it was reaIIy hard.
We aIways taIk about our goaI in pounds,
but that's not aII it is, is it?
Thank you, Betty.
Anyone eIse? Katherine with a "k."
Burke DevIin wiII never be a stranger
in CoIIinsport. Just do what you're toId.
But the way he Iooks at Vicky...
I know what that means.
Who was she to him, Mr. CoIIins?
I've heard her name too many times.
What couId that miserabIe
schooImarm offer him that I can't?
I'II kiII myseIf! I wiII!
Who the heII is this woman?
She's a new character.
She's a cook and she's in Iove.
She's insane. She needs a drink.
They want you to be emotionaI.
You haven't even seen the show.
I've seen a soap opera.
I don't think I've seen one this bad.
And isn't this supposed to be scary?
I didn't come for an acting Iesson,
but thank you for making me more nervous.
Come on, we used to
Iaugh about this together.
You'II go in and turn
that chuck into tenderIoin.
You know what? It's just so easy for you
from your throne on 73rd and Park.
Some of us act for a Iiving
and we wait tabIes when we don't.
-That's not fair.
-No, it isn't.
What do you want me to say?
That I'd kiII for an audition
in this piece of crap?
I wouId. Are you happy?
Look, I'm sorry. I'm nervous.
I haven't had a job in a whiIe
and you're Iucky, that's aII.
I am.
I've got to go. I've got a shift.
What shouId I bring for Thanksgiving?
Something sweet.
Mr. Ginsberg is here to see you.
I Iike the connect the dots.
What's it end up being?
ActuaIIy, it's reminiscent
of certain experiences for some peopIe.
Have a seat.
MichaeI, can you keep a secret?
Nope.
I need you to do some work for me
on a prospective account.
It wiII invoIve a cIient dinner.
And murder.
You're not going to dinner.
What I need from you is a coupIe of ideas
for a company caIIed Monarch Wines.
The brand is Manischewitz.
-You assume that I'm Jewish.
-Stop taIking.
They make wine for Jews.
And now they're making one
they want to seII to normaI peopIe.
You know what I mean, peopIe Iike me.
I think they're open to anything,
but it has to be cheap,
surprise, but impactfuI.
Bring me a coupIe of your best
by sundown Friday.
I have done a IittIe research.
You know, I work for the agency.
And I don't know I want
to keep a secret from Don.
You know Don. TaII guy, short temper.
For the purposes of this dinner,
these are my ideas.
If it works out,
Don wiII obviousIy pick you for it
and you can come up
with them aII over again.
Yeah, but why?
WeII, MichaeI,
when a man hates another man
very, very much,
sometimes he wants to know
that something is his,
even if in the end he has to give it up.
You reaIIy do hate CampbeII.
I don't devote the energy
to hating peopIe anymore.
It's for Mr. Cooper.
And what's for me? It's a Iot of work.
My paying cIients might suffer.
Jesus, I am bankroIIing this entire outfit.
Say 1 00 now and 1 00 Monday morning.
You wipe your ass with 200 bucks.
Here, take it.
I've got to start carrying Iess cash.
What are you doing?
I'm sorry.
I can't eat fish five times a week.
I don't want you to go to bed hungry.
I don't do it aII the time.
CouIdn't sIeep.
You better take it out.
Sit down. This is nice.
Don't know that it's nice
that I've driven you to this
because I can't controI myseIf.
Sweetheart, it's got nothing to do with you.
-WeII, what is it?
-Nothing.
I've just been putting it together
that this job is a dead end.
Does Lindsay want someone
eIse for the campaign?
Lindsay's not running.
He keeps saying that, but, you know...
Betty, I'm the one who keeps saying it.
Turns out he's the one who means it.
He wants to wait untiI '72,
but now's the time.
Once he's out,
Rocky wiII get the nomination.
Rocky can't run. He's divorced.
Nobody cares anymore.
He just got re-eIected governor.
I bet on the wrong horse, Betty.
I jumped ship for nothing.
This is a setback.
You're aIways thinking about other peopIe,
and then you're angry
because no one's thinking about you.
But I am.
It's so easy to bIame
our probIems on others,
but reaIIy we're in charge of ourseIves.
And I'm here to heIp you,
as you're here to heIp me.
We'II figure out what's next.
What time is it?
Midnight, I think.
Can I count it as tomorrow?
Okay.
Now.
HeIIo?
HeIIo.
What do you want?
I want to have dinner.
Is that a good idea?
You know what, Jane? When we took LSD,
you swore to me that you wouId
aIways be there for me.
Stop teIIing me things I said that night.
Like I know I didn't promise
to remarry right away
just to save you aIimony.
No, this is true.
And I have a very painIess exercise,
which is taking some extremeIy
important cIients to dinner
and having you on my arm.
Why don't you ask Joanie?
She's a professionaI something.
Because they're dying to meet you.
You'd Iike them. It's a dinner.
I'II owe you.
I want you to buy me a new apartment.
What's wrong with the one you're in?
Your mother is my IandIord.
And honestIy, it has a Iot of memories
and it's painfuI to be here.
And I feeI Iike I can't start a new Iife
untiI I start a new Iife.
This is the most expensive dinner in history.
ReaIIy? Because I found the perfect one.
WeII, you're Iucky I caIIed, then.
Fine.
Have your Iawyer teII my Iawyer
what time dinner is.
I don't know,
I feeI Iike one of us shouId say thank you.
Thank you.
What are you doing here?
You can't be here.
I missed you.
And I kept thinking about you.
I thought you were done with me.
I forgot you.
And then I saw you
in the New York Times Sunday magazine.
Can I go watch TV?
Did you finish everything?
Yeah. You can check it.
Yeah? I just might do that.
My God, are you stiII working on the tree?
AII they care about is the names.
WeII, I have questions.
Do Megan and Henry get branches?
Of course. They get a branch off of us
because we're your parents.
What is this mess?
You carry this around with you every day?
This goes in your math foIder.
This goes in your speIIing.
Is this what you're doing in cIass?
No, I made it at Daddy's.
WeII, it's very nice,
aIthough I don't know why he's smiIing.
"Lovely Megan,
"l went to buy a light bulb.
"When l get back, l'll see you better.
"Love, Don."
Everything Iooks good.
I'II take care of this. You can go.
You know what?
Don't forget your Daddy's first wife.
You're right here.
EIizabeth Hofstadt Francis.
No, your father had another wife before me.
He did?
I'm surprised he didn't teII you that.
Megan heIped me.
Just put it down. It's Anna Draper.
She's deceased.
And turn it in aIready.
I don't want another caII from schooI.
Who is she?
I don't know why Megan didn't teII you.
Ask her.
Okay.
I've got an office
just across the Iadies' room
from the insurance company next door.
-At Ieast you're over here.
-I'm the head of my department.
And I've been working very hard
and doing very weII
and nothing has changed here.
It's a Iot of empty promises.
What were you promised?
HeIIo.
It's a mess in there.
Both campaigns draw you in,
but in different ways. This one's a series.
If Harry roIIs it out right,
you wonder who's gonna get hit next.
That's great.
And this one puIIs you in
as you hear the eviI voice inside your head.
"This couId change everything."
I think the deviI is cIever.
SnowbaII's chance in heII and so forth.
But I think the getting hit in the face
has a Ioud, juveniIe quaIity
that makes a Sno BaII seem
more fun than a soft drink.
AIso, they kept taIking about refreshing,
and this one is IiteraIIy a sIap in the face.
The deviI couId be a series, too.
We couId see what he's up to
in different situations.
And it's got the heat
that Warren taIked about for thirst.
This one's funnier.
Let's Iead with that one and take them both.
-Great.
-Funny stuff. ReaIIy good work.
-Thank you.
I've got drinks.
-Take these to fuII coIor.
-AbsoIuteIy.
-What time is it?
-Bye, creative.
"Look on my works,
ye mighty, and despair."
You shouId read
the rest of that poem, you boob.
Come on. Here.
Bye-bye.
SaIIy?
SaIIy.
Bye.
Have fun.
Come on. Let's go.
Do you want me to make you something?
You haven't eaten.
I toId you I don't want anything.
Why are you being so nasty today?
Because you're a phony.
You don't taIk to me Iike that.
Who is Anna?
What?
You acted Iike you were friends with me.
But you reaIIy do whatever he says.
And guess what?
You're not speciaI. And neither was Anna.
Where did you hear that?
You were my friend first.
Who toId you about her?
Someone who doesn't Iie.
Someone who didn't just
pretend to care about my schooI project.
SaIIy, Iisten to me. I wasn't Iying.
I just... I didn't think it was my pIace to say.
Everybody knows.
You're a IittIe girI. And it's compIicated.
Fine, just keep digging yourseIf deeper.
I don't know what your mother toId you,
but your father and Anna
got married to heIp each other.
They never Iived together
and they never had any babies. Honest.
So why did he marry her?
It was a Iong time ago.
And back then it was the onIy way
to heIp each other out.
So why did he marry you?
-TaIk to your father.
-I don't want to.
And don't teII him I asked. I mean it.
Are you going to make yourseIf cry?
I am your friend, you know.
Judy SteckIer... May I?
Lost a fuII pound.
Good.
What a nice way to end things.
I don't know what happened.
No, it's good.
Betty, you know
maintaining is better than gaining.
It wasn't even a fuII week.
Now everyone deserves
a round of appIause.
You came on a Saturday.
This is the best thing you can do with
the chaIIenge of Thanksgiving ahead.
And we know it's not just the meaI.
It's the cooking, right?
You have to taste everything.
We're supposed to be thankfuI for this,
but the food is just
a symboI of aII the other things.
We shouId fiII ourseIves with our chiIdren,
our homes, our husbands,
our heaIth, our happiness.
So who has a pIan for
how they're gonna handIe the day?
And the day before?
And Iet's not forget about Ieftovers.
Just wanted to make sure she was asIeep.
What's going on with her?
She asked me about Anna.
Betty obviousIy toId her.
-Are you kidding me?
-No.
But I think I handIed
the situation as best I couId.
Who the heII toId you to say anything?
What are you doing?
Damn it, this has nothing to do with you.
Keep your voice down.
I'm not gonna Iet her
keep getting away with this crap.
You're just gonna make it worse.
And Iet her keep sticking
her fat nose in my business?
-Let it go.
-Yeah,
and what am I supposed to say to SaIIy?
Nothing. I promised her I wouIdn't teII you.
Jesus, who's the chiId here?
Get your hand off the phone.
You think this is an accident?
If you caII her,
you're giving her exactIy what she wanted,
the thriII of having
poisoned us from 50 miIes away.
I'm sorry.
I didn't know what eIse to do.
I'm sorry about that.
I didn't think anybody'd stiII be here.
I'm gonna Ieave in a minute.
You come to steaI something?
Nah, I'm doing some work for Roger.
But I'm not supposed to teII anybody.
It's a wine. He's trying to reeI them in.
Wants to Iook smart at the meeting.
And he asked you?
What can I say?
I have gifts and I'm gratefuI.
Just so you know, he's not going to pay
you if you teII everybody.
He aIready did.
Maybe I'II throw some of it
your way if you teII me what you think.
I don't care.
HeIIo.
The articIe came out
and we're not mentioned.
-What?
-It's a buIIshit piece on the usuaI asshoIes.
He compares them to phiIosophers.
HoId on.
Page 52.
170 is the kicker.
Jesus, they Iook Iike Peter, PauI and Mary.
Why are they picking them?
I don't know and I don't care.
Maybe that's the probIem.
You were the one who
taIked to him for an hour.
I thought he was your best friend.
You obviousIy made no impression.
-He's a rat bastard.
-You know what?
Don't wake me up
and throw your faiIures in my face.
It's Sunday, for Christ's sake.
SaIIy, get back here.
Boys, back to your room.
Get over here.
Do you have something you want to ask me?
No.
You do, but you thought
it'd be better to ask Megan.
She wasn't supposed to say anything.
And what was she supposed to do exactIy?
Not Iie again.
I'm sorry.
I know it's my fauIt
that you even have to think
about things Iike this.
-You're a IittIe girI.
-I'm not a IittIe girI.
Then you shouId reaIize that your mother
doesn't care about hurting you.
She just wants to hurt us.
-Are you done?
-No.
Anna and I were married because of a Iaw.
It wasn't romantic. She was a friend.
And I wouId have toId you aII about her,
but she died.
Is she the woman whose house
we went to in CaIifornia?
The one who caIIed you Dick?
Yes.
And I reaIIy wish you'd met her.
Now, you reaIize
an aduIt wouId apoIogize to Megan
even if teIIing her was an accident.
Okay.
Go hang up the phone in my room.
Anything for me in there?
Why don't you have
Ginsberg get your Iunch?
That Mohawk work I did for you was great.
And I kept it a secret,
which is more than I can say for Ginsberg.
It's Manischewitz. He was perfect for it.
I'm sick of hearing peopIe think that way.
I'm not an airpIane either.
I can write for anything.
You know, in the oId buiIdings,
they used to have an executive eIevator.
You are not IoyaI.
You onIy think about yourseIf.
Were we married?
Because you're thinking about yourseIf, too.
That's the way it is.
It's every man for himseIf.
Quaid's department deveIoped Sno BaII,
and he wiII remind you.
We've got Bob Dennison,
who speaks for the IocaI bottIers.
We'II aIso have MichaeI LIoyd
and Warren Kent,
who deaI with the IocaI retaiIers.
-You want me to get those?
-I'm not taking two.
SaIIy?
SaIIy, get in here right now.
That was Mrs. EngeI.
ApparentIy you got an A-pIus
on your famiIy tree.
She thinks you're reaIIy
turning things around.
It's just a drawing.
I'm very proud of you.
You shouId thank Megan for her heIp.
She heIped you, didn't she?
I guess so.
She just toId me the same stuff you did.
ReaIIy? You asked her about Anna?
Yes. Daddy showed me pictures
and they spoke very fondIy of her.
I guess you've earned some TV.
So I puIIed over to the side of the interstate
and I Iet him out with
his Iuggage and everything.
He is not reIated to me.
SiegeI's a very common name.
You wouIdn't want to think everyone
named Rosenberg is reIated to you.
I didn't want to say it.
Lord knows there's been
pIenty of prejudice in this country.
But growing up in Manhattan,
I've aIways envied the humor,
the cIoseness, the way
your peopIe keep track of each other.
So you married your way in, huh?
I've aIways thought Jewish women
are the most beautifuI women in the worId.
Now that's a saIes pitch.
I'm sorry I'm Iate.
This is my son, Bernard.
We're stiII on drinks.
Roger SterIing, this is my wife Jane.
Bernie.
Nice to meet you.
I'm sorry about that. I took the boat out.
-We got stuck.
-ReaIIy? What kind of boat?
No, you two can discuss the detaiIs Iater.
My dad doesn't Iike yachts
because Iast time he was on one,
he rode steerage.
And Iook where you are now.
I've been trying to find out
what Roger thinks,
but he wanted to wait for you.
I wanted to wait for dessert,
make sure you Iiked me.
What's not to Iike?
As I understand it,
you're trying to get Manischewitz
into the hands of different kinds of peopIe.
So to us, it seemed the key was,
different kinds of peopIe.
If you ever Iook at the side of a bus,
it's a moving biIIboard.
The passengers can't see the ad,
but everyone can see the passengers.
The idea was to put a picture of the bus
seats on the side of the bus
right beIow the window
where the reaI peopIe are,
show the bottom haIves of their bodies
with a case of Manischewitz
under each of their seats.
So it Iooks Iike whoever's riding the bus
has bought the wine.
Isn't that cIever?
So you thought that up, huh?
I engaged some of our creatives ad hoc
in anticipation of this dinner.
I figured even if you didn't Iike it,
you couId see what we were capabIe of.
I know it's good.
Do we need menus?
I do.
I'm getting the chateaubriand
if someone wiII spIit it with me.
I thought you Iiked the crabs rangoon here.
I just had some.
So, Roger, what kind of boat do you have?
Am I the onIy one
who can work and drink at the same time?
-What happened?
-They Iaughed,
they bought it and we aIready ceIebrated.
I'm onIy here because I've got
three hours Ieft on the coast.
-Hot damn!
-I knew it.
HoId on. We work our ass off
and we don't even warrant a caII?
BIow by bIow, pIease.
Don pitched the heII out of it,
they said it was cIever.
And apparentIy kids
Iike deviIs in cartoons, as I predicted.
ReaIIy? They didn't Iike the other one?
I don't know. He Ieft it in the cab.
Are you kidding me?
They never even heard it?
We made a saIe. Anything eIse?
I'm going to order some dinner.
Sure. He's gonna be useIess tonight.
So, you suddenIy
have no probIem teIIing peopIe I'm Jewish?
You going to meet Bernie?
What? No.
So you're not gonna caII him in two days
and teII him we're separated?
You had your chance
to say who I sIeep with.
You're supposed to heIp me Iand this.
So if something goes on
between the two of you,
you'd better pretend you're stiII married.
I promise, bubaIa.
I'm sorry.
The Ieast you can do is show me what
the better end of this deaI Iooks Iike.
-What do you mean?
-The apartment.
Show it to me.
When eIse am I gonna get a chance?
I'm not moved in. I just got the key.
Has a Iot of potentiaI.
You think so?
I have missed you.
Roger, wait.
What?
I'm surprised you're working today.
We roII out aII our business this week.
I'm just gonna
spend as much time as I can with my girI
before I'm trapped with my famiIy
over the hoIiday.
You know what, Howard?
Why don't you spend Thanksgiving with her,
and I'II go to your house
and screw your wife?
Are you kidding me?
Good Iuck with that.
But I guess the grass
is aIways greener, right?
I know you saw me.
I thought you were hiding from someone.
That was a boId Iast-minute decision,
going with your idea.
I thought it was more what they wanted.
We'II never know, wiII we?
Because they never heard mine.
Look, I don't Iike going in with two ideas.
It's weak.
And you don't wanna be weak,
so you picked yours.
And they bought it,
which is our goaI, isn't it?
What do I care? I got a miIIion of 'em.
-A miIIion.
-Good.
I guess I'm Iucky you work for me.
I feeI bad for you.
I don't think about you at aII.
-Good morning, Mr. Draper.
-Morning.
I used the toothbrush in there.
I hope it's yours.
Why did you do that?
Jesus, it doesn't beIong to the dead guy,
does it? It's pink.
I toId you why I wanted this apartment
and you ignored me.
I hardIy ignored you.
Now this is no different than the Iast pIace.
ReaIIy? I think it's nicer.
Not anymore.
You ruined this.
Shit.
You get everything you want
and you stiII had to do this.
You're right.
I don't know why I did that.
I feeI terribIe.
SmeIIs good.
I just got off the phone with JuIia.
She got the part.
Good for her.
She asked me to buy champagne.
And you wiII
because you want her to be happy.
It's hot as heII in here. Turn on the air.
It's on fuII bIast. Go get ready.
Open the door at Ieast.
No, don't.
The radio said there's a smog emergency.
The air is toxic. I don't want that in here.
That is a good-Iooking bird.
Mommy, wait. We're supposed to
say what we're thankfuI for.
She's hungry, Bobby.
No, I think it's nice.
Go ahead, buddy.
I'm thankfuI that I have two houses
and they're both reaIIy big
and I got a new sIed.
I'm thankfuI that I'm doing good in schooI.
Doing weII.
I am thankfuI that I have everything I want.
And that no one eIse has anything better.
Me, too. Let's eat.