.
- Previously on "Good Girls."
- I would suggest we put Sara
on a list for a transplant.
- A girl at Madison
just got hit.
- Jesus.
- Perfect match.
- Are people pulling
your pants down?
- They wanna know what I am.
- We could send her
to St. Anne's.
- She's an atheist who enjoys
a bow tie.
I don't think that Catholic
school is a good fit.
- It's cancer in your prostate.
- Couldn't make it sound
a little more serious?
- Can I call you Big Mike?
- My friends--
[gunshot]
[all screaming]
- You shot me in the foot!
Stay away from me!
Take what you came for
and get out of here.
- Just put the whole thing
on the "I'm what's keeping you
out of jail" account.
- Would you ever want
to grab a coffee?
- I had fun tonight.
Should I put on some tea?
- Yeah.
- Who's the boy?
- That fool we arrested.
He's ours now.
- They have him.
The FBI.
And he is talking to them.
- You think I need you?
Ain't nothing but a damn
charity case to me.
Go home.
- I don't see how
you're gonna let me do that.
- You're sure he's
coming for us?
- We know too much now.
- Maybe we should turn
ourselves in.
It's better than waiting
to be murdered.
- He's the one who should
be in jail.
- Then let's put him there.
[Two Feet's
"I Feel Like I'm Drowning"]
- ♪ Yeah
Uh-huh ♪
♪
♪ You keep dreaming and--
- We hire a hit man.
- Seriously?
- We don't need him dead.
We need him in jail.
-Let me finish.
We hire a hit man,
and then we frame Rio
for the murder that
the hit man commits.
- Oh, well, when you put it
like that, then...
- Who's the hit man gonna hit?
Random innocent?
Someone who cuts in line
at the Starbucks?
- Oh, there are candidates.
- I'm sure there are.
- Look, nobody said this was
gonna be easy, okay?
- If it was,
the FBI would have done it.
♪
- ♪ I feel like I'm drowning
♪ You're killing me slow
♪ So slow
- Mind control.
Turns himself in.
- And I'm done.
- It's called brainstorming.
You throw stuff out,
you see what sticks.
- I've got something
in the morning.
- More important than
being murdered?
- We're meeting with
the finance people
from the hospital.
- What are you gonna do?
- Say, "We can pay for
that kidney, no problem."
♪
Write a bad check and hope
they don't realize
until she's open on the table.
- It's a good plan.
- Go with God.
- ♪ And your friends
all start leaving ♪
♪ You're so plastic
- I'll call you tomorrow.
- Park in your garage,
just in case.
- Yeah, and don't let anybody
pull up next to you
at a stop light.
- How am I supposed to do that?
- Just keep inching forward.
- You know what?
Don't even stop.
- Yeah.
Run the reds.
♪
- Do you wanna just--
- I'll tell Stan
I drank too much.
- It doesn't have to be a lie.
- Yeah, you can crash
on the couch.
- ♪ Slow, so slow oh no
♪ I'm drowning
♪ My life's okay
♪ Yeah just when you're
not around me ♪
- Oh, thanks.
I'm not staying.
- ♪ My life's okay just when
you're not around me ♪
If you're waiting on my boy,
you're wasting your time.
He ain't coming tonight.
♪
Yeah, so, if I were you,
I'd go back home to that
beautiful family in Baltimore.
Let's just call this thing
what it is, yeah?
I mean, not that I mind having
my picture taken,
but it must be getting pretty
old for you people,
chasing my ass all over
the city and not coming up
with jack.
- I think I'll talk
to Eddy myself,
if you don't mind.
♪
- Good luck with that.
- ♪ I'm drowning
- Her match was removed from
life support late last night,
so I'd say we're in
a 24 hour window.
Once we hear,
you sign the consents,
we deposit the payment,
and Sara goes straight
to surgery.
- Um, how much of that
does insurance cover?
- Your out of pocket was 20%
after deductible.
- And that's what now?
- $87,400.53.
- Okay.
- Specific.
[both chuckle]
- So, do you all need us to
write a check now, or--
- That'd be great.
- Yes, right now is--
- Fantastic.
- I can do.
- Not a problem.
- Can do.
- Yeah, we've got that.
- All right.
- [chuckles]
- Of course, my pen runs out.
- It's not--
- Babe, do you have a--
- You know what?
I think I do have a--
No, wait.
You're not a pen.
all: [laughing]
- You cannot write with that.
- You could try.
It's not gonna happen.
- You--you can use mine.
- There we go.
- Okay.
- Yeah.
- Uh, this can be a really
anxious time,
so just be sure you take
some time to practice
self-care, okay?
- Oh, yeah.
- We're all about that Namaste.
- Yes, regularly, yes.
- Great.
- How much is in there?
- $3,500.
- GoFundMe?
- Hang on.
But I think about $1,000.
- Okay, well,
we still got options.
- Like what?
- If corporate comes through,
call them again.
- I already did,
and GoFundMe's at 800.
- [sighs]
I thought you said 1,000.
- I was wrong.
- Okay.
All right, well,
church could do another
car wash or a rummage sale.
I can pass the hat
at the station.
Hell, we can go door to door,
but people are gonna need
to step up.
- They already have.
- Well, they need to step up
their step-up.
- Stan.
- [sighs]
- This check is gonna
bounce so hard.
- I know.
- And it's not just
gonna bounce.
It's gonna ricochet.
- I know.
- It's a two year felony
for writing a bad check, Ruby.
You can go to jail.
- You can go to jail
for a lot of things.
- Well, then, we might as well
just rob a bank.
- All right, just...
- [sighs]
- Calm down.
Okay?
- Mmm-hmm.
- Breathe.
- [sighs]
- Where'd you get French fries?
- Under the seat.
- Give me one, please.
Thank you.
[mimics chewing sounds]
Delicious.
Hey, guess what Wednesday is?
- Trash day.
Hey, you know who that is?
- Um, I don't know.
Maybe the Lee kid.
- I've just never
seen him before.
- Hmm.
Wednesday is our anniversary.
- I know.
- Yeah, it's our
20th anniversary.
- I know.
- I could make a reservation.
I mean, we gotta eat.
- Dean.
- Look, I just--
I think that we have to decide.
Like, if we're not gonna be--
Then we just--We gotta call it.
'Cause right now we're stuck.
We're, like,
in this weird limbo,
and I guess, like, I'm--
I'm saying that I just--
I gotta know.
- I'm sorry,
you need to know what?
- Is it our anniversary,
or just another Wednesday?
Buckle up, guys.
- Hmm.
How bad is it?
- It's only been a week.
- You hate it.
- It's fine.
- Do all the girls own horses?
Does the gym teacher
wear a habit?
Or does she have nun shorts?
- We don't have gym.
- Hey, then it's not all bad.
- Like I said.
- Look, Dad and Nancy just get
to make the decisions
for right now,
but I promise you
you do not have to stay here
for much longer, okay?
- I gotta go.
- Hey, you look dope
in the suit.
Love you.
- Love you.
together: Never put no one
above ya.
[dramatic music]
♪
- Annie bananie.
I want you to meet Sally.
I am grooming her
for assistant manager.
- When did you start here,
Sally?
- Three days ago.
- Huh.
Quite a promotion.
- Well, you know, uh,
some people are born leaders.
And, uh, others aren't.
And, you know,
I'm gonna need to start, uh,
delegating a bit more now.
[pop music plays]
- Why's that?
- If you must know,
I am, uh, dating someone
very special.
- Is she Jewish?
♪
- Is she?
- Uh, so, Annie's drawer was,
uh, 78 cents short last night,
Sally.
- Let me show you how we fix
that around here, Sally.
Watch and learn.
Hmm.
78.
Then...
[beeps]
Hmm, mmm, mmm.
Bada bing.
- Yeah, so you're gonna need
to stay on the checkout girls.
Especially this one so that
the vault matches
end-of-day receipts.
Now, where things can go really
wrong is the seafood counter.
Now, those guys think anything
on ice is a fresh catch,
even if it's been sitting
around since Christmas.
Sally, I can't tell you how
many potential lawsuits
I have settled over crab salad.
- Hey.
- What's going on?
- You scared the hell
out of us.
- I have an idea.
- You cannot text 911--
- When we have a literal fatwa
on our heads right now.
- Unless it's an actual 911.
- Let me know when you guys
are done and it's my turn.
What is the one thing that
we know about this guy
that the cops don't?
- He wears his hoodie funny.
- Like, half on, half off.
- Yeah, make up your mind, bro.
- That's correct.
But he also launders money
at my work.
Which we found out
the hard way.
Hello?
People go to jail for that.
- We could tell
your FBI guy.
- And what do we say when
he asks how we know?
- Uh, we can't exactly say
we robbed the joint
and got more than we expected.
- We don't have
to tell him anything.
We just have to give them
a reason to look.
- Oh, hell no!
- It's already familiar
territory!
- It's right up there
with the hit man idea.
- But all we have to do
is get the vault open
and the cops will do the rest.
- Oh, my God.
Mind control never sounded
so good.
- They'll never see it coming!
I mean, nobody hits
the same place twice.
- Yeah, 'cause it's stupid.
- But it does get
you your kidney.
[rock music]
We would have to take just
enough for Sara
and then leave the rest
for the feds.
- I mean, we could take
a little more.
♪
- Okay.
- Hello, old friend.
.
- All right, so the store
has gotten some major
security upgrades.
- How major?
- Three new eyes in the sky.
- Oy vey.
- Mmm-hmm.
And a brand new vault.
Which is very high-tech.
- What about your boy
from the treehouse?
- Okay, still not my boy.
And he's not working nights
because apparently
he's in love.
- Eww.
- With what?
- [scoffs]
Right?
- What about Tyler?
- No upgrades on Tyler.
Although he did lose
seven pounds,
so he might run
a little faster.
But he just discovered pho.
- It's pronounced "fuh."
- What does pho have
to do with it?
- Longer dinner breaks,
'cause he does the whole
ceremonial Vietnamese thing.
- All right.
That helps.
And there's panic buttons
at each register now.
- Wait, what?
- Yeah.
- They call the cops?
- Or SWAT, National Guard.
I don't know.
We've never used them.
But whoever they are,
they guarantee response
in ten minutes.
And new linoleum floors.
Very slippery.
- Okay, is that it?
- Yes.
Except for the motion detectors
at the loading docks,
which are infrared.
- Oh, sweet Jesus.
- But that's it.
Except for--
- Oh, my God.
What now?
[quirky music]
- Hey, what is that sound
of crazy footsteps?
What, you only love me
for the candy.
Please, put the candy back!
Put the candy back.
Please, please, put it back.
- Surprise.
Can you drop the kids off
at your mother's tonight?
- Yeah, what--what's going on?
- And maybe you should
stay there, too.
- Are you in trouble?
- Yeah.
- I mean,
is it bounce house guy?
- Yeah.
- Oh, my God, Beth.
- But I've got this.
I'm gonna fix it.
And it'll all be over.
- Let me help.
Please, I mean, I've gotta
do something to help.
- Why don't you make
that dinner reservation?
- Really?
Yeah, okay.
I will.
I can do that.
- Yeah.
I love you guys.
together: I love you too, Mom.
- Say goodbye to Mom.
- Goodbye.
- Bye, Mommy.
- Bye.
- I'm done.
- You barely touched it.
- Can I have pizza?
- Me, too.
- No, baby, this is all you're
allowed to eat
before your surgery.
- I'm not having surgery.
- You know what?
I don't even know what y'all
are talking about,
'cause I'm getting notes
of hickory up in here.
Just a--honey chipotle.
Maybe a little garlic.
- Mmm, mmm-hmm.
- Right?
- Yeah.
I've got, like, a smoky
citrusy oregano thing going on.
- You know what
this tastes like?
- Straight up pizza.
- Mmm-hmm.
Pepperoni and pineapple.
- Salty sweet goodness.
- I wanna try some.
- Back off, man.
- Theirs is way better.
- Mmm-hmm.
- [chuckles]
Knock yourself out.
- [clears throat]
So, I got some good news today.
- Oh, yeah?
- Yeah, uh, corporate's gonna
come through with that advance.
It's gonna be a bitch
to pay back,
but they wanna help.
- Yeah?
- Yeah.
- [chuckles]
[kisses]
Hey, you know what that
is right there?
- What?
- That's that boomerang
of yours coming back.
- Well, the accounting office
is in Dayton,
so I'm gonna head down there
tonight and, uh,
get the money first thing.
- Mmm, I don't want you driving
all night alone.
- It's fine.
Beth said she'd come, so--
- I don't taste pizza.
- [chuckles]
And one day they're gonna
realize how far
you go for them.
[kisses]
- Oh, you think?
[Tinie Tempah's "Illusion"]
♪
- Nobody move!
This is a robbery!
We're gonna make this quick
and easy!
Do what we say,
and nobody gets hurt!
- Who's in charge here?
- Come on, come on, come on!
I said who's in charge here?
Somebody better start talking.
- It's me.
I am.
.
- Come on, come on, come on.
Over there, come on.
Come on, let's go.
Let's go, let's go, let's go,
let's go, let's go, let's go!
All right, all right,
all right, all right,
okay, okay, that's it.
Come on, come on, come on,
come on, come on, come on--
- Hey, uh-uh.
Not you.
- Wh--why?
- 'Cause you're gonna
open the cash vault.
- Sally, I need your key card.
Sally, don't be a hero.
Just give them what they want.
Hey, it's gonna be okay. Go on.
- All right, everybody down!
Face to the ground!
Come on, you guys.
Not like that.
Come--come on, you guys.
Like this.
Like--like nap time, okay?
Come on, come on!
Come on, I don't wanna
see any eyes!
If I see any eyes,
I swear to God,
I will put a bullet
between them!
[suspenseful music]
♪
- Let's go, bitch.
- Ow!
Really, with the
excessive force?
- Oh, my God,
I was in character.
- Well, Mr. De Niro, now I'm
gonna have a bruise.
- You gotta make it real.
Come on, come on, come on.
- I'm trying, okay?
I'm going as fast
as I can.
- Well, which one is it?
- It's this one,
but it's got, like, a ring
within a ring situation,
and there's all these library
cards on it.
- Just--just let me try it.
- No.
You have gloves on.
Just chill.
- And you have no nails,
so just let me try it.
- God, chill!
Oh!
- Wh--
♪
[beeping]
- Keep your heads down.
I'm watching.
♪
[beeping]
- There it is.
- You sure?
- Yeah, I'm sure.
I'm looking right at it.
It's like it fell into
a furry salad.
- Well, can you reach it?
- Dude, it's way down there.
- But you got those
long sauce arms, baby.
Come on!
- How much time do we
have left?
♪
- Six minutes.
- Doesn't anyone else
have a card?
[Brooks & Dunn's
"Boot Scootin' Boogie" plays]
♪
- Out in the country
past the city limits sign ♪
♪ Well there's a honky tonk
near the county line ♪
♪ The joint starts jumping--
- Come on, whip that lasso,
girl!
- I'm trying!
- Put your hips into it.
[clapping]
Now you're talking.
♪
- With my butt.
[laughs]
- ♪ Where all the
cowboy folk-- ♪
- I'm really bad at this.
[laughs]
It's fun, anyway.
- You're fun anyway.
- ♪ I work hard for my money
when it's quitting time ♪
♪ Oh get down turn around
go to town ♪
♪ Boot scooting boogie
♪
[suspenseful music]
- Can you--
- [shushes]
- Three minutes.
- Oh, my God.
I can feel everything.
- Dude.
- Oh, my God.
Oh, God.
- No!
- Who's got that--
[celebratory noises]
- Sauce arms forever!
- Yeah!
- Yes!
- Nobody move!
Count sheep.
♪
- Good to go.
[sirens wailing]
[Irma Thomas' "I Haven't Got
Time To Cry"]
♪
- Annie?
What are you doing?
♪
- ♪ You left--
- Where did you get that?
- I'd like you to put all that
money back now.
- ♪ But I know I know
I'll go on ♪
[sirens wailing]
♪ 'Cause I haven't--
- Do you remember the time
you broke that window
on that Prius because you
thought there was a dog
in the backseat that was gonna
die from the heat,
but it was actually just
a leather jacket?
- Yeah.
- Well, I didn't tell anyone
about that.
- It's not the same.
- But couldn't it be?
- Put it back, Annie.
- ♪ A year ago
♪ I'd have died
♪ I would wait wait wait wait
and wonder why ♪
♪ Oh but I've learned
♪ That I--
- Come on, let's go.
- Go, go, go!
[overlapping shouting]
♪
- Go, go, go!
Clear.
- ♪ Plenty more where
you came from ♪
♪ There's a whole lot of fish
in the sea ♪
- Let's go,
we gotta move!
Everybody up!
Let's go!
- All right, folks.
- Go, go, go, go, go!
- You're safe, ladies.
Let's go.
♪
- ♪ Because I believe
♪ I believe, yeah, yeah,
I believe ♪
♪ I've got to believe
in faith ♪
♪ And I just haven't
♪ Oh no no no I
haven't-- ♪
- Tyler, please.
You don't wanna do this.
- I don't have a choice.
- I'll split it with you.
- I don't want it.
- I'll be your girlfriend.
- I'm gay.
- Huh.
- Wh--
- Tyler, please.
There has to be something
that you want.
Anything.
[cops shouting]
- Go!
- Let's go!
- Please.
- ♪ No I ain't gonna cry
♪ No no no no no no
- It was like his body
just knew what to do,
you know?
Like some reflex that
lay dormant until called upon.
Like Van Damme meets Bruce Lee,
but more lethal.
- She's exaggerating
a little bit.
- No, I just can't believe
that this whole time
I was working
next to a hero.
- I'm just pissed
they got away.
- Congratulations.
- Thank you.
Thank you, sir.
- Good work.
- Thank you, thank you.
- You did good, son.
You did good.
- Thank you.
[chuckles]
[suspenseful music]
♪
- Hey, how you doing?
- Right this way, sir.
♪
.
- What's that sound?
[beeping]
- Is it one of your toys?
[beeps]
Where are those robots
that Daddy got you?
[beeps]
Is it you that's beeping?
[beeping]
[distant TV sounds]
[beeps]
What is it?
Come here, baby.
[beeps]
- [grunts]
- Okay.
- Two, three, four...
That's 87,500.
- Sorry I don't have
smaller bills.
- Oh, it's--
Do you need a check
for your records?
- Just shred it.
Thank you.
Okay.
- Okay.
- How'd she do?
- Oh, baby girl's a warrior,
like her mama.
- Can we go see her?
- No, they're gonna call us in
when it's go time.
- I can't believe we're here.
- Believe it.
- Doctors, urgent care,
what?
It's all gonna stop now?
- No, you'll find something
to worry about.
[both chuckling]
- I always do.
[upbeat music]
- And 40 years later,
the blizzard of '78
still has people--
- Tonight, a Grand Rapids
woman speaks out after her
personal information
was used to e-file
a fraudulent--
[indistinct chatter]]
[dramatic music]
♪
- Experts are warning
to file your taxes--
- More I-75 closures coming
your way as the river bridge
project continues
to expand south.
[knocking]
Travelers should expect just
one open lane near--
[knocking]
- I don't know if he's FBI
or CIA or--
Jesus, Mary, and Joseph,
I feel so stupid, you know?
- Where did you meet him?
- At church.
- But you didn't say anything,
right?
- No, I don't think so.
I don't know.
I trusted him, you know?
I mean, I--
Like, I liked him.
I'm such an idiot.
- No, you're not.
- There, that's him.
[tense music]
- Mary Pat.
♪
- What?
- You are going
to need a drink.
- It's three in the afternoon.
- Then let's have a double.
♪
- Hey, Mr. Boland,
someone wants to test
the Maserati.
- Oh, uh, could you do it?
I gotta get home.
- You got a hot date?
- Eh, maybe.
[Eric Carmen's "Make Me Lose
Control" plays]
- ♪ My darling
- [singing]
♪ Turn the radio up
♪ To that sweet sound
♪ Hold me close
never let me go ♪
♪ Keep this feeling--
- ♪ Keep this feeling alive
♪ Make me lose control
[shattering sounds]
[horn honking]
- Mrs. Boland?
- Yes.
- He's gonna be fine.
- Oh, God.
Thank you.
- Just a couple
of bruised ribs.
Minor whiplash.
- Can I see him?
- He's up in imaging.
We're running a CT
just to be safe.
This is for pain.
- And this won't interfere
with the radiation?
He's on so many things now
because of all
the side effects.
- I'm sorry,
the side effects of what?
- Of the cancer.
Did you take his blood?
- Yes, we did.
[She Keeps Bees'
"Greasy Grass"]
♪
- Could I get some water?
- Of course.
♪
- ♪ Victory vision
♪ Seen them coming
- I have cancer.
- When will you know more?
We'll know more
after the appointment.
- What did the doctor say?
- There's no question.
- He has cancer.
- Cancer.
- For everything I did,
I just wanna say thanks
for letting me come back.
- You're bad when we
live here.
- Since when?
- Since he got cancer.
- --racketeering this evening
following the robbery
of an Ashfield area
Fine & Frugal.
Local authorities working
with the FBI say the men
laundered money through
several small businesses
in Wayne County, including
the Fine & Frugal chain.
According to authorities,
they were able to charge
the defendants after
a tip left by robbers
led a team of investigators
to the gang's illegal
financial activities.
- ♪ Took his eyeballs
♪
♪ Died in greasy grass
.
[pop music on radio]
- I did something.
♪
- You know where my mind goes.
- I know, baby.
- Like, it's PTSD level.
That treehouse really
messed me up.
- Do you want
to hear this or not?
♪
- [clears throat]
- So, I'm on the
freeway this morning.
And instead of taking
the Gratiot exit,
I just keep driving.
And I go all the way
to the border.
And then I go all the way
to that craft store.
- You did a pop-by on Big Mike?
- Oh, my God.
How's his foot?
- What did he say?
- Well, I go straight
up to him.
He's up on this, like,
forklift thing.
And I say, "Listen, just
because Rio's out
out of the picture doesn't mean
that we have to be."
And he gets down,
and he reaches into his pocket,
and he pushes a big fat gun
to my forehead.
And he says, "I don't wanna
deal with new players
in Detroit."
And I said, "Bitch,
we are Detroit."
- Bitch, he could have
shot you.
- Yeah, well, he really didn't
like what came next.
So I gave him a choice.
I said, "You're either with us
or you're on your own.
So, what's it gonna be,
Big Michael?"
- Big Michael.
- And he just looks at me
for the longest time.
And I'm like, "All right,
here it is.
At least I'll go in a blaze
of glory."
And then...
He shook my hand.
And he loaded up the car.
You guys.
I have six huge boxes
of wrapping paper
in that car.
- Yo, Daddy.
I told you she got cool.
- Who are you right now?
- [laughs]
You should see your
faces right now.
- Wait, what?
- Yours is whiter than usual.
[laughs]
- You made all that up?
- Even the forklift part?
- [laughs]
- Man, can you imagine?
- I mean, I gotta say.
Kinda sad it's not true.
- Well, it could be.
- We got robbed.
Again.
And I am P.O.'ed.
Pardon my French.
- How much have you had
to drink?
- I need to...
Listen.
I'm gonna blow your mind
about something, okay?
- You smell like a brewery.
- These women.
I know you're in some kind
of shady business with them,
but they are not good people.
In fact,
they are criminals.
- I--what did they do?
- They--they hit my store.
For a second time.
- Oh, my gosh.
That is...
So crazy.
- I know this is a shock.
And God knows you don't
deserve this,
but you fell in
with a bad crowd.
- What about Annie?
- That one is garbage.
- Is that why you tried
to rape her?
- [scoffs]
Uh, who told you that?
Was it that piece of trash?
Because that is not
what happened.
- What happened?
- It's complicated.
- Well, I want to know.
- We...
We sort of had a thing.
- You dated her?
- I mean,
she flirted with me constantly.
You see the way
she flaunts her goods.
Well, the low cut blouses,
that tattoo of hers.
I mean, it's a walking
billboard for...
S-E-X.
- So you raped her?
- No.
No.
See, I feel like you're not
even listening to me, okay?
[stammers]
Annie--she's no...
She's not like you.
She's not a good Christian
like you.
I mean, girls like that, they
want that kind of attention.
- Rape?
- No.
Just--
The rough stuff.
And, look,
there's a difference.
You know me.
I'm a gentleman.
But when a tease like that
pushes my buttons--
and you know what button
I'm talking about--
I'm apt to give her what
she came looking for.
And I'm sorry if that's not
pretty or romantic,
but it's human nature.
You know?
It is science.
- Do you have anything
you want to add?
- You recorded me?
Why would you do that?
- I could ask you
the same thing.
- That was before.
- Before what?
- Before I liked you.
- I think you'd better go.
- I want that back.
- Just because you want
something doesn't give you
the right to take it.
[door slams]
- Went old school.
Cinnamon Schnapps.
- My personal favorite.
That's like bat mitzvah
old school.
- [sighs]
Sadie's almost that age.
- Damn.
We old.
- Dude.
- She just looks so happy.
You know?
- Just stop.
- It was like there was this
whole other planet
called St. Anne's that
she never knew about
where everyone's cool with her.
And they play hackey sack.
And I've literally been
keeping her from it.
- She's there now.
- She could have been there
months ago.
Do you promise
you won't be a dick?
- No.
- Maybe I'm not the only person
who knows what's best for her.
- I'm sorry.
Say that again.
- Dick!
- I just wanna make sure
it's not the Schnapps.
- She needs you, too.
Not the Schnapps.
- That is literally exactly
what I needed to hear.
Not the Schnapps.
- Well, we just did in two
seconds what they pay lawyers
for in blood.
- Leveled up.
- Like some grown-ass folk.
- Yeah, except grown-ass folk
don't use the term
grown-ass folk.
- Hmm.
True.
[dramatic music]
♪
I should go.
- Me, too.
♪
- Chocolate shakes,
chocolate chip cookies.
- Mmm-hmm.
- Burgers.
What's the one that comes
on a donut, Mom?
- The donut burger?
Those look nasty.
- I want one now.
- Mmm-mmm.
- Okay, okay.
- You're new kidney's
gonna quit before
it even takes.
- Yeah, let's not do that.
- Can I have more Jell-O, then?
- Jell-O's good.
You can eat Jell-O
till your ears turn blue.
- I'll get the nurse.
I love you, boo boo.
- I love you, Mama.
- I got this.
You can stay with
hungry mungry.
- What's wrong?
- You know that guy
that I called a while back?
- The one with
the goofy mustache?
Excuse me, can we get some
Jell-O for 111?
- Of course.
- Yeah, the, uh, the feds
and the DPD took his gang down
last night.
- That's good.
What?
- Tell me what to do here,
Ruby.
- I don't--
- See, we got him because
they were laundering their
money through this grocery
store, and, uh, we wouldn't
even have known any of it
if, uh, these two women hadn't
robbed the place
a couple nights ago.
- That's lucky.
- Hmm.
- I don't think we should
leave her alone.
- It's the same store Beth's
little sister works at.
- Oh, my God.
Was she there?
- That's how you're
gonna play this?
- I mean, I haven't talked--
- It's the same damn store.
The same damn night that you
and your friend, Beth,
were going down to Ohio
to collect 87 grand in cash.
- Hang on, you think--
- There's no business,
is there?
No corporate.
All this was just
a bunch of BS.
- How could you think
I would ever do that?
- Your face.
Right now.
- I did it for us.
- I'm a cop, Ruby.
- I had no choice.
- What the hell am I
supposed to do?
[Spelles' "Wild Heart"]
- I don't know.
- You asked what it would take
for me to walk out the door.
♪
You knew the answer.
And you did it anyway.
♪
- ♪ In my dreams
♪ I am weightless
- Hey, honey.
I'm home.
- ♪ I am weightless
♪
♪ I swim like a comet
♪ Through the darkness
- Would have been here sooner,
but I got tied up.
♪
Surprise.
- I'm sorry, Beth.
- He didn't do anything.
- Oh, he tried.
He tried.
[laughs]
Got more fight in him
than I thought.
Ain't that right, champ?
♪
Oh, I'm sorry.
Does this--
Does this bother you?
- Let him go.
- What, you can't even handle
a little blood?
- [grunts]
- I thought you wanted
to be me.
I mean, that's what all this
is, right?
You tryna put me away.
I know you must got big plans.
But, see, you didn't think
things all the way through.
♪
It takes balls to do what I do.
You wanna be the king,
you gotta kill the king.
This stuff's medieval, darling.
- Please don't do this.
Please don't kill us.
- [laughs]
I ain't gonna kill nobody.
[laughs]
No, man, you are.
♪
♪ This is my escape
- So, what you think?
You got what it takes?
- ♪ Until I wake
♪ So let this
♪ Wild heart run free
♪
♪ Let this wild heart
run free ♪
♪