.
- Previously on
"Good Girls"...
- Are we going
to lose this house?
- No.
I mean, I don't know.
- Nancy and I are
suing you for custody.
- Can I have lunch money?
- Those kids take it again?
Douchebags.
- The drug that
you're talking about?
Ten grand a month,
out of pocket.
And I'm guessing
that may not be an option.
- How much is in the vault?
- 30 grand,
give or take.
- So when do you wanna do this?
- Ladies and gentlemen,
this is a robbery.
- You know how fast
they're gonna lock you up?
- [screams]
[glass clinks]
- [pants]
- He wants us to pick something
up for him in Canada.
It's wrapping paper.
It's just wrapping paper.
I just need to know
we're good.
I'm gonna need
to hear you say it.
- We're good.
- Here's to going
back to normal life.
- L'chaim to that.
- So what'd you
wanna talk to me about?
- Mom, mom, mom.
It's not fair.
For Tommy's birthday, we all
went out to a Pistons game.
We got box seats, and his mom
bought us all jerseys.
And then--
and then after that,
they rented a hotel
with room service.
- Yeah, and now Tommy's mom
can't afford college.
- Well, I want
a birthday party.
- How about a sleepover?
- With a chocolate fountain.
- You could nuke a Hershey bar.
- Mama?
- This is the worst
birthday ever.
- Mama?
- Listen, well, we can't just
afford a really big,
fancy party right now.
We just can't.
- Mama?
- But I promise you,
I'm gonna make it special.
I promise you, okay.
- Mama!
- What is it?
- Who's the man?
- What man?
- The man on my bed.
[upbeat music]
*
- No, no, stay--
stay here, stay here.
*
Hey, you wanna go swimming
at your dad's?
- Yay!
- Yay.
*
[indistinct chatter]
- Yo, Ruby.
- [sighs] That's my name,
don't wear it out.
- How does one become
a waitress here?
- Excuse me?
- Like, what college
has the best program?
[chuckling]
- I'll check if we're hiring.
- Do you have
to buy the uniform?
'Cause that's some--
I mean, that's some high
quality polyester right there.
I mean, that would set me back,
what--ten bucks?
- Ah [chuckles].
- Just go make him
another one.
He can't eat this now.
Come on,
chop-chop, Ruby.
- Is there a problem,
milkshake?
- What'd you call me?
- It's a trick I use
to remember orders.
Since I didn't go to college
and my memory's not so great.
You always order
that milkshake,
which you never finish,
so you can be sure
to leave my tip
in the bottom
of your nasty ass cup.
My two percent tip.
Three, if you're
feeling generous.
*
It's not the money that I mind.
I mean, if you can't afford it,
I get it.
I feel for you.
But please, let me know if
there's anything that I can do
to make your experience here
more delightful.
No? Well, then,
I'd appreciate it
if you left your
85 cents on the table,
and not in your shake today.
Cool?
Okay.
*
All right, sweetie, enjoy.
- Ah!
[shrieks]
- Oh, that might be hot.
- Ruby, get some ice.
- [whimpers]
- All right, the Marks Express
is leaving, choo-choo--ow!
Zipper.
What? What're you doing?
We--we're gonna be late.
- I hate everything.
- Excuse me?
I just got you these.
You told me they were "lit AF."
- They're too big.
They fall down.
- These are not too big.
No way.
I mean, you'd have
to really yank on them.
Hey, why are you so worried
about your pants falling down?
- I'm not.
- Hey, what--what's going on?
Tell me.
- No.
- Sadie, talk to me.
[calm music]
*
- Are people, like,
pulling your pants down?
- They wanna know what I am.
*
- So no big deal,
we'll buy you some belts.
Maybe something pink,
and pretty,
and girly, and sparkly, and--
alright, all right, all right.
Not the money maker.
Just hurry up,
put something on.
I don't care what it is.
[call phone vibrates]
Be outside in two minutes
or you're dead, I mean it.
- [whispering] Will you
tell us what's going on?
This is freaking me out.
- [whispering]
Oh, my God.
- Who is that?
- I don't know.
- What do you mean
you don't know?
- I mean, I came back
from the grocery store
and he was
just there.
And, I mean, I'm assuming
he's, like, an associate
of the gangbanger.
- Come on, I thought
we were done with that.
- Yeah, what the hell?
- Okay, okay, we were.
And then...
God, this sounds so crazy
even saying it--
- Spit it out.
[snaps fingers]
- I--I--
I offered to do another job.
- Uh--
- You asked for this?
- [guffaws]
- It's not like
we don't need the money.
We all still need the money.
- [snorts]
- So you asked for this?
- No, well, not this.
- [laughs]
- Shh.
- I'm sorry.
[chuckles]
I just can't believe
it's you and not me.
Come on, it's crazy.
- Look, I just--I just said
that we would possibly,
if the circumstances
were right,
pick up another load
of the fake cash.
- You volunteered us?
- It's not drugs.
It's paper.
I mean, it's literally paper.
- You can't sign people up
for criminal activity
like it's a bake sale.
- Noted, but can you
just help me
get this person out of
my house right now?
- Oh, you want some help now?
I'm sorry, why don't you
call your BFF,
the other gangbanger?
- He's not my BFF.
I don't even know
that guy's name.
- No, but I bet--
I bet he does, right?
Maybe I can, uh...
Okay, I guess I'll do it.
- Yeah, mm-hmm, I'm not.
- Just watch my back, okay?
Please.
- Just be careful.
[foreboding music]
*
- I'm sorry, I'm sorry.
- [stammers]
- Sorry, sorry, sorry.
Oh, God, okay.
Well, this is not a phone.
Just--just,
t--take this, take it.
Just take it.
- Oh, my--
*
- Okay.
Ugh.
Okay.
I have it,
I have it.
- What's the last number
he called?
- Papa John's.
- The last person, Annie.
- "Mom," "Mom,"
"Mom," "Mom," "Mom..."
- Oh, my God, why didn't
he just go to his mom's?
- "Mom," "Mom," "Mom..."
- I know, seriously.
- "Mom" and...
"Rio."
- That is not what I meant when
I said we'd do another job.
Who is that guy?
- He works for me.
- Do--does he wash the money?
- Regardless, there's been
a miscommunication.
- Oh, so you think you can pick
and choose what you wanna do
and when you wanna do it?
- She thought it would be
like driving for Uber.
- Who's at fault
is not important.
We are not qualified to take
care of a gunshot victim.
I mean, your friend needs
professional medical attention.
You're shaking your head.
Why are you shaking your head?
- 'Cause that kid
ain't going to no hospital.
- Why not?
- 'Cause there's people
looking for him.
- What if those people
show up here?
- Trust me, ain't nobody
gonna shoot up
Beaver Cleaver's house.
[upbeat pop music]
- No, I'm sorry,
that is not gonna work.
- No?
- I--[sighs]
- Oh.
Mm.
*
- I have children.
- * Looking like a zombie,
animal, animal *
* Hey, get out my way
- He's up there in
my daughter's bed.
I'm never gonna get
that blood out.
- I mean, she could sleep
on the floor.
Kids love that stuff.
- I'm pretty sure it'll cover
a new mattress.
- * Don't save me
*
- So, would we get
that money now, or...?
- When I pick him up.
- When's that?
- Sounds fair.
- So, we got a deal, ladies?
Or what?
- [exhales deeply]
- * Don't save me,
don't save me *
.
[telephone rings,
indistinct chatter]
[muffled speech]
- Mr. Petersen.
[fully audible]
Mr. Petersen.
Agent Turner
will see you now.
- [exhales]
- What happened after
they crossed the border?
- Wish I knew.
I lost visual.
- Mm.
Gummy?
- Yeah.
- Please.
So, just so I got this,
okay, these women,
they took a car--
- Stole.
I mean, they stole a car.
- And drove it over the border.
- What's your gut say?
- I mean, jeez.
Any number of things.
International drug ring.
Human trafficking.
Sleeper cell.
- Homegrown jihadis.
- I'm not ready
to rule out anything.
- Mmm.
- And the one
that works with you?
- Oh, I mean, if anyone
got radicalized, it's her.
[laughs]
- I bet.
What's her name?
- Annie.
- My Annie was a Paula.
She lived in my dorm.
- What?
- Ah, we both loved Hoobastank.
- Wait, hold on a second--
- But it didn't matter.
I was stuck I the friend zone.
- No.
- Just like you, right?
- No, that's not it at all,
actually.
- You sure about that, Leslie?
- They have committed crimes.
I can prove it.
Well, I can't prove it.
But I can.
But I can't.
I mean, I wa--I want to.
- I'll tell you what.
I'll do a little digging, okay?
But you gotta do
something for me too.
- Name it.
- Go to O'Brien's.
You know the bar on Birmingham?
Have a couple of cocktails,
and find yourself a nice girl.
Preferably one
that's interested in you.
- And you know
what they call it?
- What?
- A sizzling skillet.
It says sizzling right there
in the menu.
What does that tell you?
- Uh, that it might be hot?
- That it might be hot.
- Might not wanna touch that.
- You think?
And now they're threatening
to lawyer up.
- What?
What does Tony say?
- That I have to apologize.
- Well, all right, then.
- Why should I apologize?
Because I didn't tell
that idiot that the boiling,
bubbling, sizzling platter
in front of him
might be hot?
What's next, We start warning
people that their ice cream
might have a bit
of a chill on it?
Look out.
- Uh.
You--you wanna know why?
- Yeah, why?
- Oh, you--okay.
Come on, come here.
Come here for a second.
Come here.
[tender music]
[giggling]
These little people.
That's why you go back
in there and you suck it up.
Think we're gonna have to put
next month's meds
on four different
credit cards.
- I know.
- And even then,
we might not make it.
- Stan, you should see
these kids.
They come in there.
They're so rude
and disrespectful
and act like they're better
than everyone else.
- Uh, you know I get
called Paul Blart, like,
every single day, right?
Paul Blart.
Mall cop.
Where's your Segway?
Now, but I take it,
because at the end of the day,
I got this to come home to.
For them--um--you do
what you gotta do.
*
- Babe.
- Mm-hmm?
- [sighs]
Chill out with the cayenne.
- That's too hot?
- It's spicy.
- Damn it.
[door opens]
- Hey, I brought chili.
Stan made it.
It's spicy.
- [sighs] Thank you.
I'm so hungry.
- Did you stay up
all last night?
- I mean,
she stayed up all night.
I slept next to her
like a baby.
- Is he still out cold?
- Um, maybe we need, like,
smelling salts or something.
- Right, 'cause it's 1892.
- You want him to wake up?
- I want him to not die
in my house.
[thump]
[upbeat pop music]
What the--
- [gasps]
Oh, my God.
- His gun.
Go get his gun.
- W--where is it?
- Uh, in the closet.
- Hurry.
- Okay.
Where in the linen closet?
- Where is it?
- Top shelf.
- There's no gun in here.
Help me look.
- * I'm a gravedigger
*
* I'm a gravedigger
- * I'm a, I'm a gravedigger
*
* I'm a gravedigger
[gun clicks]
- [gasps]
*
- Beth, there's no gun in here.
- Found it.
.
[tense music]
*
- Where am I?
Where am I?
- Uh, my house.
You're in my house.
- Who the hell are you?
- I'm a friend
of your friend's.
He thought that you
would be safe here.
- I need a car.
- What?
- Give me your car keys.
- Do you understand
that we actually saved you--
- Give me the keys!
- Okay, I'm sorry.
- Now!
- I took the bus,
I took the bus.
- I have really weak nails.
I can't get it off.
- Okay, downstairs,
on the counter.
And just take it.
*
- [stammering,
whimpering]
*
- Two car seats
plus a booster?
What's that gonna set me back,
like 600 bucks.
- Well, maybe he'll realize it
and bring 'em back.
- That's not how
carjackings work.
- I don't want him back.
He just had a gun in my face.
[sighs] Guys,
what is even happening?
What are we doing?
- What do you mean?
- I mean, I am so tired
of almost dying.
- Oh, are you?
- Okay, let's just try
to get through this, okay?
- Oh, Carl.
- No.
- Carl who?
both: Emma's favorite bunny.
- He was on the dash.
- Now he's on a drive-by.
- Ugh.
- Mom?
- Hey, sweetie,
what are you doing here?
- Just don't be mad at Dad.
- Why? What did he do now?
- He told me
all about the party
with the bounce house
and the water slide,
and I invited, like,
all my friends.
Five can't come,
but--but 32 can.
- Hey!
Don't be mad.
- Do you wanna
go play some video games?
- Yeah, definitely.
- Let's do it.
- You're a dead man.
- Go upstairs right now and
tell him we can't afford it.
- You didn't see
his little face.
- I see his little face
every day.
- Oh, here we go.
- Every day for the rest
of my life
I have to say no to those kids
because of what you did.
- You know what he wants
for his birthday?
- I don't know, probably
an Xbox or "Minecraft"
or something very expensive.
- His mom and dad
back together.
- That's what he asked for?
- That's what he asked for.
- Damn it.
- Yeah.
- I would've gone for the Xbox.
- [snickers]
Least we can do
is throw him a damn party.
- Happy retirement?
- They were on clearance.
No one will notice.
- Yeah.
- Potatoes are dirt cheap.
- Hmm, what am I gonna do with
potatoes at a birthday party?
- Um, hot potato,
Mr. Potato Head.
Two uses.
- Bake 'em.
- Ah--three uses.
- How'd y'all find
everything today?
- Depressing.
- Fine.
- Yep.
- Still not sure
how you're gonna use
50 pounds
of potatoes.
- Well, just to let you know,
our return policy is 30 days
with a valid store receipt.
- Wait, is that on anything
in the store?
- Yeah, anything in the store.
- Anything,
in the store.
[upbeat pop music]
- * Pass me the bowl,
got the milk and the spoon *
* Yeah, she got
the coco puffs *
* She got the coco puffs
* She got
the coco puffs *
- Phew.
- Perfect.
- We're gonna need
a bigger cart.
- * Got me so high
I feel holy *
* We on that green guacamole
* And I've been [...]
the whole day *
* Man, we can shut it down
* She imported, man
She came from out of town *
* Show me how you do
* Show me
how you do *
* Show me how you do
[laughter]
- * Pass me the bowl,
got the milk and the spoon *
- Now we're ready.
- Just forgot a few things.
- [clears throat]
- Oh, I think there's
a coupon for this.
- Oh, that's all right,
we don't need it.
- Yeah, save it
for the next guy.
- Okay, would you
like to donate a dollar
to the homeless?
- N--not right now.
- So sorry.
- Money's kind of tight.
- Sorry.
[phone dings]
*
You guys, I gotta go.
It's Sadie's school.
- Yeah, go.
- I'll call you later.
*
- Where is she?
- Gosh, she's back in class.
I just finished talking to her.
- Well, what the hell happened?
- She punched a kid
in the face.
- Oh, okay.
Well, thank God.
- Thank God?
She punched a dude.
- Believe me,
he deserved it.
- I just barely talked them out
of suspending her.
- Greg, did she tell you why
she punched him in the face?
- N--no.
- They pull her pants down.
- What?
- Yeah, in the cafeteria
in front of everybody.
- Are you serious?
- Yes.
- Well, we gotta go tell them.
- No, no, no, no.
Greg, what is wrong with you?
That just makes it worse.
Trust me.
- Annie.
- Greg, in ninth grade
my mom went to the principal
because there was
a rumor about me
involving a coat closet
and some over the pants--
- I--I--remember.
- You do?
- [chuckles] Why do you
think I hung out with you?
- Shut up.
Just don't say anything, okay?
Please?
I will handle it.
- Ah, that terrifies me.
- [sighs]
I know.
- This is so messed up.
- Yeah.
I know.
- He couldn't sleep last night.
He was in so much pain.
Poor thing.
It's a third-degree burn.
We took pictures.
- I might need a skin graft.
[soul music]
- Well, we've all been sick
over this whole thing,
especially Ruby.
Isn't that right, Ruby?
- That's right.
- And she's so thankful for
this opportunity to apologize
in person.
Isn't that right, Ruby?
- That's right.
- She's gonna have to say
a little bit more than that.
- All due respect--
- I'm sorry.
This woman was careless
and rude and hurt my son.
- No--wait a minute.
Your son hurt himself.
- You went out of your way not
to warn him that plate was hot.
- Are you for real?
- Just say you're sorry.
She is sorry.
- And yet we still
haven't heard it.
Do you all have children?
- I do.
- Look at the example
you're setting.
- [mouthing words]
*
- I'm sorry.
Okay?
- Thank you, Ruby.
- It's not okay.
That was completely insincere.
And kind of bitchy.
- Oh, you want me to mean it?
- That'd be nice.
- I'm sorry.
How was that?
- That's great.
- Ah, no, no, no.
Wait a second, Tony.
- Eh--
- Let me give it another go.
I'm sorry.
*
I'm sorry you're too stupid to
understand basic human decency,
and how to treat anyone--
especially service people--
with respect.
- She doesn't mean that.
- No, I do.
I am one sorry bitch.
- Ah...
- I'm sorry you have your head
so far up your ass
that you think it's okay
to blame everyone else
for your son being a moron.
I'm sorry he's such
a punk-ass bitch
because that is a surface burn.
And I am especially sorry that
the friends you bring in here
are as entitled and as spoiled
and as awful as you,
because if kids like you all
are our future,
God help us all.
Now, that's what
I'm sorry about.
*
I'll go clean out my locker.
.
[funk music]
*
- Ah.
- Uh, uh, uh.
*
- Seriously?
- I upgraded you
to the 32-inch.
And got it for you
at wholesale price.
- Why?
I wanna do something nice.
- So that maybe
we could start fresh.
- Why?
- I've been praying on it
and...
I'm not proud of my part
in everything.
- Oh, so this is like
an "I'm sorry I tried
to rape you" cake?
- That was too many words.
- Whoa.
- Hey, there's
the birthday boy, huh?
[chuckles]
Hey, check it out.
This is for you.
- What is it?
- Well, just a little
something.
Some exfoliant,
a little--little scrub,
loofah, some--
bubble bath, you know?
You, uh, like
to take baths, huh?
- Okay.
- Get yourself
all squeaky clean?
- Okay.
Ah, you managed to make
that disgusting.
[clears throat]
- Hey, you got
turkey pinwheels, huh?
- Yeah, feel free to grab some
on your way out.
*
- Hey, how much do you think
they'd pay for this party?
- I have no idea.
*
- He's lined up
in the shotgun...
- Oh, oh, oh,
are we still up?
- No, tied 21-21.
Wester caught a two-yard
end zone pass, wide open.
- Ah, come--
- That's PI, that is PI.
- Come on, fellas.
- Every single time.
We never get the call.
- Really?
- Why don't we get that call?
Look at this.
[sighs]
- So how you holding up, man?
You know, with everything
that's going on.
- Great.
- Good.
- Yeah, we're doing great.
- All right.
- I mean...
It's been tough.
- Well, brother,
marriage ain't easy.
- [chuckles] It's like,
take your eye off the road,
you're gonna hit a speed bump
every now and then, right?
- No doubt.
- Just gotta keep moving on.
You know?
- For sure.
- But, I think
she'll come back.
- Well, pssh,
bro, for sure.
- [sniffles]
I mean she's got to, right?
[sobbing, sniffling]
- Tell me one thing.
- Yeah.
- When they gonna bring
Big Play Slay into the game?
- [chuckles]
- I mean, he gets it done.
He always does, right?
- Right? Yeah.
Ice. Dripping.
- Oh, oh, I'm sorry, my bad.
Ah!
- It's a good play, finally.
- Yes. One stop.
- Dude.
- Can they even do that?
- Isn't there some kind of,
like, HR protocol or something?
- [snickers]
It's a diner, not Microsoft.
- So unfair.
What did Stan say?
- I can't tell Stan.
- Oh, honey.
- Not when we're this
deep underwater.
I just--you know, I gotta get
something else going first.
- Well, good news is
there are plenty of other
extremely depressing
and unpleasant jobs out there.
Right?
[chuckles]
What?
I'm just--
I'm just saying, you know.
You want fun,
you rob a grocery store.
- Hey!
- You don't work
minimum wage.
all: * Happy birthday,
dear Kenny *
* Happy birthday to you
[cheers and applause]
- Yeah, whoo, whoo, whoo!
Happy birthday, buddy.
- Don't forget to make a wish.
- I wish that Daddy
could live at home again.
- Okay.
Got anything else?
- Come on,
blow out the candles, baby.
[indistinct chatter]
all: Yeah!
[overlapping chatter]
[tense music]
*
- Excuse me.
- Daddy, Daddy.
Daddy, Daddy?
- Hey, does, um...
- Daddy.
- Does Mommy ever
have any, like, you know,
new friends come over?
- Just a man in bed.
I'm not supposed to
tell you that.
- Huh.
[electronic dance music]
- You can't just walk in here.
- The door was open.
- It's because
I'm having a party
with children
and their parents.
Oh, my God, you brought a gun?
Of course you brought a gun.
- Is this your husband?
- Yes.
- What's he do?
- He sells cars.
- Is he good at it?
- [stammers]
Why does that matter?
- Yeah, he don't look too
trustworthy to me.
- What do you want?
What do you want?
- Came to pick up my boy.
- That's hilarious.
He's not here.
And by the way, when he left,
he held me at gunpoint,
and then stole my car.
So I'm gonna need
payment for that too.
- Oh, I'm sorry, what payment?
- Excuse me.
- Yeah, you get paid
when you do a job.
Did--did you do a job?
- He left.
- Then that's on you.
- What am I supposed to do?
Chain him to a bed?
- Oh, baby, what you think
this is, little league?
And you get a trophy
just for playing?
- I tried.
- I don't give
a damn if you try.
You gotta win, bitch.
- Beth, you--
you okay?
- Fine, yeah.
Fine.
[distant chatter]
- Cars, huh?
- Bye, guys, see you later.
- Oh, sorry.
- Excuse me.
- Hey, have we met before?
- Nah, I don't think so.
- You look so familiar.
- Nah, just a friend
of the family.
[chatter]
- I'm coming.
Thank you so much.
all: One, two, three,
atom bomb!
Oh!
[laughter]
One more time.
Let's go, come on.
[laughter]
- Okay, ready?
All right, go.
One, two...
- Atom bomb.
- Mmm.
- Hope you didn't
pop the bounce house,
'cause I gotta return that.
- That thing is awesome.
[clears throat]
So...
who's your new friend?
- What?
- You know, the guy
with the throat tats.
- Oh, he dropped off
the bounce house.
- Hmm, you were fighting
with the bounce house guy
in our bedroom?
- It's really none
of your business.
- Emma says he sleeps over.
- Oh, well, Emma also
thinks the Easter Bunny
sleeps in her closet, so...
- Is he the reason
you're not wearing your ring?
- Oh, my God.
- What? I have a right to know.
- You lost your right
when you stuck your penis
in your secretary.
- Come on.
- I want you out.
- What?
- Yeah, I want you gone now.
- No, it's Kenny's
birthday party.
- Kenny's birthday party is
over, and I am exhausted,
and I would like to put
the kids to bed.
- It's my house too, Beth.
- The hell it is.
- And you're still my wife,
so...
- Yeah.
I gotta get on that.
- Oh, yeah?
What does that mean?
- What do you think it means?
- Hey, you guys,
it's time to come in.
- Beth, please.
- Guys, time for bed.
- Can we just sit down
and talk for a second?
- I don't have
anything to say.
Guys!
- Just wait.
- What, Dean?
What?
- I just--
- What?
- I have cancer.
[laughter]
children: Atom bomb!
- Atom bomb, atom bomb.
.
- What am I gonna
tell the kids?
- I don't know.
- How are we gonna
pay for it?
- I don't know.
- What if he's really,
really sick?
[whimpers]
- We'll get
through it together.
- How do you know that?
- 'Cause we always do.
- When did life become
this big monster
that we just have to
constantly feed?
- All right there,
little Nietzsche,
go back to sleep, okay?
- I can't, I have to return
all that stuff.
- Don't worry about that.
I'll do it.
Where's the receipt?
- In my purse.
- Okay.
- I can't believe I spent
ten grand on a party.
- [chuckles]
Did you see that
little kid's face?
You're an amazing,
amazing mother.
- So are you.
- Besides, all that stuff
is getting returned,
so it doesn't matter.
- [sniffles]
[pensive music]
*
- Can you make breakfast?
- Hmm, well, that depends.
What'd you have in mind?
- My mommy usually
makes crepes.
- Well, Auntie's
specialty is cereal.
Mmm.
Hey, go inside
really quick, okay?
I'll be right there.
Go on.
- Yo.
Thanks for loaning me the whip.
- What did you do to it?
- Yeah, sorry about that.
- My sister drives that
to carpool
- I filled up the tank.
Things got a little out
of hand, so I mean,
I owe you all some time,
for real.
[upbeat music]
*
- Hey, do you need a ride?
- * They say they coming for
you but I don't want none *
* 'Cause I really
don't care... *
- Get the pudding.
Ooh.
- Ah.
- * This may be communism
but I tell you this is mine *
- Oh.
[chuckling]
[indistinct chatter]
- * What, what you've
been thinking *
- Oh.
- * I set it off
* What, what you've
been thinking *
- Yo, what's for lunch?
*
What you got?
- Just, like,
a veggie medley?
*
- Mommy wants you
to lose a few, huh?
*
So which one of y'all
little bitches
likes to pull
pants down?
You?
How about you, Porky?
I said, who is it?
- Are you kidding?
- I'm sorry.
- Here's how this is gonna go.
You pull pants down ever again,
I'm gonna break every bone
in your body.
- [scoffs]
Yeah, right.
Wait till he finds out
who my dad is.
[grunts]
[whimpers]
- What was that
about your dad?
I couldn't hear it over the
sound of your bones snapping.
Next time it's your thumb.
And you never
rat out your boy.
Snitches get stitches.
- * Now carry on
*
[door clanks]
- Agent Turner.
- Where you been?
I've missed you.
- Oh, really?
- No, sarcasm.
- Look, I just wanna
show you one thing.
- Leslie--
- Will you just take a look?
Okay, I saw this guy, okay?
He was with the three
of them before.
And saw him again yesterday.
Whatever they're into,
he's involved.
- Text it to me.
- Really?
Okay, great.
Um, uh, what's our next move?
- Just text it, Leslie.
- I could go undercover.
You know, I'm not afraid
to get my hands dirty.
"Donnie Brasco"
is my favorite movie.
[percussive music]
*
- ...at the very core of
our democratic system is...
- Jesus.
- Yeah.
- I mean, it's kind of awesome.
- And then it does take
a pretty dark turn.
- Yeah, believe me, I did not
know he was gonna do that.
I just tried to scare him
a little bit.
- Where did you find this guy?
- Uh, at work.
- So much for
background checks.
- [chuckles]
Right?
- Oh.
- My opponent makes the point
that the electoral system
of democracy negates the need
for civil disobedience,
however...
- I feel like she
really thinks she's in front
of the Supreme Court right now.
- Yeah, she's pretty amazing.
- Duh.
- Wait, wait,
where are the teachers?
- Lucky for us,
apparently this school is, uh,
pretty understaffed.
- You know, at St. Anne's I bet
you they'd just expel a kid
if he pulled
someone's pants down.
- Yeah, and they also
use the Bible
as their science textbook.
- [sighs]
- God, why do you
have to do that?
- What?
- Just, like--
You know, we were actually
having a nice moment.
We were like vibing.
- Vibing?
- Oh, I'm sorry,
we were "getting along."
Whatever.
Then you just say
something stupid
and you ruin it
every time.
- All right, I'm sorry,
I'm just saying that I feel
like she would be happier
at a place like--
- Yes, I know what you feel,
okay?
You've made that abundantly
clear, thanks.
- I'm not just talking
about her.
- Oh--oh,
you're doing this for me?
- You're killing yourself
trying to support her.
- Oh, my God,
okay, you know what?
I really appreciate it, Greg.
Thank you so much
for looking out for me.
That's just so
sweet of you.
Just so you know,
I have some pretty dope stuff
in the works right now.
- [chuckles]
Yeah, like what?
- Laugh it up,
you'll see.
- * Good morning,
good morning *
- Mom.
- * We talked
the whole night through *
* Good morning,
good morning to you *
* Good morning
- See, that's why they're gonna
put us in assisted living
when we're old.
- Okay.
- Where you going, early bird?
- Um, I picked up a few
extra shifts this week.
- That's my girl.
- Do you mind
holding it down?
Probably be late a lot.
- Psh, I got these people.
- Okay.
- Oh, hold on.
- Oh, yeah.
- I'm proud of you.
- For what?
- Sucking it up.
I know it wasn't fun.
- Oh, you know,
they go low, we go high.
- [chuckles]
Bye, baby.
- Bye.
- Okay.
Guys, Mommy going.
- Bye, babies.
both: Bye, Mom.
[upbeat music]
- We have
a business proposition.
- Aw, you guys didn't
hit me up to do brunch?
- To clean your fake money
without having to deal
with drug dealers
or street people.
- Street people?
- I got a system.
- It's a liability.
- It gets the job done.
- How'd your friend
get shot again?
- What're you proposing?
- Let us do it right here.
- You wanna clean
fake cash here?
- Or any big box retailer.
You know, Walmart, Costco.
They have very generous
return policies.
- And no one thinks twice
about a wife buying her husband
a flat screen TV
or new tires for the minivan.
- We trade it all in
for fresh cash.
- Fake money in,
real money out.
*
- Y'all got it all
figured out, huh?
What's in it for you?
- 20% cut of the profit.
- Oh, is that right?
[chuckles]
There anything else
while we're at it?
Y'all want health care?
Union breaks?
- Just for the record,
I'll never smuggle anything
up my butt.
- I could be talked into it
if the compensation was
appropriate--wait.
Where are you going?
- Uh, I gotta go
buy a duvet cover.
- Are you in or...?
- We'll give it a try.
- We're not here to try,
we're here to win, bitch.
- Oh, my God.
*
- 10%.
- 15.
- 12 1/2.
- Okay, deal.
- Cool.
I usually pay 30.
- * I feel brand-new
[keyboard clacks,
mouse clicks]
- Hey, what're you doing?
- Um...
Just playing Dr. Google
and freaking myself out.
- Yeah, maybe don't do that.
- Yeah, right.
- When will you know more?
- I got a bunch of scans
and tests next week.
- Okay.
Well, I'll go with you.
- You don't have to.
But that would be great.
Um, hey,
I just wanna say thanks
for letting me come home.
- You're gonna be
okay in here?
- Oh, yeah, totally.
Kenny's psyched,
so am I.
I get to sleep on the top bunk.
- Uh, I--better go get that.
- Yeah.
Hey, Bethie.
Don't worry,
I got this.
- I know.
[upbeat music]
*
- Hi, I'm looking
for Mrs. Boland.
- That's me.
Can I help you?
- I'm hoping you can.
*
.
[upbeat music]
- * Don't save me,
don't save me *
*
* Don't save me,
don't save me *
*
* Don't save me,
don't save me *
*
* Don't save me,
don't save me *