You're bleeding
through your bandage.
Good morning.
Don't we need to
get you to a doctor?
I am a doctor. That didn't
come up last night?
We didn't do a lot of talking.
I'm good.
You never told me
what caused your accident.
I was stabbed by a patient.
That'll teach me to overbill.
If she likes crippled guys, I'm
free for the next six minutes.
What do you want?
Forty-five
year-old truck driver.
Recurrent seizures,
no metabolic or structural...
Does this look
like a good time?
Sort of. At least
as good as the other
12 times that I've
called and paged you
in the last three weeks.
Those times,
I just didn't feel like
talking to you.
Kinda like now.
I'd apologize again,
but I'm still waiting
for you to accept
the first one.
You do work for me. I am entitled
to ask when you're coming back.
I don't know when
I'm coming back.
I don't know if
Got a problem with that'?
Fire me.
It's good to see
you in the hospital.
As a patient,
if not as a doctor.
Believe me, I'd rather be
the guy with the clipboard.
How you doing?
Arrhythmias are gone, fine
motor control's improving.
Not what I meant.
If you need to talk to
someone, a professional...
I'm fine.
Fine enough to
get back to work?
You don't have
to work for House,
but you do owe me
20 clinic hours.
What'? Getting knifed
doesn't buy me an extension?
Buys you whatever you need.
But I know you.
If all you do is
physical therapy,
and your
nighttime version of it,
you'll lose your mind faster than
you regain those fine motor skills.
I have this terrible pain in my left shoulder.
It came out of nowhere.
And nothing seems to help.
Any other symptoms? Chest pain?
Light-headedness?
No, none at all.
What were you doing
when the pain came on?
Just sitting and praying.
She'd been helping to
make the altar breads
that morning,
but no hard physical work,
or repetitive motion.
Couple of possibilities.
You have enlarged
lymph nodes, so
I'd like to start by
ruling out breast cancer.
And I do mean rule out.
It's probably nothing.
I'm gonna do
a quick breast exam.
Do you mind
stepping out for a moment?
Not at all.
Thai was so I could ask
about the second possibility.
Left-sided pain means it could be
angina, which is made worse by stress.
Might not be a coincidence
that the pain
started on the verge
of a major life change.
How did you know?
Blue veil means
you're a postulant,
haven't taken your vows yet.
Brown vestments
means you're Carmelites,
cloistered nuns,
which explains the chaperone.
You're about to withdraw
from the world for good.
I was a seminarian.
Who obviously
didn't take his vows.
Cassock made my ass look fat.
Do you mind unbuttoning your
shirt and lying down for me'?
Okay.
I have had second thoughts.
I'm kind of a wreck.
A life of perpetual enclosure
and almost complete silence?
If you weren't
wrestling with this,
I'd say there's something
really wrong with you.
I'm going to admit you.
There's a little mass here, and
I'd like to get it checked out.
It's just a benign fat
deposit, her imaging's clean.
Stress test, too. It's not angina.
So why the shoulder pain?
Is it possible that
she hurt her shoulder?
Thanks a lot.
I didn't tell him.
You were cagey about
where you were going,
and Chase has been
cagey in general.
Good chance I'd find the two
of you in the same cage,
so I had Park follow you.
How are you feeling?
Better.
Heard your arm's
healing nicely.
Good to see you on your feet.
Patient's a nu n?
Were you turning back to your
long-abandoned faith in time of trouble?
She was next up in the clinic.
And I don't want your help.
You got stabbed, you blame me.
But what did you learn about me
that you hadn't
known for years?
Maybe I was an idiot before,
and I'm not one now.
Or maybe the reverse is true.
Thanks for all your help.
Your soul sister is
having a fungal infection
from the unprocessed wheat
in the altar breads.
Explains the shoulder pain
and the jumbo lymph nodes.
Thanks for all my help.
I'm sorry I led House to you.
It's part of the job.
Maybe we could get
a meal after work tonight
if you want some companionship.
You asking me out on a date?
No. I just...
I guess that sounded...
Must be scary to be back.
All those knives and needles,
infected blood and tissue
everywhere you look.
Just thought you might need
someone to talk to about it.
Just knowing you're there
for me is enough. Thanks.
Ever surf Kirra Point?
Obviously you're Australian.
I've surfed all over the Gold Coast.
Don't tell me you have.
The closest I got was Waimea Bay.
I grew up on Maui.
If you don't mind me asking,
why are you becoming a nun?
You're asking because I surf?
Well, I know that Jesus walked
on water, but...
Plus the average postulant's
a lot younger than you.
What were
you doing before this?
Not much of anything.
Worked as a nanny,
moved around a lot,
bunch of failed relationships.
And then what? God spoke to you?
You heard the calling?
Something like that.
Does there have to be some dramatic
moment where the skies part?
Usually, yeah.
Is that what happened to you
when you entered the seminary'?
Mom drank, Dad worked, they
stuck me in Catholic school.
Priests and nuns were the
closest I had to family.
Turned out that wasn't much of a
reason to join the priesthood.
Is that why you left?
Something like that.
I think I may throw up.
What's wrong with me?
Not a fungal infection.
You're probably wondering,
why the soda balloons.
I'm not.
Well, I'll tell you.
You're not the only one
whose life
spiraled out of control
when you got
knifed in the ventricle.
Taub has decided...
I need help with my patient.
She's vomiting. That's not
from a fungal infection.
So what are you
planning to do now
that you're not working for me?
I have no idea.
Almost dying's been clarifying.
I can do anything.
You can do anything,
so you come back to
the same building you
worked in for years?
Guess you can cross
that off your bucket list.
Can we get to my
patient sometime soon?
As soon as you admit that
you're a confused mess, sure.
You'll help me.
Because even though
you don't find my
case interesting,
you find my interest
in it interesting.
When you put it that way...
Ascending cholangitis.
Missed me!
It can't be,
bilirubin's normal.
Clinical signs can show
up days before lab signs.
This is great, we should
make this a regular thing.
She can't feel her foot at all.
What does this mean?
Means I've gotta spend more time
consulting with a colleague.
His 17-ketosteroid levels are low.
How can he be...
He tried to tongue-kiss
Park when you were closer.
Think his sexuality's normal?
I need more help. My patient has
a new symptom, ischemic foot.
Get the lecture out of your system,
so we can talk about my case.
Let me start
with an allegory...
Okay, I'm curious...
Your overreaction
to your stabbing is
to blame me even as
you're drawn to me.
Taub's is to take moronic
self-defense classes
that won't defend
him against anything.
Krav Mega. Which helped
me block your shot,
and will continue to
help me defend myself
in a building full of
drugged-up strangers.
Taub has to accept that
by instinct and genetics,
he is a coward,
who's better off running
and hiding at
the first sign of danger.
I've already fended off six
of your blitzkriegs in a row.
And the seventh? And the eighth?
And the nth?
If you get him,
what's that gonna prove?
That unexpected things happen.
By definition, no class
can teach you to expect them.
Which is why Taub is
idiotic to study them,
and you're idiotic to attach
any significance to them.
Blood clot.
Her D-dimer's normal.
On the other hand“.
What if he's right about the
blockage, but wrong about the cause?
Vasospasm.
Explain everything
but the lymph nodes...
Any minor infection could
have caused those.
Calcium channel
blocker to treat.
Are you okay?
I almost got you killed by
bringing a scalpel into that room.
I could feel better about that.
You saved my life, too.
I think the ledger's clear.
But how can you
not be traumatized?
Can't change what happened.
I can only make
better choices from here.
So you're Zen about it, but won't
let go of your anger toward House.
I'm seeing a trauma counselor.
I think you should, too.
I'm okay. Just knowing you're
there for me is enough.
The convent lets you have this?
I borrowed it from
one of the nurses.
I'm still on temporary vows.
It may be the last time I
hear Eminem for a while.
You're using an iPod, but I've
never seen you use rosary beads.
What day did Jesus die?
I know, one gospel says Passover,
another says the day before.
How many times did the cock crow
before Peter's third denial?
Once or twice?
You can't argue away my faith.
Why'? Because it's so strong
even plain contradictions...
Because it's not that strong.
I'm not saying
I don't have faith.
I just haven't
felt the calling yet.
No one joins the clergy
without having an epiphany.
Like God's love is
speaking to you directly.
It's the silence,
the contemplation, the order.
I need them.
I'm hoping everything
else will come later.
That's not an answer. If you want
silence, you can get earplugs.
I tried the outside world.
It wasn't enough.
Have you been married?
No.
No kids?
You never found a career?
Doesn't sound like the outside
world got much of a try.
What you're
headed towards now...
Fourteen hours
a day in silent prayer,
never having a family,
never touching
another human being...
Just because that's what
you'd miss the most...
The nurses talk.
Nothing's wrong
with having fun.
They said you were almost
killed three weeks ago.
You go right back to fun?
Is that why you want to be a nun'?
Someone broke your heart?
No.
I'm just looking
for something more.
So am I.
I'm late for
work in the clinic.
Really? George Washingbaum?
He was a character
in the Flintsteins.
Just hiding out till
House leaves the cafeteria.
Those self-defense classes,
you think they're making
any kind of difference?
Not as much as
House's surprise attacks.
He thinks three steps ahead,
so I do, too.
Which is why you should accept his
apology and come back on the team.
He's annoying' he's maddening,
but he makes us all better.
Note to self.
Foot color's good,
arterial pulse is good,
capillary refill's good.
And her shoulder
pain's all gone.
Looks like you're
ready to go home.
I'll get the car
and meet you out front.
I'd say I'm in the book, but not the
one you'll be reading from now on.
Six years ago,
I was a nanny in Honolulu.
For this beautiful
two-year-old boy.
I loved him, probably spent more
time with him than his own parents.
One day, I was in the park,
talking with another nanny.
He wandered out of the
sandbox, into the street,
into the path of a moving car.
That could've
happened to anyone.
I don't think so.
And even if it did,
they'd blame themselves
for the rest of
their lives, too.
You shouldn't.
And you shouldn't run from
what can still be a good life.
I'm running to God.
After what happened to you, don't
you want to remake your life?
Not by hiding myself away.
I hope it works out for you.
It is gonna be hard,
not touching anyone.
Who knew Mother Inferior
was a smokin' hottie?
No wonder you're
playing handsies with her.
You think I'm hitting on a nun?
Angry at God,
or I just need a challenge?
Or you're
terrified of intimacy,
which is why
you're a serial slut,
but right now you're grasping
at an emotional life raft.
Ideally, someone for whom
intimacy's not an option.
That actually makes sense,
which I can't say
about anything else
you've been doing.
I'm not emotionally
involved with her.
And much as I'd love
to hear you contradict me,
I have a 7:30
appointment to explore
my intimacy issues at La Scala.
I'm talking to this agent
he's a bit of a sleaze,
but he's really excited
about representing me.
Although he can't take on
any new clients right now,
he's trying to get me an audition
for one of those online soaps.
Have you ever
watched one of those?
Am I boring you?
Unfortunately, yeah. Sorry.
Hi.
You're not supposed to be here.
Or anywhere.
You were right,
I was running away.
Oh, now you're shy.
It's brighter in the morning.
So, are we gonna spend the rest
of eternity in a lake of fire
while pointy-tailed demons
poke at us with sticks?
This is a little scary for me.
I had a whole life planned, not
that I wasn't struggling with it...
And then I met you.
Don't worry, I know you're
not the relationship type.
I'm not not the relationship type.
I was married once.
Relax.
You're fine.
So what's next for you?
I have to find a place to live,
get my old job back...
I'm sure I'll feel guilty,
start doubting...
Well, as long as
you keep dealing with
your doubts in
the same way, then...
Moira?
I'm sorry,
did you say something?
Your neck...
What?
Are your ears ringing?
Yeah.
What does that mean?
Let me get you back to
the hospital right away.
The artery
that's bringing blood
to your brain,
it's coming apart.
It means you could stroke. I've
paged a team of our best doctors.
I don't have to cough as much.
It's clotted up.
Is that bad?
We're almost there.
Get me her 02 level.
What are you doing?
I want to make sure I can
position her wrist properly.
- For what?
- ABG.
I don't need an ABG,
just get a pulse ox.
I'll do it,
grab a consent form. Go.
We need to
operate right now, okay?
Good. To operate.
Can you repeat this? "No
ifs, ands or buts about it."
No about it, and no ifs...
Get her into OR 11.
Carotid dissection,
four-inch pulsatile mass
in her neck,
and some Broca's aphasia.
There's gotta be a clot
keeping her from bleeding out.
Pulse?
Bounding, four-plus.
It was a three-plus
twenty minutes ago.
Twenty?
I thought she just got here.
That blood looks pretty dry.
Cut yourself shaving?
You know, that can
happen when the nun
you woke up with
coughs blood on you.
You slept with a nun?
Forget nun,
you slept with a patient?
Former. To both.
Internal neck trauma?
That's impressive.
It's happened to me
a few times. Up high.
Dr. Chase.
The clot's broken. Bring
her in and pack her nose.
We're gonna need
number three Vicryls.
We're gonna fix this.
You're not going
to operate on her?
Kapur and Carlyle
are unavailable,
Reilly's done far fewer
dissections than I have.
He's also slept with her far
fewer times than you have.
Your judgment's compromised.
I spent the night with her, doesn't
change how I make an incision.
Tell him.
Do the surgery.
You're trying to
score points with him
at the risk of
a patient's life.
He's the better surgeon.
Vascular clamp. You're not
going to put her on bypass?
It'd take a half
hour to set up.
You clamp now,
she could stroke out.
She's already got
neurological symptoms.
We wait 30 minutes, she'll
definitely have brain damage.
You're trying to make sure
she's either perfect or dead.
She's not going to die.
If I get this done
in five minutes,
she won't stroke out.
You don't know that you will.
And you can't know because you
can't think clearly about her.
Vascular clamp.
Occlusion time,
9:46, 23 seconds.
Vascular scissors.
We're over five minutes.
Ultrasound.
Good flow.
Lighten the anesthesia.
You're not going to
close the wound first?
No.
Can you hear me?
Repeat this.
"No ifs, ands or buts."
I'm sorry about before.
You're scared, aren't you?
That's why you
wanted companionship.
It's why you cried out
when House shot at Taub.
What exactly are you scared of?
A needle stick? Some other
nut pulling a scalpel?
I'm scared of everything.
It sucks that there was a
stabbing, but you'll get over it.
Like you have?
You weren't even there.
I know. I...
I left the room,
it was pure luck...
I was in the room.
That was pure luck, too.
I get that you're scared and guilty.
You're still a doctor.
I don't have time to
teach you to act like one.
We removed the artery,
found nodules.
Could mean lupus.
Negative ANA.
Where are you going?
Great thing about assigning
Taub fraudulent lab work
is you know exactly
where he's gonna end up.
Great thing about assigning Taub
obviously fraudulent lab work
is you get to watch
his inner paranoiac at work.
And then,
two to the head.
Can we talk about my patient?
Quite a journey.
Starts with a surgical
tool in your heart,
and ends with
a surgeon's tool in a nun.
What's the plan?
The plan's to cure her.
If it's not meaningless sex, kinda
screams out for an end-game.
You're the dog that's chasing the Popemobile.
You sure you want...
Oh, my God.
Taub is interrogating
the janitor.
He must think that
I hired him to attack.
Actually, why didn't I do that?
Plaques could be
confused for nodules.
Which would mean...
Syphilis?
Explains the shoulder
and foot involvement.
Hope you practiced
immaculate contraception.
Lock and load.
Boo-yam
Boo-yah to you, too.
But I hadn't had sex in years.
Tertiary syphilis
means you've had
the disease for
at least that long.
Does that mean
you also have it?
Probably not
contagious at this point.
Can it cause hallucinations?
It's unlikely. Why?
While I was on the operating table,
it didn't feel like a dream,
I saw the boy who
I was caring for,
the one who died.
He walked right up to me.
What did he say?
He just held my hand.
It was like he forgave me.
Do you think that's crazy?
I think it should give you
solace, help you to move on.
You slept with your patient?
You're off the case.
I saved her from brain damage.
You think my judgment's
the least bit compromised?
She's still sick.
If she dies, we'll be
in the middle of
a brand new investigation.
This is about you
covering your own ass?
I gave you time, leeway,
and you decided to do
whatever the hell you wanted.
House can dance
all over the rules,
gets me knifed,
and he gets a pass.
I break a rule,
no one gets hurt,
but you kick me
off my own case?
Unfortunately, yes.
I'm sorry. I took
that scalpel for you.
That's why I did this.
Three weeks ago, you never would
have slept with a patient.
And you never would have
operated on her after.
You need help.
I need to get away from House and
everything that reminds me of him.
By breaking the rules, not
caring what anyone else thinks?
You're gonna get away from
him by turning into him'?
It hurts.
Right upper quadrant,
pain and distension.
What's wrong with my stomach?
Nothing. This is your liver.
The liver failure could be from
intraoperative hypotension.
Checked the anesthesia sheet,
pressure was fine throughout.
Thrombus?
That voice in the hall that
none of us have any reason
to be listening to is,
not surprisingly, wrong.
Abdominal
ultrasound was negative.
Then we have to
assume liver failure's
just another symptom
of whatever she's got.
Trousseau's syndrome could send
clots, cause the ischemic foot,
add the enlarged lymph node,
macrocytosis...
Disseminated
T-cell lymphoma.
Wilson said it wasn't cancer.
Wilson says it's
not breast cancer.
Sarcoidosis.
Normal ACE level.
Highly insensitive for sarcoid.
Negative chest X-rays aren't.
Then we've gotta biopsy.
Yeah, Foreman's clearly wrong.
You're clearly not
grasping at straws,
because you're clearly not
emotionally involved.
I know you want to
believe this is something
we can cure.
It's not. I'm sorry.
How soon will they
know if it's cancer?
Within hours.
And if ii is?
There's always chemo.
You say that like
it's not gonna work.
It could extend your life.
Years?
I'll be here as
much as you need.
You still never told me
why you left the seminary.
Mary Knoller.
Wife of the groundskeeper.
He caught me with her,
got me with a rake.
Those scars on my ass you may
have noticed...
Why didn't you
tell me that before?
Because it was so shallow.
I wasn't exactly wrestling with
great theological questions.
I don't believe that.
You don't sleep with
the groundskeeper's wife,
not unless you're struggling
with whether you belong there.
I always wanted to believe.
Would've made my life a lot easier.
It never took.
Doesn't
mean
it's too late.
Are you having trouble
talking, like before?
I can get the words out...
Just feels heavy when I do.
Where?
Wherever my
chewing muscles are.
I'll be right back.
House finally got you?
He tried, but...
I gotta go.
You should have seen it, it was perfect.
She has jaw claudication.
If you only heard claudication
and carotid dissection...
I'd say giant cell arteritis,
and I'd tell your former teammates
to put her on steroids.
She's gonna live.
Yeah.
And then what?
They say my liver
function's better,
that I can get
out of here soon.
And when you do' I want to
take you to Puerto Escondido.
Mexico?
The Mexican Pipeline.
Early May is when the surf
really picks up, but...
What's wrong?
I spoke to the prioress...
You're going back?
I felt the calling.
When you saw the boy?
I felt God's love, his grace. I've
been waiting my entire life for that.
It's not real.
I know you didn't feel anything
when you almost died. I did.
You fell oxygen deprivation, you felt
your brain releasing noradrenaline.
You didn't say that before.
I wanted you to
move on with your life.
I wanted to reassure you.
I wanted you to feel better.
And now you don't?
Now...
I think I love you.
"Noradrenaline and Near-Death
Experiences." Oh, dear.
You saw God?
She did. She wants to go
back to the monastery.
And now you're preparing
a PowerPoint presentation
to keep her in your garden
of earthly delights.
You're an idiot.
Because I've
found someone I love?
Because you're an idiot.
At least you two
have that in common.
Her feelings are based on a chemical process.
They're gonna wear off.
You just slept with her, your
brain is exploding with oxytocin.
You think that's gonna last
through the ages?
She's throwing away her life
because of blind faith.
So are you.
She's found something she wants
to build her life around.
It's a total illusion,
but apparently she'll take
a little ignorance
with her bliss.
And you want to take that away.
How many times have you thrown
the truth in people's faces?
Because it's the truth.
Not because
we're gonna live
happily ever after.
Either your
relationship just blows up
like every other
non-magical romance,
or she stays with you
but blames you for
stripping all
the meaning out of her life.
This has nothing to
do with the truth.
You don't like that
I'm reassessing my life,
that I want to
change it, that I can.
Anyone can screw up a life. I
never said that wasn't possible.
You're incapable
of human connection,
so you want
everyone to be like you.
If I wanted you to be like me,
I would be urging you to make
a stupid, stubborn decision
that blows up your life and
leaves you lonely and miserable.
You reassess your life
when you've made mistakes.
You didn't.
You just got stabbed.
Don't look at the book.
I haven't done a jugular line
since my residency,
I don't want to
needle the carotid.
What's the first step?
- Palpate the SCM.
- Where?
Middle third of the neck.
I'm happy I knew you.
So am I.
Robert.
Twenty-four-year-old
water treatment worker
with pyrexia and double vision.
A mystery.
How'd he get sick
working in a sewer?
Ed Norton was
the picture of health.
Abscess?
Would have seen it on the MRI.
Diphtheria paralyzing
the ocular muscles?
No, paralysis
was first. Aneurysm?