We're in the car, honey. We're
going to the hospital for tests.
We're in the hospital. We're
going to the doctor's office.
Can you tell me
what this is called?
You use it to get
food from inside.
Yes, but what's it called?
Is it a spatula?
No.
Good.
Is it a can opener?
No. It's... it's.4.
You're trying to
make me look stupid.
You can go to hell! Why don'!
You kill yourself?
Andres.
It's okay.
There she is.
Here I am.
Here. Come on.
You just need to answer
a few more questions,
then we're going home.
We'll have lunch, okay?
Okay.
I'm sorry.
I have Alzheimer's.
I know.
The mood swings come on quickly,
but it's under control.
Don't worry. He's actually
perfect for the drug trial.
On.
Thank God.
We can start as
soon as next week.
Andres! Oh, my God!
And res'?
Early onset familial Alzheimer's.
Brazilian descent.
Blood chemistries
showed high ammonia.
Vomiting stopped after the
ER put him on antiemetics.
Any recent health issues?
Just a sore throat
a few weeks ago.
How advanced is he?
Could be hyperalimentation.
Advanced enough,
but no IV feedings.
The wife shut down her
floral company to stay home
and feed him every meal he's
had in the last four years.
Do we owe this case
to your guilt
at having ignored
your own forgetful mommy?
My guilt over my mom is
why I put up with my dad.
You're taking this case
because we're running a Phase Two
trial on an Alzheimer's drug.
You couldn't round up enough
doddering, old guinea pigs,
so you need us to
fix this little piggy?
I'd like to sit in. Especially
since you're short a team member.
You mean Taub?
Got him in here.
He asked for personal days.
His daughter's sick.
Isn't that the point
of having a spare?
I denied his request
After I'd already approved it,
which you knew because
I sent you a memo.
Dr. Adams, taped under your
chair is an index card.
Would you read ii, please?
"Wednesday, 2:43 p.m.
"A black pawn will believe
he's the black king
"and attempt to capture the
white head of diagnostics."
It's 10:15 on Friday.
Damn it. {SIGHS) Look, the
point is, I saw this coming.
Dr. Foreman and I did not
always see eye to eye,
but he never had
the power to overrule me.
Now that he has the power,
he won't be able to resist
the temptation to use it.
With great power
comes great micromanaging.
And great vests.
I know you're
the better diagnostician.
I'm not gonna interfere.
I'm only hereto help.
Could be transient nitrogen
load from a GI bleed.
Not if the vomiting's
persistent.
Which we won't know, because
the ER put him on antiemetics.
Take him off.
Wait. He was
puking his guts out.
We'd risk aspiration.
I'm just disagreeing,
not overruling.
So glad you're on board.
Take him off antiemetics.
Do an upper endoscopy
to check for bleeds.
It could be
a bladder infection.
We'll run a pregnancy test.
I'm not pregnant.
Any type of birth control
can fail.
Not mine.
Oh, I'm sorry. You said
you were married?
Yeah. Happily...
It's okay. Sex can wane
in any marriage over time.
No, no.
We've never had sex.
We kiss and cuddle, but neither
one of us is interested in sex.
You're both celibate?
No, neither of us.
Celibacy is a choice.
This is our orientation.
We're asexual.
Not quite sure what box
to check here.
You're making a mistake.
If I had the power to veto him,
given all the crap I've put
up with over the years,
I don't know if I could
use it objectively.
I do.
I can. I have.
It might be easier if you'd
stay out of the room.
I thought it'd be different.
This week.
I'm supposed to talk to his PO about
getting his ankle monitor off early.
You're saying he
should defer to you?
No. I'm just saying what he's
doing doesn't seem rational,
which makes me think it's rational
in a way I'm not privy to.
He always has a plan.
And he's always
self-destructive.
He may just be shooting
himself in the ankle.
I know it feels strange. Dr. Chase
is just looking in your throat.
We're in the hospital.
You're fine.
That's a pretty nice
trophy there, Andres.
He coached youth soccer.
Took a team that
was zero-and-six
all the way to the state
finals at Long Branch.
Hey, thanks for
doing this in here.
Switching rooms can
be very disorienting.
You take very good care of him.
I love him.
Sickness and health, right?
Upper esophagus is clear,
moving on to the GE junction.
Hi.
Hey.
I'm sorry, family members
only during procedures.
I'll wait outside.
Oh, no, please, it's okay.
Joseph helps me
with my husband sometimes.
He's a good friend.
Which means not family.
Wait, we're gonna
be here a while.
Why don't you show Joseph where
the visitor's lounge is'?
Okay.
What?
I'm surprised you didn't go
into the diplomatic corps.
Oh, you think they're...
No.
If they're having sex,
it's probably
with their genitals.
Mallory-Weiss tear. Vomiting
must have torn the lining.
You know that close to 1% of the
population identifies as asexual?
We really got to get you laid.
If I have to plow that
furrow myself, so be it.
I've a patient who's asexual.
Is she a giant pool of algae?
It's a valid
sexual orientation,
according to this article,
at least.
Yeah, I think I read that, too.
Is that Fugliness Weekly?
She's perfectly
fine-looking.
Happily married for 10 years.
To a guy who loves penis
enough for both of them.
He's asexual, too.
Ran a complete physical on her.
Nothing wrong except a
common bladder infection.
Hundred bucks says
I can find a medical reason
why she doesn't want
to have sex.
You're out of your mind
if you think
I'm letting you anywhere
near my patient.
Fine, I won't go near her.
Just give me her file and any
blood samples you have leftover.
No contact whatsoever. You
talk to her, the bet is void.
No contact. Plays to
my strengths, anyway.
Right now's not
a good time, House.
Not for the Dean of Medicine,
but it's the perfect time if
you're a member of my team.
Which one are you?
What did the endoscopy show?
No signs of
ulcers or blockages.
But you found a tear
just below the esophagus.
Explains the bleeding.
Doesn't explain why he vomited
so hard he ripped his insides.
His liver enzymes are slightly elevated.
Gallstones could...
No complaints of pain.
Steatohepatitis would make
his AST and ATL levels rise.
Are you calling his liver fat?
Start the patient on statins,
do a biopsy to confirm.
And knock him out, I've
heard he's a wiggler.
There's no need
to put him under.
We can confirm fatty liver
with an ultrasound.
Just making an observation.
Well done. And now,
as a member of my team,
you can make the equally useful
observations that the sky is blue,
I'm wearing pants, and I'm
ignoring your first observation.
Of course.
Wait.
And there it is.
You're trying to screw
with my confidence.
Well, if I wanted to do that,
I'd tell you how much
the nurses hate you.
You're trying to get me to
define myself as a subordinate
to keep me from
ever intervening,
even if it's fully in
the scope of my duties.
Like now. This isn't
about diagnostics,
it's about what's safe
for the patient.
Do the ultrasound.
Ultrasound it is.
And the nurses love you.
You don't think I knew House was
gonna tell you to ignore me
and not do the ultrasound?
This is an ultrasound machine.
Which you're gonna use to do
an ultrasound-guided biopsy.
You've probably got
a kit stashed here...
"Cuddy Dark will waste his afternoon
chasing conspiracy theories."
You're letting him
get inside your head.
He can do a lot
of damage in there.
Dr. Chase,
he started vomiting again.
This is why we stopped
the antiemetics.
We needed to see if
it was still a symptom.
Okay.
Here. You want this?
Get your hands off me.
You're taking my head!
It's okay, Andres.
You're in the hospital.
10 milligrams of diazepam.
Already on it.
Hey! NATALIE: I'm fine.
I'm fine.
Foreman.
Blood in his urine.
We resumed the antiemetics
and increased his sedation.
He really went after her.
Maybe he found out
about her "good friend."
It was just paranoid rage.
Typical of Alzheimer's.
We don't even know if they
were sleeping together.
A few hours ago, you were sure.
And that's significant why?
Sorry, only the bleeding's
medically relevant.
No' I wasn't being rhetorical.
If they are sleeping together,
why do we disapprove?
You're pro infidelity?
She's not married.
If marriage is feeding
and cleaning someone
and limiting conversation to
repeating a few simple commands,
then I was married
to my pet rat.
And a lot of people
owe me wedding gifts.
And we're walking,
we're walking.
I don't care how sick your spouse
gets, you don't jump ship.
Alzheimer's is different. She can't
share her problems with him,
or plan for the future. The man
she married no longer exists.
Yes, he does.
He's in there.
This is why you get married.
Said the divorced woman
to the divorced man.
I didn't jump ship. My husband
sank it when he cheated on me.
Commitment's not conditional.
She is there for him in the
only way that matters now.
She gave up her life
to take care of him.
Proves she's an idiot.
If she had any sense, she'd
have stuck him in a facility
and jumped on that strange...
Dr. Foreman. We were
just looking for you.
I was right about
the antiemetics.
If we kept him on them
like I said,
he wouldn't have gotten
agitated and punched his wife.
Yes, we're back to my
supposed diabolical plan
to shake your confidence.
Let's see if this helps.
If you're speaking
as a team member,
then I'd say you're a moron.
'Cause taking him
off the antiemetics
gave us crucial
diagnostic information.
If you're speaking as Dean of Medicine,
then I'd say you're a moron.
'Cause your micromanaging
kept us from doing a biopsy.
And if we had, the patient would've
been anesthetized hours ago
thus unable to go all
Chris Brown on her ass.
Unless one of your index
cards actually predicted
the guy was
gonna punch his wife,
everything you're saying is
post hoc rationalization.
Dr. Park, would you please
reach under that chair?
"The patient will
punch his wife."
You clearly wrote that
after the fact.
Dr. Adams, would you please
reach into my pants?
"Dr. Blackenshmurtz
will accuse me
"of writing about the
punch after the fact."
And look,
there's a photograph of me
holding a newspaper
dated last Tuesday.
How could I have gotten
my hands on that?
You done? Rhabdomyolysis
fits the vomiting,
pigmenturia and renal failure.
No muscle symptoms and
urine had no myoglobin.
TTP fits, though.
Start him on plasmapheresis.
Unless...
Unless I need to say,
"Mother, may I?"
And "mother's" an abbreviation.
Fresh plasma will replace
the damaged red blood cells
that are clogging his kidneys.
That sounds hopeful.
How's that feeling?
I've never been hit in the eye before.
I feel kind of badass.
I think maybe you should go.
Look, I'm fine, okay?
I'll see you tomorrow?
Okay.
We're not having an affair.
It's none of my business.
I mean, not really.
'Cause nothings happened, but we've
talked about it a lot and...
It's just really hard
doing this by myself.
When's the last time you
had a full night's sleep?
Um...
I don't know.
Three years?
You're not gonna
get any rest here.
People who are sick
are not the only ones
who need to be taken care of.
Why doesn't Chase
have to be here?
You think he knows anything about
women who don't want to have sex?
Hormone levels are normal. This
woman seems perfectly healthy.
What does it matter
if she says she's asexual?
It's the fundamental drive of our species.
Sex is healthy.
Orgasms oxygenate the brain,
lighting up over
30 different areas
and making us forget how
boring Susie Cooper is.
That last one may
not be universal.
How about damage
to her spinal cord,
blocking the signals
from her genitals?
Sex drive is in the brain.
I suppose it could be
psychological intimacy issues
caused by childhood abuse.
She's been sharing a toilet with the
same guy for the last 10 years.
It's not the same.
Sex releases oxytocin, it's the
neurochemical basis for bonding.
And that's why men always
marry their right hands.
It's different for girls.
No, it's not.
I've tapped over 30 guys
and never wanted to
see most of them again.
I lived next to a Jewish frat.
We are veering wildly off track.
Please continue.
This woman's life is probably
better off without sex.
Eliminates most of
her insecurities,
she's immune to
most advertising,
and can have honest
relationships with men.
Not a lot of them.
We've run every lest and
ruled out all the options.
You're gonna have to accept
she just doesn't want sex.
Lots of people don't have sex.
The only people
who don't want it
are either sick, dead or lying.
So maybe she's lying.
You think she's had
a boyfriend on the side?
For 10 years?
Sticking around the whole time?
It doesn't make sense.
What does.“
Thirty?
Everybody lies.
Higher or lower?
Followed your advice
and took the night off.
It seems to have
done you some good.
Mmm-hmm.
Where's my husband?
He's not in the hospital.
So he just walked out?
All of the shift nurses had their
hands full with a double code.
Perfectly
reasonable explanation.
Same thing happened to me.
Couldn't find my keys for days.
The police have been notified,
I have staff searching.
You told me
it was okay to leave.
I'm sorry.
He has Alzheimer's!
It's freezing outside!
And he's sick!
I mean, you don't even know
what it is yet, do you'?
The plasmapheresis
hasn't had time to work,
but TTP is our most likely...
Okay, I have to
go look for him.
Hey. Don't be an ass.
Can't you see she's upset?
No, she's guilty.
Instead of being at her husband's
side, she was under you.
Okay. That's...
Yeah, he already
said I was an ass.
Personally, I applaud your decision
to step down off your cross
and get on with your life,
but your misplaced guilt
is shutting down your brain.
We need you to sit, focus,
and answer our questions.
So it's 6:00 a.m.,
patient wakes up,
and the first thing he sees...
In moments of confusion, Alzheimer's
patients regress to old routines.
So what would your husband
do on a Saturday morning?
Nothing. Be at home.
What about a year ago,
five years, or 10?
I don't know.
He trained for a marathon once.
Soccer practice.
We took a cooking class.
The soccer trophy you were
telling me about, it's gone.
Where was practice?
It was close to here,
on Chesterfield.
Okay, he comes, he thinks
he's wailing for practice.
He'd want to get out
of the wind,
but somewhere he could
see the kids arrive.
There.
Over here!
On three.
One, two, three.
Nothing.
Not dead till
he's warm and dead.
Get him to the ICU.
Start him on
extracorporeal circulation.
That'll raise his temperature too
quickly it'll cause acidosis.
We can deal with
his metabolism crashing.
We can't reverse brain
damage if we go too slowly.
Either way, if we don't get
his temperature above 95,
it's not gonna matter.
Multiple warm lavage is safer.
Do what House says.
He has no heartbeat,
he's not breathing.
How can he not be dead?
Body slows down when it cools,
but it doesn't fully stop.
We're warming his blood outside of
his body and then putting it back.
It'll raise his
temperature enough
that his heart
should naturally start.
Then we can shock it
back into rhythm.
And if it doesn't start?
Then there's nothing we can do.
You think it's possible he
knew what he was doing?
Like some part of him gets what
he's putting his wife through,
so he tried to...
Kill himself?
It's what I'd do if I were him.
At least I wish I would.
I meant run away.
You think you should kill
yourself if you become a burden
to the people who love you?
If you really loved
them back, then yes.
That's really dark.
It's not naive.
I just believe people are capable
of more than you do, apparently.
We've got brain activity.
Temp's at 93. His heart
should start soon.
My dad left me alone to
care for my alcoholic mom
and raise my baby sister.
I was just a teenager.
I spent half of my time
changing diapers
and the other half
cleaning up my mom's vomit.
But it must have been important
that you stayed
for both of them.
Mom died after a few years.
It was ugly and painful, and
she went with me hating her.
My sister ended up drinking
half of her life away
and hating me
because I couldn't help.
After Mom, I had nothing left.
So do I wish Mom had used a
gun instead of a bottle?
Yes.
I didn't know.
That's why I told you.
Ventricular fibrillation.
Give him 300 milligrams
amiodarone.
Be careful.
Once we establish rhythm,
any accidental movement could
crash him back into V-fib.
Clear.
We still have a long way to go.
Cold can be protective
to the brain,
but there is a
possibility of damage.
We also need to confirm and treat
whatever's making him sick.
I just gotta do
a standard battery of tests.
Blood, urine, EEG.
Is that really necessary
for a free flu shot'?
Excuse me, I have to deal with
someone who's having a panic attack.
I specifically said
the bet was off
if you contacted the patient.
Exactly. You never said anything
about the patient's husband.
The deal was a medical reason
why she doesn't have sex.
I admit I was stuck
until I realized
that the medical issue
was not hers, but his.
She's lying to compensate.
It's a tale as old as time.
Boy meets girl.
Girl falls for boy.
Boy says,
"I'm asexual."
Girls says,
"Yeah, me, too."
Your twisted logic
can't hide the fact
that tricking a patient
into being tested
is completely unethical.
Come on. Don't you think she
deserves to know why her husband
won't bend her over
the kitchen counter?
You love all that caring crap.
You're not doing this out of
the kindness of your heart.
You're not even doing this
out of medical curiosity.
I thought I made it clear
I'm doing it for the cash.
Two people are happy, and your
natural impulse is to destroy it.
How do you know she's happy?
Did she tell you?
No, chirping birds flew out of
her butt carrying a banner.
All right' I admit
that my natural impulse
is to doubt people's
claims to happiness,
but yours is
to be a sucker for them.
You tell me which one's worse.
He just opened his eyes
a little while ago.
His heartbeat's doing well and
his body temperature stabilized.
There he is.
Is that Portuguese?
Yeah.
Honey, I don't understand.
What's he saying?
I don't know.
I tried to learn when we
got married, but I just...
It's okay, it's okay.
His body temperature is rising.
It's above normal.
Wait, I thought you said it was
stable Why is it still rising?
I don't know.
Vomiting, liver, kidneys
and now fever.
I don't want to tell you how
to do your job, Dr. Foreman,
since telling people how to
do their job is your job.
But when your
less-than-competent
administration of this hospital
affects what's written
on my whiteboard...
Get to the point.
The word "fever." Could come
from the patient's illness
or it could come from the
fact that you allowed him
to saunter out of your hospital
and take a nap in the snow.
He couldn't have caught a
virus while he was outside,
fever came on too fast.
The hypothermia could have
caused cell necrosis.
TTP was the diagnosis
when he walked out.
Fever's a little high,
but it still fits.
We should
continue plasmapheresis.
We're missing symptoms.
We should add language
loss and aggression.
Should we also add forgetfulness?
He's got Alzheimer's.
We've just been assuming.
Because the patient's wife said
he exhibited both for a year.
He's never hit her before
or lost all his English.
We have to consider any change
since he's been
admitted as relevant.
"Have to?" Do I need
to pull out another card?
Disseminated viral infection,
with encephalitis.
Patient complained of a sore
throat a few weeks ago.
Start him on interferon.
Encephalitis
makes his brain swell,
which causes symptoms that are hard
to distinguish from his Alzheimer's.
With the interferon, his
English should come back
and the aggression
should subside.
But you're not sure?
Unfortunately, no.
And you're not sure if he has
brain damage from being frozen?
So best-case scenario,
I just had a glimpse
into his future?
I can't take care
of him anymore.
Chances are his
menial state will improve.
You could get
more time with him.
We married six months
after I met him.
A year after that,
he started forgetting things.
I've known my husband longer with
his Alzheimer's than without.
I've watched more of him disappear
than I ever got to know.
I just can't do this anymore.
You lose.
Blood work shows
high levels of prolactin.
Add that to some peripheral
red-green confusion,
puts my money, excuse me, your
money, soon to be my money,
on a tumor near his pituitary.
Probably started growing
in his early teens.
Lowering his libido and
causing erectile dysfunction.
A year on dopamine agonists
and he'll be a sex-crazed creep
just like the rest of us.
Completely fascinated
by Susie Cooper.
I would prefer to be paid
in a single $100 bill.
Always wanted to use one
to light a cigar.
Hooray for us. We
disproved his asexuality.
We also probably
ruined his life.
He'll thank us.
Then he'll doze off.
And then, in a couple of
hours, he'll thank us again.
It could destroy his identity.
It's like a gay person being
told they're really straight.
So don't tell him.
Yeah, why bother telling a guy he
has a tumor growing in his head?
He'll notice it eventually when
it starts leaking out his ears.
It's a slow-growing tumor.
He'll probably die of
boredom long before that.
You always do this. You meddle and
force me into impossible situations.
You knew the second you told me
about this case
that I'd get involved.
You wanted me to meddle.
'Cause no matter
how much you wanted
to believe
in this chaste romance,
you didn't buy it either.
Where's that petition
House's PO sent over
about him getting
his ankle monitor off?
On your desk.
You played me.
This whole thing was
about your ankle monitor.
You weren't trying to
undermine my confidence,
you were trying to inflate it.
You manufactured
conflict with me
so, eventually,
you could let me win.
You knew it was encephalitis,
but you waited
for me to say it,
because then,
with my ego boosted,
you thought I'd be in the mood
to take off your monitor.
Because I'd think
I could control you.
You're right.
Take off my monitor.
See, the beauty of the plan
is if ii works, then you
think you can control me.
If it fails,
then you will actually
have proven that
you can control me.
It's pretty genius.
These are your training wheels.
If you think you're up to this
job, it's time to lose them.
Second half of my plan
might need work.
V-fib.
Two rounds at 360
without establishing a rhythm.
Wait! Dr. Foreman!
Clear.
He's back.
I sure hope this
Alzheimer's drug trial
is worth a lot
to this hospital,
'cause we're wasting a
crapload of time and man power
just to let this guy
watch his mind shrivel
and keep his wife miserable.
Heart attack while he was on
interferon rules out encephalitis,
but I still think I'm right
about the neuro symptoms.
It's probably
aseptic meningitis.
We would have
seen meningeal signs.
Given his abnormal mental
status, not necessarily.
Dr. Foreman! Would you please
reach under your chair'?
It's just wet gum under here.
Where's the card?
What card?
I'm happy to leave if you have a
better theory than aseptic meningitis.
Toxins.
If this guy went
on a walkabout,
chances are
he's done it before.
Wife keeps the doors
in the house locked.
There's plenty of
nasty stuff to get into
during the middle of the night.
We asked about toxins
on the history.
The wife said she was sure to clear
the house for her husband's safety.
And I'm sure she succeeded.
She's a PhD
in toxicology, right?
She's an ex-florist. Search
the home for toxic plants,
methyl bromide,
any medications.
Stop.
You're not infallible.
You were wrong
about encephalitis.
Just before you were.
Run CSF tests, find out what's
causing the meningitis.
You said you weren't gonna
overrule me, diagnostically.
And you said I wouldn't
be able to help it.
Apparently, you were
right about that one.
Fine. I'll look
for toxins myself.
You can't go to their house
without Foreman's permission.
Don't need it, I'm gonna talk
to the toxicology PhD upstairs.
What about gifts
from South America?
Anyone send any
fruits or vegetables?
I don't think so... No.
I'm gonna need your boyfriend
to collect samples of plants
in and around your house.
Toxins are the most...
Wait. You understand him?
What's he saying?
He's repeating
"blue shack."
You know what that is?
Is it somewhere where
pesticides may be kept?
It's where
we had our first date.
Do you have a cleaning lady who
might bring her own supplies?
What's he saying?
If it's not relevant to the case, I
don't care, and neither should you.
Please.
This might be the last time I
ever know what he's thinking.
"When I saw her waiting...
"Waiting for me at the table...
"The way her eyes looked
when she smiled...
"I felt like crying.
"I knew she was the woman
I wanted to marry.
"And every time
I see her, I say...
"There she is."
He's still in there.
What did he say?
He asked who you were.
Don't get your hopes up.
Have your boyfriend
get me those samples.
How did you even know
to look for a tumor?
Dr. House noticed hormone
levels in your blood
and consulted with me
as an oncologist...
Who cares how they found it, okay?
They found it.
Are there any side effects
to the treatment?
Some nausea, dizziness,
and as the tumor shrinks,
there will be
behavioral changes.
Like what?
Well...
The tumor interferes with
certain natural systems.
It lowers libido and causes
erectile dysfunction.
You mean the treatment will
make me want to have sex'?
What if I don't
want the treatment?
I would strongly advise...
Look, you have
a brain tumor, okay?
You have to have the treatment.
Okay, look,
I know who I am, okay?
And I'm not one of them.
Hey, look, we'll adjust.
Okay? We can go
through this together.
You mean have sex?
I can't make you do that.
Maybe it won't be so bad.
It'll be terrible.
It's actually pretty fun.
From what I remember.
But you said that...
I know.
I know. I wanted to
spend my life with you
and I knew that meant
making certain sacrifices.
But a girl has needs.
You dropped
in the US. News rankings.
With respect, Mr. Laffont, that's
only because we temporarily
shut down our
diagnostics department.
It's up and running again.
I'm actually concerned it might be
because of the change in management.
If you want my money, I'll
need to see a five year plan.
Am I boring you?
No, I just, those flowers
are from last week.
They should be dead by now.
Excuse me?
Sorry, I have to go.
It's Reye's Syndrome.
Patient had a sore throat a few
weeks ago before he was admitted.
Reye's in adults is a reach.
Not if he took aspirin.
Aspirin in adults is a reach.
Especially in a house
with locked medicine cabinets.
It wasn't in
the medicine cabinet.
The wife used to
run a floral company,
still does a few orders
from home.
She uses crushed aspirin
in the water
to make the flowers
last longer.
So the husband
has a sore throat,
takes an aspirin
without her knowing,
realizes he's got a sore
throat, takes an aspirin,
realizes he's got
a sore throat...
You can stop me
whenever you like.
Have Chase start him
on steroids.
I already did.
Then why are you telling me?
Because I wanted you
to hear it from me.
There she is.
Here I am.
Your eye.
What happened?
It's nothing I can't handle.
MRI confirmed
macroprolactinoma.
He's doing the treatment
And the wife?
Come on.
We saved a man's life,
course-corrected two people's
wildly screwed up worldviews.
Not bad for a day's work.
I think they were happy, even
if it was based on lies.
Most happiness is.
Better to have shtupped
and lost
than never to
have shtupped at all.
We can't smoke in here.
We also can't summon people
into the clinic based on a lie
motivated by a petty bet,
and yet it happens.
It's an imperfect world.
Well?
Disgustingly satisfying.
He said it was okay.
Is one of you Dr. House?
You've seen Spartacus, right?
I got an order here to deactivate
and remove his ankle monitor.
Robbie?
Hey, sis.
It's been years.
I know.
I thought of you
on Mom's birthday.
Is everything okay?
Yeah, yeah.
Fine. I just...
wanted to see how you were.
I'm fine.
Bikes go faster
without training wheels.
Now get out, I have work to do.
Whoops.