Nice tie.
Are you at least gonna
call the cops this time?
Oh. Then they might stop.
Just when they're beginning
to capture my eyes.
Come on, Dad.
Let Rodrigo do this.
Your arthritis is obviously...
I can pick up my own lawn.
You know, if you wanted, you
could put an end to all this.
Of course. There are other
ways to save the company.
I'm only moving it to China
because I'm craving egg foo yung.
You know, I just got off the
phone with some investors.
Yes, and they want
a controlling interest?
We get to stay here
with the people
who've been so
loyal to this company.
Everyone keeps their jobs.
It's been a family business for 120 years.
There's no way I'm letting...
What's wrong?
Dad?
I need you to
drive me to a doctor.
This would totally suck.
Patient's visited China a lot recently.
What about the JBE virus?
Why don't you check
his vaccination record
before you make
another stupid...
OMFG. 50% off cupcakes.
How sick is the patient?
'Cause this expires today.
Central serous retinopathy? It's
linked to type-A personalities.
Funduscopic exam was normal.
If you don't let me
read my email,
then I won't be
able to read the email
to the entire staff
from your ex-boss.
Thank you.
"Last month, I had an incident
involving another PPTH employee.
"Though I can't speak to
the details of the case,
"while my disciplinary
hearing is pending,
"I want you to know
that I have completed
"voluntary sexual
harassment training.
"And on a personal note, if my
actions caused anyone distress,
"I sincerely apologize."
You are so fired.
What? He apologized.
What? Because he
said he apologized?
He's saying he's sorry
that someone, namely you,
overreacted,
namely by punching him.
He grabbed my behind.
The word is it was a celebratory
slap after you completed
your first ever
AVM embolization.
He grabbed it, he
apologized for grabbing it
and now he's taking classes
because he grabbed it.
The classes make
him sympathetic.
Which, in turn, makes his
unrepentant attacker evil.
Which, in turn, in turn,
makes you so fired.
100 bucks says
I won't get fired.
Oh, you don't want to bet me.
Oh, my...
You're fired.
Uh, the bet is...
But I thought...
after...
then... if only...
The bet's that I'll get
fired after my hearing.
I'll take that action, too, but
you're already a C-note in the hole.
You're late.
Considering I don't work
here, arguably, I'm early.
Pearl earrings?
Knee length dress?
It's not a very
shameful walk of shame.
I was at a job interview.
I hope it went terribly.
Thad Barton? We only
help rich white guys'?
I am an equal
opportunity exploiter.
I only help those who can help
myself
I have
a department to re-fund.
Atropine poisoning.
He's moving
his company to China
and his employees are
hanging him in effigy.
They could have moved
on to the real thing.
Pupils are normal.
Thyrotoxicosis?
Not a terrible idea.
I'm gonna go give
him PTU and TLC.
I have no idea what that
second one stands for.
Things don't seem small anymore.
They were...
I woke up from a nap
and everything went from
really small lo really huge.
Well, then these giant balls of
medicine are not gonna work anymore.
The change actually
makes things simpler.
Your occipital lobe is acting
up, giving you a migraine.
But I don't have a headache.
Not all migraines
present that way.
It's called Alice in
Wonderland Syndrome.
- Seriously?
- I never joke.
Good news is it's
treatable with medication.
Bad news is it can
make you very, very late
for very important dates.
I sometimes joke.
Thank you, Doctor.
Well, if you really
want to thank me...
My department's not
really a department
'cause my boss says
he doesn't have the money,
which provides
a nice contrast with you.
We're trying to find
money in our budget
so we don't have to move
our operations overseas.
I get it. Answer's no.
Shouldn't have said anything.
I'm just glad that the symptoms
showed up before you left for China.
'Cause I'm not sure
the doctors over there
would be so optimistic
considering...
What are you
guys talking about?
Oh, just how different
the two cultures are'
For example, our opinions
on mental illness.
'Cause here, it's considered a
normal, treatable condition.
Ls everything okay?
Everything's fine.
I could have you
checked into a facility
that exclusively
treats mental disorder.
How's that sound?
Whatever's gonna
get him better.
Let's try the medication first.
You're hired.
You guys are gonna love
Doctors Chase and Taub.
Keep your Nazi sentiments
quiet around the little one.
You got the money?
How?
Patient's a smart businessman.
But he's destroying
thousands of jobs.
Jobs are not being destroyed.
They're being relocated.
The fact that you see
that as inherently bad
means you're
an irrational patriot.
To put it another way,
a patriot.
Patriotism is natural.
We've always relied on our
tribes to keep us safe.
It's helpful for
society if its members
have positive feelings
about that society.
Iranian women?
Drag queens in Uganda?
Patriotism is nothing
but loyalty to real estate.
Real estate that's been conquered
800 times by 800 different regimes
with 800 different cultures.
But each time,
it's just the best.
I claim this burger in the name
of Queen Isabella of Spain.
I'll go check on the patient.
I have hepatitis C.
She got it from me.
Hey, how's my dad doing?
Great. His vision's
back to normal
and if he remains asymptomatic
through the night,
we'll be able to
release him in the morning.
Any chance that could
happen before 9:00?
Our stock dropped a couple points
today with the news that he's sick.
I would love for him to get out
of here before the market opens.
No offense, but I think it's
terrible your dad's closing down
all your American operations.
I don't think he's moving
the company out of greed.
He's moving it out of grief.
My mom,
she died four months ago.
Non-Hodgkin's lymphoma
and ifs been hard for him.
Living in their house,
driving down the same streets.
I mean, he's constantly
reminded of her.
Dad?
I need
an intubation kit in here.
What's going on?
Angiography showed a hemorrhagic
site in the left lower lobe.
I think it could be
hyperviscosity syndrome.
Are you sure Foreman's okay
with us being in his office?
He's never gonna know.
He's actually
in here right now.
Blood count and protein
count are normal.
I think it could be
hyperviscosity syndrome.
Sorry, but after Park sent
out her hospital-wide
non-apology apology
this morning,
I assume that plagiarism
is the new black.
If it makes Andrews
look sympathetic...
Copying him makes
you look pathetic.
And I will pay you not to go
to anger management classes.
What about another
clotting problem?
Factor V Leiden deficiency.
It's possible.
Adams is the one who needs
to deal with her anger.
Myelodysplastic syndrome.
I heard about your conversation
with the patient's daughter.
You were hostile.
Well, their company is making a
decision I strongly disagree with.
Yet you were never
anything but courteous
to the racists and
rapists in prison.
Those guys made
decisions you supported?
Myelodysplastic syndrome.
I'm guessing it has
something to do with
the funeral you attended
yesterday morning.
I was at a job interview.
You got to work at 9:15.
Closest hospital
with an opening
in your specialty
is 45 minutes away.
It's not possible.
My condolences.
I wasn't at a funeral.
Well, that just leaves
everywhere but a job interview.
Get out.
Who goes there?
Reveal yourself.
Now.
Well, we would
but orthopedics is still
squatting in
two thirds of my office.
Which is weird because you got
a large check last night.
From a corporation that's going through
a very public belt-tightening,
means this donation
was given under duress.
Patient didn't tell me
the whole story,
but he did say he'd be thrilled
if we didn't cash this.
Got a policy review meeting in
here in five minutes. Goodbye.
What are you doing?
Holding your ass.
You really didn't know?
House...
I was trying to
help you out here.
I figured for sure
he'd punch me in the face,
thus proving it's
a natural response.
My God, you have
superhuman discipline.
And glutes.
Get your hands off me.
Sorry.
Go.
Why did you do mm?
We have a bet.
But he's the chair of the
disciplinary committee.
Forget about the bet.
You two really need to
do your homework on me.
Treat the patient
with activated protein C.
If he has myelodysplastic
syndrome, he'll bleed out.
And if he has Factor V Leiden
deficiency, he'll throw another clot.
Exactly.
It's a conclusive test.
There's no actual risk.
As long as you're
both paying attention
and are both good
enough to work here.
I hear one of you
thinks I'm a real bastard.
I guess that would be me.
Your boss uses blackmail and you
question my professional ethics?
Will you be instituting worker safety
regulations in your new factories?
Oh, absolutely.
What about juice boxes
in the break room
for the children
you'll be hiring?
Charges of child exploitation
against American companies
have been blown
way out of proportion.
My 10-year-old cousin lives near Cebu
City, works at an American factory.
I am so sorry.
It's the best thing for him.
It sucks' but the Filipino
factories suck worse.
And the schools would
suck if they existed.
So this is
the family's best hope.
Are you okay?
Is it supposed
to itch like this?
Itching. Interesting.
Not interesting.
Already went away.
Doubly interesting.
Means we have to explain the
arrival and the departure.
Ooh!
That's real mature, House.
What do you mean?
It's outlandishly childish.
I custom built this puppy.
It's got 106 LED's,
each one sending
light to your eye
at a slightly
different wavelength.
Turn that off.
The different wavelengths
are stimulating
your autonomic nervous system.
It's making you feel like you're
on a boat in choppy waters.
On, cool.
You think I'm not.“
You think I'm not gonna
go to Foreman with this?
You will and I'll deny it.
He'll believe you,
but then these two
believe that the policy of protecting
American jobs starts at home,
so they'll never
testify against me.
And you won't be
able to prove anything.
Now, if I punched him in the
face, that he could prove.
I remember you saying something
about how loyalty to
real estate was stupid.
This is about reclaiming
stolen property.
Loyalty to real estate is stupid
because loyalty is stupid.
First patriotism, now loyalty.
You hate ice cream, too?
French vanilla, yeah.
To willfully identify
yourself with something else
is a perversion
of self-expression.
I had a thought.
Other than the fact
that loyalty is the basis
of all meaningful
relationships.
The daughter said that her mother
died of non-Hodgkin's lymphoma.
What if she was misdiagnosed?
Dutch chocolate's not bad.
Gotta give them that.
Her lymphoma could have been
caused by a virus, HTLV-1,
which our patient contracted
through having sex with his wife.
In other words,
loyalty gave him cancer.
I like it.
Start him on radiation.
Chang and Eng Bunker, the most
famous conjoined twins in history.
2011 is the bicentennial
of their birth.
The best Halloween costumes are always
the ones that need an explanation.
What took you so long?
We already lost one of them.
You need help
with the lacerations?
No. I think
I've got palliative.
Why don't you
take preventative?
Prevent what?
He got in a fight.
Which he started, which means
he's both irascible and stupid.
I told the drunk,
racist frat guy
the proper term is "conjoined
twin", not "Siamese".
Well, I can't comment
on the drunk or the frat,
but Chang and Eng
were both, in fact,
born in Siam and they were,
in fact, twins.
If your name was Richard, it'd be
okay for me to call you a dick.
I thought maybe
some of the tripe
you learnt in
anger management class
could help keep this guy
out of here the next time.
Sometimes, it's incredibly satisfying
to wind up and punch someone
who really deserves it,
but when you think about
the consequences...
Okay, let's go.
I thought you wanted me
to help him with his anger.
No. I got
everything I need.
"Sometimes, it's incredibly
satisfying to wind up
"and punch someone
who deserves it."
Wonder what the committee's
gonna make of that.
This is a waste of time. There's
no way that Robin gave me an STD.
I know this is hard and I
am sorry about your wife.
If you'd like to
talk to someone
we do have grief counselors
at the hospital.
You sound like my daughter.
I miss my wife, but it's not
driving my decision making.
You were CEO since 1988.
You decided to move your company
right after your wife died.
Stands to reason that
your emotions factored in.
My wife...
is the only thing
that keeps me here.
I visit her grave once a week.
So your daughter was wrong.
You just really
need a lot of money.
You ever hear of Kongo Gumi?
A construction company in
Japan, founded in the year 578,
family owned and operated,
building Buddhist temples
for 50 generations.
Went bankrupt five years ago.
You have any idea how that
last CEO must have felt?
I'm sorry.
I have to move.
Your heart rate is speeding up.
Do you feel any
tightness in your chest?
Yes. I figured it
was from the radiation.
I think you're
having a heart attack.
Come in.
Dr. Wilson,
I need your advice.
Um...
I bet House $100
that I wouldn't get fired
after my disciplinary hearing.
Ever since then,
he's been acting like
he's actually
trying to get me fired.
That's because he is actually
trying to get you fired.
Does he hate me?
Not sure that's
relevant to the equation.
So it's really over $100?
Not sure the amount is relevant.
He's fighting for his honor.
He'll ruin my career.
Not sure that's.4.
What if I bet him
$200 I will get fired?
He sees competing bets with the same
person as a disgrace to the game.
He'll be even more
motivated to beat you.
If you were me,
what would you do?
You have to give him something
he values more than honor.
And you should
update your resume.
EKG and
troponins were equivocal.
It's not even clear
if our patient
just had a heart attack
or what it was.
Let's look at segmental
wall motion abnormalities.
Get him an echo to confirm.
And I need $200,000.
His company's lost one third of
its value since he was admitted.
And you want to do
some insider trading?
I take it felonies aren't a
violation of your parole?
It's not insider trading. Just
betting on myself to solve the case.
Once we cure him, share price
goes up, I pay you back.
No.
No, you don't say "no" '
you make a counteroffer.
I'm not loaning my boss money.
Fine. I'll make a counter.
$100,000?
$20,000?
I'll buy options instead of shares.
More risk, but more upside.
But that's as low
as I'm gonna go.
I could do $5,000.
Really? No backsies.
If you double
your clinic hours.
Six a week.
I've seen how you
disrespect those patients.
So you want twice as many
of them to be disrespected?
Spend more hours with them,
you'll treat them more humanely.
And this time, a land war in
Russia will be a good idea.
Deal?
Here's what I'm thinking.
You went to a parole hearing
where one of your old
patients was denied.
Hence the attire,
hence the tardiness,
and most important,
hence the anger.
You think you can
restore the cosmic balance
by doing extra good here.
More annoyingly
by having me do it.
And deal.
Of course,
you know this means war.
Oh, I know.
I mean, you'll escalate
and then I'll retaliate,
and the cycle will continue
until we've both gone too far.
At which point, I'll maybe get suspended
and you'll go back to prison.
Happy pranking.
Patient had V-Tack in
the echo lab, so we cathed him,
but coronary
arteries were clean.
If the plumbing's fine, check
the electrical. EP study.
Nice idea.
Even has a metaphor in it.
Not worth more than my honor,
but delightful all the same.
I'm not going to lose.
My college roommate is the
editor of the Yale Law Review.
She's writing
my opening statement.
Well, then you'll be
eloquent in your loss.
This case boils down to,
"He said, she said."
He said, "I've been working
at this hospital for 15 years
"and I am taking
self-improvement classes."
She said, "I've been a
fellow for two months
"and I'm kind of weird."
No, he said, "I'm a drunk idiot
"who thinks he can
grab girls' behinds
"without ramifications"
Wait, he was drunk?
In the hospital?
I already told Foreman he'd
been drinking that night.
Andrews was taking sexual
harassment classes, not AA.
That means he didn't get
in trouble for drinking.
Which means that
Foreman signed off on it,
which means that he set
all the wheels in motion.
Forget that. Wild speculation.
Go do the EP study.
You already knew Andrews was
drinking that night, didn't you?
Yes.
I think you should
cancel my hearing.
I hope this isn't going
where I assume it's going.
You're the one who
brought Andrews in.
You set the wheels in motion.
We had a patient who was going to
die without an AVM embolization.
Andrews was the only
neurologist I could reach.
He told me he had a few glasses of
wine and that he shouldn't do it,
but he also said
that you were good,
and you were ready to do one as
long as you were supervised.
So we agreed that
he would come in,
but wouldn't touch the patient.
I can understand
the rationalization.
We'll see if the board agrees
when I tell them the whole
story at my hearing.
I already did.
I had a closed session
hearing last week.
The board decided to
dock me two weeks' pay.
Oh.
You've been working for House for
two weeks, it's already too long.
No sign of any electrical
abnormalities in the right atrium.
I'm so dead.
I think House set me up.
Have you sent the committee
a character reference for me?
I thought you
don't like favors.
I don't like gifts.
It wouldn't be a gift,
it'd just be you
telling the truth.
I hardly know you.
02 sat is 89. Did we perforate?
Is he tamponading'?
Heart rate's only 90
and neck veins are flat.
Then why isn't he saturating?
Seems healthy to me.
Let's release him.
My option to sell Barton Foods
at $34 is about to expire
'cause I thought the patient
would be better by now.
Instead,
I am going to lose $20,000.
Twenty?
Your five plus the five
I stole from Wilson
plus the 10 I got on margin.
You're gonna have to talk
to my bankruptcy attorney.
Unless... There is a way that
you can get your money back.
Give me the full $200,000.
And extrapolating. Tomorrow, you'll
owe just shy of a million dollars.
It's your own fault. You forced
me to go with the options.
Your damn anger issues are
screwing with my finances.
Regular stock this time,
nice and safe.
I'm not angry.
I don't know if you're trying
to make me angry, but...
You refuse to bet on yourself.
That means low self-esteem.
So if I give you $200,000,
I'll feel smart and pretty?
Low self-esteem
can be brought on
by exposure to one's relatives.
Nice clothes and anger, classic
symptoms of a family gathering.
You were late the other day
'cause you were
having breakfast
with Grammy Adams
or Cousin Itt.
She was nagging you
about finding a husband.
All right.
This is getting annoying.
I'll just tell you what I was...
Uh-uh-uh-uh!
No spoilers.
They ruin everything.
Pulmonology was that way.
Our patient's lung problem
is not a lung problem.
It's a brain problem. We're
consulting with neurology.
That's my old boss.
You don't actually think
this is neurological.
I don't know what it is.
But maybe I should just
accept the patient's death
if getting help would
lead to awkwardness.
Dr. Andrews, my associates,
Doctors Adams and Park.
Ah.
Nice to meet you,
Dr. Adams.
Hello, Dr. Park.
You two know each other?
It's a small world.
Dr. Park, maybe you'd like to
update our esteemed colleague
on the condition
of our patient?
Micropsia, bleeding, tachycardia
and difficulty breathing.
Cute butt, huh?
Can we go now?
What, you really want to
turn your back on this guy'?
Sorry. Carry on.
Uh...
Well, it sounds like there could
be spinal cord involvement.
Have you considered normal
pressure hydrocephalus?
Okay. Normal pressure
hydrocephalus going once.
Normal pressure
hydrocephalus going twice...
It's not his spinal cord,
it's the wiring between
his heart and his brain.
Autonomic
dysregulation syndrome.
We do a tilt table test, see
how his heart rate responds.
That'll confirm.
Well, if he has normal
pressure hydrocephalus,
a tilt table test
could put him in a coma.
Then it's a good thing
he has ADS.
You really believe
in this diagnosis?
Because if this is
just a pissing contest,
you're at a severe
anatomical disadvantage.
It's autonomic
dysregulation syndrome.
No, it's normal
pressure hydrocephalus.
Do a spinal fluid test
to confirm.
We're doing the tilt table.
That makes sense.
You'd rather have House
fire you than Foreman.
This bet's gotta be a test, see
if I can handle working with him.
I need to prove I have the
confidence to disobey him.
Do you have any medical
justification for your diagnosis?
The symptoms fit
and Andrews is a hack.
Do you think I'm right?
Let's go.
No.
You need to go
prepare for your hearing.
Fifteen more minutes,
Mr. Barton.
A skin resurfacing
laser is missing.
And why are you
asking me about it?
Because you work for House.
What would House want
with a skin resurfacing laser?
I have no idea.
Have you seen it?
My feet feel hot.
That's completely normal.
No. But House has
been talking about how
badly he wants to
remove those prison tats.
It's a very expensive machine
and I'd like it back.
Please tell me
if you hear anything.
How expensive?
$200,000.
He took it.
I have no idea.
Park's hearing's
about to start.
You're covering for him. I did
the same thing many times.
My advice to you,
figure out what line you aren't
willing to cross for him.
Because, eventually,
he'll ask you to cross it.
How are your feet?
Mr. Barton?
Can you hear me, Mr. Barton?
Oh, no.
We have convened
the Disciplinary Committee
to decide
the appropriate action
that should be taken
against Dr. Chi Park
as a result of her actions
on October 7th of this year.
Dr. Park, do you have
an opening statement?
Dr. Foreman,
members of the committee,
thank you for giving me this opportunity
to speak to you today. I...
Good news. You can cancel the hearing,
because I'm firing her myself.
She's not yours to fire...
Then you guys better fire
her for insubordination.
She went rogue and my
patient is now in a coma.
I'm the one who did the test...
No. It was my idea.
Seriously, House?
At least I'm smart enough
to know what I don't know.
She went out of her way
to defy me, she needs...
Damn it, she...
Just fire her!
My apologies.
My apologies, Dr. Park.
Dr. House's comments
will, of course,
have no bearing
on this hearing.
Please continue.
I, uh...
I can't believe you did that.
Right back at you.
Our patient's dying
We need theories.
It's gotta be normal
pressure hydrocephalus.
Andrews predicted the coma.
Yeah, but even a broken
doctor is right twice a day.
The patient wasn't
wet, wabbly or wacky.
The coma had to
be a lucky guess.
If you didn't
think he was right,
then why did you want us to
collect his spinal fluid?
I didn't. I wanted you
to do a tilt table test.
You have a wonderful
way of communicating.
I knew Park wanted
to do a tilt table.
If she listens to me, I waste
an hour, if she defies me,
then I get the test
I want and my 100 bucks.
Up high.
You're an ass.
You're angry.
Yes. Now I'm angry.
Let's run the test for normal
pressure hydrocephalus.
No.
What else would
explain our symptoms
and make our patient go
into a coma during that test?
What about
hepatic encephalopathy?
No. We already tested his liver enzymes.
They're normal.
Or his liver's so far gone,
it can't even produce enzymes.
That's desperate.
It fits the symptoms.
And Andrews is a hack.
Go biopsy to confirm, unless
you want your own hearing.
You'd have to hire me first.
So you do realize
that it is unacceptable
to hit someone
in the work place?
Yes.
Completely unacceptable.
I wasn't thinking.
I guess...
I mean, I guess,
technically, I was thinking.
It happened so fast,
I didn't... I...
It's like...
It's like it wasn't even me. I would
never do something like that.
Even though I did.
I'm sorry I'm not
making any sense right now.
I don't know. I just really
love being a doctor so much,
and I barely even
have $100 and...
Please don't fire me.
Is this theory more
promising than the others?
We'll know in a few hours.
How are you holding up?
Other than the fact
that my dad's in a coma,
terrible.
Tomorrow morning, I am supposed
to sign a piece of paper
that will move the company
and cost thousands of
employees their jobs.
I thought you'd
rather see the company
go under in New Jersey
than thrive in China.
It's what my dad wants,
and it's still his company.
I'm really just
keeping the seat warm.
But unless he wakes up
before tomorrow,
it's gonna be my signature
on that piece of paper.
You don't have to sign it.
I'll let you know
when we have the results.
Biopsy was clean.
It's not his liver.
I also ran
the spinal fluid test,
and you were right
that Andrews was wrong.
His ICP was not normal,
it was elevated.
What about HTLV?
We ruled that out
three days ago.
Because of his heart problems.
But.“
Once something gets
taken off the board,
I'm the only one who's
allowed to put it back on.
You owe me 106,804 won.
Or $100 US.
God, but you're petty.
Okay. So, two options.
Either we figure out
what's wrong with this guy,
or we figure out how to make this
company profitable in New Jersey.
Eastern equine encephalitis?
Thinking in here.
Brain scans indicate
it could be Loa loa disease.
Shut it off!
Apparently we're
allowed to do this now.
Get out of here, House.
Start the patient
on plasmapheresis.
He'll wake up in an hour.
It's been a pleasure having
you in the neighborhood.
This diagnosis was brought
to you by the letter Y.
Dad! God, you're okay.
I'm thirsty.
It's a side effect
of not dying.
Turns out your blood
was getting thick and syrupy
from complexes of large
Y-shaped antibodies.
They were clogging up
your blood vessels,
causing your organs
to shut down, one by one.
Usually, with
hyperviscosity syndrome,
it's caused by
an elevated blood count
or protein count,
but yours eluded us
because it was
caused by antibodies
from your rheumatoid arthritis.
Now that they're
being filtered out,
your blood will be a little less duck
sauce, and a little more soy sauce.
So I'm gonna be
completely cured?
It's not all about you.
Your stock price will be completely
cured once you sign this.
It's a press release.
It says that you're healthy,
you're going back to work,
and you're signing the lease that
officially moves the company to China.
He just woke up. Dad, you don't
have to deal with this right now.
Actually, he does. Because the
market opens at 9:00 a.m.
And this means a lotto me.
You may remember me from the
time I saved your life.
If you move it,
it'll be without me.
I know you object,
I know you disagree...
Dad. I can't do it.
If this is really about
family, you will not do this.
Morning.
I got lucky this time.
No, you didn't.
I made this bet so you'd stop
actively trying to fire Park,
so you'd be neutral. You went
out of your way to help her.
She obviously earned your respect,
passed whatever test you...
I sabotaged her hearing.
You do read the school
paper, don't you?
If you had
sabotaged her hearing,
she would have gotten more
than a slap on the wrist.
What you actually did
was make her emotional,
and make the board members
see her as a victim.
Because the panel
feels badly for
incompetent doctors
who nearly kill people.
You know that everyone
on that panel hates you.
You know the minute you
recommend firing anyone,
they start discussing how
big a bonus to give them.
That's just hurtful.
Fact is, winning $100 from
you gives me more pleasure
than winning $100 from her.
Here's your 5 grand.
What 5 grand?
Just take it.
Trust me.
I found her
sleeping in the park.
Says she ran away because
her daddy didn't love her.
And that is exactly what happened
as far as you can prove.
Congratulations. You're
not going to jail. Today.
But you do know I just
can't let this slide.
Well, you need to
keep up your rep.
Fine, clinic hours.
I'll double them.
Okay.
Twelve hours a week.
No. Three times
two equals six.
And three times
two times two is twelve.
I know about
your deal with Adams.
Call Chase and Taub.
Get them in here.
The boys are back.
This check is for
significantly more
than what I told you it would
take to fund the department.
I know.
You paged me?
Congratulations.
You caught your boyfriend
cheating that morning.
You had a big fight,
that's why you were late.
You re-pitched an STD.
You haven't gone
two consecutive minutes
without using
the word "loyalty",
which explains the anger
and low self-esteem.
And the desire to feel pretty
after having been rejected
explains the clothes.
It wasn't my boyfriend.
It was my husband.
I was at my lawyer's office
signing the divorce papers.
Wow.
I missed the fact
that you were married.
We've been separated
for almost a year.
So... Old news?
No anger left?
It's all bought and paid for.