Good.
- Oh, yeah. Rose petals. Nice touch.
- Really? You don't think it's too much?
It's me and Alex's first Valentine's Day,
and I don't wanna overdo it.
Nah.
- Is that a bearskin rug?
- Yeah. Yeah, I got it at Big Lots.
Had to buy it in bulk.
If you know anyone
who wants a bearskin rug...
I got eight.
- Oh, that's good.
Okay, here we go, 8:00 sharp.
So game-plan review.
You take the living room
while Sarah and I are in our bedroom.
Then at precisely 9:30,
Alex and I will saunter off to our room...
leaving you and Sarah ample time
to watch Love Actually.
Ah, yes, a hit with ladies
around the world.
- And men.
- Hmm.
Don't worry about your soufflés.
I will make sure they rise to perfection.
- Alex. Okay.
- Good luck.
You too. Okay.
Oh, wait. Chuck, Chuck, Chuck.
Just one more thing.
It's Valentine's Day.
We both have girlfriends.
- I know.
- Ha, ha.
- Okay, go.
- Okay, okay, go.
We did it.
Thank God. I haven't slept in three days.
You know what else we haven't done
in three days, or three months?
Are you saying it's time
for Mommy and Daddy...
to celebrate Valentine's?
Can we not call ourselves
Mommy and Daddy in the bedroom?
- How about "Who's your daddy?"
- Still no.
Oh.
Let Clara cry it out.
It'll prepare her for the real world.
- Or at least the nursery.
- You're such a good dad.
And you're a good mom.
- I can't do it.
- I can't do it either.
What do you need, little baby?
Come on.
Ha, ha. Oh.
I'm gonna treat you so good,
you're never gonna let me go.
- Pretty Woman reference.
- Isn't that about a prostitute?
Yeah, but Julia Roberts
is so delightful, isn't she?
Mm-hm. Wait for it.
Boom. Homemade, baby.
Well, I have a surprise for you
underneath this, you know.
- Do you really?
- Mm-hm.
They're in the fridge.
- Morgan and Alex have the living room.
- What do you mean, "have"?
Like in college when you gotta
hang a sock on the door...
- A sock? Why would you do that?
- Doesn't matter. I'm gonna go out there.
It's only been five minutes.
Not a lot could have happened.
- Did you hear that?
- I did.
It was like our souls are so close,
they're vibrating.
- That's what it is.
- Yeah.
That's exactly what it is.
- What's happening?
- I don't know.
Throw the chocolate sauce on me.
Get in there.
- Make that happen. It's working.
- Ah. Okay.
Squirt it again. We have to be in sync.
- I'm stuck.
- Ah. Ah. What does it mean?
Surprise.
I agree, general.
There better be a damn good reason
why they're not picking up the phone.
I'm going to get them right now.
What was that?
Oh, my God.
Dad, hi. What are you doing here?
- What are you doing here?
- I was...
Sarah had these chocolate-covered, uh...
So I was...
Come on, Chuck, you said I have
the living room for 90 minutes.
"Have"?
What do you mean, "have"?
- Have in a biblical way, like...
- We were, um...
- Not a biblical way, in a spiritual way...
- Beckman. Mission. Now.
Happy Valentine's Day, everybody.
Chuck 4x16 - Versus the Masquerade
We were just transferring energy, okay?
It's not a physical thing.
- You know, it's an emotional exchange.
- Drop it, Grimes.
- We're having company?
- Hey, what the?
Who are those guys?
NCS. They're making some additions
to Castle.
Ooh. Maybe they got my comment card
about the eucalyptus steam room.
They're covert ops, Bartowski.
Nothing to do with your mission.
Tonight there was supposed to be
a joint CIA-NSA-Interpol bust...
of Alexei Volkoff's
three most trusted lieutenants.
We tracked them down...
but by the time we located them,
they were already dead.
And we believe the killer was this man,
Boris Kaminsky.
Boris may be trying
to take control of Volkoff Industries...
by eliminating anyone
who could claim power.
- Is there anyone left to make a claim?
- Possibly.
Volkoff left information on every contact
in the Hydra Network...
except for a woman
named Vivian McArthur.
- I never heard of her when I was there.
- Doesn't surprise me.
We believe that Volkoff
was purposely hiding her...
because she is his chosen successor.
Which means Vivian is Boris' next target.
Do we know anything about her?
The only connection between her and
Volkoff is a manor in Somerset, England.
There's a party there tonight.
Perfect time for Boris to attack.
You need to get to Vivian before he does
and bring her back to Castle.
Uh, quick question, uh, G.B.
This party, is there a theme
we should dress towards?
Sarah, I gotta tell you,
masquerades really creep me out, okay?
It's like Eyes Wide Shut,
but, you know, not so boring.
Don't get me wrong,
I'm a huge Kubrick fan.
- It's just a bunch of socialites.
- Yeah, it could be that.
Or it's a sex-crazed orgy where
they don't want you to see their faces...
or know their secrets.
I've been to those parties.
It doesn't look like this.
- What? What? Really?
- Come on, Chuck, don't be ridiculous.
We gotta find Vivian before Boris does.
Know what that means?
Time to mingle. Good luck.
Huh? No.
Don't you think we should stay together?
Wow. Do I taste a hint of pear?
Elderflower liqueur
with some muddled thyme.
You're an impressive bartender.
It's like you were born to do this, no?
- Hmm.
- Thanks for the drink.
She's right. This is fantastic.
It doesn't surprise me.
With Chuck being a full-blown agent
and he and Sarah always taking point...
leaves you stuck here, behind the bar.
- I am an integral part of this team.
- Excuse me.
- Might I have an extra lime?
- Ah. Yes.
Thank you, dear.
And look who's talking.
You live in Charah's apartment.
That is our apartment, okay?
And Chuck and Sarah like having me there.
We have a special dynamic.
Good evening.
I am Charles Carmichael
of the Worcester Carmichaels.
- Who might you be?
- I'm a heart.
- Hors d'oeuvre?
- Don't mind if I do. Cheers.
- Hello. Enjoying the party?
- I am now.
So how do you know Vivian?
We share a mutual friend.
Wake up.
You live with an engaged couple.
- It's like you're their kid.
- What? Pfft. That's ridiculous.
Yes, living with a couple
has its hiccups, you know?
But things are really good
at the apartment, so...
They won't be that way for long.
You gotta grow up sometime.
Know what I'd do?
I'd go out on top
before the situation gets worse.
So tell me,
do you know where to find Vivian?
Honestly, I don't even know
what she looks like.
- It's the first party she's ever thrown.
- Interesting.
Aah. Hot, hot, hot.
Oh, good show, good show.
Hot. Hot but good, very good.
Aah. Yes, some wine would do good.
Please, help yourself.
I'm sorry. I can get you another.
It's okay. I've probably had enough.
Ahh. I can't stop thinking
about Eyes Wide Shut.
- Yes. Right?
- And I like the idea of a theme party...
but you put these people
behind masks, and it gets...
- Creepy?
- Yeah.
- And a little sexual.
So Vivian,
do you know where she is, by chance?
I haven't had the opportunity
to say hello.
I'm sorry, I don't.
But if you do find her,
please, be sure to let me know.
I'd like to thank her
for this exquisite party.
So how do you, uh...?
How do you know Vivian?
I don't think anyone really knows her.
If this was her attempt
to get to know the neighbors...
she's failed miserably.
Well, at least there's an open bar.
I mean, she got that much right.
Uh, do you know where I could find?
Hey. I found Boris. Casey, Boris is here.
- He's wearing a green mask.
- We're on it.
- We need to find Vivian.
- I may have just met her.
Hi, sweetie.
Good boy. Shh.
- Vivian.
- Vivian McArthur?
What are you doing here?
Whoa, what's going on?
We know you're an associate
of Alexei Volkoff.
Alexei Volkoff?
What are you talking about?
- We're CIA. We're here to protect you.
- Protect me from what?
- Get in the stable.
- Stop. Don't move.
Take her alive. Kill the others.
We need to lose these guys.
- What's the best way out?
- I don't know.
Um, the house is back that way.
Casey, we're trapped
in one of the stables.
Copy that. We're on our way.
Some things never change.
Come on, Grimes, let's go.
Let's do this.
What the hell was that?
This can all end now.
Just give me the key, Vivian.
- What is he talking about? Key?
- I don't know.
I have nothing to do with Alexei.
I haven't seen him in years.
Then why does he pay
for the manor you live in?
Because I'm his daughter.
Vivian, if you want to live,
give me the key.
Look, can you please tell me
what this is all about?
Your father is an arms dealer and murderer
and all-around bad guy, okay?
- No, my father is an oil executive.
- We'll explain it later.
I have an idea. Chuck, get ready to flash.
They're trapped in the back stables.
Come on.
- What are you doing?
- Saving you.
No, we're saving you. Get in.
You are amazing. You are the best spies.
That was so awesome.
Good Lord. What happened to you two?
- You smell like vomit and Cheerios.
- We had a baby.
We need help.
Follow me.
Luckily, we have
a sleep-slash-baby aisle.
Ah.
You need the new Sleep Sheep.
Look at this.
It says it can record
Mama's soothing voice for the baby.
So there you go.
On my way
I would like to...
What is that?
I'm sorry, Jeff and Lester got their hands
on one of these and did some recording.
Jeff has some strange nap habits.
I'll have them shut it off.
No, no, no. Thanks for your help.
- That's exactly why I got myself snipped.
- Huh?
I may see you, I may tell you to run
On my way
- Babe, that song.
- We need that.
Okay, I'll just go ask them for it.
- Wait, wait, wait. What if they say no?
- They can't say no.
We should take it.
- Are you sure about this?
- Oh, yeah.
Good, because I have a plan.
I would like to...
- Eleanor Bartowski-Woodcomb.
- Hillary Rodham Clinton.
- Oh, are we not playing that game?
- We are not.
I came in here to breast-feed.
Maybe I could go somewhere else
to nurse.
Perhaps the backroom?
We should follow her.
Well, I believe her.
Everything she says checks out.
I do too. It seems like she has no idea
who her father actually is.
I think he lied to her her entire life.
Then why does Boris think
she has this key?
Hi. I was wondering, um,
is it possible I could stay with you tonight?
No, no, everything's fine.
They didn't get to enjoy
their Valentine's Day either...
and it's their apartment too.
Listen, I'll handle the paperwork again
if you guys take care of that.
Since you two got engaged...
Mr. Sensitivity might be feeling
a little irrelevant.
- I'll go talk to him.
- No, no, let me talk to Morgan.
You debrief Vivian.
Maybe he feels like a third wheel because
we only hang out when you're around.
You know, Morgan and I could use
some one-on-one time.
It'll be fun.
Okay. Have fun.
Let me ask you a question.
You and I don't usually do
this kind of thing...
so I was just wondering
if there's a reason that you're here.
No. No, no. I was just looking to hang.
Cool, cool. Let's hang. Ha, ha.
- Yeah.
- Okay.
So, uh, I know you guys
like having these toys around.
- Toys?
- Yeah. Maybe we can play with them.
Bang, bang.
Yeah, uh, sorry, sorry.
No offense, please, but these, um...
They're not toys.
They're collectibles.
- They're not for playing.
- Oh.
Chuck and I had to pool all our money
to get these guys.
- Original 1977 Kenner line.
- Well, I'm sorry. I didn't know.
They're really fun to look at.
The trick is...
Chewie always goes
on Han's right side.
So... Anyway, I've been arranging them
this way since I was about 13...
if you can believe that.
They're toys.
They're just toys, aren't they?
- They're just toys.
- No, they're collectibles.
- It's different. They have value.
- No, no, no. Wait a minute.
Wait, you're not here to hang.
You're here because I'm a third wheel.
Casey was right.
Oh, my God. I play with toys.
I live with a couple. I am a child.
Oh, I'm like your child.
You guys are like my parents.
Oh, my God.
It's okay. Calm down. It's fine.
I mean, look at this. I can't...
I can't do this anymore.
I have to grow up.
I have to move out.
That's what I have to do.
I have to go.
So my father, he actually killed people?
- Did you spend much time with the man?
- Honestly? No.
He put me into schools,
sent me on trips all over the world.
He made sure every minute
of every day was occupied.
But he was never a part of my life.
Or, uh, he was trying to protect you...
from the very dark and dangerous world
that he was a part of.
Yeah, maybe.
And now you have a chance
to do what you want.
Right.
Now I just have to figure out
what that actually is.
After the party, I'm sure we can safely
cross being a socialite off the list.
I can't believe I still don't know
what to do with my life.
Can I not be a spy for a second?
- Oh, please.
- Okay.
You should've seen my life
a few years ago.
I was working a dead-end job,
I was living with my sister...
and then something...
An opportunity just fell in my lap.
Afternoon, colonel.
Paperwork, bartending...
Any chance your skills are being wasted?
You were at the bar.
- What are you doing in Castle?
- Director Jane Bentley, NCS.
I was in England to observe.
I'm not like Agents Bartowski or Walker,
or even General Beckman.
I see your true potential.
You started working for the NSA...
because you were America's
best sharpshooter, and now...
You're so much more than this.
It seems your team
doesn't need you anymore.
When are you gonna accept that
and move on?
Getting to a point?
I'm putting together a new team,
and I want you to lead them.
- What's the directive?
- You're curious. Good.
I'll be in touch.
I never expected this to be my life.
But here I am...
and I'm happy.
And if you give it some time...
I'm sure that you can find that
for you as well.
So, what happens now?
Okay, well, now the best thing to do
is get you into a CIA safe house.
I've spent my entire life
being hidden away by my father.
This is serious.
This is very serious business.
Boris has gone after your father
and is taking out everyone close to him.
He knows where you live.
Wait, okay, so why don't we use that
to our advantage?
- What do you mean?
- Use me as bait.
- No.
- This is the first opportunity I've had...
to take control of my life.
I can't let it slip away.
Charles, I know it's asking a lot,
and I know that I'm a Volkoff.
But will you help me?
Please?
Yes.
Yes, I'll help you.
I may say to run
- On my way
- I may tell you to run
On my way
Oh, honey, I think I'm losing my mind.
I know. I used to love this song.
Okay, it's been two hours.
If I turn it off,
do you think Clara will stay asleep?
It couldn't hurt to try.
Babe, it could be worse.
- Really? Could it be?
- Hey, we're doctors.
We've gone without sleep before.
We were born for this.
Okay. You're right.
Well, pick me up with a golden hand
I may see you
I may tell you to run
On my way
Hey, Morgan, buddy, hey,
I gotta pack for the mission...
but Sarah said you were moving out,
so I told her that was, of course...
completely ridiculous.
No, she's right. I'm doing it.
I'm gonna move out.
No, but, see, that's totally ridiculous.
Morgan, I'm so sorry about busting in
on you and Alex on Valentine's Day...
with the rug and the...
The point is,
you had the living room for 90 minutes.
We had a deal, I broke it. I'm so sorry.
I am not moving out because of
what happened on Valentine's Day.
No, I'm moving out because it's just...
It's been a long time coming, you know?
Neither of us wants to admit it, but...
Admit what? What do you mean?
Heh. Chuck, do you realize you and Sarah
are gonna be married in a few months?
My friend, married. Heh.
You should have your own place.
It's ridiculous.
I have a serious girlfriend now,
who, by the way, takes me seriously.
I just think it's time we both grow up.
We are grown up. Come on.
Why wouldn't you wanna live
with your friends?
- Aren't you happy? I'm happy.
- Of course I'm happy.
But we were both happy...
when your father let us build a fort
in the attic and sleep there all summer.
- That was a great summer.
- That was a good summer.
But things change and...
It's not really a bad thing.
I think it's gonna be okay.
- Where are you gonna go?
- I don't know.
I gotta finish packing up,
and then I'm gonna head out that door...
and I'm just gonna open myself up
to the universe.
- So moving to your mom's?
- Yeah. Yeah, pretty much straight over.
Come on, this is okay. This is okay.
Bright side, this is not gonna be hard
to split up, okay?
I've done most of it.
From what I can figure, the original
Super NES with "Donkey Kong," yours.
Right, sure.
And you'll be taking
all of the Hong Kong wire fu...
and Miyazaki flicks, I assume?
You know what happens
when you assume.
- You're usually correct.
- Yeah.
I guess really all that's left
to take into consideration is our, uh...
Han Solo and Chewbacca original '77
Kenner line collector's edition.
- We went in on these together, buddy.
- Sure did.
So we just each take one?
No, no, that's crazy talk.
We can't split them up.
You can't separate Han and Chewie.
Chewie's Han's first mate
and constant companion.
- What up?
- Ha, ha.
Plus they're worth more, ahem,
as a set, so...
So we should sell them.
We don't need to decide right now.
We can sleep on it.
We can decide tomorrow.
- Totally.
- I got a big mission ahead of me.
Right, sure you do. And you know what?
I have so much more packing
to do and...
So I'll just sleep with him tonight, then,
in my room.
Not sleep with him.
But he's gonna be in my room.
And, you know,
Chewie will just stay with me.
- For the night, obviously.
- Obviously, obviously.
- Okay, then.
- Okay.
- Chuck, is everything okay?
- Yeah.
Ahem. Yeah. Ahem.
I was just resting. Stretching.
I was stretching.
I find the wall to have...
It's a lower-lumbar thing. Mm-hm.
- I'm fine, I'm good.
- I'm sorry about Morgan.
It's fine. I'm fine. He's fine.
We're fine, so... How's the...? Ahem.
How's the packing for the mission going?
You ready?
Yeah.
If we're gonna use
Boris' knowledge of you to our advantage...
we're gonna need to know the details.
Walk us through a day. We need
to figure out when you're vulnerable.
Odds are Boris is doing
the exact same thing right now.
I wake up at 6:00.
I make breakfast, get dressed...
and then I take Artemis out
for a morning walk.
Well, hello, Vivian.
How do I look?
- You said the details are important, right?
- Mm-hm.
Here.
I always wear this.
Perfect.
- Are you okay?
- Shouldn't I be the one that goes?
Absolutely not.
You should stay here, where it's safe.
Everything's gonna be fine.
Sarah's had years of training.
And Casey will be watching
my every move.
I'm at the north gate.
If Boris attacks, he'll do it here.
This is it.
Are you sure she'll be all right?
She always is.
Everything looks clear.
I've got a mile until the gate.
I'll be waiting.
It's time.
Whoa, whoa.
- Casey, something's wrong.
- I'm coming to you.
Whoa, whoa. Easy, boy.
Whoa, whoa.
Whoa, whoa!
I'm coming, Walker.
Sarah? Casey, what's wrong?
What's happening?
Is everything okay?
Stay inside.
You shouldn't be out here. Go.
Casey, where are you? Where is Sarah?
Sixty seconds out.
I'm on my way. Stay with Vivian.
- What do you think you're doing?
- I'm not doing this.
I'm not letting anyone die for me.
I have spent my whole life hiding.
It ends today.
All right, let's do this.
- It's not Vivian.
- Then kill her and find Vivian.
She's the only one
who has what we want.
Walker. Walker.
There's too many of them.
Go and get Chuck, okay?
Shut up.
You know I'm not leaving you here.
Let's get you under cover.
The road's up ahead.
You okay back there?
Yeah, yeah.
We got company.
I didn't spend 10 years
in equestrian school for nothing.
Hyah! Hyah!
- Do you think we lost them?
- I don't know.
I know. No, we haven't.
Hyah!
- Go, Artemis, go.
- They're gaining on us.
Come on. Go, go.
Listen, it's only a matter of time
till they catch us.
We're carrying too much weight.
- Well, what do you suggest?
- Plan B.
Don't stop for anything.
Well, that was kind of cool.
Sarah, Casey, where are you?
Sarah. Hey.
Sarah.
Where's Vivian?
I've reached the stables.
Good. Stay there. We're on our way.
Vivian.
What do you know?
Alexei Volkoff has a daughter.
Must have taken a lot of work
to keep you under wraps.
Now just give me the key
and I'll make it painless, I promise.
- My father never gave me any key.
- Yes, sweetheart, he did.
When you were young.
A token of his affection.
So think hard, Vivian. Where is it?
I don't know. None of this makes sense.
My father didn't want me
to be involved in this.
Really? You were skeet shooting at age 7,
had your black belt at 13...
and by the time you graduated,
you were fluent in five languages.
Your whole life,
your father's been grooming you.
You are his succession plan.
But he was wrong about you.
See, he couldn't recognize
what you really are:
An indecisive, weak little girl.
Look, I know what you did was hard,
but you had no choice.
- Boris would have killed you.
- But now he's gone.
And the rest of the lieutenants are dead.
There's no one left to put the pieces
of Volkoff Industries back together.
What happens to it now?
Without a leader, your father's empire
is just an empty office in Moscow.
Vivian, did Boris tell you anything
about the key?
What he was looking for?
No, he didn't. Sorry.
Time to go.
- You sure you'll be all right?
- Yeah.
I can't thank you enough.
For your advice, for everything, Charles.
I think it's time I figured out
what to do with my life.
Well, I'm sure you'll think of something.
Bye.
So this is, uh?
This is it, huh?
Yeah. Yeah, this is it.
Buddy, I know you're committed
to moving out, and I get it...
but I can't tell you enough
how much Sarah and I love you.
And love having you here.
Ahh. Dude. I love being here.
It would be easy to leave
if things sucked, though, you know?
And I need to grow up.
Maybe that means leaving behind
something that's great too.
The end of an era.
It is indeed.
- We'll still have game night, though.
- Every Monday.
So, what's gonna happen
with Han and Chewie, huh?
Where are they?
Did you sell them already?
Well, I mean, Chewie is Han's first mate
and constant companion.
It just didn't seem right to separate them.
More importantly,
I thought they should stay in the family.
You moved her into the nursery?
You think she's ready?
Honey, she's 3 months old.
It's time for Clara to be in her own room.
Besides, she's not alone in there.
- Which means that we can be all alone.
- I am way ahead of you.
I already have our outfits laid out
and ready to go.
I've been waiting for this
since Clara was born.
- I love you.
- I love you too.
I'm not leaving my team.
What I have here is good.
But you've been here for four years...
longer than any other assignment
you've had.
- Yeah.
- These people mean a lot to you.
For God's sake,
you saved Agent Walker's life today.
But you're not gonna spend the rest
of your career with this team.
Sooner or later,
you're gonna have to move on.
Why not today,
when you can go out on top?
I'm not leaving Burbank.
You won't have to.
The mission's right here.
Huh.