Hi, I'm Chuck. Here are a few things
you might need to know.
I'm not gonna fight you on this anymore.
If you trust her, that's enough for me.
Your father never wanted you to see this.
See what?
Flash, come on.
My mom did something to me
with that device.
You mom gave us a way out.
Sarah, I can't flash.
The Intersect is gone.
We're in a real mess,
Agent Bartowski.
Your trust in Agent Frost proved
a colossal error.
I know I screwed up, general.
If she weren't my mom, I would have
shown much better judgment.
Which is why you haven't
been ejected from the agency.
But Agent Frost
is extremely dangerous.
She and Alexei Volkoff
are now top priorities for capture.
Agent Walker, Interpol reported
a sighting of them in Istanbul.
Move out immediately.
- What about me?
- Until the Intersect is working...
you're Chuck's shadow, in Burbank.
Uh, general? I'm sorry.
I'm sorry, but are you saying
that the Intersect can, in fact, be fixed?
Our scientists think
your mother used a suppression device.
There could be countermeasures.
So it's only been suppressed.
It's not gone, like "gone" gone?
I'm not a scientist, Chuck.
But you're about to meet a lot.
You can ask them.
This is pretty snug.
The Intersect is an implanted collection
of memories.
A suppression device hides
those memories...
under what you might call
a psychological rock.
We need to find that rock
and remove it.
Here we go.
Ooh.
What was the point of the water?
I was just wondering.
Mm-mm.
All right.
And that's day 31.
Great session, fellas.
The file you requested, Mr. Bartowski.
Thanks, Greta.
Is it strange that all of the new
employees have been named Greta?
As long as they're spicy.
That's strange
that you don't find that strange.
But speaking of strange. You've been
giving off some real sad sack vibes lately.
Bit of a whiny wuss, if you ask me.
Do you ever wonder
if this is all life is gonna be?
You know, Buy More? Burbank?
Are the best years behind us?
- Whoa, whoa.
- Wow.
- That sounds like candor.
- Yeah, no.
Yes. No. Yeah, no.
I mean, I can handle candor.
I'm an emotional man.
But candor from you?
No-ski, Bartowski. No interest.
- You knew that.
- I must be worse off than I thought.
I don't know why.
My life would be a never-ending
Cialis commercial if I had her.
- Hey.
You look gorgeous.
- How was, uh?
- Russia this time?
I wish I had good news.
There's no sign of your mom
or Volkoff anywhere.
- What about his headquarters?
- Boarded up.
For the last month,
every trail has gone cold.
They're underground. Any luck with...?
Tests?
You'd have heard.
And by that I mean you'd have heard
my giant sigh of relief, even in Moscow.
- Ha, ha.
- You'll get it back soon enough.
When? What's the timeline?
I'm hoping very soon.
Because I haven't been on a mission
in a month.
I wake up
with my trigger finger twitching.
It's itchy. Literally, it itches.
Um, all the scientists who were checking
me out, they hit a wall.
But they're sending a specialist in.
Should be here any minute.
- Better be good.
- Casey...
nobody wants to put the team back
together on missions more than me.
He's not being fair.
- Hey.
- Don't let anybody pressure you.
Hey, hey, no pressure, buddy,
but, uh, Casey is a disaster.
- Morgan.
- No, I'm worried about the guy, okay?
I was talking to Alex.
He went over to move furniture.
He stood there, staring at her fish tank,
muttering about an itchy trigger finger.
I need the Intersect back. I get it.
- He gets it.
- Okay.
Look, the specialist is probably here
right now, so wish me luck.
Really, really, really good luck.
Hello?
Stop! Oh!
Whoa, ho, ho. Whoo!
Amazing work, Agent Carmichael.
You've got the stones of a bull.
Thanks. And who might you be?
Agent Rye. Jim.
CIA psyops division, Langley.
Forgive the dramatic introduction...
but I need to know
what kind of man I was working with.
And you, taking on three ninjas
without the Intersect?
Impressive.
Thanks. Ha.
You're, uh, different
than the other scientists.
I don't believe the psychological rock
can be hoisted off the Intersect...
by watching kittens play with yarn.
- Huh.
- My method is physical...
psychological, painful...
brutal.
Brutal? Can't wait to get started.
Chuck, if you're serious
about restoring the Intersect...
then I promise you, at the end
of this process you will be a spy again.
Now what do you say?
You with me?
Let's get physical.
Chuck 4x08 - Versus the Fear of Death
Visualize for me
the rock sitting on the Intersect.
Done. It's, uh, granite, I guess.
Ooh.
With specks of marble. The kind of...
Talk to me about size.
Is it large, small?
Large-y small? I don't know, it's... Ow.
- What was that for?
- We're starting with pain therapy.
That was the required dose
to lift a small psychological rock.
Great, great. Got it.
Small psychological rock.
Okay, good. Got it. Ow.
- Why?
- That was the shock for a medium.
- I need to know what I'm dealing with.
- Oh, so if it's a boulder...
are you gonna hit him with a tank?
- I have to do this.
- We are digging deep into my mind.
- It looks like he's hitting you.
Agent Walker, how long has it been
since you've done kempo karate?
Not since spy candidate school.
- Naihanchi one!
- Unh.
- Naihanchi two! Bear kata.
Old man kata. Hyah, hyah.
Well executed.
And you smell delightfully
of grapefruit.
Once we determine
the proper method of treatment...
be it fear, pain, anxiety...
this will happen with the Intersect,
like her memory of kempo.
We just have to find the right stimulus
to reactivate.
Agent Walker, no more interruptions.
Yes. Thank you for coming in today.
Next time, buy something.
That's all I'm...
Dude, dude, listen to me.
That new Greta just disappeared
into thin air.
- I've seen her do that before.
- Mm-hm.
I thought it was in my head.
- No.
- She also has a tail.
That is in your head.
But this disappearing...
isn't that highly suspicious?
I'll answer for you.
Yes, beautiful Lester, it is.
Follow moi.
Black forest ham on honey oat
with chipotle sauce...
banana peppers and jalapeños?
- See?
No Buy More employee
is that sophisticated.
Oh.
God, you got beaten to a pulp.
Yeah, well, neuroscience hurts.
You know, I don't know
about Agent Rye's method.
He seems a little unorthodox.
Well, yes, granted. No question
about that. But he's doing his best.
And I'm willing to endure pain
if it means getting the Intersect back.
Chuck, your physical and mental health
are important too.
Ah, ah, ah.
Why are my earlobes sore?
Okay, I think I know how to fix this.
Oh. Ahem.
Oh.
Oh, yeah.
I should get beat up more often.
Chuck, this, um, treatment,
the experiments...
promise me you're not doing it
for me or us.
No. No, I'm doing it for the team.
No, I just...
I've never been a spy without the
Intersect. And I quite like being a spy.
Doing great things, doing them with you.
I want that back.
You don't need the Intersect to do
great things. You're great on your own.
But am I a spy?
Yes.
Yes, but you're Chuck Bartowski...
and you do that all on your own.
Massage oil should be warm.
I'll be right back.
I think we should start
with some top half.
- Aah!
- Honey, we have company.
What happened?
Did you flash?
What the hell is going on?
- Yes or no?
- What are you doing in our bedroom?
Since our pain experiments failed,
your fault, not mine...
I think the key to restarting
the Intersect is fear.
What are you doing in our home?
The castle's a safety zone.
And apparently this place is too.
Chuck feels protected by you.
We need to up the ante, again.
PFOD.
P-F?
Pfod?
Pure fear of death.
We need uncut, pure,
adrenalized fear...
rocketing through your plasma
right now.
This was close,
but, hey, that could be the cure.
Holy...! Ha-ha.
Boy, you scared me half to death. L...
Two civilian employees
have been watching me.
I'm getting annoyed by this.
I have a way of dealing
with annoying things.
It's pleasant. But only for me.
Oh, I see.
And, uh, could you tell me
which two civilians...
might, uh, that be?
Why'd I even bother?
Of course, I will keep an eye on them.
Okay.
- Go home. Go home.
- You go home.
- Get out of here.
- This way.
Chuck can't go on a mission
without Intersect. That's insane.
As well as being an expert psyops
operative and neurological Ph. D...
Agent Rye is a fully trained
field operative.
If he thinks the Intersect will be restored
on a mission, he's going.
And a mission just hit our radar,
Agent Rye. I think it fits your bill.
- Is it dangerous?
- Incredibly.
- Chance of violence?
- Guaranteed.
- Great.
- This is not great. This is crazy.
Agent Walker,
this is what Chuck wants.
Right, Chuck?
Whatever it takes
to get the Intersect back.
Chuck and Agent Rye will be
going to a chalet in Gstaad, Switzerland...
for the auction
of a 100-carat diamond...
the Cane Volto.
Our intelligence indicates leaders
of criminal and terrorist organizations...
plan to attend the auction.
This stone is more than it seems.
Method for money laundering,
payment for illegal weapons.
- Yeah, we've done this before.
- Thanks.
Ooh.
Chuck, your job is to win the auction
and bring the stone back to the U.S.
A room full of underworld killers.
Sounds great, right?
- Casey and I will be there as a backup?
- No.
No. With them in Gstaad,
Chuck will never reach maximum fear.
Walker, you and Casey will monitor
the mission from Castle.
What?
Chuck is going alone
with Agent Rye?
I'll be able to flash
if there's no safety net.
Yes, Chuck,
but then there's no safety net.
We got a plane to catch.
Let's move out.
- Wish me luck?
- Chuck, don't.
Don't be a hero.
Just come home safe to me, okay?
Quite a tableau.
Sometimes the scenery makes me cry.
Isn't it amazing being a spy?
I wish Sarah was here.
Not in, uh, an official capacity,
of course.
The only way in or out
of the chalet is the gondola.
Things go south, we're trapped.
You'll produce enough adrenalized fear
to lift a car, let alone restart the Intersect.
He's a big boy, Walker.
Yeah, Chuck's never been on a mission
without the Intersect.
Tell me, honestly, if things go wrong,
do you think that he can handle himself?
I don't know. But I know he'll try.
Which is exactly what worries me.
I'm just gonna just check in again.
For the sixth time.
Chuck, are you there yet?
Yeah, we're here.
Sarah, Switzerland is amazing.
Other than the fact
that this place is populated...
with a crowd
of international psychopaths...
the air is so fresh,
and the chocolate, so milky.
Uh, Chuck, listen, listen. If you get
cornered and you still can't flash...
just don't do anything crazy.
Don't worry. Everything's gonna be
just fine. I'll talk to you soon, okay?
Hey, are you sure
I don't need a disguise?
Hmm.
Someone could recognize you as CIA
and come after you with a knife.
Ha, ha. That would be great.
Ladies and gentlemen,
if you'll take
your seats, we will begin the auction.
Thank you.
The seller, Aldebert De Smet.
- Better known as the Belgian.
- Oh.
I bet I know how he likes his waffles.
Belgian. Yes, yes.
- I love your humor. So disarming.
- Oh.
De Smet is known for industrial
espionage not precious gems...
which is another reason
this auction seems odd...
aside from the crowd.
We've got underworld players
from Russia, Serbia, Montenegro.
Wow, you really know
your Euro baddies, don't you?
Focus. When you win the bidding,
your competition is not gonna be happy.
If you're lucky,
they'll follow you and try and kill you.
Fingers crossed.
- Good luck.
- No, wait.
You're going? I'm alone on this?
It's your best chance to flash.
- Okay.
- The Cane Volto diamond.
Very rare, 100 carats...
D colored, internally flawless.
Bidding starts
at 25 million Swiss francs.
Do I see 30 million? Thirty million.
Do I see 40?
Forty. Do I see 50?
Sir, you're already the high bidder.
Do I see? Fifty.
Sixty?
Sixty million Swiss francs?
Bid again, get bullet in back.
Holding at 50 million?
Fifty million going once?
Nice try, Rye,
but I'm not falling for it.
- Going twice.
- Sixty million Swiss francs.
I'm not afraid of your phony
Russian accent or your finger gun, okay?
- Bid again and die.
- Do I hear 65?
Ooh, let's get crazy.
Eighty million Swiss francs.
Eighty million to bidder number three.
Oh, I didn't die. What a shocker.
Stop fooling around, okay?
We got a job to do.
Do not bid.
Eighty then, going once...
One hundred million Swiss francs.
One hundred million,
ladies and gentleman.
Going once...
twice...
sold.
You can go.
- I blew it.
- You absolutely blew it. And no flash, huh?
- Have you had this chocolate?
- Yes, it's so milky.
So good. Thought that Russian
would get your blood pumping.
I thought it was you.
The Russian? It was such
a horrible accent. It sounded so phony.
What kind of a spy am I?
I can't even be scared properly.
But listen, I had a thought.
Who carries around a hundred million
Swiss francs on them? Nobody.
The diamond is gonna be here
until the money is transferred.
Until then, we can get a better look
at the thing.
You're good, Chuck.
Genius minds think alike.
But I say we do more
than just look at it.
Let's steal it.
You all know of this new Greta.
She's beautiful, yes.
And efficient, sure.
But why all the suspicious behavior?
We're forming a fact-finding mob
and we want you, my friends, involved.
We are calling it
Operation Get-A-Greta.
The objective is to root out
why such a nefarious individual...
is working here at the Buy More.
Oh, crap. They're onto Greta.
- What do we do?
- Tell Greta. She'll handle it.
Right, she'll... Wait a minute.
What do you mean, "She'll handle it"?
Hey.
- Who is she?
- Assassin.
No, she'll chop them up
into a bunch of pieces.
Are you kidding me?
I mean, these are our sort-of friends.
- Colleagues?
- Hmm.
No, huh? It doesn't matter.
No assassins. We have to handle this.
We don't have to do anything.
You're on your own.
Come on, I thought we were a team,
you and I? A damn good one.
The team is DOA
without the Intersect working.
So why protect something
that's going up in smoke, hmm?
You wanna waste time with these idiots?
You're on your own.
Hey, Chuck, hold on a second.
Do you happen to have the time?
Amazing. Where did you learn that?
Star Trek.
Star Trek? Really?
No, not really. Bangladesh.
Meditative trancing.
The secret is mind over matter.
- But I love the show.
- Well, who doesn't.
There is nothing in here.
Well, what are we supposed
to do now?
Now you flash.
How can I? I don't exactly fear death.
Security measures
will activate in four, three...
two, one.
- Security measures?
I've heard of this thing.
The temp drops about
150 degrees in 30 seconds.
So unless you wanna become
a Chucksicle...
I suggest you flash.
It's not happening.
Concentrate.
Feel the fear lifting the rock.
No flash, no flash.
Maybe Sarah can help us.
Yeah, Sarah can help us.
I got no service. What are we gonna do?
My teeth are freezing.
Chuck, can you flash?
It's not happening.
How about now?
Nothing.
All right. Move out of the way.
I honestly thought you would flash.
You knew the combination
this whole time?
We have a mission to complete.
I came prepared.
- But I honestly wasn't prepared for this.
- There's more than one diamond.
What is going on? This has gotta be
worth billions of dollars.
They can't just be diamonds.
On my missions, it's never just diamonds.
Yeah, you're right.
They're working some angle.
Do you always carry a loupe?
Yeah, well, when I heard the mission
was diamond-related...
I took the liberty of grabbing a loupe
out of Castle's closet.
I took an online gemology class
on the flight here.
It was very convenient.
Like I thought, fake. It's made of glass.
But there's something embedded inside.
Microdot.
Replace it with our phony.
This is a fake too.
Great work, Bartowski.
Now we gotta figure out what the story
is on these phony diamonds.
Rye, I don't understand.
A minute ago, I was truly fearing
for my life. Why isn't this working?
We need to explore a more sophisticated
level of fear therapy.
The psychological rock has keyed
onto a deeper anxiety...
a person...
a relationship.
- With whom?
Ah. What are you...?
With her.
Well, this has been a quiet lunch.
Uh. I should let you get back
to your books.
And you back to work.
How is that going by the way?
- What have you heard?
- Just what Morgan's told me.
That he's about ready
to have an intervention on you.
Look, we both know you haven't been
on a mission in a while...
but I think there's a little more to this
than just an itchy trigger finger.
What gives?
I'm preparing myself psychologically...
in case I get sent back
to Afghanistan or Iraq.
I got soft. I made friends here.
Well, you know Morgan is scared
of the team being broken up too.
And if you are transferred,
which might not even happen...
don't you think it'd be better
to be nice to your friends...
than drive them away?
Just a thought.
Hey, fellas.
What are you doing?
Can you tell me what this is?
Not a lure for the new Greta.
Do me a favor. You need to back off
this Greta thing. For your own good.
The operation is underway.
You can't stop this pit bull.
- He's got a taste for meat.
- Who's gonna be meat? You guys.
- You don't scare us.
- Yeah.
We won't be stopped.
And we can't be stopped.
And we won't be stopped.
I think I see her. Move.
- Move.
- Hey, what are you...?
Hey, now! Wow, ha-ha.
You have to stop that.
I have a bad ticker.
This is absolutely the last straw.
They put a webcam in my locker,
bugged my price gun.
The psychotic one follows me, narrating,
"The tracking of the Greta marmot."
What does that even mean?
Which one do you think
is the psychotic one? Doesn't matter.
If they discover my identity,
it'll breach national security...
and a CIA facility will be at risk.
It's time to neutralize the risk.
Oh, hold on a second, please.
They don't know anything, okay?
You... Trust me, they have
the mental capacity of field mice.
They bother me again,
they meet my favorite friend.
Understood.
I'm magnifying the microdot.
God only knows what's on it.
But it can't be good.
We'll start the analysis
and send it back to the team at Castle.
Do you really think that Sarah is the
emotional rock sitting on the Intersect?
Why do you always call for her
before you flash?
You did it in the bedroom
and in the vault.
- Yeah, well, you know, I was...
- Scared.
Perfectly normal.
For a Nerd Herder.
But a spy, Chuck,
handles his fear on his own.
- Or her own.
- Ask yourself a question.
Are you a spy
or are you a guy with a spy girlfriend?
I'm a spy.
The microdot is heavily encrypted...
but it appears to contain photographs
and blueprints for CIA assets.
Belgian is selling our intel
to the highest bidder.
And there are
a dozen other fake diamonds.
Colonel Casey, Agent Walker,
finish decoding the intel.
Bartowski and Rye, capture the Belgian
and recover the fake stones.
Until we know
what's on those microdots...
this is code red
and could likely get very ugly.
I feel it's essential I go
with Chuck and Rye to Switzerland.
Um, I think Sarah should
let us handle this...
seeing as this is the only way
I will get the Intersect back working.
We're talking about real danger now.
I can only handle fake danger?
I know Intersect is important but
none of Rye's therapies have worked.
The microdot contains highly sensitive
information the wrong people will kill for.
I can take care of these people
without you holding my hand.
Why does it make sense
to risk your life?
It's what I do, I'm a spy.
No, Chuck, you're not.
Not right now.
The mission is best accomplished
with the proper manpower.
Agent Walker, get to Gstaad.
A supersonic jet will have me there
in five hours. We'll talk.
Okay? I'm sorry Chuck.
I just can't let you risk your own life.
Greta to the cage.
Greta to the cage, please.
A delicious, though complicated,
footlong sub...
with black forest ham...
honey oat...
- No, no, no.
Chipotle sauce and banana peppers...
- What are you doing?
- If she doesn't kill you, I will.
...and jalapeños...
has been found
with your name on it.
So come to the cage.
Now we wait.
So I see our little lure worked,
eh, Greta?
If that is your name.
Come, sit.
What the hell are you doing, moron?
Listen to me. Mm-hm.
We can do this the hard way
or we can do this...
the way...
that's very difficult.
Whoa, whoa, stop, guys.
Greta, guys...
- ...quit this now.
- No.
I have had it. This stops here and now.
Who are you, Greta?
And what do you know?
Okay, there it is.
There it is. We are prepared
for the knife eventuality.
- Jeffrey, please disarm her.
- No.
Whoa, mama.
The only question is, do you wanna die
with your wig on or off?
Are you talking about my hair?
Wait, no.
Whatever you're thinking, do not do it.
- It is not worth it.
- Stand down. Now.
Stand down.
What is going on here?
Her locker was full of credit card slips.
And she was making off
with the head massagers.
She's been sneaking around
because she's a thief.
You swine. How could you do
that to me after I trusted you?
Let's go. Let's go. Come on.
Thank you. Well, done.
- Casey, thank you.
- Mm.
- Okay, you're going downtown.
- Thief?
How does a thief disappear
into thin air?
There's an old walkway behind the walls
in the HTR for electrical repairs.
Should have been boarded up
after the fire, but she found it.
Why did she transmogrify
into a woodland creature?
- Shh.
- Why does she have a tail?
Consider that ignored.
You fellas did a great job.
Buy More thanks you.
That was intense. We caught a thief.
And I need a change of trousers.
Hey, hey, hey, Chuck,
I think we got a visitor. Yep.
The Belgian just entered the vault.
- There's no microdot.
- Evidently, we, uh, had a security breach?
Get surveillance footage
of the vault and the hallway.
- And meet me at the gondola.
- But the Russian buyer...
No time for that. Pack up the diamonds.
We're leaving now.
Gondola.
Perfect. Enclosed space, no escape.
- We'll arrest them there.
- Uh, Sarah's plane is almost here.
Well, we can wait for her and lose him.
Or go be heroes.
- Let's be heroes.
- Thattaboy.
Yes.
Hey, it's Chuck.
You know what to do.
It's me again. Why aren't you getting
my calls? Call me, okay?
I love you.
Colonel Casey,
I've admired your work for years...
but this outpost and its personnel...
are unprofessional.
And I'm disappointed in you.
Well, listen, Agent Greta.
I don't know who you've worked with
or what crew you were on.
This is the best damn spy team
in the world.
We are strong. So do us a favor,
don't let the door hit you in the ass.
- We are strong, aren't we?
- Mm.
Yeah, even if we are missing
a few pieces.
Doesn't it feel better
being part of a team...
than always suffering alone.
Right. I always forget
the no-touch thing. Point taken.
Oh, man. Speaking of missing pieces.
Casey, why is Chuck on that monitor?
This isn't good.
- Hey.
- Chuck's on the microdot.
- The Belgian knows he's the Intersect.
- What?
Come on, Chuck, pick up the phone.
- Chuck.
- Sarah.
- Where are you?
- We're about to arrest the Belgian.
- If anything happens, I know I'll flash.
- The Belgian knows...
- Walker, we can handle it from here.
- No, wait!
All right, just follow my lead.
If we get into real trouble, you'll get us
out of it. You don't need Sarah.
This is all you.
Last chance, Chuck.
On or off?
On.
Aldebert De Smet,
you're coming with us.
No, no, no.
Agent Carmichael is coming with me.
The assets in your head
is worth far more...
than the entire list embedded
in these microchips.
Surrender or die.
- They know I'm the Intersect.
- Scared?
Me too.
- Drop your weapon.
- No tether, no Sarah.
We're in it up to our chins.
- How we feeling, Chuck?
- Not great.
- I sort of flashed, but I'm not sure.
- All right. Well, let's find out.
Rye.
- Rye!
- Two hundred feet to the rocks below.
Talk about some serious danger, huh?
Ow.
Anything?
No. No, nothing yet.
Believe me, I'm plenty terrified.
Help me up.
Sorry, Chuck, not gonna happen.
What? No. My hands are slipping.
Rye, I may actually die right now.
Fantastic. This is your final test.
The wind's picking up.
You're looking death in the face.
Only thing that can save you is Intersect.
Focus, Chuck. You can do this.
- No, this is crazy. It's not coming back.
- But you know the rock is Sarah.
Tell yourself you don't need her
and give in to the fear.
But I do need her. I love her.
I'd rather love Sarah
than have the Intersect. Help me up.
The CIA didn't send me out here
to affirm your love, Bartowski.
You need the Intersect up and running.
Now, get that rock off your chest...
and be a real spy like me.
Did I just get shot?
No, no, no.
I certainly did.
Grab my hand or die.
Come on.
What's going on? Where are you?
Pursue Agent Carmichael
and we will kill him.
Slowly.
There will be no further warning.
No. Please wait.
General, I want immediate authorization
to hunt down this son of a bitch.
I would grant if there was indication
De Smet was in Belgium.
- There's no indication of his whereabouts.
- They were at Gstaad Airport.
I have a witness who saw them board
a private jet, tail number CLM...
CLM1211. I know, Agent Walker.
The plane didn't just disappear.
It had to have landed somewhere.
We put a code red out to
every clandestine agency on the planet.
The moment there's a sign of Chuck,
we'll mobilize every resource.
Colonel Casey, you've got your mission.
You're running point.
And me?
Sarah, he's out there. We'll find him.
But until there's intel,
go home and get some rest.
You'll be informed
of any developments.
I'm staying right here.
You're going home. That's an order.
Bartowski's smart.
Intersect or no, he'll be fine.
This is all my fault.
He did this to prove to me
that he could be a spy.
What do you want?
I want the Intersect.
What are you doing, Walker?
I'm gonna go find Chuck.
We'll go together.
Wherever he is, we will find him
and we'll bring him back.
Thank you.
I don't have it, Mr. Belgian... De Smet.
It's gone. I lost it.
Please, Agent Carmichael,
don't take me for a fool.
The less you resist,
the less painful this will be.