Hey, I'm Chuck. Here's a couple of things
you might need to know or just forgot.
This isn't a code, Devon.
This is a real car.
My dad must've left this for me.
Your father never wanted you to see this.
See what?
Come on! Flash!
Sarah, my mom did something to me
with that device.
I can't flash. The Intersect is gone.
Agent Carmichael is coming with me.
Surrender or die.
- What do you want?
- I want the Intersect.
It's gone. I lost it.
The less you resist,
the less painful this will be.
You know what I really want?
This could be a very good "show me,
don't tell me" situation, I think.
I want you to flash.
- What?
- I want you to flash for me.
Come on, do it. Show me.
But I can't. You know that I can't.
The Intersect's not working.
Why are we talking about this?
Are you sure that you can't flash?
Well, yeah.
Yeah, I'm pretty sure.
But we could do other stuff, you know?
We could, uh...
We could kiss more or talk.
No. Never mind.
Why? No. No. Hey.
Hey, you. Hey. Hey.
You know, there's pills for this.
Easy. Easy, buddy.
This is all in your head.
You have got to get over this.
I mean, come on.
You really expect to keep
a girl like that without flashing?
This doesn't make any sense.
Why are you here?
I shouldn't even be here.
I was on a mission in Switzerland.
I was on a gondola.
I was taken by a Belgian.
What is going on?
Why isn't this working?
He knows he's in a dream.
Lester was the wrong choice.
Intensify the current.
Try something else.
I just need to figure out...
the right combination of people
from his life to use.
You've got to dig it out.
I can sell the secrets in his head for
more money than you can imagine.
Telling me again isn't going
to make this go any faster.
Agent Carmichael's brain will access
the Intersect if it's properly motivated.
It was clear from interrogation
that anxiety...
is his strongest motivating emotion.
God knows he is a neurotic man.
When we find the right mix of people
from his life to pressure him...
he will become so anxious
about not having the Intersect...
that his brain will be forced
to flash.
But this woman,
she will do most of the work.
Nothing makes him more anxious
than this Sarah Walker.
Five countries in three days,
and nothing.
Where's Chuck, Casey?
Got every agent in Castle
out looking for him. We'll find him.
Let's regroup with Beckman.
She'll have something.
We have nothing. The Berlin team
had an address for a lieutenant.
By the time we got a search warrant,
he had disappeared.
The same thing happened in Caracas.
Target dropped behind North Korean lines
where we couldn't follow.
General, a lot of bureaucracy
is keeping us from finding Chuck.
I know,
but we have to work with our allies here.
Get a couple of hours of sleep.
I'm not going to sleep. Chuck is
out there without the Intersect...
with people who think he has it.
He's never been more helpless.
I know. And be assured that
the Intersect is a priority to the U. S...
as is finding the Belgian
before he sells our secrets.
Forget the secrets,
this is about Chuck.
General, I'll make sure we get some rest,
check back with you later.
Don't. I know.
Being a worried girlfriend
isn't gonna help him.
- You need to be a spy, a professional.
- Fine.
- Where do we look next?
- Is she off?
Yeah. Welcome back.
And Daddy got something Daddy likes.
Oh, Daddy.
I'm Daddy. You guys were kind of...
Okay, you were just looking at me...
This is from our Swiss field op,
which, by the way, I just love saying.
His name is Anand Chanarong,
an aide to the Thai ambassador...
but he is also a known associate
of one...
Guys, come on. Baddie the Belgian.
He handles all the Belgian's dirty work.
Extortion, kidnapping.
And he's in L.A. At the Thai embassy.
Which is Thai soil.
It's not in our jurisdiction.
- We don't have jurisdiction, Walker.
- Come on, Casey. Be a spy.
Who told you to bring this in here?
This is the ugliest rug I've ever seen.
We're looking for the Belgian.
- Who are you?
- He's taken somebody.
Charles Carmichael. Goes by "Chuck."
What do you know about him?
You have no right to be here
on Thai soil.
Hi, welcome to American soil.
Now, where's Chuck?
Chuck 4x09 - Versus the Phase Three
I'm asking you again,
where can I find the Belgian?
You don't understand
how high the stakes are.
You're gonna tell me exactly
what I wanna know.
Listen, I think Sarah's about to go
all Kill Bill on this dude.
Beckman knows somebody stormed
into the embassy and stole a national.
I'm new, but I think that's
international incident-y.
Walker knows what lines not to cross.
Walker!
A word, please.
- Well, can it wait?
- No.
He's not talking. And he's a smirker.
Just because I helped bring him here
doesn't mean I'm giving you free rein.
You need to cool down,
get some rest.
- I'm not going anywhere.
- Yeah, I was wrong.
You're not acting
like a worried girlfriend.
No, you're acting like a spy
I used to know.
Before Chuck.
Langston Graham's wild-card enforcer.
I didn't like that Sarah Walker.
You know why? She was unpredictable.
Now you're gonna go home. I insist.
- You insist? How are you gonna do that?
- I insist. I insist.
Hey, hey, listen to me. Look, Sarah,
we all wanna find Chuck, okay?
But I think we could all use
a little rest too, right?
I know I'm super cranky
if I get under nine hours.
So let's calm down
and let's go get a few winks...
and then you go back to your manhunt
nice and well-rested, okay?
You have two hours.
Wow.
Man, that was scary. Did I do okay?
I was kind of shaking there.
I know it's not scary for you, but...
I can't believe you have a 36-hour shift.
You're pregnant, it's not okay.
Honey, the nurses reserved me
my own broom closet.
I have a very nice cot.
I will steal some winks.
Between long shifts
and the stressing about family...
I'm worried about you and the baby.
Listen, I promise
to take care of myself.
- You need to be calm and peaceful.
- I will be calm and peaceful.
Not too calm.
Don't go falling asleep at the wheel.
- Speaking of, can't you take the Sienna?
- I like my dad's ride.
Did your dad's ride get five out of five
stars on side-impact protection?
What is this?
Whoa.
What is this thing?
- I've never seen anything like it.
- I don't know.
I thought I'd found everything
of my dad's that there was to find.
- Do you think it's spy stuff?
- I don't know.
Well, we could try and turn it on
and figure out.
Right.
I don't want it to be spy stuff.
You do it.
- Nothing.
- Shoot.
I'm late. I can't believe
that I have to work for two days.
This is all I'm gonna think about.
Babe, remember,
we're staying calm, okay?
Go to work and don't worry.
I'll call Chuck and figure it out.
No. No Chuck, okay?
If this is spy-related,
it's gonna reel him back in.
I wanna keep him safe.
Chuck, listen to me very closely.
If you don't access the Intersect,
forget about Sarah...
Ellie, Morgan,
and this Awesome character...
no one will love you.
You'll be nothing.
You will lose them all.
How you holding up?
Not great.
Yeah. No, me either.
I've had this awful taste in my mouth
ever since Chuck disappeared.
Makes me think, wherever he is,
he's probably eating something icky.
Strange twin thing.
Do you know what this is?
No. Nope.
Never really saw that before.
I really miss him.
Fine. Okay, I fold.
It's Chuck's proposal plan.
I hate myself.
Chuck was planning on proposing?
Yeah.
See, it's a combination of things
that are important to both of you.
And some of it
is just from when he was little.
So here is where he was gonna
drive up in his DeLorean, of course.
And that'd be you, coming down
on a wild stallion. You'd meet here.
You were gonna hop in this Lamborghini
and take off down the coast and...
This might be an older draft.
It's been revamped since puberty.
When was he planning on doing this?
I don't know.
Ever since he lost the Intersect...
the proposal plan got put on hold.
Did he think that I wouldn't
wanna marry him without the Intersect?
- Is that how I made him feel?
- No. No. Chuck knew that...
Chuck knows that you love him,
Sarah, okay?
It's just you're kind of a big fish,
you know?
And to a regular guy
with no supercomputer in his brain...
I gotta think that
that's pretty intimidating.
That's not the reason
why I love Chuck.
I do wanna spend my life with Chuck,
with or without the Intersect.
That's fantastic. That's great.
He knows that, right?
Because you told him that.
Oh.
You're certain you know nothing
about the whereabouts...
of the aide, Anand Chanarong.
- Haven't heard a word, ma'am.
- How mysterious.
I want you to keep an eye
on Agent Walker.
I think she might be on the edge.
What are you doing back here?
Is the camera in Chanarong's cell
still out?
- What's in the bag?
- Go.
- You're not gonna wanna be here.
- I'm not going anywhere.
I insist.
Do you feel like talking yet?
An American agent in a government
facility would never use any of that.
- I'm not afraid.
- You're right.
Normally, I wouldn't threaten the subject
with death by ammonia injection.
Burning somebody
from the inside out...
doesn't sound like something that's
in the Geneva Convention, does it?
But this man that I'm looking for,
he loves me.
He wants to marry me.
I see.
It's amazing what a woman would do
to find a husband.
Even the toughest spies in the world are
just racing against that biological clock.
Tick, tick, tick, tock.
You got me.
I'm just a needy, love-crazed girl
on a husband hunt.
Who's trained in over 200 ways
to kill you.
Afraid yet?
The Belgian has a hideout in northern
Thailand near the Burmese border.
That jungle's filled with killers.
I'm going with you.
You're not going where I'm going.
I'll do anything to get him back.
And I'm not gonna take you down
with me.
You were right. I'm different
without Chuck and I don't like it.
- You let me out of here. You need me.
- No. I need Chuck.
Walker.
Walker!
Who's got a screw loose?
- That has two meanings.
- Hey, guys, thanks for coming.
I'm hopeless and I was hoping
to get this computer fixed...
before Ellie got home from her shift.
Lucky for you, my Tuesday trapeze class
was canceled, so we're all yours.
You have a Roark 7?
Yeah, I guess so.
Oh, one other thing.
This little project has to stay a secret
from Chuck. Can we do that?
Yeah, yeah, absolutely we can, my large,
chiseled, dulce-de-leche-colored friend.
But we want a little something from you,
if you know what I mean.
No, I actually have no idea
what you mean.
Four words:
My abscess, Lester's gout.
Medical consult for tech expertise.
You in?
Yeah, uh, anything for Ellie.
Good. Fabulous. Fabulous. All right.
Now let me look at the computer
while Jeffrey takes off his pants.
Yeah, I need to get my kit.
Hey.
I closed my eyes for a minute
and then she was gone.
She is so sneaky,
she must make an awesome spy.
- Walker went AWOL. Open the door.
- I figured she'd do something crazy.
I might be responsible. I told her
about Chuck's plans on proposing.
What? You threw gas on the fire.
Can't you ever keep your mouth shut?
Well, I'm sorry, Casey, okay?
I over-share to connect.
- I'm a connector.
- Open the door.
Yeah. Okay, I...
What?
I want in, okay? No, listen to me.
Chuck is my best friend.
And I wanna do more
than sit behind some computer.
Absolutely not.
Chuck's in the jungles of hell.
It's too dangerous.
Well, fine. I mean, you want out,
I want in, all right?
Come on, I'm ready to go.
I have a backpack.
Casey, it's Chuck.
Fine.
- Deal?
- Deal.
No bullets for you.
Come on, we're going to Thailand.
You can talk to me.
I heard the Belgian has a hideout here.
Is that true?
First, sit down, relax.
Join me for a drink.
He has my boyfriend. Where is he?
Maybe I can be your boyfriend.
Anyone else wanna be my boyfriend?
Sarah, no. I can't lose you.
Please don't go. I'll do anything.
You say that, but then you don't flash.
You clearly don't want me enough.
I do. But I can't flash.
I know you wouldn't do this.
I know this is a dream
but please come back!
It's not working.
He's still aware enough
to suppress the Intersect.
Look at this.
I'm stimulating the hippocampus...
as much as I can
without causing permanent damage.
Don't take this the wrong way,
but you are boring me.
Push harder.
Then we are in Phase Three.
We wipe out everything in his head
but the Intersect.
We lobotomize him.
So there would be no personality...
no memories, no thoughts
in the way of the Intersect.
All right, let's do it.
That was very impressive.
I'm guessing you are the woman...
who has been fighting her way
across Thailand.
The people have been talking much
about the giant blond she-male.
Can you tell me
where to find the Belgian?
He's taken somebody
very important to me.
I don't like the Belgian,
so I will tell you where he is.
But first, a little fun.
I will give you the information
if you can beat my best fighter.
It's been months
since he's had a good match.
He kills too fast. Ha, ha.
I think you might make things
entertaining.
So yes?
This ends now.
I definitely know how to use this,
dirtbags.
Smart move.
Good move, gentlemen.
Nice beard, nice beard.
- Sarah.
- Oh.
- Morgan?
- Yeah, yeah, are you okay? Hold on.
You using this?
Here, some water. Some water.
- How did you find me?
- How did we find...?
Half of Thailand is talking about
the giant she-male tearing through town.
But it's okay now. Casey and I are here.
Oh, my God. Scary snake. Scary snake.
King cobra.
Walker, what are you
doing here all alone?
This place is nothing but scoundrels,
assassins and warlords.
The scum of the earth.
Ah, Mr. Casey, your usual?
Come on, let's get out of here.
A deal's a deal. The fight's not over.
I beat your guy,
you tell me where the Belgian is.
- I'm gonna finish this.
- What? Seriously?
Does no one care
there is a cobra in there?
Okay. Move it over. Oh, oh, come on.
You are not getting bullets
for a long, long time.
There was a lot of bullets.
Tons and tons of bullets.
I can't work with this.
Nando, Pozidriv screwdriver, stat.
What is this? This is not a Po...
Are you gonna earn your lanced boil
or aren't you?
Ah, you know what? Just go. Jeffrey.
Hey, we only got a few hours left
till the end of Ellie's shift.
- I can't make heads or tails of this thing.
- Can't anyone upstairs help?
Ooh. What a relief.
So I just insert the softener and...
- Yeah, that should do it.
- I really appreciate your help.
You're a heart doctor and don't often
deal in the darker corners of the body.
No, no, sure don't.
Now, you have a part
that Lester needed?
Sure do. Here you go.
Thank you, Michael.
Nice thing you're doing for your lady,
by the way.
Thanks. I'm gonna go wash up.
Yeah!
- Hello?
- Hey. Finally got you.
- I haven't seen you in a few days.
- Ellie...
Ellie, Ellie, listen.
I don't know how to tell you this,
but I'm in major trouble.
- What's going on?
- Listen.
Okay, please don't be mad, but I've been
spying again and I've been taken, okay?
I need you to call Sarah. Call Casey.
Now, where's Chuck?
I am somewhere in the jungle
in Thailand.
And I am running for my life.
- Can't you flash?
- Well, uh, no, I can't.
Uh, I think you can.
Ellie, you don't sound very upset.
Well, I just know that you could flash
if you really tried.
This is all a dream too.
I can't get out of here, can I?
No, Chuck, you can't.
My name is Dr. Mueller.
I'm the one doing this to you.
If you don't access the Intersect,
I'll be erasing everything that is you.
Your thoughts, your memories, your life.
- You're real.
- I'm very real.
Now, Chuck, do you want to disappear
or give me the Intersect?
I can't.
Look, I'm sorry about Castle,
but Chuck is...
No, no. It's all right. Moron told me
he blabbed about the proposal.
I'm not leaving until I find him.
Neither am I.
Wow.
It's like your gun is your soul.
Your metaphorical yes...
to a question she couldn't possibly
bring herself to ask. Emotion later.
- Tonight, we find Chuck.
- You're with the gear.
- You ride in the back.
- I ride in the back.
Initiating Phase Three.
How long will it take?
To wipe his mind clean? It varies.
But look at this section here.
It's beginning.
Goodbye, Chuck.
Hey, Chuck. Chuck.
Hey. Hey, wake up, buddy.
Hey, son. Get on up.
You've been sleeping
for a long time, man.
I know...
I know that this is still just a dream.
But you are all very real.
- Of course we're real.
- No, no, no.
I was taken.
And I almost escaped.
No, that was a dream too.
Like The Manchurian Candidate.
Or that episode of either Family Ties
or Hogan's Family?
All right, I don't know
what you're talking about, buddy.
But we sure would like it
if you were to flash.
Ha!
See? See, I told you
this was just a dream.
A dream that hurts. Ow.
- Here.
- Okay.
Here's my pitch. What if we
didn't use guns this time, okay?
If you don't use guns,
they don't use guns.
If they don't use guns, we have
a mission where nobody gets shot.
- You see what I'm saying?
- Hmm.
A diversion instead.
A magnet. Ready, Morgan?
Guns. Let's use lots of guns.
What do you think it feels like
to watch your life disappear?
Chuck?
- Hey, Chuck.
- Morg?
It's me, buddy. Yeah.
I'm right here, okay? Now just flash.
Right. This is a dream.
This is only a dream.
Chuck, over here.
I need you to flash, son.
Okay. I'm ready to wake up now.
I mean,
remember when Sarah left you?
Oh, my God. That was...
That was funny. I mean, man...
Chuck, I'm on TV.
What's it gonna be, Bartowski, huh?
You wanna be a nerd,
or you wanna be a spy?
Flash or become expendable,
Agent Bartowski.
Flash, okay? Flash now, Chuck.
- Do it.
- This is your last chance.
- Flash.
- Do it, Bartowski.
What's the matter?
Don't you love your country?
- Can I get out?
- Yes, and you'll flash.
Understand?
Do you love your country?
Do you wanna be more than a nerd?
- You need to flash right now.
- No! No, I can't! I can't!
The government wants you to flash.
Only you can prevent
forest fires, man.
This is dangerous. Be careful.
Is this a hostel? Or is there a...?
Is there a hostel nearby?
Because... It's a book. It's just a book.
Oh, man. Help me out here, guys.
Hey, you!
Shut up.
- Get on your knees.
- Who brought their dad to the party?
I have some friendship bracelets.
All right, this is like a violation
of my civil rights.
Looks like we didn't need the guns.
What's up with the she-male thing?
Chuck, it's okay.
Ellie. Ellie, help me. Help me.
I know you're not real,
but help me wake up.
Chuck, I'm right here.
We all really need you
to flash, though.
No. No, I can't!
No, get away from the door.
Stay with me.
Help me!
Argo? Thomas? What's going on out there?
None of the guards are answering.
Let's get out of here.
I've been looking for you.
- Chuck!
- There really is no use.
- He's almost completely gone.
- Shut up.
Chuck?
Chuck. Oh, my God.
Chuck, come on. Please wake up.
Chuck, listen to me. I'm here.
Chuck, I'm here.
But you're not.
You're not real. This is a dream.
I came to rescue you.
I'm right here, Chuck.
Chuck, please, come on.
Hey, hey, hey.
Tell him what you told me before, okay?
He'll hear that. I know it.
This is your chance.
Don't be Sarah Walker the spy,
be Sarah Walker the girlfriend.
Chuck, please.
Chuck, I love you.
Please wake up.
I have so much that I wanna tell you.
- I found your proposal plan.
- No, no, no.
This is my mind playing tricks on me.
You don't know anything about my plan.
You were gonna do it
on the beach in Malibu...
where we watched the sunrise
after our first date.
- There were several racecars involved.
- I revised that.
I wanna spend the rest of my life
with you.
I don't care
if you have the Intersect or not.
Without you, I'm nobody.
I'm nothing but a spy.
Come back to me, Chuck.
I wanna marry you.
Oh, Chuck.
He's okay. He's okay.
Hmm.
- Yeah. Yeah. He's okay.
- Hi.
Bro, you almost done yet?
Ellie called to see
if I've figured this thing out.
While I'll examine dark places for that
woman, I'm at the end of my rope.
Not to worry,
my supple yet hard-bodied friend.
- You really don't need to call me that.
- Okay, people. Gather, humans.
You, uh, minions ready to see
what your broken bodies have wrought?
- Do it.
- Here goes.
Nice work, amigo. You did it.
Hmm.
Needs a password.
"Knock, knock."
It's an impenetrable riddle.
I could hack it.
Take me about 12 hours.
And, uh, maybe I should try
a colonoscopy.
Okay, everyone out, now.
- Let's go. We're done. Thank you.
- That's a no to the colonoscopy?
Congratulations, team.
The Belgian is in custody and America's
secrets are safe once more.
Oh, yeah. That's what I did today.
Agent Bartowski,
I trust you're feeling better?
Yeah. Uh, yeah, I feel fine.
I'm a little hazy on everything,
but, um, much better. Thank you.
And Agent Walker,
you are back to normal?
- Yes, uh. Yes, I am, general.
- Very good.
Because we have something
important to discuss:
Agent Bartowski's position in the agency
without the Intersect.
Excuse me?
Government still wants me?
The Intersect appears
to be buried for good...
but we'll find a use for you.
You're an asset with or without it.
Yes, he is.
Ahem. One last thing.
You're absolutely certain...
that even though the Belgian and
Chuck were both found in Thailand...
you had nothing to do with the Thai
official who woke up this morning...
with no recollection of where he went
for two days?
Hmm?
No, ma'am.
Crazy coincidence.
Welcome back.
- I agree. Welcome back.
- Thank you for coming with me.
Beckman knew, right?
I think she knew. I mean...
Hey, wait up, Casey.
- Okay, so I'm still a spy.
- More importantly, you're home.
Hey, um, you should know...
that the proposal plan that you found?
Just a rough draft.
- So you do remember what happened?
- Yeah, maybe a little.
A scoch.
Don't think you know all the surprises
that I got hidden up my sleeves.
Because my sleeves are
chock-full o' surprises, you know?
Mm-hm.
I'm surprised I could get in here with
all the surprises that are in my sleeves.
I got magic coming your way, baby.
Okay? Magic.
- Magic. Magic.
- Mm-hm.
- I've got no magic. You ruined my life.
- I saved your life. I took a Thai leech.
But now I can't use my
proposal plan, buddy. Come on.
I need something new.
I need to surprise her.
- How can I surprise a super spy?
- It's fine.
Team Chuck and Morgan have
To blow Sarah's mind.
By the way, you should've seen Sarah
without you, man.
Maybe it's good you lost the Intersect
because now you know...
that girl loves you.
I mean, she will do anything for you.
- Thanks, buddy.
- Yeah.
No, seriously. Anything, okay?
I had to pick a Thai tooth
out of her arm.
Ow.
I've got people who take teeth
and leeches for me.
- I'm a lucky guy.
- It's good having you back.
Ugh. I'm so happy to be home.
And I am so happy to tell you that you
have nothing left on your plate today.
- Hi.
- Hi. Mm.
Your husband has fixed this computer.
Really?
Oh, you're amazing.
All we need now is a password.
The prompt is "knock, knock."
Know what it could be?
It's not, "Who's there?"
Already tried that one. Ha, ha.
I know what it is.
When I was a little girl, I would always
mess up the "knock, knock" routine.
My dad would say, "Knock, knock,"
and I would say, "I'm here."
It made him laugh so hard,
I never wanted to do it right.
Oh, my God.