Hi, I'm Chuck. Here are a
few things you need to know.
I'm going undercover into Volkoff
Industries. I'm gonna take them down.
Hydra is the heart
of Volkoff Industries. But it has a flaw.
- So you destroyed the system?
- Of course not.
I just downloaded all the data
to a more secure backup location.
All I want you to do
is to kill John Casey.
Throw me out the window.
There's a platform down there.
- Give this to Chuck.
- Huh?
Dr. Resh to Labor and Delivery.
- Hey, what'd he say?
- John's in good hands.
His doctor is a friend. Thinks he'll regain
consciousness in a day or two.
Thank you.
Casey's family.
Chuck and I do anything for family.
- Thanks for coming by, EI.
- Of course.
Thanks.
Hey, he is the strongest man
I've ever met, okay?
He'll pull through.
- You guys hear that?
- I think I did.
I don't know. Did I?
- A grunt. That is a Casey grunt.
- I think he's trying to say something.
- What do you got? Go ahead.
- Pants.
Pants. Pants. He said "pants."
That means...
Why pants?
The man's never gonna wear
pants again.
He means his pants.
Maybe there's something in them.
- That's... Yeah.
- Yeah. Good observation. Way to...
Got it. Here it is.
It's, uh, like, a half an eye.
That's half an eyeball.
What is he doing with that?
Casey, where did you get this?
Where did you get this eye?
Sarah.
What'd he say?
He said Sarah.
Volkoff's security is down.
We have exactly two minutes.
Let's hope this tells us where
he downloaded the Hydra network to.
You should answer it.
Hello, Alexei.
Frost, it's me.
Yes, I know, I can see you.
It's really dark there. Where are you?
Awful.
Andre wasn't working out in Budapest...
so I had to let him go
off a 30-story building.
Twenty seconds.
Oh, that's just awful.
- Well, I really should be going.
- All right.
Sweet dreams, my sweet little pea. Mwah.
Good night, darling.
Did you find its location?
Looks like Volkoff is entrusting the Hydra
to another person.
The Contessa.
We received a message from Agent Walker.
Seems she'll be in the field
a while longer.
She's learned that Volkoff is planning to
transfer the Hydra network to the Contessa.
What about the piece of Hydra
I flashed on?
Eimacher designed Yuri's eye. There's a
good chance he designed for the Contessa.
General, there's got to be
another way, okay?
Sarah pushed Casey out a window.
This ends now. She needs to come home.
As I said before, my superiors
will follow up on Eimacher...
and the rest of the information
in the Hydra fragment.
I'm sorry, but you're too close to this,
Agent Bartowski.
- Okay, fine. What am I supposed to do?
- You wait.
That's all you can do.
Okay. Hey. It'll be all right, buddy.
We'll go outside, get some fresh air.
We'll play bocce.
No.
No, Morgan, I can't do this anymore.
I watched my mom leave us
and my dad follow her.
I let Sarah go and now Casey,
and the whole time, I did nothing.
Nothing, while one man took everything
away from me.
Ellie's right.
Bartowskis take care of their family...
and right now, it's time I put mine
back together again.
This was my father's mission. I have to
finish it. We're gonna take down Volkoff.
We? Really? You were kind of talking
in the first person.
And I'm not usually invited on these
climactic missions. So I'm in, though.
- I mean, which guns do we grab?
- No guns.
- We need...
- Office supplies?
No, Morgan. We need a plan.
- This is gonna work.
- Yeah, it is.
- Course it is. It's a good plan.
- Thanks.
I've been doing a lot of yoga, so I feel
I'm peaking mentally and physically...
so no problems there.
You think this is what they call
a, uh, suicide mission?
What? No, of course not.
Look, the first step is, we find the guy
who designed Hydra, Roni Eimacher.
And, Morgan, this is going to work.
I promise.
Heh. Of course.
Oh, man. We're gonna need some help.
Get someone up here immediately.
We've got a problem with the...
What the hell is going on?
Who's doing this?
My God.
He's still alive.
Chuck 4x13 - Versus the Push Mix
Armand.
We have a problem.
In the form of Stephen Bartowski.
Orion was killed by The Ring.
Well, then somehow a dead man broke
into my computer system last night.
He wants something very dear to me.
I'm gonna take Frost to a safer place.
I want you to figure out where
Orion has been hiding all these years.
- Where can I find you?
- I'll be visiting an old friend.
The Contessa.
- Hey. Hey.
- Hey.
Thanks for meeting me here.
I appreciate that. Hold on one second.
Out and boom.
Push mix for Ellie.
What the doctor ordered.
Oh, thanks, bro. I know you're busy,
it's just, Ellie hates my music.
But Rusted Root's rad, right?
Yeah, yeah, they're radical.
Awesome. Good.
- Happy to help.
- The plan is in place.
No deep terror can eat away at me
from the inside now.
Deep terror?
- I say "deep terror"?
- You said "deep terror."
Huh.
I gotta run. I gotta find someone to
make Ellie's placenta into vitamin pills.
Aah! I have to unhear that.
How do I unhear that?
I don't know how to unhear... Um...
One more thing, really quick.
I'm gonna be gone for a little while,
so I took the liberty...
of setting up some protection
for you and Ellie through the CIA.
- Protection?
- Just in case.
But promise me, if anything comes up,
you call that number...
an undercover team will show up
and they will take you anywhere.
- Well, thanks for everything, Chuck.
- Yeah.
Pardon me, Jeff.
I bet you Bartowski put a bunch
of indie crap on this push mix.
It's like, "We get it, you're cool."
He has no respect for the unborn.
The first sounds that a child hears
should not be from an audio disc.
- What's the matter with these people?
- They should be raw, unfiltered, live.
This baby needs a performance.
Delivery-room style.
This baby needs...
Jeffster.
So I tracked Eimacher through
his online "Settlers of Catan" league.
- Ooh.
- Yeah.
Turns out, he is a engineering
professor at UC Irvine.
Great. This'll be easy.
I've done a thousand missions like this.
Quick snatch and grab.
Where are you gonna take this guy?
We can't take him to Castle.
Beckman told us to back off.
I actually don't think we need Castle.
Oh, my God, where am I?
- Is this a bathroom?
- No, this is hell.
Listen, you're gonna
tell us who the Contessa is.
The Contessa?
I have no idea who you're talking about.
Do not play games with us,
Roni Eimacher.
Roni Eimacher?
My name's Barry Greenfield.
Barry Green... Oops.
If you'll excuse us
for just a moment, Mr. Greenfield.
That is not Roni Eimacher.
I know it's not Roni Eimacher...
but you gotta admit,
it looks a lot like him.
Okay, all right. Fine, fine.
What are we gonna do?
I'm gonna tranq him
and just put him back.
Perfect. Wait a minute.
He's seen half of our faces, Chuck.
- Doesn't that mean we have to, uh, khh?
- Are you crazy?
We just have to find the real Eimacher.
And this time, bring the picture.
Please don't hurt me,
I'm just an engineer. Wait.
- Am I in a bathroom?
- What? No. Jeez.
No, it's hell.
I mean, it's clearly hell, is it not?
We went through all this... It's hell.
You designed the glass eye...
that Alexei Volkoff
stored his Hydra network on.
You are in trouble. Volkoff kidnapped me,
forced me to create the Hydra device.
He said he'd kill everyone I know
if I didn't do it.
- What'd he say?
- So you've never met the Contessa?
The Contessa? No, that's where
he took me to design the Hydra.
What does that mean?
The Contessa's not a person, it's a...
Welcome to the Contessa.
What do you think?
- Beautiful.
- Yeah, I love her.
I bought the old girl years ago,
on Craigslist Dubai.
She's got anti-aircraft missiles,
sonar stealth technology...
and an old-fashioned
ice cream parlor.
I like to think of her
as my floating fortress of fun.
Captain, good to see you.
The Hydra network must be on this ship
somewhere. This is our chance.
But Volkoff brought us here
because he's nervous about something.
He wants to stay mobile.
We have to go for the Hydra tonight.
And nothing can get in our way.
Let's do this.
I told you to take the flippers off.
We're in.
Okay.
We gotta get to the lower decks.
That's where Eimacher said
the server was.
Hey, what's going on, buddy?
We gotta go.
You never told me you were gonna wear
something underneath that wetsuit.
Morgan, you're not wearing any clothes
under there?
Underwear. I'm wearing underwear.
I mean, how do you even fit anything
else there? Where does it go?
It doesn't matter. I'm cool like this.
I look like a seal. A seal that does yoga.
- Yeah.
- Yoga seal.
- Yoga seal. All right, just don't squeak.
- Okay.
We're as close as we're ever gonna get.
Tonight, whether or not
we find the Hydra, you're going home.
What do you mean?
I promised Chuck
I wouldn't come home without you.
Yes, I made a lot of promises too.
I don't want you to become me.
And I will not allow my son
to become his father.
So tonight, it ends.
Armand?
Whatever system Orion used
to contact you is untraceable.
I need to figure out
if he's working with someone inside.
I told you to find Orion.
I'm well aware of his connections
inside my organization.
Then let me prove
Frost's loyalty is only to you.
Give me access to Hydra.
Hold on.
Do it.
It's not on this deck.
- What the...? Hey.
- Chuck?
Sarah.
- What are you two doing here?
- Taking down Volkoff.
How did you even find us?
You shouldn't be here.
She's right. This is my mission.
It's dangerous.
This is our mission, okay?
I never should have let you go.
Either one of you. You don't have
to do this alone. We're here to help.
Seriously, guys, it's gonna be okay.
Chuck has a plan.
The server room is right down there.
Mom. Mom? Mom.
When we get back, we need to have
a talk about the benefits of tranq guns.
There's the door to the server room.
I'll try and hack in.
Hang on a second,
this dude's got a key card, right?
Maybe this will help us with a way in.
Um, Morgan, we don't know
what's gonna happen if you do that.
See? Easy.
- Wait, this can't be right.
- What?
- Oh.
- Ahh.
Guys, I think I'm gonna die in here.
- Morgan, what's happening?
- Lasers.
Lots and lots of lasers
and they cut things.
Hang on, buddy.
Hang on, buddy, I'm in the system.
Awesome, Chuck. Nice work. You got
the door to the server room open.
Now just turn off the lasers.
I don't think I can do it from here.
Morgan, if you can get
into the server room...
you can power them down
and open the door for us.
- He can't go through those lasers.
- I can't go through these lasers.
This could be the only chance you have.
We have to hurry.
Yes, you can. Yes, you can, Morgan.
I can do this.
I'm a yogi, all right? I am peaking
mentally and physically.
So I just need to use my ujjayi breath,
okay?
Now, come on.
Warrior 2 pose.
Transition, slowly, into Warrior 3 pose.
Huh. I didn't know I could do that.
Guys, I'm stuck.
Okay, okay, okay, buddy.
I'm gonna try something else.
Easy. Easy.
Your strength is in your core.
Oh, God.
Oh, not good. Lasers are moving now.
No, no, no. Worse now. Worse now.
Oh, God, it's slicing through my wetsuit.
Morgan? Are you okay?
Morgan? Morgan, don't you ever
do that again.
It's all right. It's all good.
Yeah.
- Kind of cold, yeah?
- Yeah.
Uh, Morgan, here.
I'm glad you're okay.
Thank you. Thanks.
And thank you for this.
Although I don't think it's gonna fit
over these shoulders, heh.
My lats have been really...
It's, you know,
it's just kind of barely... Ahem.
Careful, Chuck. Don't touch that.
Okay.
I'm in.
All of Volkoff's contacts are here.
I am transferring Hydra
to a CIA offshore server...
now.
Hey, babe, watch me glide.
Devon, my water just broke.
But you're not due yet.
- What is Clara thinking?
- It happened about 10 minutes ago.
I took a shower and had a protein bar.
I'm ready to go. Let's go have a baby.
Okay. I'm prepared for this.
Yes, you are. You have a plan.
You have an awesome plan.
Okay. Everything's gonna be just fine.
Where's my push mix? I got it from
Chuck. It couldn't have disappeared.
Devon, it's fine, really.
I don't need a push mix.
Let's just go.
I'm gonna grab some water for the road.
I'm not ready for this.
Perfect plan not perfect.
Oh, God, it's gone.
No push mix, no baby.
It's all gone.
Are you expecting someone?
Mrs. Woodcomb,
your transport service has arrived.
- Let's move quickly.
- Devon, did you arrange this?
Voice identification required.
Damn it, only Volkoff can access this.
It's connected to his voice.
You and Morgan need to get out of here
right now.
You all need to get out.
Volkoff will be here any second.
- No. Not without you.
- Hey, hey. We're all going. Let's go.
Frost, I am very disappointed in you.
Death is the solution to all problems.
It's a quote from my favorite poet
and humanitarian...
Joseph Stalin.
Good job I didn't tell you
all my secrets, isn't it?
Just know...
you did this.
- Shoot them.
- All right, you can shoot them...
but not before I get one shot off
and one is all I need.
Get out of here, Chuck.
Morgan, go. Go now. Come on, Sarah.
Come on, come on. Come on.
Mom, come on.
For them to get out alive,
you have to stay.
Yes, I know.
- Run.
- Mom.
- Chuck, come on.
- Mom?
- Come on.
- Mom.
- Are you okay?
- Yeah.
- We better get out.
- This wasn't part of my plan.
Come on, we have to go.
You have nothing to say to me?
No perfect excuses?
No "Trust me, Alexei"?
- No.
- Nothing?
Give me the gun.
No one touches my Frost.
Armand.
Come, please. You have to see this.
There's something
I've got to show you.
Come, please. You have to see this.
"Meet me at Twin Pines Cabin.
Godspeed, my love.
Orion."
- What is this?
- You tell me.
Armand found it on our server
a few moments ago.
- I've never seen this before.
- Really?
Because this message led Armand
to hundreds more.
You've been talking to Orion every day
for years.
Night after night, behind my back.
That's why you didn't want me near you.
I have no idea
what you are talking about.
Stop lying to me.
You knew your husband was alive.
You knew the whole damn time.
I believed in you.
You want the truth, Alexei?
The truth is, my husband, alive or dead...
will always be 10 times
the man you are.
And every moment that I was with you,
I was thinking of him.
I'm going to visit your husband.
And when I come back...
I'll bring you his body.
Moron, Grimes.
You're here.
Of course I am.
I, uh... I brought you a bonsai.
Thought it might feel more like home.
Would have brought guns...
but don't think they would have let me
through the door with those, so...
Save your strength, Dad.
The doctors said you need a rest.
Listen, I, uh...
I kind of like having my dad around.
I don't just like it,
I've gotten used to it, so...
I spent most of my life thinking
that my dad was dead...
and I'm not ready to do it again,
okay?
My contractions are 10 minutes apart.
Let's go ahead
and administer the Pitocin.
Can I get 10 cc's of Compazine?
I'm a little nauseous.
Of course, Dr. Woodcomb.
Is your husband all right?
Yeah, he'll snap out of it.
He was like this once before
during his exit exams.
He'll be fine, I'm sure.
This is the location Orion listed
on his communiqué.
Then let's finally put this ghost
in the ground.
I'll do this myself.
Stay here and keep guard.
Orion.
We finally meet.
- Charles.
- Hello, Alexei.
I believe you were looking for me.
Morning, sunshine.
Oh, you seem very proud...
using your father's toys
to lure me in.
Oh.
I'm not dead yet,
so you must want something.
Oh, you're right, actually.
There is still something I want.
I hadn't figured you as the vengeful type.
Is it because I spoke disparagingly
about your father?
This is because you took my mother
from him.
You took his whole life and his death...
His death was ages ago.
Isn't it time you moved on?
Heh, bearing grudges.
A bit childish, isn't it?
You can't kill me for the same reason
your mother and your girlfriend couldn't.
What do you think is gonna happen
to all those people you love...
if you put a bullet between my eyes?
I have access to everyone.
I have to admit, it was a good plan.
Using my own jealousy against me.
But it had its problems.
How could it not?
After all, you are your father's son.
Just know this...
if it wasn't for you...
everyone could have gotten
out of this alive.
And now for the sister.
I told my men to kill your mother
if they didn't hear from me.
And they won't...
so cheers, Charles.
Here's to a family reunion.
I can't believe you haven't figured out
the solution yet.
Solution?
To what?
Gotcha.
Death is the solution to all problems.
Got it, Chuck. We got the pass code.
What is this?
Death is the solution to all problems.
That fake communiqué
you received from Orion...
that wasn't just a play
on your weird affection for my mom.
That was also a virus
that my father created.
And now that I have your passcode,
that virus will begin to transfer...
the entire Hydra network
onto this computer.
Technically, I guess you could say...
that in the end...
it was Stephen J. Bartowski
who took you down.
Fitting, don't you think?
You know, my father,
he taught me a lot of things.
Like looks can be deceiving...
and fight for your family.
Something's wrong.
- Aah! Unh.
- Mary, quick.
And, of course...
never use a gun...
unless you absolutely have to.
Yeah, I probably should have told you,
I have this thing about bullets.
I was never gonna kill you, Alexei.
After all, I am my father's son, aren't I?
You've made one mistake, Charles.
All the information you've got
is right here in your father's little cabin.
And outside that door,
I have dozens of heavily armed men.
If I don't walk out of here,
they're gonna come in for me.
You're gonna need an army
to get out of here alive.
Will they suffice?
Arrest him.
I just received word
from Frost and Walker.
They're en route to Burbank.
- It was a good plan, Agent Bartowski.
- Thank you, general.
Tell your mom to come visit.
It's been fun.
Chuck? Chuck. Hey, excuse me, guys.
You first.
As you were.
- We have to get out of here.
- What's up? Everything okay?
Just got a call from the hospital.
Ellie's having her baby now.
- What? Oh. Oh.
- Yeah, yeah. Yeah.
Uh, general, can we borrow a van?
You just arrested Alexei Volkoff
and obtained the Hydra network...
we have spent the last 20 years
searching for.
Lieutenant, get this man a chopper.
Thanks.
You're dilated to 10
and fully effaced, Dr. Woodcomb.
Contractions are two minutes apart.
The baby's coming.
Can you get the doctor?
Babe?
Honey, look at me.
I need you to go outside
and take five minutes for yourself.
Pull yourself together
and then come back to me.
You're all I have right now, Devon.
I need you.
Ew, pregnant women.
Ooh, pregnant women.
Excuse me, candy striper.
Hi. Listen, could you point us in
the direction of the Woodcomb womb?
- What?
- Without us...
that kid is gonna grow up listening
to Snow Patrol and Coldplay.
We just can't have that, can we?
I'm sorry, but no one goes in there
unless they're a family member.
So I suggest that you take a seat.
Dr. Adler, Room 315, please.
Hey, Awesome. I heard Ellie's in labor.
Where is she?
Why aren't you in there?
Oh. Don't make the same mistake I did.
I missed my daughter's birth.
Missed her whole damn childhood.
Alex's mom had to raise her
all on her own.
There's not a day that goes by
I don't regret that.
Now, you get in there.
Move it.
- It's time to push.
- Okay.
Ahh, push it
Oh, God.
Ooh, baby, baby
Baby, baby
Jeffster.
Ahh, push it
- Oh, no.
- Aah! Get up on this
Oh, baby
Salt-N-Pepa's here
Salt, Salt, Salt
John.
Walker.
- I'm sorry, I didn't...
- Glad you're back.
Want you to push it, babe
Cool it by day then at night
Working up a sweat
Come on, girls, let's go show the guys
That we know
How to become number one
In a hot party show
Now push it
Ahh, push it
Push it good
- Let's go, guys.
- Aw.
It's over.
No. No, we did what
we came here to do, Jeffrey.
Cover song by cover song,
we are shaping the youth of America. Unh.
I'm not allowed to do that anymore.
- Are you family?
- Yes.
Okay. Well, only one of you
can come in.
Um, Mom. Mom, go ahead, please.
Just make sure
she knows we're all out here, okay?
I will.
You came.
We all did.
Don't push yourself.
- I can do it, you know.
- No, I got it.
- Where'd Alex go?
- She went home.
No, I didn't. I just went to get a coffee.
Whether you like it or not, Dad,
I am not going anywhere.
Neither am I.
Good luck trying
to get rid of me, guys. Ha, ha.
I like you guys.
Your line is, "I like you too, Morgan."
Ellie, she's so beautiful.
Congratulations.
Thank you.
Devon?
Awesome. Ha, ha.