Hi, I'm Chuck. Here are a few things
you might need to know.
My dad must have left this for me.
Oh, my God.
I didn't think you could top
abandoning me for 20 years.
Then you shot me.
Sarah, my mom did something to me
with that device.
My name is Alexei Volkoff.
I believe you were looking for me.
Sarah, I can't flash. The Intersect is gone.
You wanted to see me, Alexei?
I've just had some disturbing news.
Agent Carmichael is still alive.
I'm as surprised as you are.
I was there.
We tied them up.
Planted explosives all around them.
And yet he survived.
It was my fault.
I underestimated him.
Let's tidy things up.
These are my top assassins
in North America.
Pierre, Victor, Hercule.
Use them.
And, Frost?
Make certain he's really dead
this time.
Are you ready for this? You
and me, training for hand-to-hand combat.
Absolutely. Remember,
I had six months of training in Prague.
Now this is Chuck unplugged.
Sounds hardcore
when you say it like that.
It's gonna be good.
I'm mostly just scared about today.
Black Friday?
The scariest shopping day of the year.
- Many a manager has fallen on this day.
- You're gonna be just fine.
- We'll learn moves, you'll get through it.
- I'm pumped.
Let's go in there
and kick some serious ass.
Get up on the floor
And show 'em all why
They gonna need sticky paper...
All right, ladies...
let's grab a pole
and make that booty clap.
What sort of hand-to-hand combat class
did you sign us up for?
Strip Kick.
Mixes the self-defense of Krav Maga
with the core workout of pole dancing.
How's it going with you and Sarah?
Any progress on el proposalito?
Well, I am working on something new.
Duck!
Whoo! But I'm keeping it
close to the vest.
What? Are you serious?
Chuck, I'm a part-time spy, man, okay?
I am a very, very serious keeper
of secrets.
Jump!
- Casey can never know about this.
- Never.
So how's the combat training going?
Ha, ha. Cinnamon's a tough instructor,
but I'm picking things up quickly.
Well, I am just happy to have you back.
Me too. And you know what?
It's the best I've felt in a long time.
Good. I thought you might be upset...
after Ellie and Awesome
canceled dinner.
What? No, no, no. Of course not.
They're doctors, it happens.
Besides, tonight is our annual
leftover dinner.
Just as delicious as Thanksgiving
without all the big-event stress.
Let it snow.
Remember, Frost wants them killed
at close range.
No sound.
I guess I was just a little worried
because the holidays are for family time.
With everything that happened
with your mother...
Well, I've developed a little perspective.
I'm ready to put the past behind me.
Really?
Ha, ha.
Don't sound so skeptical, all right?
If my mom were standing in front of me,
I honestly think I'd say:
"All is forgiven
and good luck being an evil bad guy."
And, uh, speaking
of looking forward to the future...
Chuck, get down.
Wow, that stuff really works.
Sarah, I can't handle these guys without
the Intersect. I only got that one move!
Sarah?
Mom?
Come with me if you wanna live.
Chuck 4x10 - Versus the Leftovers
Okay, we're here, we're safe.
Start answering some of my questions.
We can't stay here. Volkoff has contacts
in the CIA. We have to move.
We should believe you.
Last time, trusting you worked out well.
Chuck, I didn't want to have to do
the things I did.
Most moms don't have to explain
to their kids why they shot them.
Or tied them up and blew up their home.
- I didn't have a choice.
- There's always a choice.
You could choose to let me...
Chuck, maybe we can step outside
for a second?
- We're running out of...
- Ah. You're not going anywhere.
What happened to
putting the past behind you?
You wanna be able to trust your mom,
not worry she'll shoot you in the face.
Which is why you should stay out of this.
There is something she's not telling us
and we're not gonna get to it with you.
I'm perfectly capable of doing this...
This is what a successful
Black Friday looks like.
You did it, son. I couldn't be prouder.
It was hairy for a minute, but...
- Like, we ran out of 7G smartphones.
- But you remembered what I taught you.
No phone? Sell them a head spa.
No head spa? Sell them a used phone.
- Heh, heh. Exactly.
- Now...
I brought this for you.
- Really?
Just think of this as my fatherly love...
in the form of fresh meatballs
smothered in marinara...
with gooey delicious provolone
melting all over it.
Wow, that is just a terrible metaphor...
heh, heh, but I forgive you
because it smells delicious.
- You deserve it.
- Okay. All right.
I should go. I'm getting a little misty.
- Yeah.
- All right.
Okay.
Excuse me? Can you help me?
Oh, jeez. I'm sorry, miss. We're closed.
Well, I just wanna buy
one of those 7G smartphones.
- Completely sold out of those.
- Please.
I'll do anything.
Uh, not that I'm not flattered,
but who has two thumbs and is taken?
Boop. This guy. Okay. Happy holidays.
Okay.
This is our finest plan yet, Jeffrey.
Smartphones that can also send
and receive calls?
I mean, people will do anything
for these bad boys.
- Who have you been talking to?
- Stop being paranoid.
Remember, this is not stealing.
This is pre-buying with funds
we don't have...
which we will post-pay
when we sell these phones on eBay.
And then, my friend?
Use the profits to make our demo.
Jeffster!
Yes, yes, yes!
Stop. Listen.
I'm gonna go see if the coast is clear,
then we'll move these out of here.
Totally.
Knock, knock. Brought some carrots.
Rich in vitamin A,
good for retinal development.
- Thank you. I'm starving.
- I bet.
You've been working on this nonstop.
- You figure anything out?
- Well, more or less.
My dad left a sort of memory problem.
He was using the brain to store data.
He was approaching it from
an engineer's perspective.
Human memory works differently.
So a few adjustments
and 36 hours of MRls later...
voilá.
Wait, are you telling me you just solved
the problem your dad left you?
No. I solved it 20 minutes ago...
and then, suddenly,
his computer just locked off. Look.
"One or 11?"
What does that mean?
I tried putting in each of the numbers.
Another mystery, courtesy of my dad.
Why would he leave this for me?
Brain scans?
I mean, this is obviously spy-related.
We should talk to Chuck.
No. I don't wanna give him any reason
to get back into that life.
What do you wanna do?
I don't know.
We know these men
were high-level Volkoff assassins.
So, what's your game here?
I was ordered to use those three
to kill Chuck.
I had to shoot them to save Chuck's life.
Protecting him has always been
my number-one priority.
- Hello?
- Ask her how disabling the Intersect...
is about protecting me.
- Are we gonna do this now?
I'm just saying. Tell her to explain that.
Fine.
So how was shutting off the Intersect
meant to protect Chuck?
It was meant to stop him
from following me.
- Yes?
- I went out on missions unprotected.
She's made me more vulnerable.
- I don't think this is helping.
- Is that him?
- Let me talk to him.
- Here.
This is why we didn't want you
in this interrogation.
- Let the grown-ups do their work.
- Fine. Hanging up now.
- Good. I'm glad.
- I'm gladder.
- Huh. Where were we?
- Tell us what it is that you're really after.
Volkoff will know that they are dead,
which means he will come here for me.
We are not safe here.
Sarah? Sarah, pick up the phone.
I was able to get what you wanted.
Fantastic.
Now, you said
you were willing to do anything for it.
First...
I need you to shave my back.
I can't reach the middle.
Thomas Jefferson Barnes.
Hey, Jeffrey...
what are you doing?
- Getting what I deserve.
Getting what you...? Real...?
Excuse me. Listen to me.
We can't afford to let strangers
shave your back, Jeffrey.
Not now, when we're this close
to making our dreams come true.
You're so pretty.
I...
And we're secure.
Come on, guys.
Come on. Right over there.
- Bring it in.
- Let's move.
Yeah.
Good work.
Now let's get what we came for.
Line them up together.
This way.
There's something she's not telling us.
You're not doing yourself any favors
by calling.
I'm sorry. If you wanna go back in,
I promise I'll stay off the phone.
One sec. I just gotta...
It's... I'm not calling you. Just... Morgan.
I can't really talk.
We're in the middle of a crisis here.
I don't know what crisis you're in.
But mine's carrying AK-47 s.
They just took over the store.
Hey. Did you...? Chuck? Chuck?
- Alexei Volkoff.
- Did you just say Volkoff?
- Volkoff is here?
- Morgan, I need you to hide.
Do not come out until I... Morgan?
Volkoff cut off our cell phones.
That's always Volkoff's first move,
kill all communications.
Hmm.
What are we gonna do?
Morgan is still up there.
Lucky for us,
this is a state-of-the-art CIA facility.
Fully prepared for an internal attack.
We've less than a minute. Impress me.
Okay, let's do some damage.
Attention, members of the CIA.
You've killed three of my men
and captured my best agent.
I'm here to get her back.
Keep talking, commie. It's party time.
Mr. Volkoff, exit the Buy More now.
K.K., go.
Weapons system online.
Better dead than red.
Weapons disabled.
Casey, what's happening?
Must have hacked in. My guns are down.
Understand, this is not a negotiation.
Give me Frost...
or I'll kill you all...
starting with the fat man
and the Indian.
God.
Progress?
Scans revealed an elevator shaft
behind the home-theater room.
K.K. Can't seem to override the system
and it's 3 feet of carbide steel.
Start cutting.
Okay, good news, bad news.
Jeff and Lester are about to die,
bad news.
Good news, I've manually locked down
all entrances to Castle.
Bad news,
we're sitting ducks down here.
They're cutting in
through the elevator shaft.
Now, we have one option.
The defenses have a manual override.
They're buried deep
in the access tunnels.
We can override the lockdown,
bring our defenses back up.
Now, you two stay down here
with Mama B.
When Volkoff calls to negotiate,
buy me some time.
Why would Volkoff pull off an assault
on a CIA facility for one agent?
- He's gotta be after something bigger.
- Well, whatever it is...
there's something
my mom's not telling us.
I'm not lying. He wants me.
He'll take on the entire CIA, risk his
whole organization, for one agent?
He...
I need to know that Frost is still alive.
Put her on the phone.
Chuck,
you have to turn me over to him.
Please trust me.
I don't.
This is Charles Carmichael.
I'm the only one
you'll be speaking with.
Charles.
So good to hear your voice again.
Now, I know how scared you must be...
cut off from help
with a madman closing in on you.
So let me offer you
a simple suggestion.
Hand Frost the damn phone!
He wants to talk to you.
Alexei, I'm here.
Frost.
Thank God.
- Are they treating you all right?
- I'm fine.
- Did they feed you?
- Yes.
Was it good?
It was delicious.
Tell them they better continue
treating you well...
or I'll make life very uncomfortable
for them very soon.
Tell them...
that I'm not leaving here without you,
my love.
Wha...?
- "My love"?
- What does that mean?
It means that Alexei Volkoff
is in love with me.
He's in love with you?
He called you "my love"?
Who is Volkoff to you? Your boyfriend?
Is he the reason you left Dad?
No.
Alexei and I have never been together.
It's just he...
- He's in love with me, that's all.
- That's all? Got it. Got it. Great.
No, you don't get it.
Sarah, explain to him.
If you were working undercover
with the biggest psychopath...
and that psychopath
falls in love with you...
That would make me
a major intelligence asset.
I see. So that's why you've been gone
from my life since I was 9?
Chuck, I'm a spy.
It was my mission.
You've been close to Volkoff.
Why didn't you take him out?
My mission was to take down
the network, not the man.
Which is something
I still might be able to do.
But if you want to save yourself
and your friends, turn me over to him.
You have no choice.
Chuck, wait.
- Hey, are you okay?
- How can I trust anything she says?
Every time I do, I wind up getting shot
or almost blown up.
I haven't been stabbed yet.
Going undercover for so long
and staying loyal is a hard thing to do.
I got lucky. I was assigned to you.
Your mom got Volkoff.
You think Volkoff really
is in love with her?
If he is, I bet he would rather negotiate
with us than risk her getting hurt.
I might be mad at my mom, really mad,
but I'm never gonna hurt her.
You and I know that, but Volkoff doesn't.
It might help us to buy more time
for Casey.
- Casey.
- Morgan, what are you doing in here?
- And where are your shoes?
- What...? Funny story. I was sitting...
Never mind about the shoes.
Where are Chuck and Sarah
and what is going on?
Volkoff's taken control of the Buy More.
He's captured Tweedledumb
and Tweedledumber.
He's gonna kill them
if we don't give him Chuck's mom.
- Jeff and Lester? We gotta save them.
- Mm-hm.
If we don't get those guns working,
we're gonna be killed.
No, no, no.
You're absolutely right. Okay.
I'll go. Get the guns running,
I'll save Jeff and Lester.
Morgan, that's a stupid idea.
Maybe, but I'm not just gonna sit here
on all fours and watch those two die.
Now, wish me luck.
Wait.
You might need that.
- Good thinking.
- Muzzle.
Right. I got it, I got it.
Yes, Charles?
You want Frost...
and we have her.
If you do what we ask,
she doesn't get hurt.
But if you don't do what we ask...
then bad things
are going to happen to her.
Very bad things.
Like...
Just very bad things.
We'll leave it at that.
Is that a threat?
Let me show you something.
This is a thermite-TH3
incendiary explosive.
When it's detonated, the temperatures
will exceed 4000 degrees Fahrenheit.
Metal will boil.
I'm gonna drop it
down the elevator shaft...
and it will incinerate
every single one of you...
including my beloved Frost.
I'd rather she die
than have to live without me.
Give her back to me...
and I'll let you live.
That's how you threaten someone,
Charles.
So much for buying Casey more time.
Okay, come on.
Ow!
Hey. You came for me. Thank you.
- No time to talk, Grimes.
- Wait. No. No.
They were supposed to sell these.
What is wrong with those guys?
Let's go. Move.
Tell your men to back off.
Don't be afraid.
I told you I'd let you live and I meant it.
But you should know...
I have your friend Casey.
Put down your weapons.
Frost.
Thank you for coming for me.
I had no choice.
Now, there is just one small matter
to deal with.
Chuck.
- What happened to letting us go?
- I lied.
But in my defense,
you threatened the woman I love.
Frost...
I hope you think
this is a romantic gesture.
- Alexei, you can't.
- Why not? You like romance.
Because...
Charles is my son.
Really?
Really.
- Really?
- Really.
So this is why he isn't dead.
I'm sorry, Alexei.
My one weakness is my love for my son.
And he knows this
and uses it against me.
Don't be hard on yourself.
We always expect the best
from the ones we love.
And rarely get it.
Why didn't you tell me?
Alexei, you run a multinational
criminal organization.
There's no room for family.
- Especially family that works for the CIA.
- What did you think I was going to do?
- Sir, there's an incoming call on the Buy...
- Shut up!
From an Ellie Bartowski.
Any relation, this Ellie Bartowski...
Mr. Bartowski?
Yeah.
No.
No. Yeah. Distant, distant relative.
Who... She lives in Alaska, I think.
Come to think of it, she's in Bangladesh.
You don't wanna...
- Not necessary.
- Chuck?
Hey, it's me.
Are you coming for dinner tonight?
I'm kind of, uh...
I'm kind of tied up here at work, sis.
No, you have to come.
I have so much food here.
We didn't get to have a family
Thanksgiving dinner. It'll be fun. Please?
I'll try my best.
Okay, great. I'll see you soon.
So...
a son and a daughter.
You didn't think I could have
a relationship with your family?
Kids love me.
I'll prove you wrong.
Charles...
Chuck.
Call your sister back.
Tell her you're coming to dinner...
and you're bringing some guests.
Okay.
Okay, I know it's tough.
We just have to be calm.
You just brought a psychotic killer
to your pregnant daughter's house.
Considering the circumstances,
I'm pretty calm.
Everything's gonna be fine.
You just have to trust me.
I've heard that before.
Alexei, you do understand...
that my daughter and her husband
are civilians?
Of course.
I don't wanna frighten your family.
I just want to get to know them.
Hi.
Mom.
I was telling you I was gonna bring
some surprise guests.
So, surprise!
Hey.
I'm Devon, your son-in-law.
- Hey.
- Come on in.
Hello, nice to meet you.
I want you to have fun tonight.
But if I get the feeling
that you're plotting against me...
I need this dinner to be perfect,
understand?
Yeah, I think we do.
I think you don't.
If it isn't perfect,
I'll take it out on the people you love.
Well, this has been quite the surprise.
I can't remember the last time
we had you here for Thanksgiving, Mom.
Jingle bell, jingle bell rock
It was 1990.
You were 12...
Chuck was 9.
The turkey was overcooked.
Heh, heh. That's right.
That's right. I remember that.
I, however, thought
the turkey tasted fine.
Jingle bell...
So, Alexei, you work with my mom.
Can I...?
I mean, am I allowed to ask
what happened to her?
Dancin' and prancin'
Well, it's complicated.
Let me explain.
Well, Ellie, in our business, sometimes
good people are confused for bad...
and bad for good.
But fortunately,
being your mother's handler...
I was able to convince the CIA
that she is good.
- In a one-horse sleigh
Right, Sarah?
Right. Absolutely.
And that's why your mother
is free to go now.
Well, that's good news, right?
Yes.
I know how painful it was
for your mother...
when she had to leave you years ago.
I know how painful
it must have been for you too.
And your brother.
Thank you for helping our mom.
You can't imagine what you've done
for this family.
Families come first.
Come on. Think, Morgan, think.
There's no Chuck, no Sarah.
It's up to you to save them.
How? How?
Okay.
- Okay. Uh, movie. Movie.
- Yes.
Gosh. Um...
Three words.
- Sounds like...
Hey, buddy, you having a good time?
Are you kidding?
This Alexei is totally awesome.
First guy I've met who's free-climbed K2,
no oxygen. Hardcore, bro.
Yeah. Yeah, he's something else,
isn't he? Heh.
You know what else he is?
An international arms dealer
and a very, very bad man.
We're in terrible danger. Don't freak out.
Bourne Identity.
No!
- Ugh. So close.
- Dude, this is not funny.
Yeah, well, it's also not a joke,
Devon, okay?
I didn't wanna have to tell you this.
I'm spying again and I need your help.
Batman Forever?
Wrong again, Charles.
You really should make some guesses,
otherwise it looks suspicious.
Uh, Bourne Identity?
- Three words.
- I said that.
Whatever. What are you thinking,
bringing this guy home?
I'm sorry. It's not my fault.
It wasn't my decision.
I can't make a move
without setting off Alexei...
but you're a civilian.
He won't suspect you of anything.
Devon,
I know you're the world's worst liar.
But right now...
I need you to be awesome.
What do you want me to do?
Hey, looks like we're out of sugar.
Hey, Chuck, you got any at your place?
Just getting some sugar.
Oh. Oh.
Oh. Cold.
CIA emergency alert activated.
Wow, that is surprisingly soothing.
- Got the sugar.
- Oh, nice.
I'll take that.
Shouldn't your cell phone be ringing?
Huh? Right.
Huh. It's the hospital.
Hello?
Uh-huh. Yeah, yeah.
Well, if you need us, we'll be right there.
What is it?
A bus accident on the 101.
They need all the hands they can get.
Oh, God.
I'm so sorry
that we have to take off like this.
It was a wonderful evening. You're so...
- Go save some lives.
- Ha, ha. Okay.
Oh.
It was great to see you, Mom.
Talk to you soon.
- Okay.
Bye!
See you soon.
Such a sad end to a wonderful evening.
You had to go and alert the CIA,
didn't you?
Don't move.
You do know that the nearest
tactical response team...
is over 10 minutes away?
Until then...
anything could happen.
Drop it, Sarah.
Mom, seriously?
You're betraying me again?
- No, stop.
- Alexei, we've had our dinner.
You've met the family.
We're leaving.
But what kind of potential father-in-law
would I be if I didn't set an example?
Chuck has to learn, you make a threat,
you follow through on it.
I didn't really have to do that...
but I just really like the sound.
Alexei, stop.
My love?
What are you doing?
This is exactly
why I didn't tell you about my family.
You don't know how to love someone.
You only know how to control them.
But you should know...
that I could never love a man
who would do anything to hurt my son.
So drop it.
Alexei, you know that I am loyal to you.
But I will not return with you...
until you promise me
that my family and their friends...
will remain safe.
And if they don't...
I will end you.
You see?
That is a real threat.
Chuck, I'm sorry for everything.
I hope someday you'll trust me.
Mom.
I already do.
Roger that, Mr. Volkoff.
Bad guys...
I surrender.
Yippee-ki-yay...
Yippee-ki...
- yay.
Yippee-ki-yay.
Yip...
Okay.
I surrender.
You're free to go.
- What?
Volkoff's orders. We're out.
I'm unbelievable.
What should we do with these two?
What's going on?
You two have some sort of orgy in here
last night?
- I don't think...
- Yes.
Tell me you weren't planning on
selling these on eBay.
That depends on
what you mean by "eBay."
Then you wouldn't have any problem
getting them out on the sales floor?
Let's say 10 minutes?
And get them fan stickers
off them boxes.
I wish I would've trusted my mom...
instead of being so angry with her
the whole time...
and now she's gone.
She can't come back,
not until Volkoff is destroyed.
He knows too much.
She's the only thing
keeping us safe right now.
Hey, bro, can I talk to you for a minute?
Sure.
- Uh, hey, what's up?
- What were you thinking?
Not only are you spying again,
but you bring it back to our apartment?
I had to lie to Ellie, and I hate lying.
I'm sorry, okay? I really am.
I was trying to protect my mom.
- Things went sideways...
- Stop, okay? Just stop. I don't wanna know.
I don't want this spy stuff
near Ellie ever again.
Never. Never ever again.
She doesn't want it near you either.
Understand?
So, this conversation never took place.
- This is one of my father's laptops.
- He left it for Ellie.
It was broke and we fixed it.
There's something on it.
Brain scans, some memory problem
that Ellie figured out.
What...? What does it mean?
I don't wanna know.
And neither does Ellie.
But if you're spying again...
maybe it can help you.
Are you sure you wanna do this?
Look, I'm not even sure
what's on this thing, but if I'm right...
then yes.
Well, let's get this over with.
"One or 11?"
What does that mean?
Well, it's the value of an ace
in blackjack...
but there's something
my dad used to say to me.
Hm.
Chuck?
I'm okay.
Guys, I know kung fu.
Again.