Hi, I'm Chuck. Here are a few
things that you might need to know.
An Intersect before Chuck?
Dad used this program to input
a new identity into an operative.
But something went wrong.
The program took over.
Agent X is Alexei Volkoff?
CIA created one of the most
murderous men in history.
If they find out we know?
They order a guy
to put a bullet in each of our heads.
The Norseman device.
It can kill a single person
in the middle of a crowd...
with 100 percent accuracy.
God, what is that noise?
Sarah? Sarah. Sarah.
No, no, no. Help me!
You awake?
Were you thinking about the wedding?
It's exactly one week away.
One single, solitary week.
Chuck, what if it rains?
- That's good luck, right?
- Well, what if it doesn't?
Are we freaking out? We are.
That's normal though.
It's normal to freak out a little bit
a week before a wedding.
Unless...
It's cold feet?
No.
No, no, because I wanna marry you.
No, I really wanna marry you too.
It's just the church...
and exchanging intimate feelings
in front of a crowd...
Wait, what if we did a dry run?
- A dry run?
- Yeah. Yeah, a dry run.
That way we can work out the kinks,
no people, no cameras.
- Practice makes...
- Perfect.
We'll be ready for anything.
The poison is called thorium.
I don't know much about it.
Thorium is a radioactive metal,
not a poison.
- Liquid or solid?
- Liquid.
It's linked to her DNA somehow.
Then the thorium's been synthesized.
Devon?
Poison guns aren't in the textbooks.
I need a bath basin, stat.
Hypothermia will decrease the heart rate
and slow down any tissue damage.
If she's gonna survive, we need
to know exactly how this poison works.
And if it's exotic like you're saying,
we need to find an antidote.
Chuck?
Hey.
Hey, baby, I'm right here.
You look worried.
No. You know, it's just wedding stuff.
Don't freak out, we're ready for it.
Sarah.
Baby, I'm gonna fix this.
We're gonna get married
and be together...
forever.
I love you.
There's only one person
who can get us that antidote...
and it's the man
who made the damn thing:
Volkoff.
Well,
Volkoff is in a supermax penitentiary.
It'd take weeks to get clearance.
Then I guess we're just gonna
have to break in tonight.
- There.
- Mom, we've reached Volkoff's cell.
Copy that, Chuck.
You have precisely two minutes...
before the alarm system
comes back up.
Already open.
That's not right.
Casey, where's Volkoff?
He's gone,
Agent Bartowski. Stay where you are.
- Chuck, what is going on in there?
- I know that voice.
Casey, you're going pale.
I go pale, you don't.
Remember when I told you
opening the Agent X files...
would draw out a son of a bitch
that would destroy our whole team?
This is the guy they hire
to kill that guy.
Agent Bartowski, Colonel Casey.
Listen, I don't know who you are
and I don't care.
I need Volkoff. Now, where is he?
Name's Decker, Clyde Decker.
And I'm informing you
of a wash order...
on the Agent X program
and Operation Bartowski.
What does that mean?
It means your CIA resources
are revoked.
Sarah is dying.
I don't care.
Now stand down or get buried.
- No.
- No?
Let me explain.
That guy might think he's a hard ass,
but I'm the Intersect.
Let's move.
Chuck 4x24 - Versus the Cliffhanger
- Chuck.
- Any news?
Sarah's temperature's down
but it's not stabilizing.
What does that mean, EI?
There's signs
of a total-body dose of radiation.
She's breathing on her own.
She's in and out of consciousness.
How long does she have?
At this rate,
I would say that she has 12 hours.
She's here.
Thanks for helping us, general.
Decker's transporting Volkoff
to a black site.
No one who's gone in
has ever come out.
We need to intercept Volkoff
in transit.
They're an hour ahead of you.
Then we need something with speed.
Can we still get into Castle?
Chuck, you realize if you go against
Decker, you're going against the CIA.
You and Sarah
will have to disappear forever.
You'll never see your family again.
I'll do anything I need to do
to save Sarah.
This should work.
Good luck, team.
- So, what's the bright idea?
- Why are you keeping us in the dark?
I want the Nighthawk.
- Absolutely not.
- It's a prototype. Never been tested.
Eleven hours and counting.
I don't give a damn.
You're not even
supposed to know about it.
Come on, you thought you could keep a
superbike secret from me? She'll do 250.
You two navigate from Castle.
Chuck, have you ever even
ridden a motorcycle?
And I hope to God the answer is no.
Charles, I know time is of the essence
but you are driving awfully fast.
Sorry, Mom.
Don't get all icy on me, Volkoff.
I come in peace.
This transfer's not about killing you. CIA
wants you for some testing, that's all.
Testing?
Regarding Agent X.
Are you playing coy
or you don't remember any of this?
Casey.
Casey, I'm coming up on the transport.
Your real name
is Hartley Winterbottom.
Nobody names a person that.
Volkoff is a fictitious profile
you created with Stephen J. Bartowski.
What on Earth are you talking about?
The tech boys wanted you
sans Volkoff, so...
Casey, Mom, light it up.
Hold tight.
We're under attack. The cargo hold's
been breached. We need backup.
Chuck, you have 60 seconds to get
him out of there. They called in air support.
Oh, gosh.
Hey.
Come on, wake up.
You're coming with me.
I am? Why?
Vivian shot Sarah with the Norseman.
Who shot whom with what?
Bartowski,
you are galactically insubordinate.
I'm almost impressed.
I'm taking Volkoff with me.
Well, one problem, that ain't Volkoff.
His name's Hartley.
Volkoff was an Intersect implant.
It's gone now.
Hello.
Gentle as a lamb.
Give up, Chuck. You're done.
Bartowski.
Are you related
to Stephen Bartowski?
I'm his son,
and you're coming with me right now.
On that?
- It looks very dangerous.
- I said now!
You are kidnapping
a government prisoner, peckerwood.
- Hang tight.
- I am.
I mean, 30 years?
- Is he still in charge?
- If only.
The Volkoff profile that you and
Stephen developed for the Intersect...
was only supposed
to last for a couple of months.
What did I do?
I mean,
what did Volkoff do for 30 years?
What kind of a man was I?
You were very successful
in a highly competitive business.
No, Mary, there's gotta
be more to it than that...
if someone's been struck
by the Norseman.
We don't have time for this, okay?
My fiancée has been poisoned.
I need your help to save her life.
Right, right. The Norseman.
It developed alongside the Intersect.
And it was a weapon of deterrence.
We were gonna collect the DNA
of all the top black marketeers.
You could whack them
if they got out of line, Reagan smart.
Yeah, peace through violence.
Remember, it was the '80s.
- Hartley, is there an antidote?
- Iridium 5.
Okay, how do we get it?
Oh, it's simple.
I can make that for you.
Great. That's great.
That's fantastic. We'll talk on the way
to the hospital. Let's go.
Once we secure the antidote
we'll discuss our plans for Viv.
Viv?
Yeah. A gal named Vivian
fired the Norseman.
Which doesn't matter right now,
what does is the antidote.
Charles, who's Vivian?
It's a Winterbottom family name.
She's your daughter.
My daughter?
And she's your enemy?
It's a long story,
terrible mistakes were made.
And now we have to clean them up.
Will you help me save Sarah?
- Yeah. Of course I will.
- Thank you.
Okay, here we go.
Okay.
That's all you got there?
These are our wedding vows after all.
I think I covered the bases.
Okay, cool. Yeah, good, good.
You go, then I'll go, and then
we'll have a little note session after.
- Okay, I'm just gonna go.
- Yeah, you get... Mm-hm.
"Chuck, you're a gift.
You're a gift
I never dreamed I could want, or need...
and every day I will show you
that you're a gift that I deserve.
You make me the best person
I could ever hope to be...
and I wanna spend, and learn,
and love, the rest of my life with you."
Talky?
Perfect.
So perfect, it's so perfect.
Oh, my God.
Sarah. Oh, Sarah.
Mine are a tear-down.
This is a page one rewrite.
I scripted a wardrobe change,
you know, and a pause for applause.
Chuck, don't freak out.
Whatever they are,
they will be perfect.
Something's wrong.
The Iridium slowed the poison
but her temperature is back up.
What are we talking about?
I think that you bought more time,
but she's still deteriorating.
Okay, okay.
Okay, what's next?
I don't know.
What do you mean you don't...?
Come on, people, think about this.
If there's an Iridium 5,
there's gotta be an Iridium 6, right?
About four years ago, Volkoff
was working on a new compound.
Very secret.
The file was labeled Lead Apron.
Way to protect
against radioactive poisoning.
Volkoff must have known...
No, I must have known
that number 5 was weak...
and developed
the next one, Iridium 6.
Volkoff kept the project close,
at his Moscow base.
EI, what's our time frame?
- A day, maybe less.
- Then we're out of here ASAP.
Got friends in Global Strike Command.
They'll give us a free jump to Russia.
- They love mixing it up with the Reds.
- Bartowski.
You may be the Intersect, boy,
but you can't outrun a bullet.
Chuck!
So of course, Chuck goes
marching back to these bullies...
and he demands
that they give me back my pants.
Says he's gonna call the Intergalactic
Firestorm Federation which didn't exist.
There's no such thing. Chuck just,
you know, made it up on the spot.
But he got me my pants back.
Yeah, I loved those pants.
Anyway, long story...
just to say
that Chuck never gives up.
You know that, right?
What are you doing? Sarah's dying.
I'm aware of that.
You're aware of that?
I could save her.
She's CIA just like you.
Let me get the antidote.
- That's all I'm asking for.
- You're fired, Chuck, as of right now.
Operation Bartowski is done.
The Buy More is for sale.
Fine. Fine, fire me, just let me go.
Chuck, there is one last thing
I need from you.
Some CIA property.
- What is that?
- A suppression device.
They say it only hurts a lot.
No, no, no, don't take the Intersect.
I need it for the antidote.
- I need it to save Sarah.
- I know, Chuck. I know.
Don't.
What do you want, Clyde?
You're going
to convince Agent Bartowski...
and his mom that this is over.
No one can know the true origin
of Alexei Volkoff.
Uncuff him.
John, I don't need to threaten you
to follow an order.
You're a Marine.
You're going to do this
to protect the greater good.
Your country.
I'm on to you.
You know
I'm not gonna bail out on Walker.
Think I'm just gonna accept your offer,
try to escape with Frost and Chuck?
But it's a setup.
When I make my move, you kill us all.
In the report, you make yourself out
to be the good guy, right?
A real hero.
Well, that's all right.
See, John...
I'm not afraid to be the bad guy.
Neither am I.
Hey, Casey, what's up?
We're making our move.
Does the CIA still have a man on you?
Yes. Yes, they do.
Take him out.
Meet me at the apartment.
Yes, sir. Okay. All right.
What's going on?
We're getting Chuck
and Hartley out of here.
Your mom and I are the magnet.
We're gonna distract Decker.
It's the only way
you'll make it to Moscow.
They took the Intersect out of me.
You're the second best spy I've ever
worked with. Go save the best one.
I'm sorry, what am I supposed to do?
You and Chuck need
to break into Volkoff Industries.
There'll be lots of security,
you have to go as your old self.
Of course, as Volkoff.
Yes, but he's not you.
He's a mean, dictatorial, conniving...
Manipulative, amoral...
Limey, with relatively good teeth.
- Sounds like I was a monster.
- You were.
And you didn't tell me this
for a reason?
My daughter.
I made her into me?
I made her into Volkoff?
I'm sorry, Hartley.
Okay, guys, we got a situation.
We need to take out the CIA guard
at the end of the hall.
- What? We don't do that kind of thing.
- Morgan? Is he dangerous?
Yes. Yes, very.
- Devon, take him out.
- Wait, what? No.
I'm standing right here.
I'm the professional spy.
Devon will go and distract,
I will be the one doing the taking out...
with a little spy maneuver
we like to call "The Magnet."
- So, what? You punch him out?
- Probably sweep the leg.
I haven't decided. I like to improvise.
Move. Up.
Chuck, new identities.
Untraceable, extremely rare.
I made them years ago
for an occasion just like this.
You have to use them, Chuck.
You and Sarah need to disappear.
I got it.
- If I've never...
- Get the antidote.
You get it to Sarah
then you disappear.
You do whatever it takes,
you save her.
Am I ever gonna see you again, Mom?
Not if everything goes right.
- Goodbye, Chuck.
- I love you.
Come on. Come on.
All right, Morgan, sweep the leg.
Or karate chop.
- I love those shades.
- Or roundhouse kick.
Or roundhouse... Or, uh...
Or, uh...
You are supposed to be the magnet.
Dude, sweep the leg?
In real life, you just make a fist
and hit him as hard as you can.
You got lucky.
So this is it.
The Volkoff Industries.
It's, uh...
Very stark.
Charles,
do you think this suit's a bit much?
Too much sheen?
Hartley, you are Alexei Volkoff, okay?
Don't think about the suit.
Just say as little as possible
and we'll be fine. Think angry thoughts.
Actually, my mind has just gone blank.
I think I've forgotten the plan again.
Simply approach the receptionist...
and tell her in a very bold and
Volkovian way you're here to see Vivian.
She'll lead us to your private elevator.
I'll slip into the air shaft, go to the lab.
I can't do it.
- No, you have to do it.
- No, I'm not this man.
I'm a scientist.
Your plan isn't gonna work, Charles.
Listen to me, it will work.
My plans always work. I promise.
But you're not the spy you used to be.
And I'm not the villain I used to be.
- We can't do it.
- Damn it, we can.
If we work together, we can.
What is it? What is going on?
What if she's up there?
My daughter.
This is about Vivian?
I don't know her.
What do you say to a daughter
you've never even met?
"I'm so sorry I've ruined your life?"
No. No.
I'm sorry, I can't see her.
- I'm gonna run away now.
- No, Hart...
Wait!
Can I help you?
My name is Charles Car...
Chuck Bartowski.
I'm here to see Vivian Volkoff.
And what is this in regard to?
She wants to kill me.
I don't believe it.
Charles Carmichael.
I'm impressed.
Walking into my office unarmed, bold.
Stupid but bold.
Sarah is still alive.
- How can that be?
- It doesn't matter.
I need a vial of the antidote, Iridium 6.
Your father stored it here.
- You need it.
- Please. I'm pleading with you.
I am here to plead for Sarah's life.
What's the trick, Chuck?
What's the clever plan
that gets you out of this?
I'm all out of plans.
The woman I love is dying
and I can only hope...
that you haven't totally
become this person.
Everything you've ever said
was done to manipulate me.
You told me
my father was a monster...
and now you tell me he's
someone else, some sort of hero.
I wouldn't say hero.
Bloody fool, more like.
I signed on for a mission
because they needed a scientist.
And then I convinced his father,
my friend, Stephen...
to let me use his computer program
to help me.
- How did you get in here?
- I just asked to be shown to my office.
Everyone was really nice.
They all jumped up to help me.
I guess
I must have been a harsh boss...
and father.
I'm so sorry.
You're sorry?
You made me your succession plan.
This was my grandmother's,
her name was Vivian.
She rode horses,
and she looked just like you.
Don't you see? You're a good
person. And you come from a good family.
You've fallen into
the wrong world and life.
- You're not a killer.
- Killed Sarah in cold blood.
But you haven't yet, there's still time.
You can give me the antidote,
and I can save her.
No. I have to be Volkoff now.
I am this building, I am this company.
I can never leave, I can never go back.
- What if you could?
- How?
These are blank identities.
Very rare. Very clean.
You'd have to give up Volkoff Industries
but if you take these you can start over.
Anywhere in the world.
The both of you.
Charles?
How will you escape?
It doesn't matter. The only thing that
matters is saving Sarah at this point.
Vivian, I don't know you
but I'd like to.
If you pull that trigger...
you will lose yourself forever...
like I did.
You can still change.
Please, will you help me?
My brother's cutting it close.
The whole place is surrounded
by Decker's men.
Chuck's never gonna be able
to get in there.
Oh, he'll have a plan.
Chuck will come up with something.
- What the hell?
- Sorry we're late, Morgan.
- Egypt took longer than we thought.
- Not a problem.
I called Sarah's bridesmaids
as soon as their plane landed.
Don't give me any grief, Casey.
We're here for Sarah.
Glad you're here.
- Meet Mary, the mother-in-law.
- Hi.
- We have a signal.
- Repeat that. What did you say?
Something is approaching by air.
I have the antidote. Let me in.
Get him out of here.
Hey.
Decker, let him in.
- Thanks for coming, guys.
- You're welcome, Chuck.
Hey, let him in, douche.
You're all under arrest.
I'm kind of disappointed
in you, Bartowski.
You thought you could get past me
with a few of your spy friends?
You should have known
I'd bring an army to stop you.
I know the move.
But we have a move of our own.
It's called the magnet.
See, while you're busy looking at me
and all of my spy friends...
you're missing something really,
really big...
care of Volkoff Industries.
Russians. So many Russians.
Russian special forces.
You really are a traitor.
Just for the day.
This is a file that contains
all of Project X, the cover-up...
and your involvement in all of it.
If anything happens to Sarah,
my friends or family...
this story hits the front page
of every paper in the United States.
- You're done.
- I quit.
Now, get out of my way.
I do.
Sarah, hey.
Hey, baby.
Good, so when we do it for real,
we'll be ready.
I think we left out
one pretty important little detail.
It's not too late.
It's not too late. It's not too late.
Please.
Uh...
Right, my vows.
My turn for vows.
They just don't cut it.
I'm sorry, Sarah.
How do I express
the depth of my love for you?
Or my dreams for our future, or the
fact that I will fight for you every day.
Or that our kids
will be like little superheroes...
with little capes and stuff like that.
Words can't express that.
Don't do it justice. They just don't cut it.
So no vows.
I'll just prove it to you every day
for the rest of our lives.
You can count on me.
Perfect.
Do you, Charles Bartowski...
take this woman
to be your lawfully wedded wife?
I do.
- And do you take this man...? Okay.
- I do.
Well, by the power vested in me...
by the Intergalactic Federation
of Planets...
I now pronounce you man and wife.
You may kiss the bride.
Come here.
Trust me, Chuck.
You and I,
we're perfect for each other.
And I want to spend
the rest of my life with you.
Away from everyone else
and away from the spy life.
I love you.
I love you, Chuck.
Nothing's ever gonna change that.
I feel like I should be James Bond
right now.
The guy who's standing with you
right now, at this moment...
I didn't fall in love with James Bond.
I fell in love with you.
Welcome to the family.
To the airport, my good man.
- Morgan, what happened to the driver?
- Oh, no, I was always the driver, Chuck.
I'm having a little trouble letting go,
I suppose.
Just roll up the partition, would you?
As you wish.
Mrs. Chuck Bartowski.
Mr. Sarah Walker.
This is Chuck Bartowski,
happily married man.
What do you want, Morgan?
Charles, sorry we missed the party
but we did send a little gift in our place.
- Did you get it?
- Hartley.
What are you talking about?
Look under your seat.
Just a little something
for my best friend's son and his bride.
Be wise with it, Charles.
Good luck.
What?
Oh, boy.
Hey, guys.
Well, well, the prodigal son returns.
From my honeymoon.
Go ahead, chump.
Whistle past the graveyard.
The deal went through.
The Buy More's been sold.
Give it a week, we're all jobless.
Leave us alone, please?
Private conversation.
Well, maybe just give it a little time,
fellas.
Get the hell back to work.
The new owner might stop by today.
I am working.
Guess it's the dawn of a new chapter,
eh, boy?
I'd watch that boy talk, redneck.
From General Beckman.
Your personal effects.
Wouldn't want you to be
without your pocket protector.
Yeah, well, I'd rather wear this
than be in business with you.
You really think
you've been fighting evil, doing good?
You're just a pawn, you always were.
What are you talking about?
You think it was all a coincidence?
The Intersect, Fulcrum,
the Ring, Shaw, Agent X.
That was all just part of the plan,
Bartowski...
pieces on the puzzle board.
See you never, civilian.
Wait, wait. Wait, what plan?
What plan?
My life was changed forever.
My friends were put in danger,
my family.
My father was killed, Decker.
A plan?
Sounds more like a conspiracy.
The question is
who could control our lives so well?
I don't know.
It doesn't matter anyway,
it's not our fight.
You forget the CIA fired our asses.
Okay, well, what if we went
into business for ourselves?
- And how exactly would we do that?
- Well, we have a base.
And the Buy More
has proven to be an excellent cover.
Mrs. B?
One thing, the Buy More just sold.
Yeah, we know.
We bought it.
Hartley turned over all of
Volkoff's assets to us, wedding present.
Eight hundred and 77 million dollars.
I'd like to refer to it as a cool billion
just because it's more fun to say.
That's a lot of money.
And who better to handle
a billion dollars than me?
Us, us, us.
Our first purchase was the Buy More
and everything below it.
Now we have all of Volkoff's resources
at our disposal.
- If you still wanna take out the bad guys.
- Damn right we do.
- You guys want a job?
- Yeah.
- Hells, yeah.
- Great.
I took the liberty of buying us a
Gulf stream and new tactical equipment.
We do have to re-outfit Castle.
So any ideas?
Freelance spies.
Yes, men and women of action
and adventure.
Under the radar. Above the law.
Oh, man, this is gonna be so much fun.
Just, uh...
Oh, nice.
Slick new gig, slick new shades.
Heh-heh. What could go wrong?
Morgan. Morgan.
Morgan?
Morgan, did you just?
Guys.
I know kung fu.