Hi, I'm Chuck. Here are a few things
that you might need to know.
Is it strange that all of the new employees
have been named Greta?
This is one of my father's laptops.
How did you...?
There's something on it.
Some memory problem Ellie figured out.
What's going down there in Castle?
Are you leveraging me
to stay in my apartment?
- Let's say I was.
- You can stay at my place...
as long as you keep quiet.
Don't tell anyone, especially Bartowski.
I hope you didn't think
this interrogation was over.
We know about your involvement
with the CIA.
I have no idea...
No idea what you're talking about.
We know that you work with John Casey.
Just admit it. This can all be over.
I don't know what you... I don't know.
Okay. Okay. Hold on a second.
I admit it.
I have worked with John Casey.
We worked together
for the last four years now.
We started in large appliances
and then I worked up to manager.
Think this is funny?
You're really willing to sacrifice
your life to protect John Casey?
My only regret
is that I have one life to give.
You go ahead. You do your worst.
Okay. Ha, ha. That was tough.
You didn't wet yourself
this time. That's an improvement.
- I didn't drink any water today.
- Welcome to the team.
Thank you, sir. Glad to be part of it.
Whoa.
So where you going there?
- Super-secret spy mission?
- Don't do that.
I'm just goofing around with you, buddy.
Roomie. First rule of Team Casey.
Don't ask, don't tell.
- What about Chuck and Sarah?
- Especially not Chuck and Sarah.
Sir.
You really care about your best friend,
you'll lock it down, Morgan.
Pfft. Morgan Grimes, you are a badass.
Oh, no, I peed a little bit.
Fifteen seconds.
- Ten.
- Sarah, stop yelling.
You know I don't work well
under pressure, okay?
God, no, no, no.
- Damn wishbone. Your turn.
- I can't do this anymore. I'm sorry.
"Final Fantasy II."
Morgan and I spent an entire summer
devouring this one.
What is the point of being a spy
if there aren't any missions?
Casey.
- What are you doing here?
- Did Beckman call?
No, I'm just, ahem, returning something.
A 50-cal sniper rifle?
Why are you checking weapons out?
I was plinking on the range. Don't want
a weapon like this to feel neglected.
What about us? Do you think Beckman
has secretly sidelined our team?
- Why else would our missions dry up?
- I don't know.
Maybe the Intersect's made the world
a more peaceful place.
- Hmm.
- What is that about?
You think we're stir-crazy,
think about Casey.
I mean, he hasn't shot someone
in two weeks.
That we know of.
Casey is up to something...
and I'm gonna get to the bottom of it.
- Sarah? Sarah.
This is so weird.
I didn't know this hallway even existed.
Maybe it's a part of all the new construction
that's been going on.
- Ahh.
- Huh.
Well, allow me. It's not like they're gonna
deny the one and only Intersect. Ha, ha.
Okay, so maybe you're not
being completely paranoid.
I haven't seen much of Casey
in the last couple of weeks.
- You think he's gone lone wolf?
- That's it.
Prowling the streets
administering vigilante justice?
Come on...
Actually, that's entirely plausible.
It's time for a spy intervention.
We need to put our partner on the spot.
Nope. I have a better idea.
Hey. What's up, man?
Hey, buddy. Um...
Mind if I come in?
You know what? I do mind,
because, uh, I just waxed my floors.
Really? Cooked that one up
on the spot, did you?
What's your new spy partner
been up to these days?
You must be referring
to my domestic partner...
for I am not privy
to Casey's spy life.
Have you seen your new roommate
disappearing at odd times?
- No.
- Coming home with fresh injuries?
- None that I'm aware of.
- Receiving solo missions...
from one
General Diane Beckman?
Can't say that I have, chief.
One more little question.
Where have all my missions gone?
Because either all the bad guys are on
vacation or Casey's up to something.
Or maybe the Intersect has just made
the world a more peaceful place.
Good seeing you, pal.
I can't believe Morgan would lie
to my face like that.
I can't believe Casey would lie
to my face. My old partner.
Wait. Didn't Casey say that Beckman
had him working on something new?
Do you think Beckman is sending him
out on missions without us?
Why would Beckman do that?
We're Casey's team.
Wait. He's on the move.
Oh, oh. Are we really doing this?
Spying on our own partner?
- Isn't that icky?
- Think about it.
If Casey is going out on missions,
then he is doing so without the Intersect.
You're right. What if he gets in a jam?
What if he needs our help?
I mean, we're not spying on Casey,
we're watching his back.
Duh.
It was nice of Devon to let us borrow his
new Sienna. It is the perfect tail vehicle.
Think about it, dual screens,
Bluetooth, 10-speaker sound system.
- And it's so comfy.
- Well, it's unassuming.
That's why it's the perfect tail vehicle.
Oh. Did I mention the automatic doors?
It's like I'm using the Force.
Okay. Ahem.
It's time to find out
what kind of game Casey's playing.
Easy. Your boss is expecting me.
I wasn't expecting you,
I was expecting Dragan.
And I wasn't expecting him
for two days.
- Slight change of plans.
- Wasn't part of our arrangement.
Oh, all right.
My employer would be happy
to do business elsewhere.
Please...
excuse my lack of hospitality.
He's all alone. What's he trying to do,
get himself killed?
Don't you wanna open it?
I would trust Dragan with my life.
You, on the other hand, John Casey...
NSA agent, not so much.
What exactly was your plan?
You just walk in here and arrest me?
All alone? Heh, heh.
He's not alone.
He wouldn't go undercover
without his team.
Yeah.
Honestly, who do you take him for?
What are you doing here?
Saving your life, partner.
Don't need saving, idiot.
Oh, really, I'm the idiot?
Please. Let me settle this.
You are all idiots.
You're under arrest.
Good work, colonel.
Wait, so this was all a sting?
Hang on a second.
Is that Greta and other Greta?
Chuck, Sarah...
meet my new team.
Chuck 4x18 - Versus the A-Team
Look at those two.
First they take over the Buy More,
then they steal our partner...
now they're taking over our spy base.
I can't believe Casey replaced us.
- I can't believe the CIA replaced us.
- Come again?
Who do you think
is taking our missions?
Honey, please. Look, I have something
irreplaceable in this little head of mine.
So let Casey have his new team.
You still got the Intersect, baby.
Let's go introduce ourselves, shall we?
So I said to him, you can keep
your larger magazine capacity...
when it comes to stopping power,
nothing beats my.45.
- That is hilarious.
Forty-fives...
Great work back there, by the way,
with the guns and the bad guys.
Pow, pow, pow.
Took them all out, that was impressive.
I'm sorry,
but I never got your actual names.
And I don't wanna keep calling you Greta.
I'm assuming Greta's an acronym.
- Captain Noble.
- Captain Dunwoody.
- Captain. Captain.
- Agent.
Rick and Vicki. Ha, ha.
It's rhyme-y, it's cute.
- You a couple?
- Don't be ridiculous.
It's against agency protocol.
Romantic entanglements
lead to lapses in judgment.
You ought to know.
Walker? Ahem. A word please?
- So, what kind of music you guys into?
- Shh.
I see, you're very busy.
I see you picked your new team
for their personalities.
Sorry you had to find out this way.
It's not like I've been your partner
the last four years.
- Please let me explain.
- No. It's cool, you know. I get it.
Beckman gave you a new team,
you've been running missions with them...
This wasn't Beckman's idea.
Colonel Casey, grab your team.
Mission briefing in five.
That is, if you're all through fraternizing
with your old team.
So who is, uh, Suzy Sunshine?
Director Bentley. She's our Beckman.
Except not as warm and cuddly.
Well, babe,
I guess it's just you and me.
- Where are you going?
- To fix this.
Oh, boy.
Why didn't you tell us
Casey was heading up his own team?
Agent Walker, you're not the only one
who has to take orders.
I'm playing the cards I was dealt.
I suggest you do the same.
Quick follow-up question, general.
Who's the A-team
and who's the B-team here?
I know you love our team
and Casey's team equally...
Enough. Both of you.
Right now you need to focus
on the mission at hand.
- Which is?
- A top-priority extraction from Tbilisi.
You'll recognize the target
of the colonel's recent sting operation...
Necati Acar, a.k.a. The Turk.
Although his arrest was important,
the real prize is this man.
Dragan Pichushkin. Arms dealer.
He's made a fortune
dismantling the former Soviet arsenal...
and selling it on the black market.
The Turk has agreed to lure Dragan
onto U.S. Soil under one condition.
That we offer his family asylum?
Precisely, Agent Walker.
All we have is a first name. Jana.
Wife?
Jana.
Jana. Mistress. Think it's probably
a mistre... No photos?
That's why we're sending you.
Wheels up in the morning.
Use the Intersect to ID Jana
and return her safely to U.S. Soil.
That is all, team.
I think she meant to say A-team.
I can't believe
we're finally going on a mission.
Hey.
What's up, Devon, you okay?
Just trying to find my baseline, bro.
Oh. Stressful day at the ER?
Trauma surgery's a cinch.
It's coming home that's stressful.
Being home with the baby's
made Ellie stir-crazy.
Must be going around.
When I walk through that door,
she makes up for 12 hours of not talking...
to another adult in about 12 minutes.
Wish me luck.
Good luck.
Hi, honey. How was work? I'm so glad
you're home. I've been dying to talk.
Remember how I've been trying
to keep track of Clara's sleep schedule?
At first I couldn't find the circadian cycle,
then I applied some biostatistics.
Voilà. Isn't that incredible?
Oh. Wait till you see the data
that I gathered during tummy time.
And here is a chart
of Clara's new vocal sounds.
You can go a little loony with someone
babbling in your ear all day long.
The problem is,
I only have one test subject.
So in order to control my experiment,
we're gonna have to have a second baby.
Joking.
Speaking of computer modeling,
whatever happened to my dad's laptop?
Devon?
Devon, are you listening to me?
Huh? Yeah. Computers.
- Brain science. Totally with you.
- Good.
I'm starting to think that my dad left me
that computer for a reason.
Maybe his research is just the diversion
that I need right now.
I want that computer back.
- I wonder what Casey's team is up to.
- Who cares?
Beckman said it herself,
this extraction is top priority.
It's the bro-in-law.
Hey, Devon, what's going on?
Chuck. We need to talk.
- Why are you whispering?
- Clara's sleeping.
- And I don't want Ellie to hear.
- Can this wait till I'm home?
Ellie wants your dad's laptop.
She thinks he gave it to her for a reason.
No, Devon. Listen to me
and listen to me very carefully.
She cannot have the laptop.
The laptop is filled
with dangerous spy stuff...
which is probably why it's buried
deep beneath Langley.
But she gave the computer to me.
- What am I supposed to tell her?
- Tell her you lost it.
Tell her you brought it
to the Buy More to get it fixed.
She'll assume Jeff and Lester lost it.
Good cover story, bro.
That's why you called the pro.
Wait. I'm seeing a square.
Close. Squiggly lines.
Excuse me.
Damn it, lady. Can't you see
that you're ruining his concentration?
I'm just here to get my computer,
then you can go back to your game.
Game?
I will have you know, Eleanor,
that our friend Jeffrey here is a clairvoyant.
Read her thoughts, Jeffrey.
She hates us.
She thinks we're pathetic.
She doesn't believe in ESP.
That's really good.
Can I have my computer?
Fine. Where's your claim stub?
- Devon dropped it off.
- No claim stub, no computer. Mush.
Okay, uh, you guys just...
You don't understand.
There's something
really important on that laptop.
Something...
private.
Go on.
Devon and I, we made a video
when we were in med school.
Um, I'd just hate for it
to fall into the wrong hands.
Jeffrey, clear our schedule.
Ma'am, we're gonna find that laptop
if it's the last thing we do.
Looks like Jana's running a little late.
Or else the Turk's enemies
got to her before we did.
Looks like this landing zone
is about to get a little hot.
That's why Beckman sent us.
Do any of those guys
look like Jana to you?
You wanted Jana? I'm getting her.
These charmers stuffed her in the trunk.
I don't like this, Sarah.
Oh, my God. They chopped her up
into little pieces.
What?
Sarah, meet Jana.
This was our big extraction?
A stupid dog?
Sometime boss's dog
gets upset tummy.
Try mixing in a cup of her dry food
with the wet stuff.
And be sure to walk her every hour...
or that happens.
Oh. Gross.
Oh, my God, Sarah.
We're the B-team.
We used to be the A-team...
the sharp end of the CIA stick.
Now we're glorified pet couriers?
Nothing has changed, Chuck.
Well, what do you call
Casey's new team, then?
I call them the competition.
Wanna be on the A-team again?
We have to earn it.
What? How?
Dragan.
Beckman said he's the brass ring.
We're gonna collar him and we're gonna
show the general we've still got it.
Except the only person
who can lead us to Dragan is the Turk...
and who knows where
they're keeping him.
- Is that...?
- Jana?
She's got an upset tummy. Think
they remembered to mix in the dry food?
If the Turk's dog is behind that door,
so is the Turk.
All we gotta do is get through
four inches of steel.
Or we chop off Casey's hand.
- Let's keep that as our backup plan.
- Sure.
Okay.
Morgan, I can hear you eating
potato chips. Open the door.
- Can't do that.
- This is ridiculous.
- Why can't we talk face-to-face?
- Trust me. It's for your own good.
Is that right? Or is that
what Casey told you to tell me?
Hey, hey. Colonel's a good man
and he gave me my orders, okay?
- To lock it down.
- Let me in.
Over my dead body, Chuck.
How about over your tranq'd body?
You were distracting me
so she could break in.
- Yeah.
- Clever girl.
- Are you using the five-milligram darts?
- Ten.
Please tell Casey
I put up a good fight.
Great. Now all we need is something
with Casey's handprint on it...
so we can access
the secret part of Castle.
Ooh. What are these?
These have a camera inside of them
that scan for any bio-residue.
Yuck. Sounds like a CBS show.
I found one,
but this handprint is way too tiny.
Looks like it belongs to a child.
Oh, right.
Bingo.
Sarah.
Not bad for the B-team.
Holy crap. Their Castle
is so much cooler than ours.
I wonder if they have that
fancy Greek yogurt in their kitchen.
Okay, you go find the Turk. I'm gonna see
if I can pull up Dragan's case file.
Please.
I told you everything
I know about Dragan's shipment.
No. Relax.
I'm not part of their team.
They are like a pair of evil robots.
Wait. They told me about you.
You are the dog walker, no?
I'm happy you're here.
Jana was beginning to walk funny.
She needs to have, uh,
how you say, a pee-pee time?
Chuck? Chuck,
I think you should look at this.
Hey. What's up?
What do you want me to...?
My dad's computer.
Why would they...?
Casey, please tell me you didn't.
I think it's time for us to go.
Right now.
You're not authorized to be
in this section of Castle.
What are you doing
with my father's computer?
The Intersect project is classified.
Classif... Classified?
I'm not authorized to be down here?
What?
I am the Intersect.
You're not as special as you think.
I think you should get out of here
before you get hurt.
I see you know kung fu.
It's very impressive,
but a little showy for my taste.
How about this style, Bartowski?
Oh, for heaven's sake.
Chuck, what is happening?
We're following the same program.
Sarah...
they're Intersects.
Stand down, captain.
So this was your idea, Casey? Huh?
You used my father's program
to make your own Intersects?
Now that you have your dream team
you don't need me around.
But that right there?
That's mine, and I'm taking it.
You don't wanna do that.
Yeah, well, my father never wanted
his invention to be used like this.
Drop it.
That computer
is property of the U.S. Government.
- Call off your dogs, Casey.
- Captain, put the gun down now.
First, you put the computer down,
Bartowski...
or I'll put a bullet
in that obsolete brain of yours.
I'd do as she says, Mr. Bartowski.
Unlike you, my Intersects aren't afraid
to pull the trigger.
Now do you understand
why I had Beckman send you to Tbilisi?
You wanted us out of the way.
The CIA's two Intersect teams
were never supposed to, well, intersect.
It was important that you not interfere
with the GRETA field test.
Right. The Gretas in the Buy More.
We've been using your store
as a proving ground...
for prospective Intersect candidates.
These two are the best of the best.
Oh. Really?
So then what does that make me?
None of this would be possible
without you.
That's right.
We've been studying you as well...
correcting your father's software
for your various limitations.
- Limitations?
- His emotional sensitivity.
His overreliance on his handlers.
- His inability to terminate targets.
- You clearly fixed that glitch.
Vicki here almost shot Chuck.
If you'll excuse us,
we have a mission to complete.
Dragan Pichushkin, our primary target...
is currently en route to an airfield
outside of Los Angeles.
Our analysts at Langley believe
that he is on this aircraft, which was...
Hijacked by drug runners in 2006.
The plane is now registered
to a Moscow shell corporation.
Yeah. What they said.
Very good.
Your team will intercept Pichushkin...
confiscate all cargo
and return him alive.
- Ma'am.
- Dismissed.
Oh. And you two are free to return home
and await further orders.
Unbelievable.
- Walker, let me explain.
- Don't. If you'd stayed with Chuck and I...
you would have been mothballed.
- I didn't jump ship.
- You didn't exactly go down with ship.
I left because you don't need me.
Don't pretend like you don't know...
what I'm talking about.
- We were a team, Casey.
You and Bartowski were the team.
I was just the backup.
That is not true.
It doesn't matter, anyway.
I wanted you to know I think Bentley's
giving you the short end of the stick.
You and Bartowski,
you're still good agents.
Yeah, well, we used to be the best.
I'm calling about the laptop.
Did you find it?
Well, there is a chance...
that we returned the laptop
to the wrong person.
- Gee, what a surprise.
- Don't worry.
I got my best man on it.
I need you to focus your powers, Jeffrey.
I need a name.
I need you to tell me
who has that missing computer.
So...
You...
are gonna close your eyes...
and you're gonna jot down
whatever letters pop into your head.
Go.
No. That's not a letter.
Deeper. Jeffrey.
Dig. Dig.
What just happened?
Did I do it?
Cia?
The hell kind of name is Cia?
You're totally worthless, Jeffrey.
Take a look at this.
Twelve hours ago.
Target leaving for the States.
I'm confident your new team
can handle a few bodyguards.
Not them. That.
He's not moving parts. Pichushkin's
moving a fully assembled bomb.
We can assume he's gonna use it.
- We need backup.
- You have two GRETAs.
- What else do you need?
- My old team.
Chuck and Sarah.
It's a five-man job.
You sure you're not being sentimental?
Pichushkin's delivering
live explosives to a metropolitan center.
We're equipped
with live ordnance disposal.
No. The colonel is right.
This is a perfect job
for Chuck Bartowski.
Bomb disposal?
I mean, seriously? Don't they have robots
for stuff like this?
It's the only way Bentley
would let you come.
- I guess expendability has its perks.
- Okay, team.
Target lands in inside 10.
You two help me neutralize
Dragan's security team...
and take him into custody alive.
Hey.
You're a vital part of this mission, Chuck.
Don't forget it.
And try not to drop the bomb, Chuck.
Once we have the bomb, you're on.
Use the Intersect to defuse it.
I know you're a little scared.
The suit'll protect you.
I saw The Hurt Locker, Casey. Okay?
I know what happened to Guy Pearce.
His suit didn't really do him good.
I'm sorry, I'm being overly sensitive.
I bet your new Intersects,
they wouldn't complain.
I had to wear one of these in Bosnia.
One of my worst missions.
There. Here, let me show you
a little trick.
This way you don't have to use
your hands to drink.
Thanks, buddy.
Good luck. It's your favorite.
Apple juice.
Oh, oh.
They are outnumbered and outgunned.
Those guards are carrying
automatic weapons.
Whoa! Holy crap.
Those two are like Terminators. They
took out five guys in the blink of an eye.
Welcome to America, Mr. Pichushkin.
Let me take your luggage.
It's yours.
Okay?
Portable fission device.
Five-kiloton yield.
Approximate fireball radius,
two kilometers.
That's a suitcase nuke.
I'm sorry. Did Casey just say...?
So you have your bomb.
I have detonator.
So I think it's better
if we just part ways.
Casey, let him go.
I've got my eyes on Dragan.
Sarah.
Help Walker. You stay with the bomb.
You need to disarm this now.
This bomb is a Frankenstein
with a hundred different components.
There's nothing in the Intersect
about how to defuse this.
Hold on, I can help.
I'm coming, Casey! I'm coming!
I'm coming. I'm coming.
Show me your hands.
Where's the detonator?
I am detonator.
Very simple.
My heart stop, bomb start.
So you have choice.
You shoot me and hundreds
of thousands of people will die...
in nuclear blast.
Or I kill you.
Not easy choice.
Vicki, no! Don't shoot!
What did you do?
What the hell just happened?
Your trigger-happy new partner
just armed the bomb.
Ooh. Portable fission device.
Five-kiloton yield.
We covered that. Our best chance is
to fly as far from civilization as possible.
What? No.
We're in the middle of L.A. County.
It's the difference between
100,000 casualties and a million.
We gotta move this bomb.
No. Casey. No, that's not an option.
We have to disarm it.
You've got the same computer
I've got. It can't be disarmed.
I can do this, Casey.
Bomb's all yours, Bartowski.
- You can't be serious.
- Move.
Okay.
- Just like old times.
- Tell me there's a plan.
- There's a plan, right?
- Yeah, there's a plan.
Okay. Casey, first of all, I need you
to pull out the primary device.
Slowly. Carefully.
We're gonna have to improvise.
- Improvi... It's a nuclear bomb.
- Stow it, captain.
That hockey-puck-looking thing
on the end?
That's the detonator.
I need you to twist and pull it. Gently.
Okay. The detonator is
from a next-gen Chinese sub...
which means the firing mechanism
had to have been modified...
to allow the warhead's deployment
in saltwater.
Saltwater. Saltwater! Yes!
These detonators, they automatically
deactivate in saltwater...
in the event of a hull breach.
- We're nowhere near the ocean.
Oh.
Saltwater, saltwater, saltwater. Hmm.
What has...?
- What is he doing?
- Casey. My juice box.
What?
Please have sodium.
Yes. Yes. Yes.
Are you about to disarm
a nuclear bomb using fruit juice?
Okay, do it.
I can't believe that worked.
Ha, ha. Up. Up.
- I love you.
- I love you too.
Try not to drop the bomb, Rick.
Aah.
Looks like things have gotten
a little crowded in Castle.
As I told you before,
this operation requires only one team.
I concur.
I've read Colonel Casey's report.
In addition to threatening
Agent Bartowski's life...
your team managed to kill the man
you were supposed to capture...
and accidentally arm a nuclear bomb.
I take full responsibility for my team.
The truth is, Director Bentley...
you should never have pursued
the Intersect field trial...
without consulting
the original Intersect.
Agent Bartowski,
that is why you will oversee...
all aspects of the Intersect project
from here on out.
And what about my GRETAs?
Intersect extraction complete.
So how's it feel?
What a relief to have that out of my head.
That poor bastard Bartowski.
Looks like that's it for the team.
Honor serving with you, sir.
Captain. Captain. Good luck.
Where do you think you're going?
I figured I was through here
since I don't have a team.
I never dismissed you, colonel.
Beckman's wrong.
The problem's not with my GRETAs,
it's this computer.
You're going to help me fix it.
Best engineers couldn't crack
Intersect code.
It wasn't meant for them.
I need someone
who thinks like a Bartowski.
What are you getting at?
Prepare yourself
for "Final Fantasy Deux."
Oh, please let that be Beckman.
Oh, come on.
A new mission already?
Beckman wants us to leave ASAP.
She's gonna brief us in the air.
Aren't you curious
as to where we're going?
I'm sure it's someplace far-off
and dangerous.
- And what makes you so sure?
- Chuck, we're the A-team.
Valid point.
Well, we might as well bring this.
It's gonna be a long flight.
I'm sure we can find something else
to pass the time.
Not to be crude,
but you were talking about sex, right?
Okay, Devon. Go time.
Babe, you okay?
I went to the Buy More
to get my dad's laptop...
and of course, they couldn't find it.
- It's my fault.
I should have never trusted
those jackasses.
No, it's my fault.
I shouldn't have pretended
to be something that I'm not.
I thought that there might be something
on my dad's computer that would...
I don't know, change the fact
that I'm just a stay-at-home mom.
Whoa, whoa. Stop right there.
You are Eleanor Bartowski Woodcomb,
Ph.D., MD.
The brainiest, sexiest, kick-assiest woman
I have ever known.
- You're not just anything, Ellie.
- Really?
You're Mrs. Awesome.
Thanks.
- What happened to you?
- I've been in a drug-induced stupor...
for the last 24 hours.
What did I tell you about letting
Jeff buy you drinks at Chili's?
Sir, listen, Chuck and Sarah tranq'd me.
They breached our apartment.
I blew it and I'm so sorry, sir.
So I'm turning in my wings.
One, you're not an aviator.
Two, these wings are plastic.
Yeah. No, I told the Southwest pilot
they were for my nephew.
That's not the point.
The fact remains, I let you down.
And I'm sorry,
I can't lie to Chuck anymore.
You don't have to.
From here on, we're on the same team.
Oh, yes. What a relief.
- Okay.
- Gotcha.
All right, that's enough.
Can I have my wings back?
- Mrs. Woodcomb?
- Yes?
Hi. I believe
that I have something of yours.
This is my dad's computer.
Where did you find this?
The Nerd Herd gave me
the wrong computer.
- I found your address in the bag.
- Thank you.
You have no idea
how much this means to me.
Hi, you're home early.
Babe, it's dinnertime.
What?
Clara is taking a monster nap.
I must have lost myself.
- Is that...?
- Yeah. Great news.
I found my dad's computer.