Hey, I'm Chuck. Here are a few
things that you might need to know
or maybe you just forgot.
I have to find the truth, Morgan.
Why my mom left, why she never came back.
This is my search.
This is all I could find.
I thought she was a prisoner
who needed to be saved.
Then I come to find out she's
just one of the bad guys.
- Hello.
- Hello, Chuck, it's your mother.
VOLKOFF INDUSTWERIES Tow Weeks Ago.
What are you doing back
here? This is a secured area.
Oh, I-I'm sorry, I was just
looking for the, uh, fitness center.
I'll, I'll just be on my way, then.
You're not going anywhere.
Show me your security ID..
No need to be rough, I... Aah!
What is this?
I see your hands are shaking.
That means the toxin is taking effect.
It's flooding your brain now, turning your
entire consciousness into one gigantic nightmare.
The only difference is, this
nightmare you never wake up from.
As you can see...
my toxin is fully functional.
Impressive, isn't it?
Very impressive, Dr. Wheelwright.
I believe I have a buyer in Los Angeles
who will be very interested in this.
ECHO PARK, CA Tonight.
- Hello.
- Hello, Chuck, it's your mother.
I want to see you in person.
Is this a joke?
Griffith Park, one hour.
Is this, is this, is this a joke?
Mom, you have any idea how long I've been
looking for you these last couple of months?
Where have you been since
I was nine years old?
Chuck, now is not the time.
Just meet me. Tell no one. Come alone.
Okay, bye.
Hey, Ellie's putting out dessert.
If you don't come in soon, I'm
gonna eat it and blame it on Morgan.
What's the matter? You look
like you've seen a ghost.
I just talked to one.
I had a feeling you wouldn't show up.
I had to make sure you came alone.
I did everything you asked.
Why all the secrecy?
I know you've been working for Volkoff.
You afraid the bad guys are going to
see you hanging around your own son?
Oh, it's much more
complicated than that, Chuck.
Meet me at the playground.
You just hate saying good-bye
like a normal person, don't you?
Okay, Chuck, I'm in position.
And who are you?
Wow.
I didn't even hear a twig snap.
You must have been doing
this for a long time.
Are you calling me old?
Not old.
Just slow.
Government-issued sidearm.
What are you.
CIA, FBI?
My story is not as interesting as
yours, so we'll start with you first.
Why did Volkoff send you here?
Oh, jumping to conclusions, are we?
Oh, I think my conclusions
are pretty justified.
I am here because I need to see...
Whoa, hey, whoa, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey. Hey
there.
How you guys doing?
You brought someone. I
told you to come alone.
No, no, no, no, technically
not just someone.
Okay, Mom, this is my girlfriend Sarah.
Sarah, this is my mom Mary.
I don't know how to say this
exactly, but please don't kill each other.
Chuck 4x06 - Versus the Aisle of Terror
Great, great. See, I can see
the connection already.
BFF. Facebook buddies.
I'll shut up now. I'll shut up.
Did you honestly think
he wouldn't come alone?
I thought maybe he would trust me.
Okay, you know what? Considering
that you left me when I was,
oh, I don't know, nine years old, and I
still don't know if you're good or bad,
I think I have every right to have
a mother issue or two right now.
You're right.
You are absolutely right.
Thank you, thank you. No
shooting necessary.
None whatsoever. Great, good, here we go.
Fully hanging out. What should we do?
Should we... should we sit down?
- I know a wonderful bakery, actually...
- Chuck...
Or we could just hang out here in a...
in a creepy, dark playground.
Where to start? Ooh, ooh, I
know, I got a story.
Tenth birthday-you
haven't even heard this one...
I ate so much chocolate cake, I
had frosting coming out of my nose.
- I could smell it for a year...
- Chuck, Chuck, stop!
I don't want to know anything about you.
- Excuse me? - I am deep undercover
in the Volkoff organization.
And if my cover is blown, they
will torture me for secrets.
I don't want to know one thing about you
or your sister that could put you in danger.
So just leave it at that.
You're undercover?
That's funny, because we didn't find
any files on you in the CIA database.
No, you wouldn't.
When I went undercover
my records were expunged.
That's convenient.
And how do we know that
you're not making this up?
Because I brought you this.
Atroxium.
A nerve gas that causes extreme
terror in its victims and,
within minutes, drives
them completely insane.
The scientist Wheelwright who created it wants
to meet Volkoff's must trusted weapons buyer.
Chuck, I need you to pose as that buyer.
Atroxium is dangerous, far too
dangerous to be on the open market.
One warhead of this could
debilitate an entire army.
I had to break cover so that I could
make sure that the CIA gets hold of this.
Okay, fine. Why me?
Because I thought I could trust you.
- Just say you flashed on him.
- Did I...?
I'm sorry, what? You know
about the Intersect?
I may not know anything about you, Chuck,
but I know everything there is
to know about Charles Carmichael.
We're done here.
Set up the meet.
I'll make sure the
CIA gets the nerve gas.
Good-bye, Chuck.
Good-bye.
Hello. Welcome to the Buy More.
And be sure to stop by this weekend and check
out our Halloween haunted house spectacular.
It's going to be scary.
Good scary, though. Like
pumpkins and ghosts.
Not bad scary like war and bears.
You know, 'cause I
find... Oh, good day, sir.
Welcome to the Buy More.
Coming in a little hot
today, aren't you, Grimes?
It's tough. Once I turn on the charisma, I
can't turn it off. It's my curse.
Listen - that little incident
in Iran showed me something.
You're either exceptionally
smart or incredibly stupid.
My father used to say
the exact same thing.
Without the smart part. But you get it.
The whole situation has
me thinking that maybe...
just maybe, you do have
something to offer as a spy.
This is what I've been
telling you guys. I-I...
Come on. Bartowski has
something to show us.
Thanks.
Sarah, you know I have a
huge blind spot with my mom.
I mean, are we crazy for doing this?
Should we even be getting involved?
I know that you've been looking for
answers about your mom for a long time,
and we're going to find some, okay? We
just have to be very cautious.
Thank you.
Just got your message. What's happening?
Good. You're all here.
Bartowski, your flash on
Wheelwright was 100% correct.
He is currently in Los
Angeles to sell the Atroxium.
I'm sorry. What is Grimes doing here?
Oh, uh, he's with me, General.
I felt that he could be
of some use to the team.
- Is that right?
- Yeah.
Apparently I'm quite the hot
commodity in the spy world.
Morgan Grimes.
Not just for the ladies anymore.
Silence.
- Of course.
- Good.
Now we need to focus.
Atroxium is extremely dangerous.
Uh, General, Sarah and I
were discussing a plan.
Um... if I were to pose as the buyer, not only would
I be able to get the Atroxium off the market,
I could also flash on any Volkoff
operatives that were involved.
So it's a... it's a win-win.
Very impressive, Bartowski.
We'll set up the meet.
Good work, Chuck.
I smell a rat.
- I found her-I
found my mom. - What?
You found your
mom? That's fantastic, dude.
- I'm so happy for you.
- Thanks. Thanks so much, man.
- I still can't believe it myself.
- When? Where?
Well, she actually came to
me with the Wheelwright info.
Chuck, your mother works for Volkoff.
Which is her cover, Casey.
- She's legit. - Better run it by Beckman.
Make sure it checks out.
I've checked, and it's a dead end.
Her CIA credentials were
erased to protect her cover.
We have to keep this to ourselves. Okay?
If Beckman goes digging, she
could put my mom in danger.
You just have to trust me on this.
Devon, your two little ladies are home!
Hey, babe...
Little babe. What are you doing, huh?
We rushed home early so we
could get a few moments of peace
before your mother gets here
and makes my life a living...
- Hello!...
- Heaven.
It's just a heavenly visit
every time she's here.
- Ellie!
- Hi, Honey! It's really good to see you.
What were you doing back there?
Oh, just a little dusting.
We have to keep this place clean
for my little granddaughter-to-be.
Aw. So I just thought I'd try
tidying up a bit... as a surprise.
- Surprise.
- Mom has another surprise for us, too.
She cancelled the room that
we booked for her at the W.
And she's gonna spending
the whole week with us.
The whole week! That, that's great!
I know! I can't believe it either.
Oh, here, darling, let
me take that from you.
Okay.
Are you sure you're okay with this?
Because if not, I can bite the bullet
and I can ask her to stay at the hotel.
Uh, no, you don't have to
do that. She should stay.
- You sure? Y.
- Eah. Yeah.
I felt the baby kick on the way home.
- Oh, my God, really?
- Yeah.
It's starting to feel so real, you know?
I'm gonna be a mom.
I don't know how to be a mom.
Of course you do.
You know, your mother and I aren't best
friends, but it might be nice to have her around.
You know, I could use a
little motherly advice.
- I'll go make up the guest room.
- Okay.
I could stay at the W.
You wanted to see me, boss?
One second, buddy.
Everything okay?
Just a bit overwhelmed
right now, you know?
Work stuff, and, uh...
I promised Chuck that I would
help him with something...
Can I ask you a
question? How do you do it?
How do you balance the Buy More
and your regular life?'Cause I...
Son, in my 12-and-a-half weeks at
the El Segundo School of Finance,
I learned one very important
word: Hmm?"delegate.
" That word is the key to
being a successful manager.
There's even a catchy phrase
for when you got too much to do:
"Get it off your plate, give
it to other people."
I think what you mean to say is:
"Get it off your plate, delegate.
" No, I do not.
You are not a rhyming
monkey, you are a manager.
You're right. Of course, you're
absolutely right.
And thank you for the offer.
I would love for you to dress
the Buy More for Halloween.
No, no, I do not have time for that.
I am knee-deep in this
new Danielle Steele novel.
Anyway, Big Mike isn't nearly scary
enough to build a haunted house.
And you need to put some
real crazies on that...
if you want it done correctly.
Good afternoon, Mr. Carmichael.
I'll show you to your table.
That would be perfect, thank you.
We just got word that
Wheelwright is en route.
Remember, cool, calm and collected.
You are Volkoff's top weapons buyer.
Just one question: can we get one of
those hostess outfits for back home?
Focus, Bartowski. The grownups
are trying to work here.
So sorry I'm late.
- You weren't here
already? - Ha-ha. Nice.
I love our little
give-and-take.
Classic Ross and Rachel.
Okay, what can I do to help?
- Grimes?
- Yeah?
A good spy is trained
in the art of silence.
Silence. Got it.
Chuck, don't fill up on bread. You're
gonna ruin your appetite.
Sorry. Don't...
Target is approaching. Give the signal.
Uh... Mr. Carmichael?
Please, sit. Make yourself comfortable.
So, um...
do we talk price?
Dr. Wheelwright, relax.
I'm about to make you
a very, very rich man.
Would you care for a
drink to calm the nerves?
Toasting already?
What's going on there, Walker?
That's Chuck's mother.
What's she doing there?
You must be Mr. Carmichael.
Chuck, remember, keep your
cover and make the deal.
I am Mr. Carmichael. And who might you be?
I work for Volkoff.
It's my job to ensure
a smooth transaction.
Smooth? Smooth? Is that right?
Well, this transaction
couldn't be going smoother.
It is chock full of smoothness.
Yes, the transaction was
progressing just fine.
Well, it may appear that way, but sometimes
appearances don't tell the whole story.
I've done some digging
on Mr. Carmichael here,
and unfortunately his
story doesn't check out.
It's a CIA trap. He's a spy.
What?
Man down! Man down! Walker, get in there!
Whoa! Holy...
Chuck, you okay? Chuck?
Chuck!
- Chuck, are you okay?
- Sarah...
My mom shot me.
My heart hurts.
I know. I can't believe your
mom betrayed you like that.
No, no, my heart actually hurts.
She shot me in the heart area.
Oh, okay. Here.
Thank you. Ah!
Oh, I'm such an idiot, Sarah.
After everything I knew about my mom, everything I
learned about my mom, I still trusted her anyway.
That's really great spy work.
You know, Chuck, even in the spy world
where everything is run by deceit,
you still manage to somehow
genuinely trust people.
You know what? That's
what I love about you.
That's what you love about me?
Not my dashing good looks or
the giant computer in my brain?
And you're funny, even if your
mom has shot you in the heart.
Oh, two fugitives and a
dangerous weapon on the loose.
Go, team.
Well, you know, we could go back to the
restaurant, see if they left any clues behind.
No, no. We got this.
Dude, you just got shot by your mom, okay?
Take a break. Have a little Chuck time.
Yeah, maybe you're right. Maybe I should.
Sorry.
Spy work or the Buy More?
HELP
Nah.
I don't know. What about there?
And then it could come swinging
and screaming at everybody.
Oh, Morgo, hey.
Um, listen, we have a few questions
regarding these Halloween decorations.
Um, what are we allowed to show?
What do you mean?
I know a really good morgue that gives
discounts on unclaimed merchandise.
Maybe we could sprinkle
some cold, dead ones in here.
Right. No, I'm gonna say
no on the dead bodies.
- So, what, I just lose my deposit?
- Shh...
Okay, look, here's the thing: I put
you in charge of decorating the store
so I can get it off my plate, so you're just
gonna have to figure it out for me, okay?
Make it big, make it fun.
But most importantly, let's
make it scary, okay?
Morgan's right.
We gotta tap into a place
that is so scary, so demented,
that it'll change
Halloween as we know it.
We gotta tap...
into your head!
Okay.
Yeah, you gotta start using
conditioner. Your hair feels like hay.
- Get in.
- Are you crazy?
You know, I didn't think you could top abandoning
me for the last 20 years, and then you shot me!
And I will do it again, if you
don't get in this car right now.
That's every bus station, subway platform and traffic
light camera within a mile radius of the restaurant.
We have no lead on where Wheelwright and
Chuck's mom fled to after the shooting.
Come on.
What rock are you two hiding under?
Chuck just activated
his tracking device.
Mom, you hit one pothole and this
ride gets very messy very quick.
Oh, I'm sorry. Have to
keep up appearances.
Oh. Oh, is that all?
What the heck is going on here, okay?
This is crazy.
Chuck, when I left you and Ellie, I was embedded
into a secret operation called Project Isis.
My mission was to destroy the
Volkoff Organization from within.
But I got in way too deep.
And I was forced to close
the door on my old life.
But then you came looking for me.
And that set off the alarm bells.
Right. So you shot me?
I knew that you were wearing a vest.
Volkoff was tapped into the
security footage of the cafe,
so he thinks that Charles
Carmichael is dead.
And that means you and Ellie are safe.
You did this to protect me and Ellie?
Chuck, you and your sister are and
always have been my only concern.
Not being in your lives has pained
me more than you could ever imagine.
But you had a mission.
I constantly relive that day
when I walked out the door.
Over and over.
And I want you to know that if I could
do it over again, I never would have left.
I would still be there, with my family.
But that's all in the past.
So come with me.
'Cause I never got you a
present for your tenth birthday.
Come on.
See, I knew that if I shot you, Wheelwright might
panic and try to unload the weapon on his own.
But Atroxium is far too dangerous, so
I just went ahead and handled it.
Handle-Handle-How did
you handle it, exactly?
This is Wheelwright's mobile lab.
He's tranq'd up inside, and the
Atroxium's ready for extraction.
And, Chuck, sorry I shot you.
Hey, it's okay. No harm, no foul.
- Oh, God. Mom...
- I know.
You activated your tracking
device when you got in the car.
Good boy.
Okay, come on, Chuck's signal
is coming from in there.
Agents will be here any second.
You're going to vanish
for good now, aren't you?
I did what I came here to do.
And now you and Ellie are safe, and
I've got to go back undercover.
Okay, okay, fine.
But, listen, before you disappear, please, go
and talk to Ellie, just for a second.
Just-Just tell her what you
told me about why you left us.
200 meters.
I'm sorry.
I'm sorry, Chuck.
Mom, Ellie's pregnant.
She's pregnant, and you're
going to be a grandmother.
We're getting closer. 80 meters.
Chuck, how'd you get here?
My mom dropped me off.
Well, she may be a bad mom, but
she makes a great spy, right?
Either way, I guess it
doesn't matter. She's gone.
- You okay?
- Yeah.
I...I'm just wondering
what to tell my sister.
I mean, do I casually drop
that Mom came back to town to
shoot me in the chest and hand
over a deadly chemical weapon?
Well, I know that you'll figure
out the exact right thing to say.
Lucky for me, I know the foremost
authority on all things Ellie Bartowski.
I'm gonna be right back. You
save some of that fun for me.
I will.
I don't trust her.
If Bartowski's mom's working for
the good guys, then why disappear?
I don't know. But Chuck believes her.
Yeah.
I know a decommissioned NSA
agent, specializes in expunged documents.
Unsavory character, but I think
he can get us what we need.
You want backup?
No.
I got someone.
I knew it. I knew Mrs. B
wasn't a bad guy. You know why?
Bad guys don't make such
delicious lemon bars.
Killer brownies, too.
Look, I need your advice for this Mor.
Hey, ah!
Oh! Oh! What the...?
Wow.
They did it. Jeff and
Lester pulled it off, man.
This looks great.
Guys, hey, excellent work with
the Halloween decorations.
The store looks incredible.
This garbage? No, no, no.
This is just to whet your
appetite for the main event.
Gentlemen, prepare yourselves
for the Aisle of Terror.
Prepare... to be terrorized!
Fernando, not now! I mean...
We got the idea from an experiment that the UCLA
psychology department did on our friend Jeffrey.
Nothing I won't do
for $30 and a sandwich.
Um... Or just a sandwich.
You see, there's this world-renowned
professor at UCLA, Professor Schofield,
who specializes in examining the
subconscious of the mentally disturbed.
- He gets right up in there.
- Shh!
So using Jeffrey and a bunch
of other nut bags as test cases,
he discovered that there are certain images
that can cause terror in even the most...
fearless lunatics. Let's do this.
So now...
get ready to see some of the
scariest things in the world.
Old people.
Public showers.
What's going on, Chuck?
- Interspecies relationships.
- Okay. What-Stop now, stop.
Uh, I'll be honest with you.
This might be one of the
worst things I've ever seen.
One of the best things?
I think he said "best." Yeah.
I don't want any customers in here.
Guys, it's scary, but
just in a really bad way.
I give up. I give up.
- Babies in costume.
- Really?
Is it a baby... or is it a snail?
- I don't know.
- 'Kay.
So, Honey, you have any parenting tips?
I mean, Devon turned out so good, I just
figured you could give me some inside scoop.
Well, you know, Devon was
amazing right from the start.
Really great genes, I guess.
I guess.
But don't you worry, this little
wonder is already halfway there.
You know, we really have to make sure that
this baby has positive female influences.
So I'm here to help.
Thanks, Honey.
Babe, is this not the most
adorable thing you've ever seen?
- It's adorable.
- Plays the "Chicken Dance.
" Devon, like this stuffed bear is going
to teach this baby how to read and write.
Here.
Babies love dictionaries.
I'm gonna see if they
have an encyclopedia.
- You okay, hon?
- I'm fine.
Your, uh, your mother
might be a bit much, but
underneath it all, she just wants
to be a part of the baby's life.
It's more than I can say for my mom.
I've been thinking about my mom.
It's weird, though.
The woman that I found is nothing like
the one I remember from my childhood.
You're trying to justify
not telling Ellie?
Am I that transparent?
No. But you don't want to hurt her.
Okay, let's get started on the detonator.
That's not good.
Wheelwright. Quick, quick.
Why is the device counting down?
Oh, that?
Well, just a safety measure
to protect against tampering.
It counts down until I verify that
the weapon is in my possession.
Okay, tell us how to turn it off.
Well, you'll need this.
But why should I help you?
Remember, if the device
goes off, you'll be exposed.
So be a good boy and turn it off.
Well played.
Get out. Come on.
There. I deactivated the safety check.
It shouldn't bother you again.
Okay, good. I'll get the handcuffs.
Keep him close while we
continue to work on this.
Yeah, hurry up.
Here, you, sit.
Aah! What have you done?
Sarah, get back!
Chuck, no! Chuck!
Your hands are shaking.
That's how it begins.
You exposed both of
us? Why? Why would you do that?
Well, I developed this nerve
gas by testing it on myself.
It was a long, terrifying
process, but after a while, I gave in.
I surrendered to my insanity.
And now I'm not scared of anything. So...
What scares you, Chuck, hmm?
Everything! Everything! Everything!
Almost... Almost everything!
Make it stop. Make it stop. Somebody
turn it off. Turn it off.
Chuck, listen to me, it's all in
your head. You need to fight it.
I'm trying, but it's horrible.
This is exactly why I don't see scary
movies, and I stick mainly to the PG-13 region.
Let's go.
Come on.
If you get me out of here, I will
consider taking you to the antitoxin.
Anything. Anything you want.
Now I'm going to kill that bitch
Frost who double-crossed me.
No, no, I can't let that happen.
Did you just lock us in here?
- Oops.
- Oh... look who's the comedian now.
Chuck!
Sarah?
It's getting worse.
These are your deepest fears.
No, please make it stop!
There's no escape. We're
both locked in here.
No!
Come on, Casey, pick up.
Okay.
Our informant should be here soon
to give us an update on Project Isis.
This is so cool. "Our informant,"
that is so cloak-and-dagger.
I love it. What does that make me.
The inside man?
The mole?
You're the magnet.
The magnet. I love that. Yeah!
Spies have the coolest names.
Okay, what do you need the magnet to do?
You already look like a spy.
Now all I need you to do is stand
here by the Vic and act like one.
Yeah?
Done.
How was that?
Wonderful.
Boo! Found you.
Oh, look. Aisle of Terror.
An unfortunate place
for you to be trapped.
Now do you feel like
getting us out of here?
Aisle of Terror...
Images that can cause terror in even
the most... fearless... lunatics...
What the hell is this?
- Public showers?
- That's peculiar.
Reminds me of Professor
Schofield's work.
That hack. Thought he knew about fear.
A baby in a snail costume.
It... it is Schofield's
work. That's crazy.
Is it a baby... or a snail?
Old people.
Oh, get it out of my head!
Interspecies relations.
The terror.
The terror. It's... It's all flooding back now.
Black licorice!
Please, please make it stop!
Man feet! Otters!
This can't be happening.
Schofield!
- Chuck. Chuck, are you okay? What happened?
- No...
Sarah, I don't want to.
I... I don't want to see you like this
so I'm just going to keep my eyes
closed until we get the antidote. Okay?
- Okay, okay, bye.
- Let's get up. Come on.
Oh, God!
Give me your gun.
No, but it's not a real gun.
It's-it's just a heavily-modified
paint ball pistol.
Which I know paint ball's
still very, very dangerous,
but what I'm trying to explain
is that it's not real...
I'll take that folder.
Casey, Casey, what is going
on? Why is there a gun to my head?
I'm the magnet. I'm the magnet
for bad guys? Are you kidding me?
Come on, man. I can't believe you.
I cannot believe that you would bring
me here and use me as a human target.
- What nerve.
- Grimes...
No, no, no, I need to finish.
And this may sting, but
you need to hear it.
You, sir, are not very
thoughtful. Not one bit.
I mean, am I alone here? Well... yeah.
What, are you agreeing with
him? Whose side are you on?
- Can I go?
- Yeah, run along.
Oh, not cool, man. That is just not cool.
- You did good, Grimes.
- Really? Thank you.
- I tried to really kind of sink into
the role, you know, and... - Huh.
Oh, I know that "huh." Why.
What does it say?
Chuck's mom's story checks out.
She's totally clean.
Perfect.
Oh, that was not a fun trip.
Well, thank God we got Wheelwright
to give up that antitoxin
before he went completely
off the reservation.
Thank you, Sarah. You're
the greatest partner ever.
- Oh, my God.
- What?
My mom.
She left a message.
She wants to see Ellie tonight
before she goes back undercover.
I honestly thought Ellie
would never see my mom again.
Uh, I'll come with you.
No, no, no. Hey, I-I appreciate your
concern, Sarah, but trust me, it's my mom.
Hi, sis.
Brushing up on your vocab, huh?
I was just trying to get away
from Honey for a few minutes.
It's ironic, isn't it?
The mother that I wish would disappear
is here to answer all of my questions.
And the mother that I wish I could
talk to has disappeared forever.
Hey, Ellie, you, uh.
You got plans tonight?
What's with all the secrecy?
I needed to get away from Castle, in
case Grimes was hanging around.
If he knew the truth, he'd
go running to his BFF.
Everything about Bartowski's
mother's life is a fake.
Project Isis.
It ended 20 years ago when Frost went rogue.
So what, she's a double agent? She's
working directly for Volkoff?
I should have grabbed her before
she dropped off the map again.
What? What is it, Walker?
So what do we do when she
walks through the door?
I mean, part of me wants to be reserved.
Show her that I'm an adult
and I've been just fine since she left.
The other part of me
just wants to hug her.
Do whatever feels right.
- I'm gonna go take a look outside.
She might have got lost. - Okay.
Chuck.
Mom... No!
- Chuck!
- Stop! No! No! Let her go!
Stop! Stop! You have no
idea what's going on!
Your mom isn't the spy you think she is.
Sarah?
I'm protecting your blind spot.
Sarah!
Chuck, what is it?
Ellie, I'm sorry, but Mom is not coming.
Why does she keep doing this to us?
Because she's a spy.