Hi, I'm Chuck. Here's a few things
that you might need to know.
I'm the magnet for bad
guys? Are you kidding me?
I cannot believe that you would bring
me here and use me as a human target.
Everything about Bartowski's
mother's life is a fake.
I should've grabbed her before
she dropped off the map again.
My mom, she left a message.
She wants to see Ellie tonight
before sheoes back undercover.
- Chuck!
- No! No! Let her go!
Stop! Stop! You have
no idea what's going on.
You mom isn't the spy you think she is.
Ellie, I'm sorry, but Mom is not coming.
Why does she keep doing this to us?
Because she's a spy.
Colonel Casey, the Project Isis
file you discover was authentic.
Mary Bartowski, alias Frost, was a CIA
agent working undeover for Volkoff
until 20 years ago, when she turned
and we never heard from her again.
Agent Walker, you made the right
decision by bringing in Frost.
- Agent Walker?
- Walker.
Oh, uh, yes, General, what's the next step?
We're moving Frost to a
black site facility tomorrow.
That means no one is to see
her, especially Bartowski.
Agent Walker, I suspect I can
trust you to keep an eye on Chuck.
Of course, yes.
Good. How is he handling all this?
- Uh, he...
- He's fine, General.
Calm, actually. Very calm.
Calm?! How am I supposed totay calm?
Sarah, I had everything under control.
My mom was going to meet Ellie for
five minutes and then disappear forever.
I asked you trust me, and
you went behind my back.
Why is it so har for
you to believe in me?
- How was that?
- You were certainly passionate.
- But I wouldn't use the "F" word.
- I didn't.
- No?
- No.
Maybe just seemed that way
because you were so intense.
And didn't Sarah have proof that
your mom was working for Volkoff?
- Whose side are you on, buddy?
- Chuck, do I have to pick a side?
- Yeah.
- Then you...
Well, no. I don't... I don't know.
Sarah and I have never really
had a fight before, so...
Not-Not a real one, not like this.
Trust me. I'm going
through it right now myself.
- You and Alex?
- No. Me and Casey, actually.
So, I'm just... You
know, I'm taking some time.
Cool off, clear the old mechanm.
- You should do the same thing with Sarah.
- You're probably right.
I mean, it's certainly not getting me
any closer to proving my mom's innocence.
My dad spent his whole
life searching for her,
and there's nothing in here th can
help us prove she's not a traitor.
You're telling me. Holy cow!
This technology is ancient.
But we can clean her up a little bit
and sell her on Ebay. What do you think?
What, are you joking? Nobody's going
to buy a Phalanx XR-12 computer.
I mean the thing only
takes triangle-shaped disks.
- And this is everything, huh?
- What do you mean?
Well, ur father left
all this stuff for you,
but is there a possibility he might
have left something for Ellie, too?
What do you mean, left something?
I don't know. Information?
Something about Mom maybe.
You know, Dad used to send me those
coded messages in the classifieds,
but I haven't found anything
since before he passed away.
What is this about, Chuck?
I guess it's just all
this stuff with Mom.
I was hoping that Dad might
have left us some answers.
I wish that we knew both of them better,
but since the only person who can give
us answers is locked away in a CIA base,
it's not like we can just
waltz in there and ask her.
Right. No. Yeah, can't.
Tom, Jerry. Good to see you guys again.
Keep up the good work. Just keep
doing what you're doing, you know?
Have fun with it. That's
what I try to do, anyway.
Hey, Ginger.
Wow, Casey, a lot of new
faces down here, huh?
Huh? We should have a mixer or something.
You know, a little get-to-know-u.
We can exchange fake
names and backgrounds.
Okay, great. Good times.
Chuck?
Sneaking into your own home...
Morgan. How long have you
been hiding behind that door?
An uncomfortably long
time, actually, but-but that's not the point.
The point is this. You and Chuck
are in a relationship crisis.
Crisis? Did he say something to you?
Yeah, actually. He-He
told me everything. And...
I think he just needs
some time to cool off.
But he always wants to
talk about... anything.
What do you want me to say here? I mean, you
did go behind his back, have his mother arrested.
I was just trying to protect him.
Yeah. Ellie said the same thing.
He told Ellie, too?
You know, contrary to popular bief, we think that there
is a heart of gold underneath this cold exterior.
Morgan, please don't touch my chest.
Oh, gosh, yeah. No, I meant
that completely non-sexual.
You know what? This is ridiculous. Neither
of us should be sneaking around at all.
If I could just talk to
Chuck, everything woulde okay.
Where is he, anyway?
- You shouldn't be here.
- I need your help.
Why? CIA thin I'm a traitor.
Chuck 4x07 - Versus the First Fight
If I'm gonna help you, I need
the truth this time, okay?
Casey found a file that said that
Project Isis was abandoned 20 years ago,
you betrayed the CIA and
joined forces with Volkoff.
- Yes, that much is true.
- What?!
20 years ago, Volkoff had started to
suspect that I was working with the CIA.
He was one step away from
discoverying my real identity.
- That you're a Bartowski?
- That I was a mother.
So I did the only thing I could.
I admitted I was CIA, and I told
Volkoff I wanted to join him.
I broke all ties with the
agency, and I went to work for MI6.
Tell me who to call, and
I will fix all of this.
No, it's not that simple.
Volkoff has sources at the
CIA. That's why I had to leave.
A 20-year mission wille wast
if he gets wind of any of this.
But you can trust me.
You're not gonna tell
your girlfrid this time?
That's not gonna be too hard, considering we're in a
fight right now and not really on speaking terms.
Do you want to...
- talk about it, or...?
- No, that's okay. Thank you.
You think that being boyfriend and
girlfriend, she could trust me from time to time.
You know what? It doesn't matter.
Yes, I can keep it a secret.
Good.
There is one person at MI6 who can confirm
that everything I'm telling you is true.
His name is Gregory
Tuttle. He's my handler.
We have a preset meeting for today
at 2:00 at the Old Duke Tavern.
Go there and give him this
code. Per fas et nefas.
- Per fas et nefas? Per fas et nefas.
- Nefas.
- Okay. - Okay? It's the only way
he'll know he can trust you.
And Chuck, he doesn't
know that you're my son.
Nobody does.
Okay, I got it.
I'm sorry. The code one more time?
Babe, what is all this?
What are you doing?
I know that this sounds crazy, but what if my
dad did leave me a message in the classied ads?
Hon, I thought you decided months
ago that there was nothing here.
I know, but I just found
out that my mom is a spy,
and Chuck said something today.
This can't be just a coincidence.
Look, every day since he's passed away, there
has been an ad for a convertible Mustang.
Ell, if there was a hidden code
here, you would have found it by now.
I don't know. There's-There's
something about it.
For sale Ford mustang 1968.
Could it be my dad's last msage
to me? Something important?
Buy more.
Nerd herd.
- Hey.
- Yes?
Because I-I value our relationship, John, I
need to be frank with you.
- We are in a fight.
- Ok.
Really? Okay? That's all
you have to say to me?
My shift ended two minutes ago.
You lied to me, okay?
You never told me that the Project Isis file had proof that Mrs.
Bartowski was working for Volkoff.
Now, okay, you asked me to shadow
you to make me a better spy,
but how am I supposed to do
at if I'm always the magnet?
Or having to wait in a van? Or
being lied to by my partner and...
friend?
Hey. Hey, Morg, I'm so glad I found you.
Buddy, I need your help on
super top secret mission.
Do I get to parachute out
of a plane on a wild horse?
No, you do not, because nobody ever does.
But you do get to wear an earpiece.
Sold. Yeah.
Morgan, buddy, remember we're undercover.
A little subtlety goes a long way.
Copy that, Chuck.
Oh, Charles.
Okay, so, earpiece is in
place, and I believe is working.
- Yes? Hello? Hello. Check.
- Stop touching it.
By touching it, u're drawing attention
to the fact that you're wearing it, okay?
You are to be my eyes and ears on this.
I need you to sit at the bar unnoticed.
Tuttle can't know that anyone
came with me here. Ready?
Break.
Do me a favor.
Can you make out the board with the
specials from where you're sitting?
Okay, let me say it again. We're
undercover. We're not here to order food.
And these earpieces are not
for personal conversations.
I got you. Just remind me to tell
you what Sarah thought of your fight.
Sarah? You talked to
Sarah? What did Sarah say?
Wh-Wh-Whoa, what are you so
nervous about? It's fine.
I did all the talking, okay?
Kept it simple and concise,
and basically explained to her that by not believing
in you, she betrayed your trust and yo family.
Your words, not mine.
Morgan. Morgan, why would you...?
That was supposed to stay between us.
Yeah, okay. One second, buddy. Holon. Ow.
Ow. Ow. Sorry. Hold on one second.
This thing's not working right.
It's like...
One second, Chuck.
Oh, my gosh.
Cheers.
Just one.
I just have to...
I hate to make a scene.
But I'll rip your throat
out with this plastic fork
if you don't tell me who you are
and why you're wearing an earpiece.
Well, that certainly
would a scene, wouldn't it?
Okay, okay. Wait, wait, wait. Ha, ha.
You're Tuttle. You're Tuttle, right? You're
Tuttle, and I have a code word for you.
It's Latin, and it's...
What is it?
Just great. Now I need to dry this out.
I got it, I got it. Per fas et nefas.
Oh, thank God.
Frost sent you.
I just want to apologize for
questioning you in such a harsh tone
and-and of course for threatening
to rip out your throat.
I wouldn't even know how do that.
You seemed very convinng to me.
That's kind of you, but
I'm just a handler for MI6.
I'm not a trained field agent, you
know, field ready, as they say.
Okay, time's up, Matlock.
There's a limit, all right?
Let's go, dry it up. Polyester, so
it's really absorbent.
Good? Okay, thank you. Come again.
Wait. Why did Frost send you?
Where is she?
My name is Charles Carmichael.
I'm her ally at the CIA. I
have her in custody right now.
If she's in custody, then
Volkoff will be looking for her.
We don't have much time.
You'll start with whoever
she was last seewith.
Please don't tell me it was you.
Bloody hell.
Morgan... help.
Testing, testing. Chuck, I'm back.
We're back in
business, buddy. Let's just...
No. No, no, no. What?
You got to be kidding me.
I lost him.
Hello, Agent Carmichael.
May I call you Charles?
Sure, yeah, that's fine.
Are we on a plane?
Yes. Been kidnapped by
Volkoff's operatives.
Nasty buggers. They must
think we've got Frost.
What are you looking at?
Not that scar. Or that scar.
Neither one of those scars. Or
your, or your, or your mole, mole.
That is a beauty mark.
Which is what I meant
by-by "mole": beauty mark.
Tomato, tomato. You're so
stunning, I can't even look away.
You're going to tell me
what you've done with Frost.
And you're going to do it now.
- He doesn't know anything.
- And you do?
I... I know that if you use those tweezers,
on those rather large hairs in
your nostls, it would work wonders.
I mean, when was the last time
a man expressed interest in you?
Hmm? Be honest.
What are you doing?
Torture 101, my friend. I've
read every manual on the subject.
Weaken the enemy
emotionally, then take the power.
Just what could she possibly do
with those tiny little tweezers?
No, no, no, no, no! Please, stop! Stop, stop!
- I'll tell you everything you want.
- No, don't.
My home address is 17 Tally
Place. My dog's name is Kipper.
And I had my first sexual experience
watching Lawrence of Arabia.
I'm not proud of it. I.
I came from a broken home.
All I want to know is what
you've done with Frost.
You are going to regret that.
I think I already do.
Look, I-I don't know anything, all right?
One second Chuck was there, and
then he was just gone.
All right? We just did what
Mrs. Bartowski told us to do.
I don't understand why he keeps
trusting her. She just hurts him.
Not anymore. She's gonna
tell us what we want to know.
Yeah. Well, just let me...
That's why we keep you
in the van. You stay here.
Maybe I should try one
last thing from the manuals.
Please don't.
The Swedish slip. It actually worked.
And I didn't have to break my thumbs.
What do we do now?
Oh, cool. A tiny weapon stand-off.
En garde.
Hello there.
A little help here? Anything?
Here! Catch!
Enough. You're gonna tell
us where Chuck is now.
I want to see my daughter.
We're not having a discussion
about what you want.
Chuck came here this morning because
he trusted you, and now he's gone.
If he's with my
handler, I know he's safe.
All right, then why hasn't he called in?
Perhaps he doesn't want to see you.
Chuck told me about the fight.
Okay, listen. I can't protect your
son if I don't know where he is.
I am trying to protect him, too.
Which is why I am not saying
a word to either of you.
The only one I know
I can trust is my son.
Mrs. Bartowski.
Morgan Grimes?
- You...
- Wait.
I haven't seen you since
you were nine years old.
You want to know something? I haven't
had a decent Rice Krispy Treat since.
What are you doing here?
Kind of a long story, but the thing is,
it's a little bit my
fault that Chuck's gone.
So, if you could tell me where he is,
I'll make sure that they
give you want you want, okay?
I promise you, you will
get to see Ellie, but...
you have to tell us.
You can trust me, Mrs. B.
If you take me to see Ellie, I
will tell you where Chuck is.
We can't get in the cockpit.
You find any parachutes?
I found one.
Oh, Charles. Girlfriend's moving.
Hurry up. We got to
find another parachute.
There's not another
one. I looked everywhere.
What-What are we going to do?
I'm just taking the piss out of you.
Of course there's another parachute.
Whoever heard of a plane
carrying only one parachute?
There we go.
- You okay?
- Yeah.
It's just, it's so... thrilling.
It reminds me of that
great episode of Alias.
I loved that show.
- You ready?
- Yeah, as ready as I'll ever be.
Let's do something fantastic.
- What...?
- Charles. You're up.
How did we... How did we get here?
Well, it was really exciting until you
knocked yourself unconscious when we landed.
Luckily, I was able to get us
into the back of this sheep truck.
Well done. Well done. Well done. Where are we, uh.
Where are we going?
Well, this lot is going to the lamb chop
factory, so don't say anything abt mint sauce.
It's all right. I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
We are going to the City of Angels
to get the ntel that will clear Frost.
That's great news.
Now, I hope you don't mind me asking, but
why are you so intent on helping Frost?
I mean, You're not...
giving her one, are you?
Giving her one what?
Oh, giving-giving her one? No, no, no!
I would... I would ver give
her one. Simply just, no. no.
We have a very professional
relationship. You know?
- Plus, I have a girlfriend, anyway.
- Good for you.
Yeah, yeah. Good, yeah.
Good, normally. Usually, it's good.
It must be really hard being a field
agent and having a relationship.
Especially when she's a spy, too.
Well, that would bring I a
whole host of complications.
Tell me about it. You know? I an, we're
right in the middle of our first fight.
Oh, I don't mean to... Please.
No, I'd like to talk about it. You
see, it all began a few years ago...
Los Angeles 123.
She knows you're coming.
No.
Come in.
Eleanor.
I'm sorry, Ellie. I have to stay.
That's okay. I understand.
Lemonade?
That would be lovely. Thank you.
I'm sorry you have to see me like this.
Things are complicated right now,
but I wanted to see you, just you and me.
I don't know what I'm
ing with these coasters.
I don't... I don't even
use coasters. I don't...
It's okay.
You're all grown up.
I mean, I know that's obvious, but...
when I think of you, I still
see a gangly little girl,
too tall for her age,
unsure how she fits into her own skin.
Your dad and I used to take you for
drives in his burgundy '68 Mustang.
You would sit between us
with your legs curled up.
Do you remember?
I can't believe I forgot.
I remember, uh...
I remember those blue leather seats.
Your dad special ordered
those blue leather seats.
Watching you sleep in-between
us on those long drives
was one of my favorite things.
I just want to know what happened.
I want to know the truth.
I guess it all begins with a scientist.
His code name was Orion.
But his real name was Stephen Bartowski.
I wish that telling you that I did this
all for you and Chuck made a difference.
But I know it doesn't. And...
Sorry. We have to go.
Okay.
Thank you.
You kept your end of the
bargain. I'll keep mine.
I know you don't think I
care for my family, but I do.
If your MI6 handler actually
exists, tell him to bring Chuck here.
There's a relay station
that I call in to.
If my handler has posted his
location, I can take you there.
Once he sees me, he'll
know he can trust you.
Make the call. Let's go.
All the intel we need to
prove Frost's an MI6 agent
is on the series of disks
in that safety deposit box.
Sir?
There it is.
Babe, are you okay? I got
home as soon as I could.
How'd everything go with your mom?
She said something when we were talking.
She told me a-a story about an
old car that my dad used to have.
A 1968 convertible Mustang.
With blue leather seats.
This isn't a code, Devon.
This is a real car.
My dad must ***** Let's go get it.
Quickly.
- Chuck!
- Sarah?
What are you two doing here? I
thought Beckman gave you orders...
I thought you were in trouble.
Agent Frost. I'm so glad you're okay.
Tuttle. You have the disks?
Oh, yeah. We're halfway there.
These will prove that
I am not a traitor?
Yes, but there's a little problem.
These disks can only be
played on a special computer.
MI6 has got one in London.
Wait a minute. No, no, no, no.
These disks are for a
Phalanx XR-12 computer.
We don't have to go to London.
I know of one here, in L. A.
Well, then, what are we
waiting for? Let's go!
Frost isn't going anywhere.
Beckman's orders were clear.
I'm king her back to Castle.
No, no. Sarah, you can't. We're so close.
Everybody, on the ground! Now!
You got to be kidding
me. A bank robbery?
No, they're not bank robbers, Charles.
These are Volkoff's men.
Please. Nobody here wants to be a hero.
Just take the money.
Take whatever you want.
Just don't take our lives.
Keep your pants on. You're not my type.
And you're not who I
am looking for, anyway.
I don't understand. How
did Volkoff's men find us?
Well, somebody must have let them here.
Don't just accuse her.
No, he's right. They must
have followed Charles and me.
Just let him explain, really.
It'll make this fight you're
having seem like a little nothing.
Just like a blip on the radar.
Is there anybody you
haven't told about our fight?
Well...
man, they've got them surrounded in
there. Casey, what are we going to do?
Well, if we go in through the bank's
roof, we can surprise Volkoff's men.
Sweet. Give 'em hell, sir.
You coming?
I - I figured you wantede to
stay in the van. You know?
How you ever going learn anything
if you stay in here, hmm? Let's go.
Yes, sir. I forgive you, too, Casey.
I can't believe you've talked to
everybody about our fight except for me.
Let's go. Come on.
Listen, I was just waiting until
I calmed down a little bit.
Okay? It's our first
real fight as a couple,
and everyone knows that that sets
the tone for all future fights.
You're going to set the precedent by telling everybody
what you're thinking and feeling before me?
See, that just makes it sound bad.
Well, you might as well have just
posted about our fight on Friendster.
Friendster? Honey, people stopped
using Friendster five years ago.
Okay, fine. You know
what I'm talking about.
You know, you only just met him
and he knows everything about us.
How do you know that you can trust him?
That's right. I totally forgot.
You can't believe in anyone
unless Beckman tells you to.
That's not fair.
That's not fair? You wait a sec.
No. You know what's no
fair, is what you did.
You could have at least told
me before you arrested her.
Oh, what? And watch you
commit trson and go to prison?
Kids, kids. You need to stop this
now. We need to do something.
You're not doing anything.
I'll stay here, too, understand?
- Yeah, he's just a handler.
- Okay.
Okay, in ten seconds, we're
going to go over the counter.
There are two guys. I'm gonna take the
big guy. You're gonna take the small guy.
I'm perfectly capable of
handling a big guy, too, you know.
- Fine.
Ready.
This is exhausting.
Yeah, tell me about it. How do you
always fight the big guys all the time?
No, I mean fighting
with you is exhausting.
- I hate it.
- Me, too.
I've been thinking about you all day.
Just trying protect
you from getting hurt.
Behind you.
I don't need you to protect me.
I need you to believe in me.
I do believe in you.
I mean really believe in me.
Even when you think I'm wrong.
Two field agents in action!
What a show!
No!
Tuttle!
Oh, my God.
I'm so sorry, Charles.
It's up to you now.
No. No, no. No, no, no, Tuttle, we're
not leaving you here.
Casey, we've got a man
down; where are you?
I'll be okay.
Get those disks... to the
computer and finish it, Charles.
For Frost.
Okay, listen, Casey is on his way.
You're gonna be in safe hands, okay?
But we need to go right now.
Wait, what-what are you
saying? What about your orders?
I'm not gonna fight you
on this anymore, Chuck.
If you trust her, then...
that's gonna be enough for me.
You're gonna be just fine.
Let's go to Orion's space.
I guess I always assumed
your father sold the house.
How long has this been under here?
I - I really don't know.
I only found out about it after he...
It's his life's work, Mom.
The computer's right here.
You're welcome.
Just another day in the
life of a public defender.
Nobody move! Freeze!
No, no! Please, I have children.
Here, take... the keys to the vault.
My car key's on there, too.
I drive a very nice Cam.
Shut up. I'm a federal officer.
And I'm with him.
You should look into the roof. I
saw an eye-opening piece on asbestos.
Dangerous, dgerous stuff, and you
got it everywhere around here.
Grimes, Grimes, muzzle it.
Right. Shutting up.
Phalanx XR-12 Secure
System Reading Disk... 45%.
Looking for an injured agent.
- Where did he go?
- He's right over...
there.
Eurybia.
Disk empty 0
Files found.
This doesn't... make any sense.
This has got to be some
kind of misunderstanding.
The MI6 files are
supposed to be on here.
This... Mom!
Stay here.
Sar... Sarah?
Where'd you go?
Chuck.
Your father never
wanted you to see this.
See what?
What I know now of you is wrong.
Chuck? Get down.
What did you...?
Tuttle.
How are you here right...?
You were-you-you were...
You were shot. What are you doing here?
There is no Tuttle, Charles.
My name is Alexei Volkoff.
I believe you were looking for me.
What are you...?
Why are you doing this?
It's really pathetic.
Orion spent his whole life searching
for a woman who didn't want to be found.
The wife he wanted so much to believe
in was exactly what she appeared to be...
a traitor.
- You told him about...
- About my husband, of course.
And that he meant nothing to her.
You know, Charles...
it really is shocking how Orion was able
to convince you to follow in his footsteps.
What was he to you?
Your mentor?
He was a good man.
He was a fool.
Just like you, Charles.
If you'd just let it alone, none of
this ruse would have been necessary.
But you couldn't let it go.
I had my reasons.
I'm sure you did.
Frost here is a master of deception.
But she wasn't able to fool
your girlfriend, was she?
And you...
when you locked up Frost, it became clear I
had to step in to find Orion's little base here
and destroy all his intelligence.
Along with all the people
who know about it, of course.
Thank you for leading us here, Charles.
I couldn't have done it without you.
I believed in you.
Don't take it personally.
There's no point in going to
the grave with regrets, is there?
Frost...
Ready.
Protect him.
Shall we finish this?
Apologies.
It really was a easure
getting to know you.
You were right about her the whole time.
I couldn't see it. I didn't...
I didn't want to see it.
Flash! Come on!
Flash!
Sarah, my mom did something
to me with that device.
Chuck, your mom gave us a way out.
She might be working for Volkoff,
but she certainly has a reason for
not wanting us to die right now.
- Come on. Hurry, let's go.
- Wait, what about my father's work?
No, we don't have time. Let's go.
Chuck... Chuck, are you okay?
Sarah, *****.
And now, All of my father's research...
everything he ever created...
it's all gone.
He said it would be
outside waiting for us.
It really is my dad's car.
I can't lieve it's been
here this whole time.
Babe, it's beautiful.
Eleanor.
"Eleanor, if you're reading this,
"then it means I'm not with you anymore.
"And I know you'll be okay.
"I only wish I could have
been the father you deserved,
"but our family had a lot of secrets...
"secrets I kept from you
because you were so young,
"because I didn't want to hurt you.
"I know you're a grown woman now,
"but no matter what, you'll
always be my little girl
curled up on the middle
seat of this car."
"This is my final gift to you, Eleanor,
"and I'm giving it to
you now for a reason.
"I trust that you'll know what to do.
I love you, always.
Dad."