They say it's a personality thing...
but to me, a martini's got gin,
not vodka.
Some folks like chocolate.
I'll take vanilla.
I say baseball over football.
And to me, man's best friend
doesn't bark or fetch a ball.
See, personally, I like cats.
Meet my Clandestine Attack Team.
Better known as the CAT Squad.
Meow.
They were the best spy team
in the business.
The year, 2003.
The girls:
Cold-hearted Carina.
Zondra, the bitch!
Amy, the party girl.
And...
my pride and joy...
Sarah Walker.
Go get them, CATs.
Meow!
Buddy. Buddy, hey.
You still with me?
Yeah. Yeah. No. I just...
Your description of the CAT Squad
has sent me into fantasy land.
Don't wanna think
about what goes on there.
According to the CIA,
the CAT Squad was badass.
I hope they're tight,
because I'm running dry...
trying to find Sarah's friends
for our engagement party.
Really? Um, here's a crazy notion.
Ask Sarah.
Yeah, uh, not such a wild notion. It's just
that she's being very reluctant to help.
She's got a complicated relationship
with her family.
She's lost touch with friends.
But I know she'd want someone there.
So I'm nudging, being a good fiancé.
I'm trying to help fix things.
Got it. Good.
Good for you. Where do I come in?
Well, uh, Carina was one of the CATs.
"Carina" Carina?
- So I need her info.
- Chuck.
Carina? Really?
I mean, Alex is gonna be there.
Alex, Carina. Carina, Alex.
Two of my lovers in the same place?
Here's her phone and e-mail
and Facebook alias.
We're friends. Restricted.
I can't post or view pictures.
Go easy on her. Break this whole
Alex thing to her gently.
Carina's a delicate girl.
Walker in a white dress? Please.
But the CATs...
- Interesting.
- What?
My old spy partner's getting hitched.
Her fiancé wants to get
the old team together.
Nice.
- Hello?
- Amy, Walker's getting married.
- Oh, my God! Oh, my God!
- Stop screaming.
How do we find Zondra?
Hi, Sarah.
Hey. Heading out?
Yes, to the in-laws.
Devon's packing up the car. We're doing
a little overnight for the grandparents.
But we'll be back with plenty of time
for your party.
How's the invite list coming?
Done. I thought.
I told Chuck that I didn't
really have anyone to invite...
but he has this big idea now
that he wants to discuss with me.
- Oh, boy.
- Yeah.
I'm excited for the party,
but digging into the past...
old friends and family, it's, um...
It's a bit complicated for me.
- And Chuck just dives right in.
- Head first.
I could talk to him.
No, I should probably try
and get over the terror...
that I'm feeling right now.
Sarah, if you ever need to talk
about complicated family situations...
wedding stuff, anything,
you can come to me.
Thank you. I appreciate that.
It does feel good to talk about it.
Anyway, have fun.
Well, not likely, but thank you.
We having company?
Oh, no, not we. You.
CAT Squad.
The CAT Squad.
- Wow, I, um, didn't see that one coming.
- Well, I thought it'd be fun.
Heh. I mean, your old team.
One could be a bridesmaid,
or maid of honor.
I haven't seen them in a very long time,
and I've changed a lot.
I think that we should have
talked about this.
This could open a Pandora's box.
- Really? How?
- Well, first of all, Carina?
She was the mellow one.
Oh, so you were a little wild
back in the day.
Hey. Hey, hey, Sarah.
I get it. I do. I get it. You're nervous.
I was terrified when I went...
searching for my mom,
but look how that paid off.
It's just... You don't really know
what to expect with this team.
Yoo-hoo, Sarah Walker.
- Oh, no.
- "Oh, no," what?
What's going on?
Is it Close Encounters?
Is this really happening?
There's our girl.
- It's my ex.
- Heard you were getting married.
- You know what that means.
- Girls' night out.
- I'm Chuck, by the way.
- Buckle up, girl. We're going for a ride.
We'll have her back by 12.
Midnight is very sensible.
Ha! Try noon tomorrow, lover boy.
Maybe.
Hello, Carina. You look well.
Morgan. Remember my...? Morgan?
Something's different about you.
I am trying a new cologne.
So that might be, uh...
Let's go.
I think she remembered me.
Sarah was right.
I honestly wasn't expecting that.
Chuck 4x15 - Versus the Cat Squad
Sarah?
Head hurts.
You're very dressed up for bed.
Yeah. We went to a club in Hollywood...
and then another one in Vegas...
and then an after-hours spot
in Miami.
Who knew that Mikhail Gorbachev
could dance so well?
I guess reconnecting
wasn't such a bad idea, was it?
- It was okay.
- Okay?
Well, okay is good. Okay is a start.
- Springboard.
- Oh, Chuck.
You saw your friends
and you had fun.
- The band's back together again!
- No, the band is not back together again.
- Why?
- Look, some of us don't trust each other.
Well, maybe you should just have a
quiet coffee and some conversation.
No, look.
We were on a long-term mission...
and the target
kept anticipating our next move.
Something wasn't right in the team,
so I swept our equipment for bugs...
and I found a hidden transmitter
in the heel of Zondra's boot.
She denied it was hers,
and she passed a lie-detector test...
and we shook on it, and we decided to
let it go, but it stirred some bad feelings.
Well, honey,
if the CIA cleared Zondra...
then it's gotta be
some misunderstanding.
Right? Time can heal those.
Margaritas don't hurt, either.
I'm working on a new recipe for the party.
Engagement parties
are not the Squad's cup of tea.
They're leaving when they wake up.
- The CAT Squad? They're here?
- Mm-hm.
Yeah. They were too tired
to find a hotel room.
Sarah, where is Carina?
Hi. Good morning.
What are you doing here?
There was nowhere else to go
except the floor.
- But the floor can be fun too, hmm?
- What? No. Get... Stop.
That was sultry.
You were just sultry there.
And are you na...? Are you na...?
- Are you hitting on me?
- Something is different about you.
The confidence, straight spine.
Can't be true, but you're behaving like
you're having regular sexual intercourse.
Martin, get back in this bed.
No. No. All the times
that I e-mailed you...
and snail mailed, texted,
called out into the night. Nothing.
You completely ignored me.
And now I'm off the market, okay?
So I would like you to leave.
I have a lot of work to...
Chuck! Chuck!
That woman is an animal, okay?
And I will be back when she's gone.
This is ridiculous.
Well, that is a snazzy outfit.
Hey. Hi. What brings you by here?
Breakfast.
- You forgot.
- Here's the thing.
I was helping Chuck surprise Sarah.
She has old work friends in town
for this engagement party.
Just old hens, and I just got caught up
trying to help...
and be the good friend, and I'm sorry.
- Let's just reschedule.
No. Two seconds,
I'm out of this fashion statement...
and I'm gonna be ready to go.
I'll meet you...
You starting the French toast?
Chuck said you would.
None of us can cook.
Oh, hi. Um, I'm Carina.
Okay. Carina, this is Alex.
This is my girlfriend.
Beautiful girlfriend.
And this is, um, one of Sarah's...
- Old hens.
- Right. Ha-ha-ha.
Well, it looks like you have
been enlisted to cook.
Yeah, as in now. We are starving.
Oh, okay. Excuse... Easy, easy.
Back inside, you. Off you go. Ha, ha.
The draft will be the death of you.
Ha, ha.
Whoa. Heh.
I'm sorry, okay? You look beautiful,
and I feel like a jerk.
Lunch tomorrow, okay?
- Sure.
- Heh, heh.
And don't worry. Morgan, I trust you.
Thank you. Well, and I know your dad.
And I trust you.
Right.
Now, that seemed like a threat.
I bet you CATs have some wild stories
from your CAT Squad-ing days, huh?
- They're top-secret.
- Are they?
We could talk about our mission
to Reykjavik. The sulfur baths?
- The floating massages.
- Don't you guys miss it?
Running around together?
- I guess.
- Sometimes.
But I also like working one-on-one.
Hey, what's up?
Anybody want some more bacon?
Anything? Nothing?
Hey, remember Pyongyang?
That dissident we broke out of jail?
All those shots
of snake's blood afterwards.
That was you and Sarah.
You guys made an amazing team.
I learned so much from you
and had fun.
I think about it a lot.
I've been on a number of missions
myself, actually, yeah.
My first one, I had to disarm
this explosive device...
using Internet pornography. So...
Wow.
This Chuck, quite a catch.
- He's all right.
- He certainly is.
Okay, well, girls, it was good to see you.
Sarah, gotta catch a flight.
- Me too. Got room on your bike?
- Yep.
I better go too. Take me?
- Sure.
- Good.
The CATs certainly pack an attitude,
and Zondra is an acquired taste...
but I do think
it's good you reconnected.
I'll miss you. Congratulations.
- I'm gonna miss all you guys. Text me?
- Yeah.
- Okay.
- Come on, girl, let's ride.
- It wasn't all bad, but I'm glad it's over.
- Walker. Good luck with, uh, that.
Keys?
Baby steps, right?
And no more surprises.
Carina.
Carina? Carina?
I'll call an ambulance.
Please.
Carina, your leg!
It's part of the bomb.
Uh...
Ladies, who's Augusto Gaez?
Augusto Gaez is the arch nemesis
of the CAT Squad...
and leader of the Gentle Hand.
The bomb fragments trace
to his factory in Rio.
He tracked you down.
Excuse me, general, the "Gentle Hand"?
Are these bad guys,
or a massage parlor?
They're brutal killers.
Terrorists for hire.
You want your competition blown away,
that's who you call.
We hunted the Gentle Hand for years,
but we could never pin down Gaez.
Every time we got close,
he slipped away.
He must have thought we reunited
to come after him.
And tried to kill you on American soil.
CATs, the mission is in from Langley.
Capture Gaez and extradite him
back to the States for trial.
I'm happy to hunt Gaez
with Chuck and Casey...
Langley said all available hands.
Carina, due to your injury...
you will monitor the mission
and provide support from Castle.
Chuck and Casey,
you're shadowing the CATs.
It's Carnival in Rio.
Gaez will throw a big party,
he does every year.
It'll be guarded,
but I'm sure we can find our way in.
- I love it.
- General, we're not a team anymore.
This comes from the top, Sarah.
The CATs are back.
So, hey, Rio.
Sun, sand, that's good, right?
You know that tracking device
I found in Zondra's boot?
We were on a mission
to nail Augusto Gaez.
You think that Zondra's working for Gaez,
that she planted the bomb?
- The government cleared her name.
- Yeah, we'll see.
Yes?
The CAT Squad is on their way to Rio.
Excellent.
The plan is going perfectly.
We're going on a mission again.
CAT Squad high-five.
- You guys are zero fun.
- Hey, Sarah. I have an idea.
I know that you have good intentions...
but can we ease up on the ideas?
This is solid, hear me out.
I'm gonna be stuck in a van with Casey...
which gives me time to review the CIA
files on both the CAT Squad and Gaez.
Run them through the old computer.
If Zondra turns out to be a double agent,
we take her down.
If she turns out innocent, you can be
friends and reconnect in a real way.
Maybe I can help you fix this.
It doesn't matter whether I have
friends at my engagement party.
I'm talking big picture here.
I'm talking you engaging with your past.
- Okay.
I can just see that little hamster wheel
turning in your head, Walker.
- All I'm thinking about is nailing Gaez.
- Hmm.
You make sure you keep
your paws out of my boot heels.
- Oh, you wanna start that again?
- Yes, I do.
Hey, hey. Cool it, CATs, hmm?
You rang, Casey?
Is it hot in here, or is it me?
Carina's assigned to Castle.
Make sure she has IT support,
food, whatever she needs.
No, no, listen to me, I can't be alone
here with that woman, okay? She...
She wants me. Badly.
John, she desires my physical person.
And I'm hunting unicorns.
You're babysitting. Get over it.
I have intel on Gaez's party.
He'll be at Cabaret Soco Na Garganta.
Near the Sambadrome.
The only question now is,
how do we breach security?
Disguise or commando entry?
Guys? Ha, ha.
Duh! It's a party.
How do Brazilian spies
work with all this noise?
We're in the club. Do you have the signal?
Camera's up.
No sign of Gaez.
He won't show till later.
I know his habits.
I've been keeping tabs on the Hand.
Convenient.
- We can cover more ground if we split up.
- I'm not comfortable with you on your own.
I'm not sure I care.
Oh. Good.
This is a hornets' nest.
Let's just do our job.
You know, CIA's gone over that
a hundred times.
Findings were inconclusive. Get over it.
Eight years ago the CATs got yanked
into a Gentle Hand mission in Milan...
but Gaez escaped before the girls
ever made it to Italy.
I figured out that Gaez was tipped off
from a CIA safe house inside Milan.
If I can prove that Zondra
wasn't in said safe house...
maybe Sarah will be able to trust her.
- You know, I used to be like you.
Wanted to fix everything.
Not now.
Grimes suggested
I approach Alex's mom.
I was tempted at first, but...
she's moved on. So...
Didn't need her life disrupted, and...
I let it lie.
I've spotted Gaez.
He's surrounded by muscle.
He's heading into the VIP room.
We can get the layout...
from Chuck and Casey.
I'm not here to discuss anything
past your needs, which have been met...
so I'm gone.
- My needs have not been met.
You're upset I never called you back.
Look, I'm sorry. Get over it.
Oh, I'm over it, sweetheart.
Yeah, yeah. And I'm with someone.
Some... Oh, the girl at the door.
So, uh, you've told her you love her?
Yeah, of... Pfft.
No. No. But I was going to, and then
her father got thrown from a roof.
I plan to do it very soon...
and I just... What...?
- So it's not even serious.
Look...
Excuse me. It's Alex.
Oh, she's at the Buy More.
Listen to me, I have to go.
Uh-uh, you're staying. You don't like it,
take it up with General Beckman.
You gotta be kidding me.
So you're at the Buy More
and I'm not.
No. You do not appear to be.
Yeah, yeah,
and I don't think that's gonna...
change soon,
because I got shanghaied...
into babysitting this injured agent.
Oh, ahem. So you're, um...
You're canceling on me again?
You're needed.
- Now.
- Uh, one sec. One second.
Would you pl...?
Yeah. I'm afraid so.
But I am gonna make it up to you.
Dinner, movie. I owe you...
so huge.
- Yes, you do owe me.
I will be in touch.
Thank you, thank you, thank you.
Mwah, mwah, mwah.
If you're done slobbering, Grimes,
there is a problem in Rio.
Um, can I asks you a question?
Your insurance paid up?
- Ready?
- Yeah, I'm ready.
I'm ready!
Chuck, Casey. NSA monitored a call
from Burbank to Gaez yesterday.
- Gaez knows the CATs are coming.
- It's a trap, guys. Abort now.
Sarah, you have to get out of there.
It's been a long time, CATs.
Drop your weapons or die.
All these years.
Enemies.
Fighting each other.
- Such a waste, no?
- You're the bad guy.
That's how it works.
Says who?
Why can't we work together?
That's why we're here? A sales pitch?
The worldwide market for the Gentle Hand
has blown wide open.
I need skilled operatives
who can open a door with a fist.
Or a smile.
Kitty, kitty, kitties.
You have been lured here
to accept a career...
with the Hand.
Or I'll bury you on Mount Corcovado.
Casey. They're tied up.
Five guards, all armed.
I'm gonna use the Intersect
to capture Gaez.
Just gonna drop down
out of the sky, hero?
Overcompensating because you got
your girlfriend's car blown up?
- That's not true.
- Sit tight till I give you the signal.
You only have a tranq gun.
A career in the Hand?
With you and who else?
Because you've already got one of us,
don't you?
Do I, Sarah?
- Why don't you let her finish?
- Why don't you shut up?
No, I would like the air cleared.
- Sarah, let's just get out of this alive.
- No.
Let her say my name.
Offer me up, Walker. Accuse me out loud
instead of under your breath...
- ...like you've been doing for years.
- That's what you've been doing.
Telling people that I put
the tracker in your boot?
The suspense is a killer, no?
Maybe it's not tough Zondra.
Maybe sweet Amy.
Suspicious.
But so is Sarah Walker...
the kitty who doth protest too much.
It's not me.
I've got no intention of joining up.
If you plan to kill us,
you may as well tell the truth.
I think that's fair.
I'd rather just kill you.
Casey? This just got ugly.
You're done. Do you wanna live,
or do you wanna die?
Keep cool.
- We are all keeping cool.
- You tell me what I wanna know...
or you're the one getting buried
on Mount Corcovado.
Okay.
- The name is...
- Yeah?
Okay.
- I think Sarah needs help.
- I'll tell you.
Hey. Hey! Wait!
I need immediate extraction.
Anyway you can. Plane, boat, car.
How about fist?
I've got Gaez. Let's get out of here.
- Ugh.
- Wait.
He was about to tell me
the name of the mole.
Now that he's in custody,
he'll never talk.
I was just... I was helping.
I was helping.
- Look at all the bad guys I tranq'd.
- I don't need help with my job.
I don't need help with my past,
so stop okay?
I don't need help!
No, no, no!
I deserved that.
Excellent work in Rio,
in spite of the hiccups.
But, Sarah, you were right.
- There's a traitor in the CATs.
- You know who my money's on.
- Thought that Carina had a shifty look.
- How well do you know Amy?
Is anyone really that perky?
Conjecture and ill will do not
make a case for treason. We need facts.
Until we have them,
I want the CATs to stay in Castle.
Casey, interrogate Gaez for the mole.
You're dismissed.
I have a job for you.
Attention, shoppers.
Buy More will be closing in five minutes.
Hello, beautiful.
Do I have the night of nights planned
for you. First of all, we are...
What? What?
Lipstick on your collar?
- Oh, that dirty little...
- Whose lipstick is it?
The wounded agent?
Miss French-Toast?
She rubbed it in to sabotage our date.
She has the soul of a bridge troll.
I really wanna believe you, Morgan,
but you have been acting so strange.
And three times in a row?
That is asking a little too much.
Okay. Oh, yes. Oh, but, Alex... Alex.
But you trust me, remember?
Do I?
The CATs left their luggage.
There might be another tracking device
and I don't want anything leading home.
Sounds like you're
trying to get rid of me.
Look, I know I screwed up, Sarah.
Okay, fine. I did some analysis
on the CATs' failed mission to Milan...
and it seems very suspect.
It's not conclusive.
But if we can figure out
who was in Milan...
You're still helping. Stop. Now.
No. Sarah. But...
Hey, Walker.
I'm not running anywhere.
You know what? In fact,
I am sick and tired of pussying around.
So why don't we settle
this old-school?
Toe-to-toe.
Yeah, let's do it.
Still got that jab, Walker.
- Yeah?
- Mm-hm.
You want some more?
Got some questions for you, Gaez.
What is she here for?
- Muscle.
- I thought it might be fun.
Ouch.
Shall we begin?
I have never even heard of an
organization called the Gentle Hand.
I'm a businessman.
Yeah. Business of terror.
Built a fortune, killed a lot of men.
But that all ends now.
I'm not the traitor.
I didn't plant that tracker.
- Neither did I.
- Where'd it come from?
- You were the only one in Milan.
- I was never in Milan.
I was supposed to be, but I got
an anonymous call to stay put in Paris.
We need to disc...
You're just gonna primp
the whole time?
- One of us had to have been in Milan.
- Carina was in the U.S.
I read it in Chuck's report.
That leaves...
Amy.
- Traitor.
- Yeah.
So what? I paid for it.
Acting like the world's biggest dope.
Wearing stupid sexed-up costumes
to fight world crime.
Now I have everything
I ever dreamed of...
except it is a little lonely.
- Join me.
- Go to hell.
I know where you live, Walker. You even
think of trying to find us, remember...
there's a target on your back.
You, Chuck, the sister with the baby.
Don't forget.
Chuck.
Think about making two trips?
Not really my style.
How's the reunion going?
Doesn't everybody want their
friends and family around?
Wouldn't you have been
disappointed...
if there hadn't been one friend
or family member at your wedding?
Yeah. But maybe Sarah
sees the world differently.
I just wanna make her happy,
and everything I did backfired.
Chuck, you bend over backwards
to help people.
It's one of the reasons
that you're so easy to love...
but sometimes the best thing
you can do is just take a step back.
Be understanding.
- You don't have to fix everything.
- So I blew it?
Bigtime. But I'm pretty sure
she still loves you.
Where is she? Where is she?
Okay, I don't know what it's gonna take to
get it through that thick spy skull of yours.
You need to understand
you are not the only game in town.
I am in love with somebody else.
- You are angry.
- You're damn right.
I'm through with you,
I'm through being your slave.
Wow, you're so worked up.
- I guess you really do love her, huh?
- You guess? You...?
You're supposed to be an
intelligence officer, and you guess?
Well, you haven't said it to her.
I just figured.
You figured wrong, all right?
Although, I really should tell her.
I do love her.
Aw.
Oh, shut up.
I'm gonna go get her back.
- You need anything, you can go to hell.
- Marty, don't move!
Marty. Here we... It's Morgan!
How many times do I got...?
Sorry, puss. Sleep time.
Come on, Chuck, pick up.
- Sarah, I am the idiot of the century.
- Chuck, Amy just escaped with Gaez.
- She's the traitor. Where are you?
- The Buy More. The store is closed.
- Where are you?
- Locked in Castle...
trying to override the system.
Gaez and Amy are headed your way.
They're in the elevator.
Okay, listen. Do not try and fight them.
Just hold tight and we'll be right there.
There's no time for that. Just stay
by the monitors and spot them for me.
Lockdown engaged.
- He's a dead man.
- Well, he's got a plan.
At least, I think he does.
My God, is he shopping?
What's he doing?
They're following you.
You've got 10 seconds.
Well, can I just take these 10 seconds
to apologize for being such a fool?
Chuck, now's not the time.
Chuck?
Give us the key to the store
and we're gone for good.
You're no match for us
and you know it.
We don't wanna hurt you, but we will
certainly enjoy doing it if we have to.
- Talk to me, Sarah. Where are they?
- They're at the Nerd Herd desk.
I wanna say that I have no intention
of opening up any more cans of worms...
or Pandora's boxes or anything else.
I want you to be happy.
- Concentrate on getting out alive.
- Be easier...
- ...if you'd consider forgiving me.
- No time. They're headed your way.
I don't like fighting girls.
What I mean is,
I was taught to be a gentleman.
Going somewhere, pussy?
Small price to pay
to find the real traitor.
Yeah, took us long enough.
I'm sorry.
I should have never
jumped to conclusions.
Me neither.
- It cost us a lot of years.
- Yeah.
We could try to make up for it.
We were good friends.
Yeah, I miss that.
Well, there is, uh, this engagement party.
- I'll be there.
- Me too.
- I have an apology to make.
- I would love to have you guys.
At the wedding too, if you can make it.
Maybe you could be bridesmaids?
I've never been a bridesmaid.
Well, pretended to once for a mission.
I did too, once, but there was
a machine gun under the pink taffeta.
- Oh. Ha, ha.
- Ha, ha.
Well, maybe we can try it for real
this time.
- No machine guns.
- Scary, but I'll give it a shot.
- All right.
- Okay.
Hey.
- Can I just...?
- Chuck, no more apologies.
I wanna say thank you.
I'm glad that the girls are here tonight.
They'll be here for the wedding.
I'm just not ready
to dive into my past right now.
Yeah. No way. Nuh-uh.
And my family...
Well, there's no misunderstanding
to straighten out, really.
I know that it's complicated.
I totally hear you. I do.
And I'm done helping out.
No, Chuck,
please don't ever stop helping me.
There are a thousand ways that I need
your help every single day...
and you're perfect.
Well, then I'll stick to those.
- Let's party.
- Let's do it.
I wanna start.
- Okay.
- We're...
We're done. It's not that I think
you were unfaithful, I just...
I mean, leggy girls...
getting half the truth...
I don't fit into this world.
I can count the amount of
special relationships I've had...
on half of one hand.
- Me too.
Then why don't I feel special, Morgan?
I just feel lied to.
I'm sorry.
No, hold on. Wait, wait, wait.
Hear me out, okay?
The reason I kept Carina
a secret from you is because...
I didn't know how to handle you
running into someone I'd had a...
relationship with.
To be honest,
there have been so few, that...
it was damn near
a statistical impossibility.
I mean...
I want you to know something, though.
Nothing happened between us...
because nothing means more to me
than this relationship.
I'd never do anything
to threaten that. Ever.
I love you.
I am in love with you.
Like, for real, "I love you"?
Oh, for real I love you, I love you.
I love you too.
But you cannot do this.
I won't. I promise.
I think I owe you an apology.
- I acted like a real...
- It's okay.
He loves me.
Hey. This is lovely.
Oh, I'm so glad that you think so.
I'm really happy to be here in a dress
and having a little wine.
So...
What's on your mind?
Oh...
Must be hard being here
without your family.
Yeah, well, I'm...
I don't know where my father is...
and I have a very strained relationship
with my mother, so it's...
- Complicated?
- Yeah.
How about you and I talk about this?
We can get Chuck involved later.
That would be great. Thank you.
- We're practically family, right?
- Yeah, ha, ha.
- More importantly, we're friends.
- Yeah.
Well, I have a question for you.
I was wondering if you would be
my maid of honor.
- Seriously?
- Yeah.
Oh, I would love to. Of course.
Aw, who says CATs can't play nice?
You never know. Maybe we'll add
another member to the Squad.