Hi, I'm Chuck. Here are a few
things you might need to know.
Wait, wait.
Vivian Volkoff is trying to kill me?
It appears she's going after the man
who took down her father.
Bad news. Ellie's been working
on your dad's computer.
My dad was trying to figure out a way...
to input knowledge into the brain
without having to learn it.
Replace the computer's hard drive
with a blank one when Ellie's not looking.
I'm great, Mom, you know?
Uh, she's sleeping
halfway through the night.
And Devon has that
breast-feeding simulator...
so I'm fine.
You know I love babysitting my
granddaughter, but I am a trained spy.
What gives?
I didn't wanna say anything
until I had any solid conclusions but...
Is that your father's old computer?
Yeah. I found it
underneath the seat of his Mustang.
I had a major breakthrough
a few days ago...
and then I found thousands of pages
that I've never seen before, all labeled X.
How far into them are you?
Not very.
But there's references in here...
to you and Dad and this Agent-X.
Do you know anything about this?
No. Did you happen to run this
by your brother?
No. I don't want Chuck involved.
I mean, obviously,
this has to do with Dad's spy life.
Look at this.
This Intersect project? Downloading
information into the human brain.
This is amazing stuff.
I've never heard of it.
Do you think that Dad had the Intersect
running with this Agent-X?
I really don't know, honey.
I don't know.
All right.
I'm gonna go give Clara her bottle.
I'll be back.
Stephen, what did you do?
Eddard, you don't let your kids
keep a dire wolf.
That's a terrible idea.
- Are you ready to head out?
- Hmm? Mm-hm.
Will you sign these when you get
the chance? Just wedding prep docs.
Mm-hm.
"Prospective husband,
prospective wife.
Legally binding, prenuptial..."
- Prenup?
- Post-it notes on the signature pages.
- Go in. I'll get a ride from Morgan.
- Didn't shower this morning?
Just the body. Not the hair.
So now I feel dirty, smelly, European.
Okay, okay. Uh...
- I will see you there.
- Great.
Prenup?
Jeez, I thought things were going
so well.
It was. Is.
She's just taking precautions.
Half of all marriages go down.
Well...
it's good to see
yours is going so well.
Hilarious. But you know what?
It works.
So you.
Spending a little money on the side?
Gambling debts I don't know about?
Of course not. You know me.
I don't know why she'd do this.
Something has got
your girl's dukes up, okay?
Get the facts.
- Smaller bites, please.
- Don't henpeck.
You overanalyze everything, Bartowski.
You talk every issue to death.
It's exhausting.
I'm exhausted just sitting here.
Wow, I really do that?
Spies have secrets. If you're gonna take
it to the next level with Walker...
you have to understand that.
Sign the papers. Be cool.
Yeah, Chuck. Be cool.
Be cool.
It's kind of new territory
for me, honestly. Cool.
Good advice.
I'm gonna get out of here
before I'm scarred for life.
Mail call.
Thank you, sir.
Me. Me.
Alex's return address.
Looks like an invite.
- No. Love letter, I think.
- Invite.
What is it, Grimes? Spill.
An invite to Alex's graduation.
Look, she desperately wanted
to invite you, all right?
But technically, in her mother's eyes,
anyway, you are still sort of...
Well, mostly dead.
She just can't.
Stupid of me to think otherwise.
Duty calls.
Team, as you know,
the bombs planted in Castle...
had Volkoff parts and design.
Langley has tagged Vivian Volkoff
as the responsible party.
- They put out a kill order.
- Off parts? What?
- Two men dead, Bartowski.
- But it could be a rogue...
in Volkoff's organization.
- Look, I've spent time with Vivian.
She's not a cold-blooded killer.
Just give me a chance to persuade her
to come in.
- She worked for us, we owe her that.
- We don't owe her.
I'll compromise.
Set a meet with Vivian.
Casey, prep a sniper team.
She gets hostile, take her down.
Roger that.
No matter how much you believe in this
broad, remember, she's still a Volkoff.
Don't let him get to you.
He's just being Casey.
Sure. No, it's cool.
I know I sprung those papers on you
this morning.
So, uh, I assume
you wanna talk about it?
No.
Prenup. Signed, sealed, delivered.
So we better gear up, huh?
I'm in position.
She makes one wrong move, I take the shot.
Look, Chuck, a prenup doesn't mean
the end of our marriage.
Well, look, hey, you're a spy and spies
have secrets they need to protect. Cool.
No. I don't keep secrets from you.
- It's just, uh, family stuff.
- Got it. Done.
Yeah. Cool.
Heads up. Here they come.
Okay.
I'm here
in the middle of nowhere. Why?
The Volkoff bombs were planted
in Castle.
Two men died
and the CIA holds you responsible.
I'd never do that. I'm a businesswoman.
I'm trying to make Volkoff Industries...
into a legitimate enterprise.
I gave a list
of every black market agent...
I swept out all the operatives.
I even brought you something.
From an arsenal
of my father's weapons.
- What is it?
- I don't know.
Look, I want nothing to do with
my father's world. Do you trust me?
- Snipers! Hit the ground!
- Casey, stand down. Stand down.
It's not us. I don't know who it is.
I can't pinpoint the shooters.
Snipers? This is a setup?
What? No, no, no. Wait, wait, wait!
Vivian, wait!
- No, this isn't us.
- Go, go, go.
Unh! I trusted you!
How could you do this to me?
- Aah!
- Vivian!
We couldn't determine the source
of the shot. It wasn't us.
- And the weapon Vivian offered up?
- It's not in the Intersect...
and we can't figure out what it does.
- It proves nothing. The kill order stands.
Okay, hang on.
What if she was being straight with us...
and it is a deadly weapon?
That enough to recall her kill order?
And who exactly is going to give us
that intel?
There's only one man who can tell us.
Unfortunately, he's also
the most dangerous man in the world.
It's true.
I cut in front of William
in the cafeteria line.
I admit, I...
have entitlement issues.
I owe an amends.
My apologies.
Explore the feelings.
I feel...
better.
Prisoner 9205, you have a visitor.
I feel like I'm about to have some fun.
Chuck 4x20 - Versus the Family Volkoff
- First off, we don't trust you.
- I understand.
I'm ashamed of myself.
There is an assassination order
out on your daughter, Vivian.
You can help remove it.
It's all my fault.
Absentee parent.
What's with this good-guy act?
Charles, Sarah, I've had a lot of time
to think about my life.
I'm not interested
in how the world can serve me anymore.
I'm interested in how I can serve
my fellow man.
Sure, awesome. Well, if that's the case...
if we identify this weapon, we can
help rescind your daughter's kill order.
That's the Norseman.
It's a DNA tracker.
A tiny sample and a target
or a family of targets...
can be picked out of a crowd
and killed instantly.
There are two other components.
Where are they?
That's valuable information.
Now, there's the conniving,
manipulative Volkoff I know.
The requirement for spiritual growth...
is making apologies
to all the people I've harmed.
Making amends.
Most important to me is my daughter.
For five minutes with Vivian...
I'll get the other components
for you.
I see.
Let you out of jail so you can escape?
Sorry, not falling for it.
Hey, Dad.
Um, I am so sorry.
Mom sent out invitations to Morgan's
new address instead of the Buy More.
Not an issue.
I'm meeting Mom after the ceremony
for dinner.
But I told her between dinner and the
party, I was having drinks with friends.
- You lied to her.
- Then I can come meet you...
and show you a video
of the ceremony and...
- That would be an intrusion. I really...
- I want you to be a part of this.
- You name the place, I'll be there.
- Great.
- Ah. Oh, uh, okay.
- Oh.
So, uh, I'll be in touch.
Great.
Roger that.
- Hi.
- See you later.
- Okay.
- Ugh.
Since Volkoff identified the Norseman...
Langley is putting the hunt
for Vivian on a back burner.
They want
the additional weapon components.
We'd be happy to, except the weapon's
not in the Intersect and the only man...
who can find the components is...
- Coming in right about now.
Say what?
- What is this?
- I'm not normally one...
to question authority, general...
- Not the time to start, team.
- Mr. Volkoff.
- Thank you.
Please brief the team.
The man who has
the Norseman targeting component...
is a well-known high seas pirate.
Ellyas Abshir.
Kidnapper, vessel thief.
Last seen in Mogadishu.
- How did the pirate get the component?
- I lost it in a poker game.
He's addicted to gambling.
I'm not buying his newfound spirituality.
What's in it for Volkoff?
The general caved to my demands.
Really? No alarm bells ringing here
for anyone else?
Not getting the sense
we're being played for suckers?
The Norseman is extremely dangerous.
Washington wants it now.
Damn the risks.
Volkoff will accompany you
to retrieve the component.
For the next 48 hours,
he is your responsibility.
So...
when do we fly?
My cover is a Volkoff agent.
I'm going in and I just need the layout.
Beckman uploaded a layout
of the compound by Sky Drive.
Only way in is through the front door.
It's a rat's nest of a hellhole.
But the gambling's good,
buffet is decent.
It should be me going in.
- That's my job.
- Then you tell him that I sent you.
It'll scare the hell out of him.
Sad, isn't it?
Why do I always choose fear
over love?
Okay, Oprah.
Park it. Come on.
Hey, you, uh, good? You're being awfully
cool about the whole prenup thing.
Yeah. It's a nonissue.
Don't you wanna know
why I asked you to sign it?
- You'd tell me when you were ready.
- It's got nothing to do with us.
No, I get it.
Is that cool?
Yeah.
So really, the missing link
isn't actually missing.
It's a misnomer
when a fossil shows a specimen...
- ...in a state of intermediary development.
- It's missing.
You think it's wise...
to argue in front of the baby?
- No.
The Agent-X file I showed my mom
is missing.
It happened after we left
for breakfast.
My mom was here babysitting.
Why would she delete a file
from my dad's computer?
Honey, you're going from zero to 60.
I think you just gotta calm down.
Mom, it's me. Can you call me
when you get this, please? Thanks.
I don't know, Devon.
Something is not right.
I'm gonna get to the bottom of it.
Watch him.
Did I hear prenup?
- You overheard a private conversation.
- I think you're handling it really well.
You're seeing her side of things.
That's so important.
You know, Dr. Nelson, the prison shrink,
he taught us...
that a major part of recovery
is seeing the opposing points of view.
Thanks, Dr. Nelson.
Charles, I've been thinking a lot
about your mother lately.
I owe her an amends. Do you think
if you talk to me, you might...?
You're a kind of a sore subject.
Of course.
- Ready?
- Okay, Charles, remember...
you're a criminal.
You work for me.
You work for Volkoff.
I'm looking for Ellyas Abshir.
Who are you?
I work for Alexei Volkoff.
Volkoff. Volkoff. Alexei Volkoff?
Did I not pronounce that correctly?
Sometimes, the Russian thing,
the W's, the V's.
Wolkoff, perhaps?
Alexei Volkoff is a powerless worm
in a U.S. Penitentiary.
He still has a little pull.
He sent me here to broker a deal
for the Norseman tracking device.
Not for sale.
- Why didn't you tell us Ellyas hates you?
- Everyone hates me.
I accept that.
I haven't mentioned my terms yet.
We're prepared to pay...
With your life?
Good.
I think maybe you're putting words
in my mouth.
Specifically the word "life."
Come on.
Somali pirates wanna take him.
Go in with that firepower,
it's gonna be a bloodbath.
If you wanna get Charles out alive...
I need to be there.
- Fine.
- I can't go like this. They'd laugh.
Let me get a little something
out of my prison kit. Please.
Pick a game.
Dice...
roulette...
cards.
You win, the tracker is yours.
I win...
you die.
Do you have Uno?
Honestly, sweetheart, I copied one file
to cross-reference in the CIA database.
When I put the flash drive in,
it disappeared.
Well, Mom,
why didn't you say anything?
I know it's important to you...
working with your dad's computer,
and I just... I felt stupid.
It's okay. The computer automatically
embeds backup files in the hard drive...
so I didn't lose anything.
- Oh, good. Good.
- Yeah.
If we're gonna make that reservation...
- ...we should get going.
- Okay.
Okay.
Go on.
Get out of here. Have some fun.
- All right. We'll see you in a few hours.
- Okay.
Let's drop this plan
and actually go to dinner.
The woman has the technical savvy
of Steve Jobs.
She didn't just erase a file.
We're gonna stand here,
wait for her to do something?
Oh, we didn't have to wait very long.
She's doing it.
Okay. She's spending the night,
we follow her in the morning.
- See what she's doing with the file.
- We're not spies.
Act like it. She's keeping something
from me and I wanna know why.
Sir, the tracking device.
I...
- Draw four.
- You're a cheater. You just cheated.
He cheated.
I saw you palm a card out of your...
Tell it to Saint Peter, dead man.
Hello, Ellyas.
You cheated.
Give him the targeting device.
You are supposed to be locked up.
What the hell is happening here?
I'll show you
what the hell's happening here.
Ooh!
Your morality is in a state
of development.
For once in your life,
you're gonna play fair.
The tracking device or your life.
- Take it. It's yours.
- Thank you.
We do have one problem.
- What's the problem?
- There's something I've gotta do.
And it's gonna be really painful.
- We need to get out of here right now.
- We got it. Let's roll.
Come on, Alexei, we gotta go now.
You know me.
You know what I'm capable of, Ellyas.
The time has come for me...
For me to...
apologize.
I want you to understand...
I, like all other men,
am still a work in progress.
What do you say, Ellyas?
Forgive and forget?
Um...
Okay?
Okay.
Go.
Okay, okay.
- I feel so free.
- Do you?
- That's...
- Ha, ha.
Thanks for your time. Such a good
feeling, isn't it? Here we go. Let's go.
Thank you, Mogadishu, and good night!
Come on.
- All that remains
- Thorium.
- My finest piece of work.
- Where does it come from?
Far-off land. To mine it, I had to wage
war against the peaceful natives...
and ordered the destruction
of their Hometree.
I'm just kidding.
They showed it
to us last week. Avatar.
- So it's rare.
- Incredibly.
And chances you don't know its location
are slim.
My grandmother always used to say
play your cards close to the vest.
And wear a coat over the vest
or you'll look like a jerk.
Team, good progress,
but Langley is getting antsy.
Well, general, we think Volkoff knows
where the killing agent is...
but he's being uncool about it.
General, I want proof you're gonna keep
your side of the bargain.
There is a classified document
on the conference table.
A communication
between Vivian and the CIA.
It's been redacted,
but you'll get the gist.
You're just gonna have to trust us.
The thorium's in a Swiss military bunker.
The locks are coded to my DNA.
We fly at midnight. Fuel my jet.
You don't have a jet.
Of course.
Old thinking.
It creeps back.
Let's creep back to your cell.
Come on.
Okay, honey, I'll call next week.
- And if you need anything, you call me.
- Okay. Thank you.
Bye.
- Target's on the move, Hot Mama.
- Copy that, Six Pack.
I got the baby, you get the car.
"Meet me at 8.
The shooting range to celebrate.
Love, Alex."
Hmm.
Hey, I just got your text.
What's going on?
Your sister is breaking
through the firewalls...
of the Orion computer.
What? No, no, no.
I knew about that, but I had Awesome...
take out the hard drive and disable it.
- He didn't.
And the progress she's making
in her access...
it's as if your father intended
for her to find out about the Intersect.
- Oh, my God.
- I've taken files piecemeal.
I think I got the dangerous ones...
but she's onto me.
She's following me.
Okay. Okay. Let's think about this.
Let's think about this.
What are we gonna do?
The time has come for her to find out
what it is you do for the CIA.
No. Mom, we've been down
that road before, okay?
She gets the truth now,
she could resent me for all the lies...
and it'll tear us apart.
- She is finding out on her own...
which could be infinitely worse.
Our family has relied on secrets and lies
for way too long.
- Bartowski, Beckman's on the monitor.
- I'll be right there.
Not you, Bartowski. The other Bartowski.
She says it's urgent.
We'll discuss later.
Okay.
I'd like the second file from Orion's
computer to be the last that I acquire.
It's not gonna be easy to keep secrets
from my daughter much longer.
Cards on the table?
Washington is hungry
to expand the Intersect program.
Ellie has unlocked material
our best technicians couldn't get near.
We've never even heard of Agent-X.
Neither have I, but that doesn't mean
it's related to the Intersect.
Still, it seems Ellie has exclusive access.
The director wants her to keep working.
Diane, she's not a spy.
She's my daughter.
Mary, I'm sorry,
but it comes from the top.
Oh, Danny boy
The pipes are calling
Volkoff is here?
What the hell is going on?
He got a 48-hour furlough
to get us the Norseman.
It wasn't in your Volkoff file.
Have you heard of it?
Just whispered about. Never laid eyes
on it, which is worrisome.
Watch your back, Chuck.
Maybe he's a changed man.
- He asked to see you to make amends.
- We're talking about Alexei Volkoff.
His mind is twisted.
Never believe a word he says.
And never let him out of your sight.
You understand?
Cool.
No guns, no ambush.
- Maybe this isn't a trap after all.
- Yeah.
Can't trust a limey with good teeth.
Well, we have Mr. Cool in there.
What do we have to worry about?
Bartowski, we lose audio,
we're coming in.
- Sounds good, buddy.
- The thorium is behind this door.
But first, to get in,
I gotta win a game of chess.
It's fully automated, constantly evolving.
Plus, there's a five-minute clock.
I guess there's consequences
if you lose.
Oh, yeah.
Well, you don't have to stay.
You can wait with your friends.
Alexei, as much as I like staying away
from life-threatening situations...
wherever you go...
I go.
Fasten your seat belt.
It's gonna be a bumpy match.
Welcome, Mr. Volkoff.
Ready to play a game?
Alexei, just stay cool.
Yeah, I know you don't like
Bartowski's groovy attitude.
God knows where he gets these ideas.
Well, it kind of threw me
when he just signed that prenup.
- That's what you would've done.
- But now I see Chuck's side of it.
Flipping out about our relationship boiled
down to the contents of an envelope.
Seeing the end
before we've even started.
So why the prenup?
I have money socked away
in case my dad gets arrested again.
Well, I'm sure Bartowski
could handle it.
Any excuse to weep and hug.
Yeah, well, it's more about
what it dredges up for me.
My relationship with my family
and having to take sides.
Caught between your parents, huh?
Tough place to be.
Hardest place for a kid
is right in the middle.
Roger that.
Check, Mr. Volkoff.
Shake it off, shake it off.
You're doing great.
You are still in check, Mr. Volkoff.
If this is Mr. Volkoff.
Guns. Big guns.
Lots of bullets.
Sort of overkill.
Story of my life.
What is going on with you?
Come on. Let's do this.
I used to love games like this. I didn't care
whether I lived or died. Now I do care.
I don't wanna die.
I'm gonna lose. I'm gonna die.
No. You're not gonna die.
We're not gonna die right now.
I get that you're trying
to better yourself.
But would a spiritual man freeze
in the face of adversity?
Would he choke and die so close
to fixing things with his daughter?
Would he hide under a table if his
fiancée handed him a prenup to sign?
No, he wouldn't because he'd be cool.
- It's not working.
- Damn it!
You still have the DNA
of the world's most evil weapons dealer.
You are a villain, sir.
Your name strikes fear in the hearts
of even the toughest of swine.
And that name is...
- Alexei Volkoff.
- You say it like you mean it.
My name is...
Alexei Volkoff.
World's biggest badass.
Killer of men, conqueror of nations.
Let's not get ahead of ourselves.
Game, guns, clock.
What's going on?
Right into my trap.
Checkmate.
Ha, ha. Good. Now get a move on...
before the computer
changes its mind, okay?
We're losing audio.
What is that? Is that Russian?
- Yeah. Go.
- We need to go.
The last level of security
is coded to my DNA.
I assume that's thorium.
Let's get this over with.
We'll get to that.
But first,
I have an amends to make to you.
Oh, yeah? Well, uh, I'm well aware
of all the bad things you've done.
- I'm learning not to hold it against you.
- It's not what I've done.
It's what I'm about to do.
Chuck?
Hey. We just picked up some Russian
on the radio.
- How long is this gonna take?
- See, you were right.
I'm Alexei Volkoff.
And always will be.
Wait, wait, wait. What is happening?
This is what we call the twist.
I have a company to run.
I need leverage to run it.
Norseman is the most dangerous weapon
in the world.
I just needed my father's DNA
to get the killing agent.
What? So this is a setup?
You were shot.
- You two never communicated.
- Yes, we did.
The minute you showed me
the Norseman component...
I knew it was a message
from my daughter.
You and I are gonna run
this company together.
Vivian, I owe you...
the humblest amends...
for being totally absent during
the formative years of your childhood.
There will be plenty of time
for that, Father.
Thorium is useless
without the other components.
The other components
are what's useless.
They can be rebuilt.
But you'll never have this.
Place the grenades.
Now, Viv, darling,
get these handcuffs off your father.
- We've got a lot of work to do.
- Sorry, but here's the real twist.
Dead by your own plasma grenades,
impossible to defuse.
Young lady...
you get me
out of these handcuffs immediately.
This is your father talking.
- Trust no one. You taught me that.
- It didn't include me.
- Vivian, you are not this person.
- You don't know who I am.
You have both lied to me,
betrayed me and shattered my life!
Vivian, darling,
I've always been on your side.
The photographs? The necklace?
Tokens from a stranger!
I don't know you.
I will never know you. Goodbye.
Vivian.
Vivian. Please.
Let's get to the bombs
and see what we can do.
Maybe I can get through them.
Gonna carry us on your back?
Is there any other escape
from this room?
She hates me.
Whoo.
No, I'm sure
she's just going through a phase.
Actually, she's not going
through a phase...
but snap out of this right now.
- Just let me die.
- We all die.
What would Dr. Nelson say?
You're not seeing it from her side.
If your recovery was real,
you'd see she's just hurt and angry.
- I failed her.
- No. You made a great first step...
in repairing your relationship.
It's just gonna take more work.
You really believe that?
We have 10 more seconds left.
Just forget about him!
Uh, modified directed EMP.
This year's innovation.
I was gonna tell her all my secrets.
We were gonna be partners.
Not anymore.
Welcome to the future.
Why did she do this?
She's my daughter.
She takes after me.
Please, Charles, take me home.
Alexei.
I understand you wanted a minute.
Mary?
- You well?
- What is it you wanted to say?
I have done terrible things.
I've been evil.
But I was drawn to the goodness in you.
Alexei, this is not necessary.
- Yes, it is.
I was not worthy of your love...
like Orion was.
Please accept my apology...
and know that I'm doing my best
to improve.
Thank you, Charles.
Remember, family and friends
are everything.
Money, greed and power are a dance
with Satan.
And he looks like me.
- Dad, don't say it again.
- Mm-mm.
We'll have dinner the day after graduation.
I don't want you lying on my behalf.
Me neither, but lying to her kind of goes
with our territory.
It's not fair for you to be torn
between two parents. Not okay.
You're my father.
I don't mind being in the middle...
as long as that means
I get to have you in my life.
I mind.
I respect that you don't wanna tell
your mother the truth, but...
we have to come up with a
compromise. I can't be there on the day.
Unless...
Unless we tell your mom the truth.
That I'm alive.
Yeah. Let's tell her the truth.
Oh, that scares me.
- Done.
- You don't have to do that.
Please forget that
that ever existed, okay?
And can you please stop
being so cool?
- That is so not cool.
- Just read it.
"I, Sarah Walker,
promise to always love Chuck Bartowski.
In return, he will always love me."
I can't read this fine print.
The fine print says:
"I promise Chuck that I will not
even contemplate the word 'divorce'...
and I will never use my prenup."
I already signed it.
Thank you.
Thanks.
Ellie.
Sarah, I have to talk to Ellie now
or I'll lose my nerve, I know it.
Your mother is right.
Ellie's better off finding out from you
than on her own.
- Should I finish my wine first?
- Come on, she'll understand.
Chuck, being a spy
isn't just what you do...
but it's about who you are.
Go and tell her.
Thanks. Be right back.
Hey, EI.
Hi. Uh, Devon's putting the baby down.
Let's, uh, go over here.
That's some look
you got on your face.
Well, uh...
I heard that you've been
kind of busy lately.
Yeah. Ha, ha. A newborn'll do that to you.
Yeah, that's true. Um...
Is there anything pressing going on?
I should get dinner started.
EI, I need to talk to you
about Dad's computer.
Oh, yeah. Yeah.
I thought that I uncovered
some secret files.
Turned out to be cheats
on some video game he was developing.
- Oh, yeah?
- Yeah. Just gibberish, really.
Chicken á la king isn't gonna cook itself.
I'm gonna get in there.
- Okay. Yeah.
- Okay.
My sister just lied to me.
She's never lied to me.
Not cool.
We build the device
as quickly as possible.
There was only one man
my father was afraid of.
One threat to Volkoff Industries.
He went by the name Agent-X.
I'm gonna track him down
and kill him.
Then no one can touch me. Ever.