That was easy.
Yeah, too easy.
Wasn't even fun.
Speak for yourself.
I like easy.
Can it! We have work to do.
Mac, get the panel.
All right, let's have a look, boys.
There's enough gold in here for
us all to retire... five times.
That gold's being used to
secretly fund terrorists.
We're under strict orders from
President Clinton to seal this place up.
While I may not like him or his
mouthy wife, those are the orders.
Anyone tries to open this door
I'm just saying, you know?
Hidden in a vault... hidden in our
bags, what's the difference, Casey?
The difference is that
wasn't our mission.
Is that gonna be a
problem for you, Packard?
Well, actually, it is a problem for you.
You're outnumbered, pal.
You're both with him, huh?
I'd like to retire young.
Maybe move to Boca.
You can't blame the boys for
thinking about their future, Casey.
You'll have plenty of time to think
about your futures... in Leavenworth.
Casey, Jeffrey and I were feeling
nostalgic for the days of the old Buy More.
So we decided, you know what would
make this place feel like home again?
Getting the gang back together.
You in, C-note?
I was never in your gang.
So what do you say, Friday
night, a little white zin,
a little Magic: The Gathering?
If you have the mana to
battle the other Planeswalkers.
"Have the ma..." This guy.
You think about it, let us know.
Symmetrical thing... Guess who?
Okay, soft, perfumed
hands... sweet, sweet feminine voice...
Chuck? That's easy. I
would know that any...
Ah, it's Alex! Aw, that's even better!
Wait a minute. Did you...
Did you just fist bump me?
Yeah, that's right because
I blow it up with everybody.
Did you know that? I do. I get... I
get silly with that, and, uh...
I know that. I know
we're dating, you know.
Just, you know, not everybody
here knows that we're dating.
Morgan, you said that you were
gonna talk to my dad about us.
I was going to.
I was. Check this out. Such a
funny story... Morgan, I get it.
My dad, he's very
intimidating. No, not, not the...
But it's really important to me
that we're honest with him, you know?
I have to get to class in 15, but... I
will talk to you later! Absolutely.
Still haven't told Casey yet, huh? No.
Well, be careful how you
break the news to him.
He might kill you accidentally.
Sound advice, Chuck. Thank you.
Yeah, you know, anytime.
Um, buddy, can you, can you
do me a favor? Of course.
Um, could you cover for me up here?
I got a little work to do downstairs.
We just got a file from Costa Gravas
detailing all of their interactions
with the Volkoff
Organization over the years.
Volkoff? I mean, that's good. This
will lead back to your mother, right?
Yeah, I certainly hope so.
I mean, ever since I told Ellie about the search,
the pressure's really been on to find her.
Ellie deserves to know the
truth just as much as I do, so...
Okay, I've gone through all of these
files, Chuck, and there is nothing on your mom.
Okay, okay, so maybe there's
nothing on "Frost" per se,
but perhaps there's
something "Frost-adjacent."
You know, something that
could lead us to her?
What about Volkoff's
prisons? What do you mean?
Volkoff has a network of
"black sites" across the world;
Basically, a private prison system
run by extraction specialists.
And if anybody is gonna know where
Volkoff's prisoners are held, it's these guys.
Ex
Special forces escspe UNIT COMMANSER JOHN CASEY
Sarah, those guys used to
work for someone we know.
After I secured the
gold using my handprint,
I dragged my former "team"
halfway across the desert,
thereby saving their
miserable, mutinous lives.
Oh, okay. Then what happened?
I had 'em court-martialed.
Of course, they promptly escaped
from a maximum security stockade.
To the Los Angeles underground, where
they survived as soldiers of fortune.
It's like The A-Team. You never...
Have you ever seen The A-Team?
I was The A-Team.
They've taken a couple of
shots at me over the years.
The last time, I taught
them to stay hidden.
Well, is there anything you can tell us
about how we might be able to find them now?
Casey, these guys may be
the key to locating my mom.
The only place I can think of to get these three
sons of bitches back together would be my funeral.
That's it!
Casey, I know how to find your old team.
We have to kill you.
Chuck 4x05 - Versus the Couch Lock
Let me get this right: You
want to use government resources
to stage a fake funeral
for Colonel Casey?
Well, yes, uh, General, I believe we have
a unique opportunity here to set a trap
for Casey's old team, who
happen to be Volkoff agents.
If they think I'm
dead, they'll come for this.
My handprint's the only way they're
gonna access that Iranian vault.
Here's the plan: First, we spread the news of
Casey's death through all the back channels
that civilians don't
monitor but Volkoff does.
Next up, we kill the Colonel.
You want him to play dead?
I'll be drugged, ma'am.
When Casey's former team
sees Casey's actual body,
we believe they'll drop their
guard, giving us the upper hand.
And then we'll move in.
We will control every entrance and exit.
Snipers will posted and at the ready.
And the audience will be filled
with agents that we've planted there.
All right. You've clearly thought
this through. The mission is a go.
Thank you, General.
Colonel Casey, Agent
Walker, you're both dismissed.
I'd like a word with
Agent Bartowski, alone.
I'm impressed; you've
really progressed as a spy.
Thank you, ma'am. Thank you very much.
But I'm not sure if
I know what you mean.
You've put duty above emotion.
I mean, using Colonel Casey as bait?
It usually takes years before an agent is
willing to put his teammates in harm's way.
Good tactical thinking, Bartowski.
Hmm, these pesky dress uniforms get a little
tight when you don't wear 'em for a while.
Listen, Casey, just want you to know
that if you feel the mission is
a little too dangerous
and you need to back out
for any reason.
I mean, I know that you and Alex have just
reestablished this kind of
father-daughter connection right now...
Walker will be there. It'll be fine.
I'm serious, Casey...
Why don't you just stick to the mission?
Tell me about the drug you're
gonna use to kill me, hmm?
What's it
called, Fake-a-deathanol?
Cute.
No. As a matter of fact, it's
called Tetrodotoxin.
Normally it would
just kill you outright,
but we've modified it so it'll just slow down
your breathing and heart rate. Outstanding.
You will come across
as being very, very dead,
but in actuality, you'll be
very much alive and awake...
however, paralyzed. I'll
show you how it works.
No, it's not like it's the first
time I ever faked my own death.
About that, because you've been exposed
to so many truth serums and tranquilizers
and what-have-you's throughout
your very long and colorful career,
we're not exactly sure how long the
drug's effects will last in your system,
so I'm gonna take the liberty of
stashing an extra hypo on your person.
I'd like a little alone time
before I die. *************.
One more thing, one more
thing, A little thing, uh...
Because Sarah and I are gonna
be busy during all of this,
we're gonna need someone
to deliver a eulogy.
I was thinking... Of course I'll do it.
Oh, man, what am I gonna
talk about, though?
I'm getting a little nervous, actually. I
think I'm starting to sweat.
Is that normal before a mish?
Can-Can I do that?
Can I all it a "mish"?
Sure, whatever, yeah.
I just thought, given the Alex situation of
it all, this is the perfect opportunity for you
to get in Casey's good
graces. I mean think about it.
Hel have no choice but to just lie there and
listen to every nice thing that you have to say.
See? This is why you, this is why...
Are you expecting somebody?
No...
We have news.
On the count of three, okay?
Ready? One... It's a girl!
Wow! Hey, wow. Amazing.
I
I didn't know you guys were hoping for a girl.
Oh, we would have been happy either way,
but I'm just excited to see my
babe with a papoose strapped to her.
Is that weird that I find that hot?
I don't - yeah, it's kind of...
I don't know what a papoose is.
Papoose. It's a good
time for them to drink.
I can't do that, obviously, but
why don't you guys...
Oh, yeah! Yeah, pop it up!
Let's do it, let's do it.
Congratulations. Thank you, thank you.
Can I talk to you for a minute? Yeah.
Uh, well, it's-it's about Mom.
I know that I said I was worried about
you looking for her, but I changed my mind.
I... I want to know
what happened to her.
Uh, what-what made you change your mind?
I just got to thinking, you
know, I'm having a little girl, and...
is she ever going to
know her grandmother?
Uh, well, I just found a promising lead.
So if it goes anywhere, you'll
be the first to know, okay?
Okay.
All right. Let's have some champagne.
Great. Well, I'll have a drink.
You will, for me. You
can have some water.
He looks so peaceful.
Oh, whoa! That's freaky.
I didn't know he could do that.
Did you know he could do that?
I knew he could do that.
Stop doing that. Don't stare at me.
Okay, I got to go over
my notes. Listen to me.
Don't you worry about a thing.
I am gonna eulogize the
hell out of you, buddy.
Right. Got this.
Snipers are all in position. We're set.
Hey, Alex, it's me, Morgan.
In case you don't
recognize my voice yet.
That's my voice.
Just wanted to call you
and let you know that, uh,
I'm going to tell your
dad about us today.
I got the perfect spot for it.
Do you find it kind of sad that
the only people who showed up
for Casey's funeral are the
agents that we planted here?
That's not true.
Is it?
No, no, you're right.
There are people here who also hate him.
Target one is in position.
What?
He just stabbed him with a pin.
He can still feel pain, you know.
Yeah, he's gonna be okay.
Just let him know,"Casey, I'm
dating your daughter."End of story.
Uh-uh, end of story."Take charge.
Showtime.
Please be seated.
Whoa, sorry.
You're sitting.
You know, if there was one word
I'd choose to describe John Casey,
that word would be: "forgiveness."
Big, gun-loving, Commie-hating
forgiveness.
There was something I wanted to
tell John before he, before he passed.
There's something I
need to get off my chest.
Oh, no... I - I know John is somewhere out there...
beneath the pale moonlight, listening intently.
I wanted to tell him
how handsome he was.
And I never got a chance, darn it.
That man could fill out a uniform.
That's not a physique
of a middle-aged man.
Am I right or am I right
or, uh, or am I right?
'Cause.
It's hot in here, isn't it?
But so what else is there to
say about, about John Casey?
Well, he was a big man.
Big biceps, big hands.
I used to call them mitts.
You know, they were like giant mitts that
could fit all the way around my neck, anyway.
And I once, I actually saw
him palm an entire watermelon.
Just one of his many strange hobbies.
Also, he has very large feet.
Should we maybe move in before
someone takes a blowtorch to his face?
No, we still have to
wait for the other guy.
I could use them as-as a
kayak, in case of an emergency.
2012 and all that.
It's okay; Casey's
been through much worse.
His neck was always very, very thick.
And I was always very jealous
of it, 'cause I think, uh,
in Roman times, it was a sign of a
great warrior to have a neck like that.
Uh, don't quote me on that.
That's Wikipedia, so it's
probably, uh, at best, spotty...
Uh, where am I going with this?
Uh, well, maybe a better question is where
John Casey would want me to go with this.
They're getting up. Be
ready to move on my mark.
But, alas, we shall never know, for he
no longer walketh among the living.
We miss you, J-Case. That's for sure.
And, uh, please, come back soon.
In song and limerick.
Is he crying?
I'm done. Good-bye.
Did you really think we'd come
to Casey's funeral unprepared?
- You're all under arrest.
- Give up now.
We have every exit covered.
I think you missed one.
Has anyone got them?
Anyone?
I lost Casey.
I can't believe this.
I got Casey to fake his own death.
And now he can't defend
himself. This is all my fault.
Call Tactical. I want a hundred men locked
and loaded, ready to go on my command.
- Did you find him yet?
- I'm working on it.
Got it, got it. Tracker's engaged. We
have a lock on his location.
Okay, I'll call the strike team.
Please be alive, Casey.
This is Agent Bartowski. Target
needs assistance ASAP.
Move in right now. Do you copy?
This is Tactical. We're at the location.
Do you have him?
They put his tracker on a what?
No, God, no! No, don't shoot it!
They took off his tracker
and put it on a cat.
Then where's Casey?
All right, so we got to chop his arm off.
It's the left one, right?
I was planning on doing it with this.
Not with a knife, no. Too dull.
What we need is a surgical saw.
I got one in the other room.
Yeah, you mess up his hand, you
won't be able to open the vault.
Move... Move, damn it.
Move.
- Mac, you look like Dr. Frankenstein.
- Now we're talking.
Like cutting into a
bird on Thanksgiving.
Doorbell. Mackintosh.
Get your guns.
Come on, come on, come
on, come on. Check it.
Hey, buddy, is there anything I can
do? Anything at all to be useful?
Um, you know, right now, Morgan, the best thing
you can do is help keep Casey's cover, all right?
So if anyone asks about him
upstairs, just say he's on a delivery.
I should get back upstairs, right?
Okay, yeah, yeah, yeah.
Sarah, there's got to
be some way to find him.
You had to order a pizza.
What, do you want to eat pizza
after we cut the guy's arm off?
- I want to eat pizza now.
- Now is the time to eat pizza.
Right, you're right.
Looks like John Casey ain't so dead.
Casey. Code red. I've been drugged.
Don't know how long... stay conscious.
Need extraction. In an alley.
4th and Hill.
I'll be in a Dumpster.
Don't worry, Casey.
I know that Dumpster.
Wait, who is this? Where's Chuck?
We're on the way.
Lester. Nerd Herd emergency. Man
down. Meet me at the Herder.
We track Casey's cell to
this alley. Stay alert.
- Damn it. He's not here.
- Yeah, well, he was.
Well, he can't have gotten far.
There's got to be a clue or something.
- Like an open window.
- He could be inside. I'll call ctical.
No, no, no. We don't he time to waste.
We're here right now. Let's go.
Always the straitlaced ones.
I told you, everyone needs to
get their freak on sometime.
What's with the uniform, you
think? I got one, too.
Sometimes I like to feel official.
- Go for Lester.
- Hey, where the hell did you guys go, man?
I got a line of customers
heading out the door right now.
- Man down, man. Man down. We
had to go get Casey. - What?
You're with Casey?
Yeah, I guess his install went sideways.
Luckily, we intercepted his SOS, 'cause from
the looks of it, he's been hitting the OG kush.
Lester... Lester, what
does that even mean?
Look, never mind.
Whatever he did, he did too
much of it, cause he can't move.
Yeah, he's got couch lock.
Bad.
Listen to me.
Forget coming back to the store, okay?
Can you just get Casey to
my apartment in Echo Park?
There's a key under the mat.
Yeah, nono, no, we got keys.
What? I... All right.
What?
Morgan... Morgan, that is fantastic
news. You stay put. We'll be right there.
Casey's safe. He's
back at our apartment.
What? What happened?
Oh, my God. Don't move.
Not moving.
Okay, don't move.
Yeah, I heard you the first time,
and I'm... and I'm-I'm not moving.
Careful, careful, careful.
Uh-oh? You don't
say "uh-oh."
You step out of that laser
beam, and this goes off.
Okay, um, I think I can try
and bypass the circuit.
Sarah, I'm so sorry.
This is all my fault.
What are you talking about?
I was so set on trying to find my
mom that I let my emotions take over,
and now I've-I've-I've put everyone
that I care about in danger.
First Casey, and now you.
Oh, my God, this is complicated.
I can't bear the thought
of you getting hurt
if this thing goes
off, so... I want you to go.
Now, please. Save yourself.
Okay, you know what? You could have told me
that before I climbed under those lasers.
I... when I... I didn't...
Chuck, you're being ridiculous-
come on-even for a man
who is trying to free himself
from high-tech explosives.
Casey and I know the risks, but,
of course, we're going to help you.
This is your mom.
I love you. You know that?
And I... and I'd say that even if you weren't
in the process of saving my life right now,
which does, by the way, make you
20% to 25% sexier in my book.
All right, 50.
Okay, all right. Listen, uh,
Chuck and Sarah are going
to be here any minute.
Right? All we got to
do is wait for them.
Do you understand what I'm saying?
You're blinking a lot.
I hope you know I don't
understand Morse code.
That could be them.
Why would they be knocking?
No.
One minute!
What do I do with you?
Okay. Okay.
Work with me. That's a good fit.
Hi, you. Hi.
What are you doing here?
Can I come in?
Sorry.
You know what? I.
I had this, uh...
this Halo tourney last
night, and it just got crazy.
I'm going to come outside and
talk to you, if that's okay.
Yeah. Good, good, good, good.
Anything I can do to help?
What, you getting bored or something?
A little.
Suddenly not so bored.
It just powered down.
Okay. Why are you saying
that like it's a bad thing?
Because I didn't disarm it.
I did.
Looks like you're in a bit of a pickle.
We set that trap for Casey.
But you two are almost as good.
So, anyway, I just came by to
see how it went with my dad.
Well, it didn't, uh... exactly go.
You know, it's a little complicated.
I'm confused, Morgan.
You called me to tell me that you'd talk
to my dad, and now it's "complicated?"
Do you want to tell me, like, what's
actually going on here?
But... can you... can
you do me a ge for?
Can we talk about this later?
No.
Right now is the option
I prefer, actually.
Okay. Then...
I'm going to need you to leave.
What?
Are you breaking up with me?
I just need you to go.
Fine. I get it.
Have fun playing Halo
for the rest of your life.
I'm sorry.
- Hey, eulogy guy.
- Oh... okay.
I'm looking for Casey.
Uh, Casey who?
That Casey.
I've got a message for him.
We've got his friends.
We're taking them on a
little gold-digging trip.
Casey knows where.
You tell him he's got
24 hours to show, alone,
or he's going to have two
more funerals to go to.
Morgan. What's up, hombre?
It's Jeff.
Okay, he-he took too much...
I don't know what.
Now he's come down with... couch lock?
Couch lock. He overmedicated.
Yes, exactly. He's overmedicated.
Now, how do I wake him up from this?
Morgan, do you need
me to come over there?
No. No. No. Man, come... Awesome, please.
You're busy saving
lives. This is nothing.
This is an average day
for Jeffrey Barnes, okay?
But listen, back to couch lock.
How do I wake him from this again?
Well, first of all, don't
panic. Jeff is still in there.
Now, just get his heart rate up.
You know, scare him or get him angry.
If he doesn't wake up, give me a call.
That's awesome.
Thank you so much, Awe... some.
No. Okay, that's weird.
Okay.
I'm sorry for this, sir, but
it is for your own good.
Man, it's like slapping a car.
Okay.
Think, Morgan. How do I get
him angry? How do I get him...
Oh, crap.
Okay, Casey.
I know you can hear me, and I have
something very important to tell you.
I've been dating your daughter.
Technically, we're on the
rocks right now, kind of,
but, you know, things were
getting pretty serious.
Hol... holding hands.
And, uh... and the kissing
was just out of control.
But I've been a perfect gentleman.
I need you to know.
Always a perfect gentleman.
Although it definitely
felt like, pretty soon...
she'd be spending the night.
I will kill you.
Yes! Welcome back, sir.
See? I knew that would work.
Bring it in. Come on.
Too soon. I see that now.
We're going to Iran, Morgan.
There's no American presence there.
We're going under the radar.
Which means no chance
of anyone rescuing us.
We are the mission.
Just you and me.
Right. Yeah, which is why I think that we
should clear the air, talk about Alex and me.
You're not getting it, Morgan.
I'm not discussing this with you
because you are not dating my daughter.
You, Alex-nothing to see here.
What is your problem, anyway?
Okay? I'm a good guy.
All right? Not to mention, stupid
me thought me and you were friends.
Were friends.
Oh, right.
Or-or maybe it's that you
don't have any friends.
Okay, I happened to notice at your funeral, the
only people who showed up wanted to see you dead.
Sorry about that one. That
was probably not my place.
If you'd like to choke me now, that's
fine, or we could wait for the plane ride.
It's a 19-hour flight to Iran.
Bring a book. We ain't talking.
So you guys are pretty much going to
kill us no matter what Casey does, right?
Mind if I ask you a few questions, then?
Sure.
I assume you've dealt with
many of Volkoff's prisoners.
Did you ever come
across one named Frost?
Frost isn't a prisoner.
She's our boss.
I'll set the computer, all right?
Now, they're down there; we're up here.
Now what?
We got water,
Yeah. Sewer, electronics,
security camera.
Guts of the bunker.
We'll tap in right here.
We can control the bunker from here.
This will give us the upper hand.
Shift-eight?
Six, six, six, six.
I got... I got it. I got it.
Ugh. There they are.
So, uh, Frost.
She a tough boss?
She's Volkoff's right hand.
When he has a problem, he sends in Frost,
and that problem disappears.
Sarah, I'm kind of starting to think
that my mom might be one of the bad guys.
Here, put these on.
Oh, it's so hot. Put them on.
Do I really have to wear these, really?
Only if you don't want
to get electrocuted.
They actually breathe surprisingly well.
Sorry, yeah. Wait for my signal.
When you hear the word "security," you
hit this switch, knock out the lights.
Got it? Absolutely. "Security."
- Hit the switch.
- No, no, no!
The word "security," wait for it.
Just testing you.
Wait a minute, turn off the lights?
It's three-to-one
down there, Casey.
Just the way I like it.
Heads up.
We got company.
That's how it is, huh?
You can't get to me for 11 years, so you
come up with the idea of kidnappinthese two?
If you hadn't been such a hard-ass, Casey, we
wouldn't all be here right now.
We'd be on a beach earning 20%.
Unless we invested in real estate.
Now drop your weapon, Casey.
All your weapons, Casey.
I would've come unarmed, but I wasn't
sure what kind of security I'd run into.
That's the signal.
What?!
Damn it.
I said, I would've come unarmed, but I wasn't
sure what kind of security I'd run into.
Yeah, we heard you the first time.
We're right here, pal.
What the hell's going on?
Grimes.
Sorry, sorry. One second. One second.
Okay.
Let there be darkness.
Don't worry about it. Get
the gold. Let's get the gold.
Any more surprises, Colonel?
Holy Goldfinger.
Topside there are 15 of the most hardcore
Special Forces soldiers you've ever seen.
Come on, come on.
They got 10,000 rounds of ammo,
a squadron of F-15
fighters a radio call away.
Your move.
Well, maybe I'll get lucky.
Is that a little girl?
That really stings!
Whoever you are, we have
Casey and the others.
Surrender or we will kill them.
So you got lucky, you hit one.
Still 14 left.
And they'll never surr.
I surrender!
I'm still surrendering.
Please do not shoot me.
I'm out, just me all alone. No
one else knows we're here.
So much for your Special Forces.
You move and you're dead.
Let's get the gold.
Casey, couch lock.
- What?
- The cable.
Oh, good Lord. Lift your feet up.
Do it, do it now.
He's gonna try and shock them.
Morgan!
Morgan, no!
Morgan.
Morgan, can you hear me?
Wake up, moron.
What happened?
What hap.
You just took 10,000
volts is what happened.
You went into cardiac arrest and we
actually lost you for a moment there.
You lost me? You lost me?
You mean, I, uh, I died?
Yeah, for, like, three seconds.
What about the bad guys?
Oh, they're alive, a little crispy.
Buddy, that was the single bravest
thing I've ever seen anyone do.
Don't ever do it again.
No. No.
Can we go home now? Yeah.
On your fe. What? Okay.
Um, Casey.
Now that we know that you're "cool," you should
know that we do "installs" like that twice a week.
Count yourself in.
We wake up in some of the
best Dumpsters in the city.
Just want to make sure
that we're, uh, we're good.
Oh, good, good.
Uh, also, you don't have to
worry about Alex and me.
We're pretty much over.
I can tell you're heartbroken over it.
So... I'd also just
like to give you this.
What is it? It's an invite.
To my party.
You know, being dead for three
seconds made me miss my friends.
So, you know, just think of it as
people who'd actually be there.
If there was ever a real funeral.
You should come.
Hey, buddy.
You look great, you guys. Beautiful.
Let me get you a beer.
Alex. I didn't know you were coming.
Please, come in. This is good.
You look lovely. Uh, so, look,
I'm really sorry I said some stupid
things the other day and, uh...
I already talked to my dad, Morgan.
I know what happened.
He said that you dumped me
because he told you you had to.
He also said that you stood up to him
and changed his mind,
which could not have been easy.
So maybe I was wrong about you.
You are brave.
Look, Alex, you know that I'm
really sorry about all that.
And, uh, this may come as a surprise,
but I don't care what your dad thinks.
Really. I like you.
And I want to be with you.
If you want to be with me.
You do, right?
That's.
You almost said no.
Of course I do.
That's good for the confidence.
Come on, let's get a drink.
All right.
Alex is here.
Okay.
She looks beautiful, huh?
Casey... thank you.
You break her heart, I
break your everything.
There you are.
Is this the part where I'm supposed to
ask you what you're thinking about?
My mom.
I thought she was a prisoner
who needed to be saved.
And... and I come to fi out
she's just one of the bad guys.
Chuck, we don't know
what side your mom is on.
Maybe not.
But there's one thing I do know:
In order to find the one
person who... left me,
I've endangered the lives of everyone who
would never leave me: Morgan, Casey, you.
I'm going to stop looking for my mom.
Oh, Chuck... No, it's okay.
I thought I had to bring my
family back together, but I don't.
You guys, Awesome, Ellie you're my family.
I love you. I love you.
I'll see you inside.
Hello. Hello, Chuck.
It's your mother.