Here are a few things
you might need to know.
That Intersect project
Dad was working on?
- I've been trying to figure it out.
- It's in my head.
From what I can piece together...
Dad used this program
to input a new identity into an operative.
But once he went undercover,
the program took over.
He became his cover identity.
- Agent X is Alexei Volkoff?
- I have a company to run. I need leverage.
The Norseman's the most dangerous
weapon. Rebuild the device quickly.
That way no one can touch me. Ever.
Right this way, Miss Volkoff. M
Sorry it's taken so long
to reassemble the Norseman...
but we've finally done it.
- I should hope so.
Miss Volkoff's patience has worn thin.
Whoever has been trying to sabotage
the operation won't find their way here.
Let me, Vivian.
If I may ask,
who's the first subject going to be?
God, that noise!
Amazing.
It located the correct DNA. It works.
You really should do
some of this dirty work.
You know, the head of Volkoff Industries
needs a public face...
that spreads fear and respect.
Thank you.
I appreciate your guidance.
Of course, dear.
After you.
I think the proper word
right now would be "freeze."
- Hello, Riley.
- Vivian...
meet the woman
who betrayed your father for 20 years.
Frost, welcome back.
Good morning.
You know what we have to do today?
Mm.
- Hunt someone?
- No.
- Blow something up?
- No again.
Mm, crawl through sewers or rat holes...
or underground lairs
filled with sewage and/or rats?
No, no and no.
Today we have a day off
from the CIA.
Today is about you and me
and our wedding.
God, that's good.
No. That's totally understandable.
I mean, you know, coups take time.
Anyway, uh, Awesome and Morgan
and Ellie have basically taken over...
every chore we have.
- Your family is so sweet.
Bending over backwards to protect us
from anything that's stressful.
I know.
There is one little thing I have to do...
that you don't get to know about
because I am adorable.
Heh, heh. Yes, you are.
Everything is perfect.
Nothing can go wrong.
Oh, Sarah, you didn't.
- Chuck!
- Why...?
Why would you say that?
Do you not watch movies?
- Well, I finally watched Mannequin.
- Oh, yeah? Did you like it?
Not good. Little help.
Oh, my God. Oh, my God. Oh, my God.
Honey, get him down.
- I got him.
- Yo!
Okay, bud. All right, just go limp.
- Fall into my arms.
- "Go limp." You go limp. Chuck!
Morning. Everything's fine here.
Nothing to worry about.
Chuck, do something.
All right, everybody calm down.
I got this.
Ooh.
Here we go. Here we go.
- You all right?
- Yeah, all good.
- Face is a little flush.
- Well, it's...
Coming down.
- Awesome.
- Impressive, isn't it?
- You don't do any core work?
- Just sitting up to reach the remote.
- Bitching, dude.
- Right?
Chuck, Sarah, that was great,
but, seriously, back inside.
I don't want you doing any work today.
Go do something romantic, okay?
Right. Romantic, got it. Thank you.
- Morgan?
- Yes, ma'am?
We have more twinkle lights, don't we?
- Yes, ma'am.
- This place has to be magical.
- Magical, Morgan.
Yes, ma'am.
Honey, you're scaring me.
Just keep it moving.
I hear you.
I'll take care of it, I promise.
Thank you, Dad.
Guys, I'm sorry.
But I need a little help here.
I just told Ellie
that I have all these extra twinkle lights.
I don't have actual twinkle lights
and she could yell at me.
Do you want me to just go out
and get some for you?
- Can you do that?
- Yeah.
You're the best. You are wonderful.
Come here.
And did I tell you how very excited I am
to have you...
as my hot date
to Chuck's wedding?
I was figuring
I'd be taking my mother.
Well, your mom is gonna have to get
her own date because you are mine.
Oh.
Well, I don't mind, I just...
Breakfast of champions, right?
- Oh, no.
- "Oh, no," what?
What, what, what?
Do we have a mission? Today?
- I have a mission.
- Oh.
I'll tell Ellie she's gonna have
to do without us.
Not you.
What's that about?
No. No, Casey. No way.
We have the week off.
You better be here to talk mimosas
or wedding.
I am.
- Your mom might not be able to make it.
- Why? What happened?
She's been taken by Vivian Volkoff.
Chuck 4x23 - Versus the Last Details
I don't understand any of
your mom's reports.
Why was she working on Volkoff?
That was our case.
She must be taking Vivian off our plate
so we focus on the wedding.
Look how she went in.
No backup, contingency.
- Have you spoken?
- Haven't gotten a chance...
to ask her about Dad and Agent X,
if she knew about it.
Where is she, Sarah?
This is her last communiqué.
A mine in Colombia.
A lot of bad-guy traffic there.
Good, so we start there.
It's a quick flight.
We'll have your mom back
for the rehearsal dinner.
I need my best man.
You need your best man.
Let's go get your mom.
Time to save the day.
No. Morgan, Morgan. Uh, I actually...
I need you to save the day...
in a different way by creating
a very romantic video montage...
of me and Sarah
for our rehearsal dinner.
Oh. Ha, ha.
Not quite as Superman as I'd like,
but, uh, of course, anything you need.
Thank you so much.
Sarah doesn't have any old pictures.
Maybe Photoshop her into some
of the different places that she's lived.
- Something kind of cute.
- Totally cute, okay. I get it. I'm on it.
- Done. I'm on it. Of course.
- Thanks, buddy. My best man.
- Means a lot to me. All right.
- Yeah. I know.
- Best man. You are the best man.
- Come on. I am, aren't I?
Jeffrey, our time has come.
Need some footage of Sarah, do you?
Why? You don't have any, do you?
We have over 1250 hours
of Sarah-related footage.
My clients have been exploring
their options as filmmakers...
ever since realizing that Jeffster
may not be as lucrative as expected.
- No way.
- I've had a camera running for years.
We have voyeur, we have candid,
we have nip slips of Chuck.
All right, good, great. Listen, all right...
Ahem. Cannot express to you the rage
that is actually building up.
On the other hand,
I really could use that footage...
to complete this present for Chuck.
So, ahem, may I have this footage?
Grimes, I am a montage artist.
- I am gonna need first and final cut.
- I'm fairly certain it will turn out terrible.
- I can hear you.
- But I do need the footage. So...
you may have first cut,
he will hand it over to me...
and then I will make it good.
Yes.
My clients will attach themselves...
under those terms.
- Agreed.
Casey. Good news.
Best-man chores are off the plate,
so I am fully avail for the mission.
Let's go save Chuck's mom.
Howitzer.
All right.
I don't know.
- I like the ones that make me look big.
- You're not coming.
Can't believe how much you worry.
Listen to me.
The wedding stuff
is gonna get taken care of.
Ellie is on it.
I need to be here for my team.
- You're not part of any team.
- How could you say that?
I have been doing a ton
of really, like, bigtime stuff lately.
You're not coming. So why don't you
just focus on your twinkle lights?
Twinkle lights.
Ouch.
Oh, God.
A lot of chickens and stray dogs,
and not a lot of top-secret holding cells.
Where do we even start looking?
How many mines have security
like that?
Let's find out
what these guards are up to, huh?
I hope you boys are hungry.
Looks like there's two entrances
to the mine.
The miners go in one.
Guards go in the other.
Bet you Volkoff is down in that one.
If your mom is still in the area,
she's probably being held down there.
What are we waiting for?
Let's do this.
- Guards are leaving. We gotta move.
- We can't just waltz in after them.
Look at the traffic.
We might be way outmanned.
Why don't we leave the table
before this thing attacks us?
Yeah. Agreed.
Move it along, Chewie.
Chewie?
Why are you calling him Chewie?
He didn't even eat anything
off that disgusting platter.
Honey, it's a reference to Star...
Oh, I love you.
I got a bad feeling about this.
Prisoner transfer from Pueblo facility.
- Do you have documentation for that?
- It was a verbal.
Which cell is available?
We'll take our man back there.
I don't know how you ran things
in Pueblo...
but you're not getting back there
without the proper paperwork.
This happens when you draw your plans
from Star Wars. Gotta get bloody.
Just hang on. Hang on a minute.
Hang on.
Uh, excuse me, sir.
Look, I don't mean to bug you...
but look at the cute little number
that came in with me.
Not the large man.
Real pretty one. Blond.
Girls like that are pretty few
and far between in Pueblo.
Know what I mean?
Two of us have kind of had...
this will-they-won't-they
burgeoning office romance going.
I'm trying to impress her,
so could you help me out a bit?
Beat your man.
- Sorry?
- Once, I snapped a guy's neck for a girl.
She melted all over me.
Is that right? I can kind of see that.
Okay, locking that one away.
Oh, now. Right now.
You want me to do that now. Okay.
Now would be the appropriate time.
Really?
Do you want to die alone?
I'm sorry.
Okay.
I did that. Wasn't that sexy?
So sexy.
All right. You two crazy kids
take him back to Cell 24.
But I think this girl has already been
to Cell 24.
She looks like a dirty one. Heh, heh, heh.
Ha, ha. Oh, I get it. Yeah, like Cell 24.
Dirty one.
- Ah.
- That's sweet. You defended my honor.
We're getting married in a week.
Let's get rid of this body.
I'll get rid of it.
You go find your mom.
I'll be right there
as soon as I get this guy's pants off.
Oh, shut up. Move.
Come on, let's go.
Looks like your mom's in Cell 13.
Okay. Let's go.
Chuck.
You're about to get married.
What are you doing here?
Exactly, which is why
we're getting you out of here now.
Oh, no, honey, I'm sorry.
I can't leave yet.
But you should go.
I can handle myself.
No offense, but that's the attitude
that got you captured.
Vivian's team has reassembled
the Norseman down here.
I can't leave without it.
I'll endure a couple rounds of torture...
then I'll find a way to break out
and get it.
- Uh, no.
- We're not leaving you to get tortured.
- We have a wedding to get you to.
- Come on, we gotta move.
- Let's go.
- Sweetheart...
I know the wedding is important,
but so is the nation's safety.
If I leave now, they will move
the weapon and we'll never get it.
Don't be stubborn.
We're here to extract you...
not finish a failed mission.
- Failed?
- Stubborn?
- Okay, okay.
I'm gonna go with Casey
to get the Norseman.
Sarah, you're gonna stay with Mom.
- I don't need backup.
- Why can't Casey stay with your mom?
No. I'm going with Chuck.
Okay, great, that's the plan.
See you soon.
I'll be outside.
Interesting choice.
Choosing your mom over your fiancée.
Oh, I was just trying
to make everyone feel...
Wait a minute.
Is that really how it looked?
Yeah. Just remember, Bartowski,
Sarah is the one you sleep next to...
at the end of every day.
She's the one you protect.
Where's the Norseman?
I don't know why Chuck felt
it was necessary to come and get me.
Chuck wouldn't have felt it necessary
if you had any backup.
Chuck knows
that I can take care of myself.
Chuck and the rest
of his family are in harm's way...
two days before his wedding.
The food here is really ghastly.
Where's the guard?
It's been moved. I don't know where.
Vivian is planning a meet to sell it.
- Gotta get to that meet.
- Gotta get out before Vivian finds out...
we know about it.
- Let's go before your girls kill each other.
You don't have to tell me twice.
Everything is locked down.
- Hold your fire. They'll never kill me.
- You don't know that.
No interruptions, guard.
Hello again, Frost.
Weapon has been moved.
Vivian is selling it. If she turns up,
keep her alive so the meet still happens.
- What do you want with me?
- I really just want to see you dead.
And I've been waiting
for my young friend here...
to be ready to do it.
Vivian, surely this is one trigger
that you'd like to pull yourself.
Vivian, I know you won't do this.
Do it, Vivian.
Don't.
Everybody against the wall right now.
Move.
- Sarah?
- Now.
I'm sorry, Frost has somewhere to be.
Hey.
- Mom, it's time to go.
- Mom?
The woman who betrayed my father...
is the mother of the man
who betrayed me? Makes sense.
There is so much you don't know
and we need to talk about.
No, I'm done talking to you.
The guards could be here any second.
Come on.
Let's go. Come on.
Come on, come on, come on.
Guards! Guards!
Since we're not on a long plane ride
with my mom now, we should talk...
about what happened in the mine.
- Okay. Talk.
So first of all, I know I messed up,
but I was trying to get us out of there.
- The place was crawling with bad guys.
- I know.
But sometimes it feels
like you can protect me from anything...
except your mom.
- No, you're right.
You're right, but I can protect you.
Even from my mom, I promise.
- Beckman needs us at Castle.
- No need to unpack.
Team, it looks like Vivian Volkoff
is indeed planning...
to auction off the Norseman device
in Moscow in 12 hours.
We must strike now. It's up to you.
Uh, but can't someone else go?
I mean, our rehearsal dinner is tomorrow.
I'm afraid we don't have time
to train a new team.
Oh. And thanks for the invite.
- Oh. No, um...
- I'm not serious.
Vivian knows all of our faces,
so how are we supposed to get in?
Agent Bartowski, if you don't mind.
An agent will impersonate
one of the buyers...
outbid all of the others
for the Norseman device...
and walk out the door. No bloodshed.
- Okay.
Except, like Sarah just said,
Vivian knows all of our faces.
I'm not sure
how to avoid the bloodshed.
Luckily, one of the buyers Vivian invited
was just detained by Interpol.
Italian arms smuggler Etorre La Barba.
- Remind you of anyone we know?
- Morgan?
General, Grimes is not prepared
for an operation like this.
We don't have time to argue.
He fits the profile.
You have your orders.
Good luck, team.
Etorre La Barba, huh?
Spaghetti pizza.
Mamma mia, it's me, Mario.
I sell the arms to the bad guys.
This is a horrible idea.
Buddy, are you absolutely sure
that you feel comfortable doing this?
Don't you worry about me, huh?
I take care of everything.
- Whatever you need, bada boom.
- You have to stop that.
Morgan will be fine.
Casey, you and I will provide
plenty of backup.
And you two will just stay here
and get ready for the wedding.
Stay here? What?
You're taking us off our own mission?
I appreciate you trying to protect us,
Mom, I do.
Morgan is my best friend,
and we've been on Vivian for months.
In which time
she's gone from harmless coed...
to one of the top weapons dealers.
Which is why I had to step in,
to fix your mistake.
Our mistake?
- Uh...
- I don't mean to be critical...
but you've been very busy
getting ready for the wedding.
- Your minds are elsewhere.
- Like on the fact...
that Dad turned an innocent man
into Alexei Volkoff.
Mom, did you know about Agent X?
Chuck,
I could not afford to let the CIA know...
that I knew about Agent X.
Neither should you.
Something else we have to clean up.
We don't have time for this right now.
Chuck and I are going.
You're providing backup.
- That's the way it's gonna be.
- I don't think so.
I agree with Sarah.
Thank you.
- That is...
- Sorry, sorry, guys.
I need to borrow the big guy.
Best-man stuff just dawned on me.
I have to...
- Thanks. It was getting tense in there.
- No problem.
The errand you gave me to take care of,
I can't get to it now, but not a problem.
Got my top people on it,
so not to worry.
Couldn't we just watch this at home?
I have things to do.
Yeah. I love popcorn and massages
as much as the next guy...
but can we just get this started?
- Moviemaking is a collaborative art...
even for an auteur.
I have many people I'd like to thank.
My rep, Big Mike, Jeffrey,
my parents-ish...
and, uh, my main man upstairs.
Anything is possible.
Let's get this puppy started,
shall we, Jeffrey?
Heart.
Pancreas.
Cockle.
My cockle.
- America.
- Stop, stop, stop.
- Please, make it stop. Oh, God.
- Dude, that is just unholy.
Thank you.
I'm gonna need the footage
from your clients.
I'm gonna be taking over.
Wait. Does that mean
Big Mike doesn't get his 10 percent?
- We weren't even paying them.
- What?
Then what was I doing all day?
How do you guys feel that went?
What do you think?
I finally got the accent down.
Don't move
or I will kill you where you stand.
And not even your madre
will recognize your corpse.
If I had my druthers,
you'd stay topside selling microwaves.
That's great,
that's great. Let's figure this out.
I thought we were past this. We're
roomies. You've been training me hard.
I've been in danger a ton of times.
You love the Snack Packs I bring
on missions.
So why, suddenly,
are you being this big jerk to me?
It's Alex.
She's worried about you.
Oh. Wait, wait, wait.
Okay, okay.
You're telling me you are being a jerk
because you care?
Yeah. Fat load of good it's done me too.
I promised Alex I'd keep you safe.
There are times on every mission
when things go sideways.
That happens, I can't protect you...
then I've broken a promise
to my daughter.
- I see your dilemma.
- Yeah.
Everything is gonna be fine, trust me.
Nothing will go wrong.
- Why did I just say that?
- Mm.
You know,
you can wait in the van if you want.
No, it's all right.
I think I'll give Chuck and Sarah
a little space on this one.
It's hard to have kids.
Can't always protect them.
Yeah. Or their idiot boyfriends.
- We're in position. Is Grimes ready?
- Just a second, Casey.
I don't know if I can do this, uh, guys.
Been thinking about it. Um,
what do I know about being a bad guy?
Plenty, buddy. Plenty.
Look at that suit.
- Part Goldfinger, part Drax.
- You noticed.
You got nothing to worry about.
We're gonna be with you the whole time
on the comms.
Not to mention the fact...
that we will be monitoring
the video feed through these glasses.
Casey will be on the opposite rooftop
with a sniper rifle.
You know he likes to shoot
from far away.
I do, yeah. Ha, ha.
You can do this.
You can totally be a bad guy.
Okay. Yeah. It's gonna be great.
This better not take long.
I already tried to kill three people
at this table.
Yes.
What do you mean?
No, you heard me the first time.
Shoot the puppy.
I'm so sick of feeding him.
Kill the puppy.
So hard to get good henchmen
nowadays. Hmm?
Thorium signature detected.
Looks like they're bringing in
the Norseman. Casey?
Welcome, gentlemen.
I'm so sorry to have kept you waiting.
You're all here for the same reason:
A chance to purchase one of
the deadliest weapons ever created.
The Norseman device.
By locking on to a target's DNA...
it can kill a single person
in the middle of a crowd...
with 100-percent accuracy.
There's no way to run...
even on the other side of the world.
Whoever ends up with it has an advantage.
But truth is...
it's an advantage I intend to keep.
Morgan, you have to die
or they're gonna kill you. Do it.
Oh, no!
Morgan...
whatever you do, stay calm.
Don't panic.
We're gonna get you out of this.
- Tell me you got a line on him.
- I got him in my sights.
If it gets hot, I'll take them all out.
Don't feel bad, Vivian.
Every man in this room
would have killed you...
without a second thought.
That's why we collected their DNA.
This one,
he killed all the families of his rivals.
Sick.
This one...
he gassed an entire village
of innocents...
just to eliminate one enemy.
Sicker.
This one right here with the beard...
Stop.
These are dangerous men, I get it.
Vivian, I'm not trying to turn you
into someone you're not.
I'm trying to turn you
into who you need to be.
- You may still get your chance.
- What do you mean?
There is a man in this room
who isn't actually dead.
Someone who has infiltrated
our organization...
by pretending to be someone
we invited here today.
He's merely feigning death.
Riley left my scope.
I do not have Riley.
Morgan, Morgan, don't move.
So, friend, are you gonna get up?
The name's Carlisle.
Sebastian Carlisle.
Carl to my friends, which you are not.
I take it you're MI6?
I've been tracking you since Munich.
It was actually rather clever.
You see, first...
Oh, I'm sorry, dear.
Next one is yours, promise.
Chuck, Sarah, Norseman is on the move.
You're on it, go.
Copy that.
Looks like they're taking it out.
I'm gonna help him
secure the weapon.
You stay here
and keep Alex's boyfriend safe.
Roger that.
The weapon is leaving the building.
Ready?
Yeah. Always wanted to say this:
Fasten your seat belt.
- Literally. Fasten your seat belt now.
- Okay, sure.
Guys, I haven't heard anything in a while.
Tell me it's okay to move.
Wait, wait, wait.
Okay, okay, go.
Quick. I'll cover you. Move.
Somebody is coming.
Oh, Casey, they got acid.
Like in that disgusting scene
from Breaking Bad.
- Never seen Breaking Bad.
- What? You'd love it, it's great.
- The perfect counterprogramming...
- Shut up.
They closed the curtains.
Can't see them.
I can't protect you
if I can't see the targets.
- Run.
- Okay.
Hey. Just one second.
Your glasses.
Show me the targets with your glasses.
And try not to move.
Morgan?
Morgan, can you hear me?
Morgan.
Yeah. Yeah.
Oh! Casey, I think you shot me.
What about the rest?
Yeah. They're all dead.
Casey, that was amazing.
Oh, Lord, I feel faint.
Just breathe. Get to the elevator.
- I'll meet you outside.
- Yeah. Yeah.
Looks like they're leaving the building.
The weapon is in the trunk.
I'm gonna get something to open it.
You all right?
Don't pretend to care.
I'm sorry for everything that's happened,
but there is so much you don't know.
I know enough. I know you're Agent X.
No, Vivian, I'm not.
Agent X is your father.
He was an MI6 agent.
He was going undercover.
He let the CIA perform an experiment
on him.
One that changed him into the man
we know now as Alexei Volkoff.
But before that, he wasn't evil.
And neither are you.
This...
This is crazy.
Don't move.
Riley, is this true?
Yes, I'm afraid it is.
But, first...
are you gonna tell her who turned
her father into Alexei Volkoff?
It was Stephen J. Bartowski.
Chuck's father.
He and Frost manipulated your father
to give up his own identity...
so they could further their careers.
- A lie.
No, it's the truth.
And I will not have you lie
to Vivian anymore.
No!
Chuck.
You saved me.
Always.
Where's Vivian?
- We have to find her.
- No.
We should go.
You two have somewhere to be.
What is it?
I totally dropped the ball
on Chuck's present to Sarah.
- Fell asleep in the middle of cutting it.
- You did what you could.
It'll be okay.
Look. There they are right now.
Guys, wow.
The courtyard, it looks unbelievable.
I can't believe you did all this for us,
Ellie.
Thank you so much, sis.
I promised myself
that I wasn't gonna cry.
Mascara.
- You ready for this?
- Absolutely.
Hey.
Man, does Big Mike need
this brandy Alexander.
- Had another deal blow up in my face.
- Oh.
But I do love the game.
What happened to your arm?
Wii tennis.
Son, it's amazing you're not single.
Casey.
How's the Sunshine Band, buddy?
Heh, heh. It's K.C. And the Sunshine Band.
No one's ever used that on you, huh?
Really?
Seriously, there is one more thing
I wanted to talk about.
I shouldn't be out there in the field.
Not if it's gonna make the woman I love
worry, so you tell Alex I am out.
Why don't you stand tall
and tell her yourself?
- No. It's better coming from you.
- No, no. Why don't you tell her yourself?
Thank you.
I love you.
Is he watching? He walked away?
Many of you might not know me,
but I'm Chuck's and Ellie's mom.
Truth be told...
I was gone for a long time.
Now that I am back in their lives,
I sometimes overcompensate.
But lucky for me,
my soon-to-be daughter-in-law...
is very forgiving.
She's never heard me say it...
but Sarah is one of the strongest...
and one of the most amazing women
that I have ever met.
So I would like to propose this toast
to her.
Sarah, thank you for taking care
of my Chuck.
May you have
many more adventures together...
and may you always
keep each other safe.
Thank you.
- I love you.
Now for the little surprise
I've been cooking up for you.
Excuse me. Hi.
Chuck, there's something
I need to tell you about the video. It's...
What about the video?
This is the first day of my life
I swear I was born right in the doorway
Lester never let you see my version.
Hope you like it.
- Everything changed
They're spreading blankets on the beach
Yours is the first face that I saw
Think I was blind before I met you
Now I don't know where I am
I don't know where I've been
What is this garbage?
- Where I want to go
And so I thought I'd let you know
That these things take forever
I especially am slow
But I realize that I need you
And I wondered if I could come home
- Hello?
- Hello, Chuck.
I hope I'm not interrupting
anything important.
Vivian, what do you want?
To make you feel pain.
The way I feel right now.
I've lost everyone important to me.
And I have you and your family
to thank for it.
Wait, wait, wait.
We can talk about this.
Or how about you look around the room
at all your family and friends...
and ask yourself
which one am I gonna take from you?
Yous see,
I still have another Norseman device.
Please, please.
Vivian, this is not you, okay?
You don't do things like this.
Please don't do this.
I already have.
What's going on?
I think Vivian is gonna try
and kill my mom.
God, what is that noise?
Sarah?
Sarah. Sarah. Sarah. No, no, no.
No, no, no. Sarah!
Help me!
Help me, help me. Somebody help.
Call 911. Are you calling 911?
Oh, my God. Oh, my God.
Oh, my God. Baby, baby, baby.
Baby, hey. Baby? Oh, my God.
Hey, hey.