And the king was freed, and
the castle was restored,
and the Frost Queen
returned home once more.
This time, she was a hero.
And the Frost Queen
promised her children
that she would never
ever leave them again.
- Good story?
- I liked it.
- The prince was cool.
- Yes, he was.
Just like my little Chuck.
- Mom?
- Yeah?
Are you going away again?
Just for a few days, then
right back to you and Ellie.
Good night, honey.
Love you.
Not nearly as much as I love you.
My mom was a spy.
After she disappeared, my father spent
the rest of his life trying to find her.
Ellie and I thought she left us, that she
just walked away, but what if we were wrong?
I need your help.
I need you to help me find my mom.
Holy cow!
I cannot belie this
was beneath your house.
This is nuts!
A secret spy base. I mean, it's
got lasers and gadgets and...
neatly organized files.
Listen, why don't you
just tell Casey and Sarah?
Because I know what
they're gonna try and do;
They're gonna try and stop me.
They cannot.
I have to find the
truth, Morgan why my mom left,
why she never came back.
- This is my search.
- No. It's our search. I'm in.
Thanks.
- Are you flexing?
- What? No, I was just kinda...
- I'm excited.
- Okay, good, good.
I can't even tell you how much
I appreciate your help on this.
But listen, one
very, very, very important thing
we cannot tell anyone, not a soul.
Not Sarah, not Casey, not
Awesome, not Ellie.
- Not Ellie.
- I get it, I know.
You promised her you weren't
gonna be a spy, you know?
So she clearly cannot know
about our little rogue spy team
- Buddy.
- Yeah?
This is not the opening of a TV show.
This is real life.
Sarah, honey, is this the
gun you were looking for?
- Yes, thank you.
- I got everything, dude.
- You ready to go?
- She's still here?
Hurry up.
Yeah?
You're the best. Thank you so much.
- A spy mission without me.
- Couples do this all the time, right?
It's just a business trip.
- Are you okay with this?
- Yeah, yeah, yeah, I'm fine. I'm, you know.
I' got job interviews and Morgan
and I are gonna spend quality time.
He signed us up for a go
cart racing league, so...
Come home soon.
I'm gonna be sick. Come
on, Walker, we got real work to do.
Like se the free world.
Enjoy your retirement, Bartowski.
What am I, what do I say? What do we...?
- I love you.
- That's good. I love you. I like that.
I love you, too.
Be safe, okay?
Nothing is gonna keep me
from coming back to you.
- Better not.
- Bye.
Mr. Carmichael, we're all set.
I have our tickets, cloned
passports, money belts.
Let's do this. Back in the
game. Me and you, real spies.
Sunblock. We need sunblock.
Excuse me.
Very sorry. Pardon me.
I knew it. I was right.
My mom's safe house.
This is where she got all of
her missions when I was a kid.
You know, speaking as the bookkeer
for our int checki account,
it mightave been a bit more affoable iwe
started here and then traveled e world.
We, we dn't really kw
about re, now did we?
- You got the code, buddy?
- Yeah.
Yeah, code, code, code. Here you go.
And if we t second, we need to he a lile
bit of a bget conversation just because...
Morga not now.
This is it.
My dad never made it this far.
Okay, Mom, where are you?
And it's not empty right? Please
tell me that it's not empty.
I don't get it. I don't get it. All
the intel led right back here.
No. No, no, no, there's got to be something.
There's got to be something.
There's got to be a... a...
a secret compartment, you know?
Or a passageway or some clue
that finally leads us to my mom.
- Yeah.
- Come on. Come on! Come on!
There's nothing.
Okay, so we didn't find your mom, but,
maybe we found a new dumpling house, huh?
All right, I don'know.
Let's pack it up, head home.
Fuel up on some dumplings and
start again from scratch, okay?
Now we can do this, you and I...
All right.
We got close this time.
I know we're going to find her.
Chuck.
Chuck 4x01 - Versus the Anniversary
Talk to me, buddy, you know?
Let it out. You want to cry? Go
for it. I got two good shoulders.
What are we doing?
Why are we even bothering
looking for my mom?
My dad ruined his life
trying to find her.
She could have come back any
time she wanted to, you know?
We're easy to find. Her, not so much.
I'm done, man. I think I'm done.
Listen, you had to try, right?
- Don't move, Chuck.
- Get over here!
Morgan. Morgan, Morgan. Coming, coming.
Give me them keys.
Yeah, here you go, sir. Here
they are. Here are your keys.
Just don't, please
don't shoot me or Chuck.
Look, if this is has anything to do
with my mom or or Albania or Tangiers,
- or that that cafe in Budapest which was...
- Oh, that was not even...
Anyway, the point is we have
explanations for all of that.
What are you talking about? I'm
here for the car. I'm a repo man!
- Repo man. Morgan?
- Right.
- We haven't made a payment in four months.
- The car cost $900.
Yeah, but we're $43,000
in debt. I was gonna..
- What? What?43 what?
- $43,000 debt, and that's...
that's above the CIA money you
had saved up because being a spy,
apparently is really expensive.
Why didn't you... why
didn't you tell me?
- Well, you were so busy looking for your mom...
- Enough chitchat.
Get away from that car.
Just, Chuck, give him a little, you
know what I mean, Intersect style.
I don't do kung fu anymore, buddy.
You got some chop socky, boy?
No, no chop socky here, sir. Fresh
out of chop socky.
- Take the car.
- That's what I thought.
*****get a job!
Working on it.
You know, Chuck, this does
not happen to real spies.
HONG KONG, CHINA
I'm cornered. What do I do?
Use the device.
Make a move and you're dead, Marko.
Please, make a move.
I thought you said the EMP was a fake.
I was wrong. Beautiful, isn't it?
Volkoff Industries'
handheld EMP generator.
Will fry every electric
circuit in a three klick radius.
Volkoff's upping the ante.
The building's elevators
are knocked out.
Mr. Volkoff's agents
will be here in minutes.
You're trapped.
Put down your guns.
You know, he really should be here.
Chuck's the Intersect. We could
use him on a mission like this.
I hate cracking into computer systems.
Well, he made a promise to his sister.
Chuck doesn't want to be a spy
and have to lie about it, too.
Your boyfriend needs some big boy pants.
He's a spy, he's good at it.
- I know, Casey. You miss him, too.
- What? I don't miss him.
- By the way, good idea to bring the chutes.
- Thank you.
Yes. Nice. I like this. But I less back.
Maybe just kind of a...
Hold that. Hold that. Right there, this
whole sleepy confusion thing.
- That's digital sex right there, my friend.
- Morgan, what are you doing?
I'm putting the spark back in
your relationship, dude. Trust me.
- Sarah's going to love these.
- What?
Good. Yeah. Actually, if you don't
mind, I'll hit the peck deck a little bit.
And put baby oil, please. Lube it up.
- What? Ba ba... What? No, no, no.
- Lube it up. Grease it up.
- Whatever you're doing, please stop.
- Okay. Okay.
I know you're down about your mom, Chuck.
Let's you and I have a little
talk right now, man to man.
Okay. Okay. Man to man talk.
What are you doing in
my room with baby oil?
More importantly, you and Sarah, okay?
'Cause every morning you're
waking up missing her,
acting like a sad sack.
I mean, I I understand
a little bit, you know,
you're you're stuck in this long distance
relationship right now that's short on intimacy.
That's okay. It's all right.
But what you need to do is open
your mind to what sex truly is.
It's sexting.
Short for sext writing.
It's intimacy for
people in your situation.
Sexting.
Sex... sexting.
- Sexting.
- Sexting. Buddy.
Now that the terrible ids are t of the
way, I told Ellie about the job hunt,
and she's already lined up
five interviews for today.
Okay. I'll grab our bus passes.
But, remember, sexting?
Yeah, sex talk? No, not going to happen.
Good luck on the job hunt.
Fine. Do it myself.
Vandalay Industries
I am so glad you could come in.
You know, with a like this
and a degree from Stanford,
it's astounding you haven't
been snatched up already.
Snatch me up.
I'm 100% snatchable.
I'm sorry, I don't use the word snatch
very often for a myriad of reasons.
Relax.
Why are you so nervous?
You know, I'm not normally.
I I'm normally... I'm
normally a smooth operator.
Like Sade. But..
Today has been a
strange, day of interviews.
Really? Well, how?
Well, for starters, have you ever had
anyone fall asleep in an interview?
Just after that, the person sitting
in your position got a little ill.
Just after that, the interviewer
started going into convulsions...
The last interview I just came from, they they
told me they were going for a cup of coffee,
and then they never came back.
I mean, how long does
it take to get coffee?
- That's really crazy.
- Yeah.
Well, I think, Chuck, that I
have some good news for you.
- Good.
- Yeah.
How would you like to join...?
I thought I told them to hold my calls.
I I... I... I don't think it's a
good idea for you to answer that.
Hello.
Yes.
It's about you.
What?
Is... is everything okay?
What's happening? Who is that?
Unfortunately, Mr. Bartowski, the
position's been filled.
What's happening? Who was that?
And I'm going to have security
escort you from the building.
Wait. I'm s... Wait, wait, wait, wait.
Hang on a second. What did I
do? Who was that on the phone?
Perhaps I could explain
whatever the situation is.
Gentlemen, this is
completely uncalled for.
Look on the bright side, Chuck.
The bus has much more
legroom than the hatchback.
- There's a conspiracy against me.
- I don't know. I...
always feel that way
after a bad interview.
Except, with me, the conspiracy
has been going on a lot longer.
You know? Like,
- kindergarten.
- Morgan, what am I supposed to do now?
These were Ellie's best leads. Where
am I going to find a job?
Well, there's... always one place.
Where?
I can't believe it's back, Chuck.
It's beautiful.
I can't believe how
fast they rebuilt it.
Oh...
...my...
Lord.
Welcome to the Buy
More. We're not open yet
but we are currently accepting
rsums. Are you interested?
For what?
A job.
Maybe.
What what, types of
positions are available?
I'm sure the store manager
can help you with that.
Have at it.
Good luck.
So nervous.
Do you want me to show
you around the store?
Yes, please. That would be
delightful. Should I hold your hand?
- No, you should not.
- Okay. Lead on.
Hello.
My name is Chuck Bartowski, and,
- it's funny, I used to work here.
- You still do work here.
Hello, Chuck. Welcome back.
Beckman had kittens when
I told her about the EMP.
She wants us to find out where Volkoff's
building it so we can blow the place up.
Another mission? We've been at it for
months, and I haven't seen Chuck in...
- forever.
- There's something else.
Beckman wants Chuck to come down here, take
a look at the EMP, see if he flashes.
Chuck is a civilian now.
We can't force him to be a spy, can we?
You might want to tell
Beckman that yourself.
Chuck.
As you can see, we spared no
expense recreating the Buy More.
- Yeah, General, I I appreciate the tour and all...
- It's no longer simply a retail store.
It's now a full fledged
CIA NSA substation.
We can patch into security
cameras all over the world.
Satellite relays
NORAD, NASA, Strategic Air Command.
Hit that red button, we go to DEFCON 1.
Is that, is that really the safest
place to put that out in the open?
There's a new laser
based security system.
General, this is crazy. You
realize this is crazy.
No, it's not. After the success
of Operation Bartowski,
- the president made you a priority.
- I beg your pardon.
The the the president president?
Like, the actual... You're
being totally serious.
General, I am out of the spy game.
You're out when I say you're out.
If memory serves, you actually
said, Chuck, you are out of the spy game.
I changed my mind. You're
back. Discussion over.
And don't think you're
going to find another job.
Why...?
You... you... you. That was
you on the phone, wasn't it?
You tanked my interviews, didn't you?
- Sarah. Back in town? - Chuck, listen to me.
You do not have to be a spy.
No, no. I know. Yeah. Beckman
just offered me a position,
and I turned her down.
How did she react?
Well, she...
Chuck, hello?
That went well, I think.
I'm... I'm sorry. I should
have called, but we just got in.
No, it's fine 'cause you're
here, and I'm here, and...
and I miss you a lot.
I missed you, too.
- This is the mission that just won't end.
- I get it. It's important work, okay?
But you're here now at least
for a little while, right?
- Few weeks? Days? Hours? Enough sap.
- Sarah, what...
- Let's take a look at the mission at hand.
Flash. - What are you...?
Well?
Thanks, Casey.
EMP, manufactured in Venezuela
at the Corta Verona facility,
which is a subsidiary of Volkoff
Industries. Who's Volkoff? Don't tell me.
Alexei Volkoff arms dealer, recluse.
He's like the Russian Howard Hughes.
We've been chasing after him for
months, and with that single flash,
we might just be able to take him down.
Good to have you back.
- I'm not staying.
- I think he misses you.
I know he does.
This is nuts, man. The Buy More
is being run by the CIA. Amazing.
Which would make you a spy?
- You are very perceptive, Mr. Grimes.
- Guilty.
I got to say, the new Castle
is pretty freaking sweet.
And it's nice to be
back down in here with u.
- Chuck, can we talk?
- Of course. Anytime. About what?
Well, I know this is awkward, but,
I just have to ask about the picture.
What, what picture?
Chuck, do you want to sext with me?
No! I don't... I mean... I...
No. No, no. No, this isn't my
idea. Cleary not my idea.
This was Morgan's doing.
Well, don't worry. I...
I thought it was cute.
Here's the thing I don't
know if you know this, but,
I actually was an agent myself
for a little while last year.
What if we got together, maybe...
show each other a few moves?
You know, I... I have a trip
to Thailand in the morning.
Sure. Sure.
- It's a new mission.
- Of course. It's the life of a...
I could show you something right now.
- Really? Yeah.
- You know.
So, six nine month
anniversary. What do you think?
Well, I I have to go away again, but when
I come back, we will celebrate in style.
Fantastic. No phones necessary.
Unless you want. I don't
know what that means.
Forget I even said anything.
- What is... what is this?
- The emblem? That's Volkoff's.
He is not afraid to advertise.
Well, I have to go debrief with
Beckman and Casey, but we'll talk later?
Yeah, great.
New Buy More rules.
Slides and trap doors and the
new superspy Nerd Herder, Greta.
Be still, my beating heart.
- She digs me. I can tell.
- Morgan.
We need to get the car back.
With the creepy guy?
Okay, I'm sorry. Again, tell
me why we're here.
I mean, this menu's
linked to an arms dealer?
Look, I thought the last
mission was a bust, okay?
But the menu could be the
link that brings us to my mom.
Maybe she was after Volkoff
just like Casey and Sarah.
Okay, listen, I get the menu
we get out of here quietly.
Yes, yes, quick and quiet.
There it is.
You young, oversexed, underworked kids.
You don't mess with a repo man.
Not ever! Yes, sir. Yes, sir, Mr. repo
man, sir.
We are not here to mess with you. We just...
Morgan, get the... get the... get the menu!
Repo man, Excuse me for one second.
I'm just going to just, very
slowly... I'm just going to kind of...
He's just reaching...
Here we go. Perfect.
Please, this is all we want and then
we're leaving. We're out of your hair.
You want a menu, for what?
- Chinese.
- Dumplings.
Yeah?
A good place?
- No. It's... No.
- I like good Chinese.
Hard to find.
Hand it over.
Buddy, you remember how we got
out of that jam in Tangiers?
Tangiers? Think it'll work?
Tangiers? What does that mean?
It means that we need
to run! Run! RunRun! Run!
Damn you!
I love dumplings.
It's really weird.
Most of these are just
your run of the mill dishes,
but a few of these I
haven't even heard of before.
Which ones? Which dishes?
For example, this. Shimira Chicken.
Shimira. Okay, Shimira is
actually a nav system for spy subs.
This is not a menu for ordering
food. This is a menu for ordering weapons.
Why would your mom have that?
Let's call and find out.
Use your dad's encrypted phone.
Who is this?
Identify.
This is Carmichael.
I work for the Ring.
The Ring was eliminated.
We are an offshoot of the Ring.
The New Ring.
I'm the head of security.
I'll need to see your organization
firsthand if we agree to work.
Then you'll have to come to
Volkoff Industries in Moscow.
Moscow, Russia.
Not a problem. The New
Ring has very deep pockets.
We're going to Russia.
Okay. I'm going to have to
sell my Millennium Falcon.
And God bless you.
- Are you still ther?
- Yes, I'm here.
Just tell me when and
where. We have a jet on standby.
Okay, so we I. D. Volkoff's facility
and we can take it out
with a single drone strike.
Have you ever been in a
long distance relationship?
No.
I either leave or they die.
I'm going to the head.
Please fasten your seat belts. We're
heading into a bit of turbulence.
Release the gas. I'll
reroute the flight to Moscow.
Moscow, Russia.
Where are we?
Desolation, frostbite.
Must be Russia.
Welcome to Volkoff Industries.
I'm glad you could finally make it.
Take a load off.
Relax.
And think about all the
terrible things I will do to you.
We're pros, Marko.
Your methods won't work on us.
Remember, I work for Volkoff.
I must break you.
Remember the plan.
We have to access the Volkoff computer
system to see what they have on my mom.
- Does that make sense?
- Completely.
Although I think my
face is still frozen.
Hello.
We're with the Ring.
The New Ring.
This is Charles Carmichael.
I'm Michael Carmichael.
So, if you wouldn't mind...
Frigid in here, as well.
The plan was for me to be Carmichael
and you to be Sven, my mute assistant.
See, here's the thing. These
people respect a beard.
And that whole assistant thing... I
don't know. I see us more as brothers.
Is that so?
Okay, okay, fine.
What parents in their right mind would name their
child Michael if their last name was Carmichael?
That's crazy. What were
your parents thinking?
What were our parents thinking?
You know. It's what people in
the movie business call improv.
Nice photo.
Good work, Walker. Get the phone.
Former Kgb Facility
I know where the server is.
It's actually not far from where we are.
If my father's codes still
work, we should be able to get in.
What do you think?
Maybe you drop a little
Intersect style on these fools.
Karate chop your way in.
I will hide behind
the receptionist desk.
You know, that, or we could
just run really fast.
Tangiers? Here?
Tangiers. Exactly.
Could work.
The case. One, two, three. We go.
Come on.
I almost got it.
I've never run so fast
in so many layers before.
- Game time.
- Yup.
- This place is nuts.
- Yeah, it's a Cold War relic, buddy.
Dude, what is this?
Morgan, that's an EMP, so
I wouldn't touch that.
- This is an EMP?
- Yes, it is.
No touching, Morgan. Got ya. Got ya.
Good work, Walker. Call Beckman.
No, I can't call. It's gonna be too
loud. I'll text Chuck. I was texting before.
- Your phone.
- Yeah, I'm kind of busy right now.
Sarah.
- She's sexting you.
- Not now, Morgan.
Got ya. Go on... my lady.
What does he say?
- He thinks we're sexting.
- What?
What does that even mean?
SOS. SOS.
Skin on skin.
Yes, please.
- Come on.
- Filthy.
- He still thinks we're sexting.
- You kiss your mom with those thumbs?
- Oh, my God!
- Oh, my God.
Daddy likes. you're in
trouble. Daddy likes.
Someone's coming.
We're inside Volkoff. Subbasement
four. Tell him!
Got it. Bypassed their security. I'm in.
Awesome. Awesome. Anything?
Well, there's nothing coming up with
her name, but I'm checking aliases,
missions my dad thought she
went on or weapons she was after.
Wait a minute. Frost.
Frost.
The Frost Queen.
My mom used to tell me a stories when I was
a kid about the Frost Queen. That can't be it.
Well, either way, let's download
it and get out of here.
It's encrypted. It's encrypted.
But I have a program that can hack it,
- and then we can download it. Right.
- Quickly.
Wait a minute.
- Crap.
- What?
It's Sarah, but it's... I I
thought she was sexting, dude.
She's here with Casey, and
they're in trouble.
Dude, what do we do? Call Beckman.
I'll call Beckman, or CIA, or the
Marines, because someone's got to save 'em.
Who's gonna save 'em?
We are.
Enough with the toes.
No one's coming.
I would love nothing more than
to put bullets in both your heads.
Yeah, go ahead and do
it. Don't jabber. Just do it.
The problem is you're not the
two agents I'm looking for.
In the past six months, two CIA agents have gotten
closer to Volkoff Industries than any other spy.
They're ghosts.
They expertly use public
transportation to avoid being tracked.
So tell me...
who are these master spies?
- No idea.
- Never seen 'em.
Morgan, this way.
Back, back, back, back, back, back, back.
- We've got them they're in the building.
- They're here.
They must have come for you.
Well, that's their first mistake.
This entire building... is a trap.
So, buddy, how rusty is your kung fu?
I haven't used it in months.
Great.
So... do you want to
speak to your friend?
Chuck, what's going
on? What are you doing here?
Sarah, I know you must have a lot of questions for me
right now, and I promise I will explain everything later.
Listen, you've got to flash, okay? You've
got to get out of here.
- I've heard enough. - No, please,
this is a big mistake. He's not a spy.
- Kill them.
- No, please, no.
Well, it all seemed a bit anticlimactic.
I'm gonna tear you limb
from limb from limb.
Okay, I got it.
Somebody please shoot this guy?
Hello?
Yes, who is it?
Look, you clearly have no idea who I am since
you only sent ten of your men to take care of me,
so let me break it down for you if
you touch one hair on Sarah's head,
I will do to you what
I've just done to your men.
Do you understand?
I'm coming down there right now.
Scary enough?
I'm scared. I was scared when you...
You are not rusty at
all, Chuck. You are limber.
I suggest you start
running... right about now.
Follow me.
That hurts. I'm so out of spy shape.
What the hell are you doing here?
Saving your lives, okay? Let's
just call it that for now.
- I'm good.
- Cut me free.
I got some Russians to kill.
Not yet there's one
more thing I have to do.
I'm waiting for you, and
I don't like to wait.
Boss, the Americans have escaped.
Chuck, why are we here?
What, the computer? This
is what you came here for?
Look, Sarah, I have to tell you the truth.
I took over my father's
search for my mom.
She's a spy, she is a spy, I I don't know.
I thought I could find her, I could
save her, I could bring her home.
- You should have told me.
- You would have tried to stop me.
Of course I would have. I
don't want you to get hurt.
Sarah, I have to do this. This is my
mom, okay, I need to know the truth.
No lying that was our rule.
In all fairness, I was just, you
know, keeping a secret. I wasn't lying.
New rule no secrets, no lies.
- Starting now.
Great, you've made up. Now, how
do we get out of here?
You can't get out.
This is a living
building, totally automated.
The security system is activated.
If you die, you die.
That sounds ominous.
Hope the file was worth it, Chuck.
We're sitting ducks in here.
Sorry, Mom.
Chuck, what are you doing?
If I set off the EMP, it disables
the building and we walk out of here.
But, Chuck, the computer. You'll lose
the file. You might never find your mom.
Yeah, well, it's not worth losing you.
Any of you.
Yeah, we get it. Pull the trigger.
Okay, great, great plan. Now what?
Now we employ the best commie
rifle ever invented Comrade AK 47.
Move it. Let's go. Let's go.
- Everybody alive?
- I'm okay, I'm okay, a little cold
- but...
- Anyone that matters?
Where's the getaway car?
Happy anniversary?
Happy anniversary.
So that's it.
That's the whole story.
Well, I'm just peeved you
didn't ask us for help.
I'm sorry.
Will you help me find my mom?
Yes.
Yes, of course.
But, Chuck, you know what this means.
You're going to have to
rejoin the Agency and be a spy.
I know.
The question is do we
tell Beckman about my mom?
No, not yet.
Chuck, what about your sister?
What are you going to tell Ellie?
I have to tell her the truth.
I have to tell her that I am a spy.
Chuck.
Sorry, I didn't mean to scare you.
That's okay.
How are you?
The interview didn't go well?
No, none of 'em, really, but there's
something that I have to do, Ellie.
It's okay, Chuck.
I know.
What?
I saw the new Buy More.
Right, yeah, I did get a job there.
- Ellie, I'm not that's not what I...
- It's okay, Chuck. It's a job.
Those are really hard to
come by these days, so...
My turn.
Let's sit down.
Okay.
What's up?
I'm pregnant.
What?
Are you what, seriously?!
I I was going to wait
until Devon got home, but I,
- I saw you and I had to tell you.
- Oh, my God.
Oh, my God, I'm so, my God, I'm hugging you.
I am I did I hurt the baby?
I hurt the child.
Chuck.
Oh, my God, that's amazing.
I'm really happy right now, Chuck.
I mean, I'm starting a family a new family
and you have Sarah and you're safe and...
just I'm really so happy right now.
I couldn't tell her, not now.
She doesn't want me to be a spy, but
our dad gave me this mission to
find our mom, to know the truth.
I can't not do this.
I have to do this.
That's not being a
spy, that's being a brother.
I cracked into the deep database for
your mom and this is all I could find.
Look at the top of the page.
She was captured?
Yeah, and there's
nothing else after that.
This whole time, Ellie and I
thought that our mom left us
because she didn't care
about us, but she was taken.
Are you going to tell Ellie?
No.
No, not yet.
If my mom is still alive, I'm going
to find her and bring her home.
Why did you bring me here?
I found out some interesting
information about you.
Someone is looking for you.
Who?
Your family.
Have you told Volkoff anything?
No, I told him nothing.
That's good.
That is... very, very good.
Please.
I have a family.
So do I.