OK, my people!
Rise and shine. Get up, Stripe.
Hey. You awake yet?
Yeah, sure as shit
ain't dreaming no more.
Company!
Something went down last night
in Her Falls
a village about three miles east.
We've got reports of a food store
broken into, shit stolen.
Locals think it's roaches.
Roaches!
We head out in five minutes. Let's go!
Hey, so, it looks like you're getting
your first real-live roach hunt?
Hey, new!
New!
It's Stripe.
Here's a little tip just in case
you get your first toe-to-toe
with one of them roaches today.
When you see one right here
try not to shit your pants.
It's only gonna piss them off.
I'll try.
- Try to ignore Len.
His aim's so bad,
he's the only guy on Earth
who could shit his own pants and miss.
Fuck you, farm girl.
- Farm girl?
Yeah.
Hunting's in my blood.
Some of us are naturals.
- Moving out!
Woo! Yeah!
Whoa, whoa, whoa. OK.
You can speak now.
It must have been roaches.
Roaches, you see them?
You see?
/ didn't see them.
! heard them.
All the mess. It must have been them.
Want a cookie?
Here you go.
- They've been in the food.
We'll have to destroy
everything they left.
No one will eat it.
We can replace that, OK?
They destroyed the cooler.
Broke it and took the parts.
The cooler?
They stole parts from the cooler?
Which way did they go?
There were footprints
in the dirt leading that way.
Parn Heidekker.
Heidekker? Is that a name?
Stop them coming.
Please, you must stop.
OK.
I have child who is scared.
I will. I promise.
Stripe!
OK. Our friend here thinks
that the roaches
went in the direction
of Parn Heidekker's place.
Local oddball, seems to be some kind
of religious freak.
Anderson, Haque, I want you to stay here
and help them torch the food.
Keep them calm and reassured.
The rest of you, we're gonna
drop in on Heidekker.
Ask some questions,
sniff around the place.
If there's roaches, we show we're
ready for them. Let's go.
So Mr Heidekker is not exactly
what you call a socialite or a mingler.
Seems like mental health issues.
He's got some interesting views
on roaches, by all accounts.
I'm putting his info
in your MASS system now.
Been complaints lodged against him
going months back.
Locals claim that he let roaches
cross his land, left food out for them.
Could be just shit talk
from the local villagers though so...
Yo, how many roaches
we got left out here?
A couple of thousand?
A couple of hundred, if that?
I mean, back home
we had millions, man.
It only took two years
to get shit back on track.
Out here you got rustic fucks
throwing them scraps.
Man, no wonder it's taking so long
to mop shit up.
But how can anyone be dumb enough
to help a fucking roach?
Hell, yeah.
Portals front and rear.
Windows blacked out.
Chimney smoke. Someone's home.
Lennard, you use the boomer.
OK, MASS check.
Everyone got the layout?
- Check.
Check.
Aikin, Balcon, Coach,
you check the outbuildings here.
Take 'em one at a time and slow.
Stripe, Raiman,
you come with me and Lennard.
We go in here.
Len and I will talk to Heidekker,
you check the rest of the house.
OK.
Optimal outcome, no shots fired.
- Except on a roach.
Morning, sir.
There's no need for this.
I speak your language.
OK.
What is it you want?
- Just to talk.
That's what we're doing.
It'd be a little more neighbourly
if we did it inside.
Check the upstairs rooms.
Relax. I'm not your enemy.
Where are they?
Where are who?
You know,
we got a whole bunch
of frightened, angry people
in that village.
Roaches have been breaking
into the food stores, stealing supplies.
You know anything about that?
No.
See, it's not just what they stole.
All that food left is
gonna be destroyed.
- No one's gonna eat it.
- Stripe.
Makes life harder for everyone.
Cross on the wall there.
You got principles.
Think all life is sacred. And I get it.
I agree. All life is sacred so...
you even gotta protect the roaches.
Right?
It's not their fault they're like that.
They didn't ask for this.
I get it. We get it.
There's shit in their blood
that made them that way.
The sickness they're carrying.
That doesn't care about
the sanctity of life
or the pain about who else
is gonna suffer.
We don't stop the roaches,
then five, ten, twenty years from now
you're still gonna get kids born that way,
and then they're gonna breed.
Bingo.
And so it goes on. That cycle of pain.
That sickness.
And it could have been avoided.
Fuckin' roach nest.
You check in there.
I'll take the stairs.
Every roach you save today
you condemn God knows how many people
to despair and misery tomorrow.
You can't still see them as human.
Understandable sentiment, granted,
but it's misguided.
We gotta take them out if humankind
is gonna carry on in this world.
That's just the hard truth.
Gotta make sacrifices.
The fuck?
Help me out here!
Fuck!
♪ Try to shame me ♪
♪ And still I'll care for you ♪
♪ You can run around ♪
♪ Even put me down ♪
♪ I'll still be there for you ♪
Rai.
Come on, we gotta listen to
Mr Sunday School
all the way back to base?
You can cover your ears.
Yeah, or...
I'll just hit permanent mute.
Lower your weapon.
Roach lover counts as a kill, too, right?
He's a civ, right?
You shoot a civ, that's gonna stay
with you the rest of your life.
Yo, Stripe, why don't you,
pull the stick out of your ass?
Because I'm fucking with him,
not you.
I guess I had you both going, right?
Alright!
Let's torch the place.
Hey, you OK, man?
Yeah.
I heard you popped one in there.
- Two.
Wait, two?
I got another one, with my knife.
With your knife? Holy shit!
Pretty good, right?
- Yeah, you fucking Terminator.
Damn.
First time out, he gets two.
You lucky motherfucker, man.
Sweet dreams for this asshole.
Gonna get a treat tonight.
Woo-hoo! Woo!
I love you.
Whoa! Miss Sharp Shooter.
Patronising fuck!
Ruthless! You're the Grim Reaper.
Yeah, well, no roach
gets away next time.
Are you still sweating that?
Well, I grew up tracking deer.
You never give up.
I don't like it when they get away.
Nice.
Yeah, if that fucker made it
to the forest
he probably made it to the border,
gone for good.
Yeah, it's alright for you.
You popped two of 'em.
It's been a while for me.
You know,
the gal is getting twitchy.
Come on, Rai.
You sleep good?
Yeah, I slept OK.
What, that's all you're
gonna give me?
OK?
You know,
if I got two in one go
I would want to come
for like an hour!
Alright, shut up. Man.
Alright.
That's the way.
Hey, you OK, man?
Yeah, think I'm tired is all.
All right,
so you did have a good night.
39, 40, 41...
42...
43, 44, 45, 46
47, 48, 49
50, 51, 62
53, 54, 55
56, 57, 58, 59...
Strong and pure.
Hey, Stripe, you OK?
- Yeah.
I mean, I don't know.
I feel a little off.
I mean, I ain't sick or nothing.
It's just...
Report to the sick bay.
Running diagnostic.
What do you see?
A cube.
Rotating?
- Yeah.
And now?
- A tree.
Like an apple tree.
- Touch the apples for me.
Full marks.
So you say you had like a headache?
- Yeah, but just quick.
Nothing big, just...
Well, everything looks OK.
No sign of any malfunction
or dropout with your MASS implant.
And physically,
you're in exemplary shape.
You've just seen combat,
you can expect some sort of side effect.
There was this, this thing...
with a light on it at the farmhouse.
A roach had it.
- A roach had it?
Kind of like a flashlight.
- Flashlight?
Kinda.
I don't know.
Seriously, you're fine. Your MASS is fine.
Blood's fine. It's all fine.
OK. Yeah.
Maybe you should speak to Arquette.
Who's Arquette?
So, you must be 'Koinanchey.'
Koinange.
Folks call me Stripe.
Why would they call you that?
Couldn't pronounce Koinange either,
I guess.
That's funny.
- Thank you.
At ease, son. Sit down.
So you recently logged
your first kills?
Two roaches?
First time out. It's impressive.
Yeah, I guess.
So what happened?
What, with the kills?
I'm in this, farmhouse.
There's this, like,
hidden room or something.
We go in and there they are.
First one, I just... It was automatic.
Just pop-pop, you know?
Right. Just like in training.
Yeah, just like that, yeah.
Yeah.
And the second?
- I mean, he was on the ground with me.
He?
It was a he.
So, this was close quarters then?
Yeah, he was on top of me.
Struggling, I mean.
I couldn't reach my rifle
so I had to stick him.
Stick... stick /.
With my knife.
And how did that... feel?
What, like...?
- Emotionally.
I didn't.
I mean, it was quick.
It was self-protection.
I guess all I felt was, you know, relief.
Just relief?
It's not unusual to experience
other feelings, too.
A moment of euphoria even.
Yeah, I guess.
I don't know,
I thought maybe I'd feel...
I don't know.
Something else?
Yeah, like... regret
Something like that,
but that just wasn't there.
So you'd do it again?
Yeah, sure.
So... why are you here?
I don't know. I mean...
I had a few weird moments.
My MASS looked like
it was glitching out.
But your implants, I mean,
they passed every diagnostic.
There is nothing wrong with that.
- Yeah, they said it's fine.
I don't know, I think I just...
...felt like something was up with it.
But there's not.
- No.
You did a big thing.
You should be proud of yourself.
OK?
It'll pass.
Let's get you a good sleep tonight?
A real good sleep.
Fuck me.
Way to go, fuck fingers.
OK, it seems Heidekker
didn't stay silent too long
once we got to work on him.
He's given up a location.
Some place the roaches
have been scavenging.
Well, alright.
It's a housing project
that's been empty since the war.
It's not far from here.
So Control wants us to do some recon
before we go back to base.
Can we hurry it up here?
We ought to burn the whole
forest down?
Give those roaches nowhere to run.
OK, you see that?
Solar panel looks cleaner than the rest.
And there are some cables.
It's got to be roaches leeching power.
Why here?
Christ knows.
All right.
Better dial it in.
Control. This is Medina.
Positive ID. Signs of activity here
at the housing project location.
Sighted one solar panel.
Looks recently wiped clean
and some caballing.
Roger so far.
You alright there?
- I can smell the grass.
We can't usually smell nothing.
You ever noticed that?
- No, I never noticed that.
Requesting course of action.
Didn't read. Please repeat.
OK.
Control says we should fall back
and await comm...
Shit!
Medina.
Fuck.
Stripe, get back!
She's dead. Come on!
OK. Ready? Cover me.
Rai! Rai, come on.
OK.
Fucking roach got a rifle.
Jesus Christ.
Fuck. Piece of shit.
OK, Stripe.
Stripe, come on!
Get it together, dude!
He fired six shots.
His rifle looks old, bolt action.
Should take him ten seconds to reload.
- We go in?
We go in and take him out.
You with me?
I'm with you.
- Let's go!
Follow me!
Ready?
OK, three, two, one. Cover me.
Come on, man! What the fuck?
What the fuck is this shit?
Let's go.
Stripe!
Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa!
It's OK. Hey. Hey. Hey.
Calm down. Calm down.
Calm down.
It's OK. It's OK.
I'm not gonna hurt you.
Look, I'm not gonna hurt you. OK?
Go on, get out of here. Go on.
It's not safe.
There's roaches here.
Go on. Get.
Come on!
- Rai, what did you do?
- Shut up! Come on!
What did you do, Rai?
Got ya.
Rai!
Run!
What the fuck are you doing?
- You're killing them!
- They're roaches!
You're fucking killing them, Rai!
Fuck you!
I don't know what the fuck's
wrong with you, man!
You got some blown shit!
Pull it together!
You alright?
You gotta get out of here.
Come on.
Come on!
What the fuck?
Fuck!
You better run.
Shh. Shh.
Here.
I'm alright.
You see me as I am.
Of course I see you.
You don't see roach?
You ain't a roach.
Roaches is all...
Fucked up?
Roaches don't speak.
You just can't hear us.
The fuck are you talking about?
- Your implants. Your army implants.
The MASS system?
They put it in your head
to help you fight
and when it works,
you see us as something other.
One of us, Luka,
was making a... a machine.
Light flashes.
Said it can interfere with the implant.
You're roaches?
But I've seen roaches.
I've seen them,
they're fucking...
- They're like...
- Animals?
No, they're monsters.
I've seen 'em.
The implant made you see this.
Fuck.
The villagers?
The locals, they...
they ain't army.
They got no MASS in their heads.
They're scared of the roaches.
They hate the fucking things.
- Everybody hates us.
Well, what the fuck do they see?
The fucking civs, when they look
at a roach, what do they see?
What you see now.
They hate all the same
because it's what they've been told.
Ten years ago, it began.
Post-war.
First, the screening programme,
the DNA checks
then the register,
the emergency measures.
And soon everyone calls us creatures.
Filthy creatures.
Every voice. The TV. The computer.
Say we have...
we have sickness in us.
We have weakness.
It's in our blood.
They say that our blood cannot go on.
That we cannot go on.
My name was Catarina.
He was Alec.
Now we're just roach.
But now...
Now you see me.
Rai?
Rai, no!
Tell me I shouldn't kill you.
None of it's true, Rai.
- What the fuck got you?
None of it's true.
Fuck you.
Get up.
Back against the wall.
Get up!
You want me to come in there?
It's alright.
I can just talk to him.
Thank you, Bradley.
Stripe.
We owe you an apology.
We didn't spot the fault
in your MASS.
I got you a coffee.
The device you found in the farmhouse,
you mentioned it to the doctor.
Is this the thing?
We found it on that old block
that you and Raiman were searching.
Looks like they reverse engineered it
from some of our drone parts and so on.
The light here
transmits a code.
It's like a virus.
It burrows into your MASS,
tries to shut it down from within.
I tell you, those roaches
are getting more ingenious
than we give them credit for.
The whole thing is a lie.
I understand why you'd say that, yeah.
Roaches.
They look just like us.
Of course they do.
That's why they're so dangerous.
Humans.
You know,
we give ourselves a bad rap
but we're genuinely empathetic
as a species.
I mean, we don't actually really
want to kill each other.
Which is a good thing.
Until your future depends on
wiping out the enemy.
Come on, sit down.
I don't know how much history
you studied in school.
Many years ago,
I'm talking early 20th century
most soldiers didn't even
fire their weapons.
Or if they did, they would just aim
over the heads of the enemies.
They did it on purpose.
British Army. World War I.
The brigadier,
he'd walk the line with a stick
and he'd whack his men
in order to get them to shoot.
Even in World War I, in a firefight
only 15%, 20% of the men
would pull the trigger.
The fate of the world at stake
and only 15% open fired.
Now, what does that tell you?
It tells me that that war would have
been over a whole lot quicker
had the military got its shit together.
So we adapted.
Better training. Better conditioning.
Then comes the Vietnam War
and the shooting percentage
goes up to 85.
A lot of bullets flying.
The kills were still low.
Plus the guys who did get a kill
well, most of them came back
all messed up in the head.
And that's pretty much how things stayed
until MASS came along.
You see, MASS...
Well, that's the ultimate
military weapon.
It helps you with your intel.
Your targeting. Your comms.
Your conditioning.
It's a lot easier to pull the trigger
when you're aiming at the bogeyman.
It's not just your eyes, though.
Takes care of your other senses, too.
You don't hear the shrieks.
You don't smell the blood and the shit.
They're human beings.
Do you have any idea the amount of shit
that's in their DNA?
Higher rates of cancer.
Muscular dystrophy.
MS. SLS. Substandard IQ.
Criminal tendencies.
Sexual deviances.
It's all there.
The screening shows it.
Is that what you want
for the next generation?
Don't feel bad about doing your job.
The villagers won't do it.
The folks back home won't do it.
They don't have MASS.
MASS lets you do it.
You.
You're protecting the bloodline.
And that, my friend, is an honour.
There's no honour here.
It's just Killing.
Lying and killing.
- No one lied to you.
You knew all of this. All along.
What are you talking about?
You agreed to have your MASS
implant put in.
Set up. Every soldier does.
We can't just embed it
and feed you a dream.
Your mind would reject it.
You have to accept it. Willingly.
It's exactly what you did.
So you see the terms
and conditions there?
Yeah, that's like
a whole essay, man.
What is that?
That's your consent video.
From when you signed up six months ago.
Basically, it says you agree
to MASS implant activation.
I didn't do this.
- Yes, you did.
- Works kind of like hypnosis.
- Yeah, alright.
Part of what you're agreeing to
is not realising
you've been put in this state,
I you follow me.
You won't recall
this conversation.
Yo, that's kind of funny, man.
- Turn it off.
- So for you to register consent...
- Turn it off, man.
...I'm gonna need
your thumbprint there.
- Right here?
- Yes, please.
That's dope.
I didn't do that!
I don't remember that!
- Just like the man said.
I know you're upset.
- Fuck you!
What's happening?
- We control what you see, Stripe.
I can't see nothing.
- Because we control it.
Give me my fucking eyes back.
Let me lay out your options.
- Give me my fucking eyes back, man!
Let me lay out your options!
Option one,
you agree to have your MASS reset.
All the recollections
of the past few days
including this conversation,
erased.
No way.
Option two's incarceration.
I'd advise you to consider.
- Fuck you!
MASS is a friend.
Without it, you will remember
everything that you did.
I ain't having this MASS shit.
No more. No way.
OK.
Well...
Maybe you should see what life
would be like without it.
What's happening?
Where am I?
Heidekker's ranch.
Three days ago.
I have it all logged, Stripe.
We can feed you everything
that you did.
Hey, no, no, no.
Please! Please don't shoot.
Please!
- Don't shoot!
- Wait! Please!
- No! No!
No. Make it stop.
No! Please.
- No, please!
Make it stop!
Please!
No! No!
No!
Fuck off! Stop it!
You will see and smell and feel it all.
Is this what you want?
On a loop? In a cell all alone?
We can make that go away.
This conversation goes away, too.
All of it.
But you gotta say the word.
Just say the word, Stripe.
And it all goes away.
Just say the word.