Stop it!
Stop what?
You're talking
about me in Morse Code.
But you know what? Joke's on
you 'cause I know Morse Code.
Ha!
Yeah, that's what
we're doing.
In our very limited free time
and with our very limited budget,
we went and got a nanny, and
then we went out and took a class
on a very outmoded and very
unnecessary form of communication
just so we can talk
about you in front of you.
Yep, that's exactly
what we did.
It all started when Dwight was tapping
his foot against the leg of his desk.
When I asked him
to stop, he said,
"I will when you
lose the baby weight."
Very well. I must have
imagined it. I apologize.
Detonator? Detonator. Where?
Michael!
Jim, are you
clicking a detonator?
It's a pen.
Michael, come on.
Get back to work,
Dwight. Please.
Fine.
Hey, tap away.
Whoo!
Things with Donna are so...
They're going great!
I... We're just
clicking on every level.
Emotionally, and sexually, and orally.
And I am not used to
relationships going this well.
I'm actually having trouble
focusing on my job.
And I like it
Who enjoys the weekends?
Of course. Now the
weekend is always great
if you have someone, which I
do. I have Donna, she is hot.
She has a Pilates butt.
But we need to find something to
do this weekend beside have sex.
Did I say that?
Yes, I did.
And the reason you are here
is that I need ideas
for things that Donna and I can do
on the weekend. So just shout it out.
I have an idea for your weekend. Okay.
Let me go back to my
desk right now. Okay.
You get out of here,
big dog.
No, no, no, no, you guys
sit down. I need ideas.
Stanley got to go.
Yeah, Well, Stanley
doesn't help with anything.
Come on, shout them out.
Shout them out.
Walk around apple orchards.
Oh!
Super romantic.
That's fun.
Eel fishing.
All right.
Curl up with
your favorite DVD.
You and Donna
should hit the Poconos.
They have heart-shaped
Jacuzzis, room enough for three.
We actually went to the
Poconos last Tuesday.
We headed up there, we went to a
little Chinese bistro, P.F. Chang's.
Why would you go all the way
to the Poconos to P.F. Chang's
when we have
the Great Wall in Scranton?
Because when your
super-hot girlfriend
says, "I want to
go to Mount Pocono,"
you go to Mount Pocono,
and you do her.
And we screwed. Whoops!
TMI!
Wait, that's crazy far. Are
you sure she's not cheating?
You know what, Kelly,
this is the real world.
Not,
The Real World, Scranton.
Oh, my God,
this is super weird.
When Ryan had
two girlfriends,
he used to take me to
some diner in Hazleton
just so the other
girl wouldn't see.
Some diner?
It was the Starlight Diner.
It's in a Life magazine
spread about Americana.
You guys think
Donna's cheating on me?
No. Michael, no.
You had a nice meal with your
girlfriend in a lovely place.
And sex. We had sex, too. That is right.
Don't make any more of it.
How?
How what? How do I not
make any more of it?
You could start by
concluding this meeting.
All right.
Okay. And she won't say, "I love you."
Oh, no.
How many dates
have you been on?
Nine dates. I said
it on the second date.
That seems quick,
even for lesbians.
Does she keep her phone
locked around you, Michael?
Does she watch how much she
drinks around you, Michael?
Does she leave the room
when she takes phone calls?
Does she keep perfume in her
purse? Does she shower before sex?
Does she shower
after sex? Does she...
Yeah, she does all that.
Sorry, dude.
Oh, no, no, no, no.
Michael, do not let
your imagination run amok.
Run what?
Amok.
It means don't let your
imagination run out of control.
Why didn't you
just say that, Pam?
Michael, do not let your
imagination run out of control.
Well, that's easy
for you to say.
You have a bad imagination, it's stupid.
I live in a fantasy world.
You do?
Yes, Jim, I do.
And I can't stay
in a relationship
that is full of
lies and deceit.
But you didn't believe any of
this was true five minutes ago.
That's what makes it so raw.
Ever since I found out that
Donna might be cheating on me,
I have not eaten or slept.
It's the not knowing,
that's what's killing me.
Oh, God, that tickles.
What do you...
I want
someone to follow Donna.
I want her tailed.
I need the name of a
good private investigator.
I think
I've got one for you.
This is you.
How much do you charge?
$100 a day plus expenses.
I'll give you 50.
Money's no object.
Done.
I'm just going to warn you, and
I say this to all my clients,
you might not
like what I find.
Okay.
And you might not
like how I find it.
Of course.
Yeah, that's terrible.
Okay, let me get back to you.
Hey, Stanley, one of my clients just
called and said that their Sabre printer
started smoking
and caught on fire.
My doctor told me to cut out
hotdogs. We all got problems.
Hey, Gabe, I need to talk to you
about something. It's really important.
There's no way that you guys
have any almond butter, right?
Yeah, I don't know. Look,
one of my clients called.
He was in the middle
of a big printing job
and the back of the
printer started smoking
and then the paper
tray caught on fire.
That's weird. I haven't
heard of that happening.
I would even settle
for apricot preserves.
What are we going
to do about this?
I don't know. Call HQ,
see if they know anything.
Yeah, that's what I'll
do today. All right.
Let me know what they say.
Wow, that dude is good.
What do you mean?
You didn't feel like
he was hiding something?
I don't know.
Like he was
covering something up?
Maybe.
Two years ago,
Andy blamed the warehouse
for a late shipment
that he forgot to process.
We got yelled at pretty bad,
almost lost my job.
Man, I was mad as
hell at the time.
But I said, "Darryl,
just wait. He's a fool.
"There's going to be an
opportunity. Just be patient."
Hey, stranger.
Oh, hi.
You work for Michael.
I work with Michael.
Right.
Dwight Schrute.
Donna, hi.
All cases are
solved with logic.
The only logical way to find out if
Donna is a cheater is to seduce her,
bring her to orgasm, then call
Michael and tell him the sad news.
Wow. It's a little early for
ice cream, don't you think?
It's never too early
for ice cream, Jim.
But we didn't
have any ice cream,
so this is mayonnaise
and black olives.
Oh!
Oh, my God.
It's comfort food,
all right?
God!
Michael, this whole Donna
thing is going to be okay.
You just...
Stop beating yourself up.
I know. Well,
I hope you're right.
We'll see what Dwight says.
Why do we have to
see what Dwight says?
Because I have him
investigating her.
I'm waiting for
a text update.
Michael,
no, no, no, no, no, no.
No, no, no, no, no.
Undo that.
It's too late to undo it.
I need to know, otherwise this
thing is going to spiral out of amok.
Michael, okay, I'm going
to talk straight to you
because I think you need
to hear it. Michael...
This
is so disgusting.
Stop eating it.
Do you want to be happy?
Look at you. You have a major
self-destructive streak in you.
I know.
And you...
You kind of torpedo every
romantic relationship you're in.
That's not true.
You're right.
I ruin everything.
And I have known
some wonderful women.
Holly, Carole, Jan.
Helene.
Helene?
My mother.
Oh!
My mother, Helene.
Oh, yeah. Yes, yes, yes.
All of the greatest
loves of my life.
You should stop this. You
should call Dwight right now.
All right.
Oh, gosh, we're both going for
the same weight at the same time.
You go ahead.
Thank you.
It's all yours.
You okay?
Yeah, I'm good.
Hey, you know an exercise for two
people that uses the whole body?
Yeah, I think I know
what you're talking about.
Tractor pull.
Too bad there's
not a tractor here.
One thing you need
to know about me,
I don't quit until
something tears or pops.
You look like you're
getting a good workout.
Can I feel your pulse?
Nope,
I'm good. Thanks.
Really?
Hey. All right.
Young man, can you
wipe down that seat?
Get out of my way.
Tomorrow's
fertilizer, am I right?
I'm out of here.
Donna, Donna, wait. Please.
I'm sorry, okay?
Listen, we both know
why I'm here.
To see you naked
while I'm naked.
You stay away from me
or I'm calling security.
Donna, come...
You're back. What happened?
I pulled muscles in both my
thighs. Thanks for asking.
No. What happened with Donna?
Yeah, no.
She's not cheating.
Oh, man! Will you help me
work out this knot? Right here.
Put your fingers here.
Ugh! No, no.
Are you sure?
I'm positive.
Yeah, here's your expense
receipts. Right there.
Who eats eight
protein bars?
People who don't
trust egg whites.
Okay. Well, I am just
glad this is all over.
Oh! Me, too.
And by the way,
I told her not to,
but she's coming over
here and she's furious.
What? No, she didn't
say that. You're right.
I was paraphrasing.
What she actually said was,
"What is with him?
"He is crazy. I'm coming
over there to talk to him."
And this was after
I had no other recourse
but to tell her
and gym security
that you had sent me there
to see if she was cheating.
Also, I joined the gym.
You'll be billed monthly.
I am not
paying for that membership.
Maybe you'd be more
comfortable in your own office.
No, I like the attention.
Is she here yet?
No.
Wait, yes.
That's her?
Yeah.
Mmm-hmm.
Right. Right. Right.
Okay, I'll talk to you later.
How could you think
I would cheat on you?
I didn't, everybody
else here did.
Everybody convinced me
that something was up.
They poisoned my mind.
That's pathetic.
Well, no, it's a lie.
That's not what happened.
I just like you. I can't
believe I get to be with you.
You work at
an adult arcade.
You could have
any man you want.
When I tell you I like you,
you need to trust me.
Not some freak.
If you want to dump me,
I totally get it.
I told you I like you.
Well, you are bonerific.
Hey, if I said that we should go
away for a couple days, you would...
Poop my pants.
Have you ever
been to Vero Beach?
Oh, my God, Vero Beach?
No. Is that on the water?
We're going.
We are?
Yeah.
What's up?
I read your e-mail.
Close the door.
Okay.
I don't have a plan exactly,
more of a loose structure.
Gives me freedom to
improvise. It's like jazz.
* Andy don't mess with me *
I'll figure something out.
Some freaky stuff going on.
I was walking by Gabe
and I heard some things.
Such as?
It was kind of mumbled.
I don't know.
The only thing I could make out
clearly was, "Andy, problem, eliminate."
Something. I don't
know what it meant.
What? You don't
know what it meant?
How about, "Andy is a problem
and we must eliminate him."
Oh! I hadn't even
thought of that.
Yeah.
Oh, hey,
I love your earrings.
Thank you.
Did Michael
get them for you?
No, I bought them myself.
Where?
Steamtown Mall.
Claire's? Zales? Ricky's?
Earrings, Earrings, Earrings?
Fancy Girl? Platinum Cat?
Where?
You know, I actually
got them in Philadelphia.
In a mall down there.
Franklin Mills?
King of Prussia?
Springfield? Governor's Place?
Franklin Mills.
What?
Hmm.
Oh!
It's probably nothing.
Okay, heart-shaped jewelry is not
something that a woman buys for herself,
a man definitely
bought it for her recently,
and it wasn't Michael.
Wait, so you like heart-shaped
jewelry, though, right?
No.
Except for the pendant
that you bought me.
Which I love.
Psst!
Creed's head
of Quality Assurance,
so he'd definitely
be wrapped up in this.
So there I am
minding my own business,
and Darnell offers me
three bucks.
All I've got to do is walk
by Andy and go like this.
Darnell's a chump. I
would've done it for anything.
I've done a lot
more for a lot less.
So, it turns out Donna and I have
a Facebook friend of a friend in common,
so I was able to see
some of her pictures online.
This was taken
two weeks ago.
And this was
taken the same night.
This photo was
taken this morning.
It's Cece.
She's never going
to do anything wrong.
Isn't that something?
Wow. That's exciting.
Hey, Michael.
Hey.
Sorry to interrupt you.
I actually have something very
important to talk to you about.
Well, it can wait.
Business related.
It can wait.
I lied, it's personal.
It's about me
and Jim, we're...
You're the only
person I can talk to.
Jim is her husband.
Oh.
And... And they're
having problems...
No, no, we're not...
...and so she comes to me.
We're not having problems,
but it is personal.
And I was...
In bed.
Yes, yes, I desperately
want to speak with you
about my sex life with Jim.
Oh, my God, look at how
cheap street-level rooms are.
Am I the only person
who enjoys people-watching?
I need you to sign this!
So bad!
Okay, weirdo.
I love...
This idea is neat.
I've never been.
Yeah.
It sounds lovely.
Yeah, I think it'll be a nice
trip. We're going to get a lot done.
You're going to want to
look at the date on that.
Oh! Wow. Look at golfing.
Are you a golfer?
I am, but I gave
my clubs away.
Swear too much.
Hey, you okay?
Yeah, I just remembered that
I have to go to the bathroom.
Pam?
Absolutely.
Look, I'm not down anymore, so if
the guys start making fun of you,
you've just gotta
stand up for yourself.
- I know. It's just, I'm scared...
- I got your text.
It said, "911."
Glen, could you
excuse us?
It's bad.
What's bad?
It's real bad.
Still no plan.
Oh, God.
It's getting bigger.
I might have to go public here, but
no one's going to believe me. Uh...
I need proof. I need, like,
a printer to catch on fire.
I can videotape it.
Yeah.
There it is.
There what is?
What?
Who the hell is this?
Who is this guy?
I don't know who it is.
God!
Lowest of the low, that guy.
Just a notch above Toby.
You know what?
What?
I'm going to kill him.
No, I'm not. I feel... No.
I'm not going to kill him.
You just have to go in there.
You have to hear it from her.
I have to hear it from her. But
you have to settle down first.
I need to have her
tell me herself. Okay.
Okay.
Right?
Yes.
I need to have her say...
I need to say, "What the
hell is that? Calm down first.
"What the hell is that?"
Hey, look at this.
Look at this baby picture.
Oh, God,
no. Oh, my God.
Hi, Michael.
Okay.
I talked to corporate. Turns out there
have been 12 reports of faulty printers.
Out of 400,000.
We've investigated. Every
time it's been user error.
They block the vents
or something, I don't know.
That's why we have
the fine print.
Thank you for bringing
this to our attention.
So, I'd like to
reward you for that.
That's good for five bucks at
Dunkin' Donuts. Any Dunkin' Donuts.
Oh.
You know what? We should really
do something fun this week.
Yeah.
Wouldn't that be fun?
How about Thursday?
Thursday works, yeah.
What do you want to do? I
can't do it Thursday, book club.
How about Friday?
Oh! Friday doesn't work.
Oh, really? 'Cause I was thinking
we could go to this concert.
Spice Girls are opening
for Weird Al. Front row.
Be a great, great concert.
Shoot. I'm working.
Oh! Okay, well,
maybe I should stop by.
Well, won't you
be at the concert?
Nope, that's Tuesday.
Well, I can make it
on Tuesday.
You're cheating.
You're cheating on me.
How do you know?
Pam told me.
Did she see me?
Nice effort.
We're printing on 24-pound
premium stock paper,
approximately 300 sheets in.
So far no signs of distress.
You haven't even
introduced yourself. Right.
My name is Andrew Baines Bernard
and if you're watching this,
it's because I've turned state's
witness, because I'm in danger,
because I know too much.
You should talk
in a higher voice
'cause the camera
makes you sound weird.
Higher, okay?
Recently certain events
have come to my attention...
Higher.
Make it higher?
Okay. I have come to the conclusion
that the Sabre Corporation...
One more, yeah.
May be
overlooking certain safety regulations.
At the danger...
It's smoking.
I knew it!
This...
We are blowing the roof off!
Blowing the roof off!
Nice, nice.
This is my partner,
Darryl Philbin.
He's been my partner
through this entire thing.
I don't want to
prank anymore.
Things get real.
It's not funny.
I'm just going to be good.
Stay in my room,
go to church, try to do
one nice thing per day.
I do not want
to prank anymore.
Who is he?
Wait, what do you mean?
The other man.
Who's the guy?
Who is it?
It's you. I'm married.
I'm the mistress?
Okay, everybody,
let's take this next hill!
Excuse me. Yeah, I'd appreciate
it if you'd just let me run this.
You know what? You had your
chance, you're no leader.
Up, out of your seat! Let's
blast! Don't listen to him.
We're approaching a
cool-down, down a gentle hill.
No! The hill's a trap. Let's take
the dirt road off to the side.
No, guys, no.
We're just cooling down.
If they catch us,
they will rape us.
Go for the cliff.
And three, two, one, jump!
No! You're dead, you're
dead, you're dead. Good jump.
You're barely alive.
Okay, now, nice cool-down.
Check your pulse rate.