Good morning, everybody.
Who would like an authentic
New York bagel, hmm?
Stanley?
Thank you.
Oh, no, no, no. I got a
pumpernickel just for you.
Wow, H&H.
You went all the way to New
York City to get us bagels?
Why? Is there a place
closer that sells them?
This is really nice, Dwight.
Thanks.
Oh, don't mention it.
You owe me one.
You all owe me one.
Good morning, Michael.
Morning, Dwight.
Hungry?
No, I had
a fish stick sandwich.
Actually, I had two
fish stick sandwiches.
My girlfriend
didn't want hers,
because I guess I'm the
only aphrodisiac she needs.
Fish sticks are not
an aphrodisiac. Yeah.
You're thinking of deer penis.
It worked.
Regardless, that was over
two hours ago,
and it is now a scientific
fact that you are hungry.
Bagel?
I don't mind if I do.
Okay, I brought cheese, too.
I'm taking one
for my lady friend.
Excellent.
Brain food.
Thank you very much.
Okay.
You owe me.
Can't a guy just buy
some bagels for his friends,
so they'll owe him
a favor which he can use
to get someone fired who stole a
co-manager position from him anymore?
Jeez, when did everyone
get so cynical?
Pam, would you
care for a bagel?
Oh, no, thank you.
Oh, that's right, you're a woman and
you need to refuse food the first time.
I'll try again.
Please, Pam, reconsider
and have a bagel.
I have an early lunch.
Michael's been trying
to get Jim and me to hang out
ever since he started
dating my mom.
I don't know. I really hoped
this thing would just die out,
but today he's planning a
birthday lunch for my mom.
And we have to go.
No way out.
These are amazing.
You took all these?
I've always found beauty
in uncommon places.
Homeless people, graffiti.
Photography lets
me capture all that.
Have you ever been
photographed before?
Oh, just by,
like, friends.
Well, here's what I've
been doing around here.
It's for a series on
exposure in the workplace.
Pammy?
Hey!
Happy birthday.
Thank you.
Girls, there they are.
Birthday lunch.
There's no better medicine
than birthday lunch.
It'll cure all of your,
"Gee, I don't know if Michael
should be dating my mother."
And fixes all
occurrences of,
"I don't really
see them together."
So, open wide, Pam,
and take a big old spoonful
of birthday lunch medicine.
Take with food.
Pam, aren't you going to introduce
us to Michael's girlfriend?
I think you guys all remember
my mom from the wedding.
Yeah, I think everyone's met Helene. Hi.
Shall we?
Wait a minute,
is that another
birthday present for me?
'Cause you already
gave me a necklace.
Oh, my God, I love it.
Tell her how you gave it to
me. No, that wouldn't be...
He put it around my neck while
I was still asleep this morning.
Nice way to wake up.
- Yeah.
The rest of the story has been
censored due to inappropriocity.
Because of sex?
Kevin!
Hey, please, Kevin.
You're fired.
Sorry, sorry, work with a
bunch of idiots. Shall we go?
Yes, let's go.
Oh, wait.
Swartz Lumber's on the phone for
you, Pam. And they say it's urgent.
Oh, you guys,
just one second.
Oh, my gosh.
Are you serious?
Shipping emergency.
I don't think
I can go to lunch.
Oh, man, that's crazy. Right
as we were on our way out, too.
I know. Isn't that
always how it goes?
Rarely, if ever.
Let me give it a whirl,
I'll talk to them.
I will handle it.
That's okay.
I feel like it's...
It's my pleasure.
Hello? Well, that's great.
Turns out, the paper
was there all along.
Oh, thank God.
Something's up. That paper
was never supposed to arrive.
So, Pammy, are you
still liking sales?
Yeah, it's exciting.
You know, Michael
and I were talking,
and maybe, if you
put in a little more
face-to-face time with your clients,
you could improve your sales.
Pam's sales
are fine, actually.
Just want you
to succeed, Pammy.
You know what, we shouldn't even
be talking about business today.
Thank you.
Today's about family.
Why did I get in the
car? I could've struggled.
I have a whistle in my
purse, I didn't even blow it.
Oh, Dwight, I have a
little surprise for you.
Let me guess, you ate the
bagel I gave you and loved it.
Yes.
And I wanted to
return the favor.
I was polishing my loafers
and I happened to look over
and notice that your briefcase
was a little worse for the wear,
so a little elbow grease,
and she's polished right
up, back to her former glory.
Well.
Feel it against your cheek.
I will.
You give me a gift,
bam, thank you note.
You invite me somewhere,
pow, RSVP.
You do me a favor,
wham, favor returned.
Do not test my politeness.
Let me get that door
for you. There we go.
Thank you very much,
and I got it for you.
Oh! Goodness. Thanks.
You know, here's
a healthy fitness tip,
if you clench your buttocks
together while walking,
you can really take the
pressure off your knees.
- Is that right?
- Observe.
Right?
That really works.
Yeah. Feel free to use that.
Anytime, okay.
Hey, hold on a second.
Do not walk around with
your jacket catawampus.
And that needs to be
straight as an arrow.
Thank you very much.
Oh, boy. Hey, thank
you very much for that.
You are welcome.
Have a seat. Allow me.
Have a seat yourself.
You know what? I am
going to preemptively
change the batteries
in your wireless mouse.
Not necessary.
No, no, no!
You didn't have to do that.
Andy is complicating things.
But I'm not worried.
This will only up my game.
Hello. Scott.
Table for four.
Welcome, Scott family.
It'll be just a moment.
I used to love coming here.
The chicken parm is good.
Big part of my childhood. Maybe
Michael will start dating that, too.
What table should we take?
So many to choose from.
Wow.
Oh, my God.
What? All I see are boring old
tables with no birthday decorations.
Oh, wait a second,
you mean this one? Wow!
Michael, you did all this?
It's not about taking credit.
Let's just say we all did it.
Well, thank you,
all of you.
Well, it was actually
me alone, so...
Wow, look at this place.
It really makes me want
to go to Italy someday.
Oh, you'll love it.
You can have my guidebooks.
I think I'm done with those
really long plane rides.
Thank you for...
Thanks for
lending me the books.
So, Mom, which birthday
are we celebrating this year?
Sticking with 49.
Forty-nine again?
That's nine years in a row. This
is now our longest family tradition.
That's funny.
Well, as long as
we're running numbers, Pam,
help me out with this one.
Let's see, honey,
you're six months pregnant,
but you've only been married for 30
days, so what does that add up to?
Ooh, burn, burn on you.
And a little bit on me, too.
You're 54 years old.
No, I'm 58.
You're 58 years old?
Uh-huh.
Congratulations.
The only time you should
care about a woman's age
is if she is
too young for you.
And I am not
robbing the cradle.
If anything,
I am robbing the grave.
Mom, have you decided
what you want to be called?
I mean, I like Nana, but I
also like the classic Grandma.
Please be Grandma. I want you to
be Grandma. Definitely a Grandma.
Michael.
What do you think? Grandma?
Uh-huh.
Yay! Grandma.
Hey, would you guys ever
do a triathlon, you think?
Maybe.
Helene?
No. I don't think so.
I am. I'm definitely going to do it.
I've already got the run
and the bike thing down,
just need to learn how
to swim. Come on, you in?
No, no. I think a triathlon is
pretty much something I can rule out.
I don't know, it just
doesn't interest me.
So, it's a matter of
interest. Good. Okay.
It's not anything you
would have ever done?
I might have done it
when I was younger,
but now there are just other
things I'd rather be doing
than running and jumping
and swimming...
Well, there's no jumping
in a triathlon. Oh!
You're thinking
the broad jump.
Would you try bungee jumping?
No.
Snowboarding? No, no, you
want to go snowboarding?
I might, I might.
Michael, what are
you talking about?
Nothing, just life
and doing things before
you die. I don't know.
Do I really want to
go snowboarding? No.
But I would like to
if I wanted to.
What's going on in here?
Andy bought lunch.
Oh, no, really?
Yep, yep.
Took a page right out of the
old Schrute book of niceness.
There is no book,
there's only a survival guide.
You bought
breakfast for everyone,
so I got
lunch for everyone.
Okay, well, allow me.
You know what?
Gosh, these tacos are
awfully complicated to make.
I will make
everyone's tacos!
So we should
get the check.
What about your gift, Michael?
Whoa, no, no, no.
No, it's stupid.
You'd hate it, I hate it.
I'm sure I won't.
Yes, you will.
He locked himself in his office
all morning working on it.
Give me. Look at
this wrapping paper.
It's got the word "love"
on it in every language.
I literally... I put no thought
into the wrapping at all.
Might as well
have been toilet paper.
Toilet paper. Let's see.
"A scrapbook of our first
memories, by Michael Gary Scott,
"for my girlfriend,
Helene, on your birthday."
That's just an
arbitrary title.
Okay, here's a penny.
What's that from?
Penny for your thoughts.
It was from the wishing
well at the mall.
You threw it in, I went back
later, waded in, and I found it.
That's amazing.
It's not amazing at all. It's sort
of weird that I went and did that.
And now your wish won't
come true, so that blows.
A poem. Oh, that I plagiarized, I think.
"I cannot go to school today
said little Peggy Ann McKay"
Shel Silverstein?
Yeah.
"I have the measles
and the mumps
"a gash, a rash,
and purple bumps
"And my teacher's
really mean
"Happy Birthday,
I love you, Helene."
It's really
nice, Michael.
I think it sucks.
I think it's wonderful,
absolutely wonderful.
Well, that's because you and
I have very different tastes,
and you like lame things.
It's a generational
sort of gap between us.
Oh, God, a scrapbook.
Home run, Michael.
You set the bar so high.
That was a bunt.
Whoa, whoa, whoa, Dwight,
I'm going to do this.
Hey, hey, hey, relax.
I got it covered.
No, I insist.
No, no, no, no, no, I insist.
Okay, Dwight,
this is ridiculous.
Don't worry about it,
you can just owe me.
Hey, where'd you go?
Oh, I just went
to the bathroom.
And then you stopped at
the bar on the way back?
Got thirsty.
Okay, weirdo.
Come on, it's time for cake.
Okay.
Honestly, for a long time,
I thought I was going
to grow old with Holly.
And then I met Helene,
and she is great,
and she already knows
and has done everything
that I have ever wanted to
do and can tell me about it.
But I think I want to
do those things myself.
Cake's really good.
I know. I love when they
use butter-cream frosting.
Finish your cake, Helene.
I want you to
enjoy that cake
because I have something
terrible I need to tell you.
And I want you
to enjoy your cake
before I tell you this
terrible, terrible thing.
Helene, I think you're
a wonderful person and I...
God, I've enjoyed
dating you
and being your
boyfriend so much,
but I have to consider Pam's
feelings as a friend and a coworker.
I cannot, in good conscience,
continue to date you,
when I know what
this is doing to her.
Michael. Michael, it's okay.
No, it's not.
I know that it took me a
little while to come around,
and it's still a little
weird to get used to,
but you obviously
make my mom very happy.
And that makes me happy.
Wow, that just...
You've really grown.
Well...
Oh, thank you, Pam.
And I hope you are as
gracious during this next part.
Helene, once again,
you are a wonderful person,
and you have
lived a great life,
and I envy it, and I want it
someday, but just in the future.
You need somebody who
understands your references.
Who is Kafka-esque?
I've never...
I don't know him.
There's another woman,
and her name is Italy,
and skydiving,
and bungee jumping.
Okay, so...
And I want kids.
And you, unfortunately,
have already completed
that part of your journey
down there. Michael.
It's not my decision,
it's Mother Nature.
And Mother has very
strict rules about
fertility.
I got it.
I'm 58. What am I
supposed to do now?
Well, hobbies.
Stop.
What's going on?
Stupid thing wedged up there.
No one in this
office will help me.
Yeah, move it.
What if Dwight dies and
I still owe him something?
That is a recipe
for a ghost.
Oh, yeah, you're gonna owe me big time.
Looks like a little
envelope, there you go.
Yup. Got it.
"To Dwight"?
Starbucks gift card.
Surprise!
It's from everybody.
$15 value.
Damn it! I am no closer
to taking Jim down.
What a waste of a day.
I could've grown poison mushrooms
that'd be this high by now!
They're mushrooms,
they don't get that high.
Pamela Beesly-Halpert.
What?
May I have a word with
you in my office, please?
I am working.
Well, this is
a work-related matter.
Really?
Yes.
Join me, please,
won't you?
I'm going to give you
a raise, Pam.
Why?
Because of all the
good work you've done.
I have the lowest sales
record of anyone here.
Don't, no.
It's not about numbers Pam,
it's about attitude.
I have the worst attitude
of any person here.
Do you want
the raise or what?
Yeah, I'll take it.
Okay, hey. Pam, Pam.
With this raise,
there are strings attached.
And that string is attached from
my heart to your mean attitude.
You're bribing me?
No, no. No, I am not.
Unless you want me to.
Do you want me to?
Because I will,
I will bribe you.
No, your face is saying don't,
unless I haven't offered you enough.
Your face isn't changing.
What is it?
Talk to me, face.
Tell me what
Pam's brain is thinking.
Come on, what do you
want? What do you want?
Do you want a million
dollars? Do you want to hit me?
Do you want me to get down
on one knee and beg you?
I want to hit you.
What?
I'll do that.
Okay.
What? I don't...
Are you kidding?
No, are you kidding?
No, I don't...
All right. Come on,
I'll take off my jacket
and tense my stomach
and you just...
No, I don't think I can
hit you in the office.
Okay.
So, we'll do it after work.
Hmm.
In the parking lot,
in front of everyone.
I'm going to hit you
as hard as I can.
Okay.
See you then.
See you.
Hey.
Hi.
Quick question.
Yeah.
Are you scared?
Never.
About what? A little.
What are you talking about?
We heard about the punch.
What punch?
Pam. She's going to punch the
crap out of your face after work.
I'm pretty sure we said slap.
No, it's a punch and Pam has
that crazy pregnancy strength now.
I'm getting concerned that
you don't seem to understand
what's going to happen.
Do you?
I'm good.
All right. See you there.
Hey.
Do you and Pam ever get
frisky? Inappropriate.
I mean, do you ever
wrestle with each other?
All the time.
Really?
Yeah.
She's strong?
She wants it bad, Michael.
Can you stop this?
I can.
Okay.
And I don't support
her choice to hit you.
I don't, either.
But at the same time,
she goes crazy,
and I do
understand her reasoning.
Mmm-hmm. I know.
I just need some time. I need
some time to think about it.
You got to do... Give me
some time to make a decision.
How much time do you need? No
more than a week, maybe two weeks.
Come on, man.
Pam, can I talk
to you for a second?
I heard about the hit. Just to be sure,
it's off company property, right? Right.
Yeah, okay, I think we
should probably be okay.
Okay.
And the power
comes from the back foot.
So, it's all one motion
through the body.
So, there's... You stay a
little low and there's a twist,
and you keep
your shoulder down.
And you kind of
throw out the arm.
Okay, wait, you're saying
it comes from the foot?
Yes.
Okay.
Yeah. Okay.
Hey, everybody.
He's not in the men's room,
although the seat was warm,
so we may have
just missed him.
My money's on Pam.
It's not a fight. What
other outcome could there be?
Michael could win.
How? He can't hit back.
Why can't you just
agree with me sometimes?
Am I scared of getting
hit in the face? No.
Every day, weirdos pay
dominatrixes hundreds of dollars
for that very privilege.
I'm scared I'm going
to love it. Let's do this.
It's okay, guys. I can handle
this. Everybody can go home.
We're here for
the show, Michael.
You're just
a bunch of voyeurs.
Are you eating popcorn?
It has almost no calories.
You ready?
Yes.
You have to keep your
hands down. I know.
Okay. All right.
Oh, God!
Michael, you have to
keep your hands down.
Put your hands
in your pockets.
Okay!
Pam, Pam.
I'm really sorry.
I'm sorry.
What are you sorry for?
So many things.
I don't know,
it's hard to choose.
How about for dating my mom?
Maybe that's it.
And dumping her
on her birthday?
Yes.
Okay, just don't ever date
a member of my family again.
Okay, I promise.
For the record,
your mom came on to me.
Holy crap!
Are you okay?
No!
You're okay.
Feel better?
No, you were right.
Wait, why are you limping?
I don't know.
Let's get some
raw meat on that face.
I've got a chicken
in the freezer upstairs.
As I watched Pam's big, strong
hand coming toward my face,
I saw my entire life
flash before my eyes.
And guess what?
I have four kids.
And I have a hover car
and a hover house.
And my wife is a runner,
and it shows.
And Pam and Jim are my best
friends, and our kids play together.
And I'm happy.
And I am rich
and I never die.
It doesn't sound like much,
but it's enough for me.
Good, good, just keep it on
there for another five minutes.
It's cold, Dwight.
Let the swelling go down.
Oh, thank you. Thanks.
I owe you one, Dwight.
Fire Jim.
No.
I'm cashing in
the favor, fire him.
What are you talking...
Do it.
Promote me.
Tri-managers.
Forget that.
Can I have an office?
No.
You know what, you can
keep your stupid favor.
It's worthless.
And this is my dinner on
your face, I'm keeping it.
Oh, that feels better.