Thank you, Sergeant.
Oh!
Rich pickings here.
Let's have a look here.
Oh! You're not dead, mon ami.
Who won the battle?
Erm, English. Worse luck.
So it's all over.
For subtitling services, contatct:
waqas.zahoor89@gmail.com
In my pocket,
you'll find a watch and a purse.
Oh. Take them, they're yours.
Much obliged.
There's nothing there.
I must have been robbed.
I'm sorry.
They're coming. I'm off.
You saved my life.
Who are you?
A Frenchman, like you, monsieur,
and if they catch me, I'll be shot.
Your name and rank?
Thenardier, sir.
Sergeant.
I will remember you.
and you remember me.
Colonel Pontmercy.
And if we both survive,
you can call on me, I swear it.
Sh, sh, sh.
Sh.
I'll get him!
Over there. There he goes.
Colonel Baron Pontmercy
for Monsieur Gillenormand.
Pontmercy? Is he still alive?
I thought he died at Waterloo!
I'll see him all right.
I'll see him off
with a flea in his ear.
You dare to come here?
Good day, Father-in-law.
Don't you bring
that up with me, sir!
I rue the day my poor daughter
ever set eyes on you.
And now the poor girl is dead,
I thank God I need
never see you again.
And yet here you are!
I was hoping, sir, that we could...
make up our differences.
Were you?
I marvel at your insolence.
Make up our differences?
You gave up all hope of that
when you allied your fortunes
with that Corsican brigand
Bonaparte!
I fought for France, sir.
Napoleon was a great man.
He still has my allegiance.
Better not say that too loud,
young man.
France has a king again, thank God.
It's your lot they're
stringing up from lamp posts now.
How do you like that,
now the boot's on the other foot?
Huh? Bonapartist scum.
You're a traitor to your class!
Sir.
Will you at least let me spend
some time with my little boy?
Never!
You will never set eyes on him.
And I promise you this,
if you break my prohibition,
I'll disinherit him.
Sir, I beg you, for Marius's sake,
if not for mine.
Never!
He will be brought up
to curse your very name, Pontmercy.
Now leave my house.
Go on. Get out. Get out!
Monsieur!
I take the child to church
every Sunday at ten.
You can see him there.
Thank you. Which-which church?
St Sulpice.
Thank you.
Please, Favorite!
You won't have to look after me,
I can take care of myself.
Go on! Bonjour, monsieur.
Bonjour, mademoiselle.
Please!
No, Fantine, you're too young,
we won't let you.
But I'm old enough
to work with you.
Come on, just let her come.
So what do you say?
Well...
..I suppose.
Oh! Thank you!
She'll be fine.
You can look after her if she's not.
You'll have to do what we say,
all right?
Don't show me up, Fantine.
I promise I'll be good.
Eh! Debout les charognes!
Get back in line!
Back in line, scum!
Eyes forward, I said!
Keep on moving! Move it! Move it!
Get back to work!
You heard me!
Pick them up I said!
Come on!
Pick up those buckets!
Filthy dog!
What are you looking at?
Well, get him out from
under there!
Yes, sir, Monsieur Javert!
Help me!
Use the ropes to get him out from
under that rock!
Come on, there's four of you!
And get that lot back to work!
Use the ropes!
All right, let him in.
He's going to have a go.
Allez! Reprenez le travaille!
Qu'est que vous regardez?
Reprenez le travaille!
Unshackle 24601
and Put him in the Guard Room.
24601!
Well, now, 24601.
What was all that about today?
You saving that guard's life.
Why?
If you were trying to get yourself
an earlier release,
you tried in vain.
There's no hope of that.
No hope at all.
Sorry to disappoint you.
Is that what you hoped
to achieve by it?
Your strong man act.
What for?
Make a fool of me?
I'm right, aren't I?
Let me tell you something
that might surprise you.
I could have been a criminal.
I was born in prison.
My parents were criminals.
Men like us have only two choices -
to prey upon society,
or to guard it.
You chose the former.
I chose the latter.
And I can tell you, if I had chosen
to be a criminal, I would
have been a hell of a lot better one
than you've turned out to be.
19 years for a loaf of bread!
You've got 12 months
left to serve.
My guess, you'll be back in here
before another year's gone by.
And next time...
it'll be for life.
Whatever you think...
..you can never win.
Guard!
Take him back.
Rich boys on the hunt.
Just like us!
Look at Blondie over there,
in the blue.
He looks as if he wants
to eat you, Fantine.
I think he looks nice.
Oh, Blondie,
it's your lucky night tonight!
What do you say, then, gentlemen?
Will they do?
I'd say they're ripe
for the plucking.
One or two of them have been
plucked before, I'd say.
I like a girl who knows
her way around a man.
Then I stake my claim
to the little brunette.
She's ravishing.
And what if she prefers one of us?
To me? Impossible.
No, no, I'm serious, gentlemen.
Keep off the grass. She's mine.
Don't be shy. Don't be shy!
Men! You could wait forever.
Come on, Fantine.
No, no, no. I'm afraid
we cannot permit you
to dance without partners.
Thought you'd never ask, monsieur.
May I ask your name, mademoiselle?
Fantine, monsieur.
Fantine.
So, are we going again next week?
As long as it's understood
they pay for everything,
and bring us there and home again.
Why not? Fantine?
Oh, yes! Of course!
Look at her. She's in love already.
No, I'm not.
Come here, pet.
You have to remember they're
not serious, these types.
They're just amusing themselves.
They come to Paris to learn
how to be fine gentlemen,
and then they go home and marry the
girl their father chose for them.
Maybe it's not always like that.
Yes, it is, it's always like that.
We're not like them.
We're not ladies, we're grisettes.
The ground we walk on,
it's not solid ground, Fantine.
We could fall through at any time.
We could be down in the gutter
and no-one would care.
Plenty more where we come from.
But why should it
always be like that?
Because it is.
This won't do.
The seam's crooked.
Unpick it and do it again.
Slow and steady wins the race!
Come on, Felix,
put your back in to it, man!
Fantine, keep up!
Come on, Felix,
we're getting left behind.
I don't care.
I just want to look at you.
Do I look very nice, then?
You look like an angel.
Favorite says I shouldn't believe
a single word you say.
Of course.
She wants to protect you,
she's a good friend.
But you know she has no need
to worry, Fantine.
You are the one with all the power
in this situation.
I'm utterly at your mercy.
I don't believe you.
Let me prove it.
How are you going to prove it?
You'll see.
Before I met you, I sought nothing
but my own selfish pleasures.
Now I want to dedicate
my life to you.
You see, I'm...
I'm a poet.
And I hope to be famous one day.
And you will be my muse.
I wonder if you know
how I'm suffering.
Are you going
to be merciful, Fantine?
Will you take pity on me?
I don't want you to be sad.
Then?
You promise you'll be good
to me, Felix?
On my life.
All right, then.
Move!
What did he do?
He struck me, sir!
All right, pull him out.
On your knees, scum!
All of you, get down!
Don't look at me!
On your knees and stay there!
Discipline must be maintained.
Otherwise, civilisation
would collapse.
Firing squad!
Present arms!
Take aim.
Fire!
To order restored now everyone
knows their place again.
The King. The King!
Good boy.
Napoleon was a scoundrel.
What was he?
Scoundrel.
And your papa, I'm sorry to say,
is a scoundrel, too.
Don't look at me like that,
I speak the truth.
A traitor to his class.
And that is why he will
never be welcome at this table.
He should be rotting in prison,
or in exile, like his master.
Scoundrel.
Good boy!
You know, Marius, it gives me
no pleasure to speak of
your father in these terms.
A boy should be able
to respect his father.
Never mind, your grandpapa is here
to show you the right path in life.
All done? Good boy.
Take him away, Nicolette.
And no more of those sullen looks,
or you'll feel the back of my hand!
Come on, Marius.
Wait, wait.
Give your Grandpapa a kiss.
Good boy.
Sleep tight.
Mind the fleas don't bite.
You'll be taking him to church
in the morning?
Yes, monsieur.
Yes, good, off you go.
There you are.
Thank you.
Monsieur.
24601.
Unshackle him.
Take off your things.
Trousers, shirt, jacket, cap, shoes.
Put them on.
What about my savings?
171 francs.
109.
171.
I kept a record in my head.
A common error.
The prisoner's calculated
the sum from the number of days
of imprisonment,
not the number of working days.
After deductions of days not worked,
that is to say Sundays,
public holidays, and contributions
for the annual Christmas dinner,
the sum comes to 109 francs.
Spend it wisely.
Here's your passport.
You are required to show this
to authorities in every town
and village you pass through.
You have your name back,
Monsieur 24601.
I wonder if you can
remember what it is.
Jean Valjean.
Are you sure about that?
Jean Valjean!
Monsieur, good evening.
She will be happy to see you,
in your magnificent trousers.
What is it, Felix?
Oh, you know me.
I get these...
..silly fancies.
What sort of fancies?
That one day I'll come round
and you'll tell me it's all over,
you've found a new lover.
I love you, silly.
But you're far too beautiful.
Are you fishing for compliments?
Well, we've had our fun, haven't we?
I wouldn't harbour any grudges
if you abandoned me now
for a younger lover.
I'll never abandon you.
You're the love of my life.
Youth must have its day.
I wish you'd stop talking like that.
I don't like it.
All right. Change of subject.
Listen.
My friends and I have arranged
a surprise for you and your friends.
Next Sunday.
A special outing, all day.
All day?
Oh, you're so good to us!
Show me your papers.
Come on.
Need another man?
Yeah, all right.
You look strong enough.
Get to it.
They got more.
That's enough for you.
What are you doing there, my friend?
Trying to sleep,
what does it look like?
Why don't you go to an inn?
I did.
Wouldn't take me.
No-one would take me.
They shut their doors against me.
Have you tried
knocking on that door?
Which one?
The house with the light
in the window.
No.
Knock there.
Have you heard what people
are saying, Monseigneur?
All the town's talking about it.
About what?
The bad man that's roaming the town.
They said he was a desperado
with a terrible face.
Well, I dare say a man
can't help his face.
Come in.
What can we do for you, my son?
I want something to eat,
and a bed for the night.
I've got money. I can pay.
A woman told me
to knock on your door.
Then you've come to the right place.
We have a bed for you,
and we were just about to eat.
Would you set another place
at the table, Madame Magloire?
It's good?
Yeah, it's good.
You were very hungry, I think.
Let me pour you some more wine.
You're a funny sort of priest.
We had priests in prison.
Not like you.
You say I don't have to
pay for any of this?
What is mine is yours, monsieur.
I've got money.
109 francs,
and five sou.
And how long did it take you
to earn that?
19 years.
19 years of hard labour.
Well, the five sou I earned today.
It should have been seven,
but he cheated me.
Yellow passport.
People take advantage.
You have suffered a great deal,
my friend.
Chained and shackled night and day,
beaten for a word,
beaten for a look,
beaten for nothing!
For 19 years.
And now the yellow passport,
so they've still got me.
But this is, er...
Hm.
..different.
This is like I'm dreaming.
Is this a trick?
Monsieur,
the bishop treats everyone the same.
Yes, God tells us
to love our fellow men.
How can I love my fellow man
when he treats me worse than a dog?
It's easy for you.
You can afford to be
kind and gentle.
You can afford to share
your food and wine. Am I right?
Yes, of course you're right.
Absolutely right. It is easy for me.
But consider this.
Even if the world has
done you a great injustice,
does it really serve you to have a
heart full of bitterness and hatred?
How could I not have a heart
full of bitterness and hatred?
I'd like to see you for
19 years in the hulks!
So don't preach to me
about God and love.
I beg your pardon.
Forgive me.
I should have considered
your feelings.
But you don't think it possible,
that kindness and love
can change a man?
No.
This is my bedroom here.
And this is where you'll sleep.
Tomorrow morning,
you'll have a cup of warm milk,
straight from our very own goat.
You give me a bed right next
to yours? Are you crazy?
How do you know I'm not a murderer?
Well, that's the Good Lord's
business, not mine.
Or, to put it another way,
I'll take my chance with you,
my friend.
Go to bed now, and...
sleep well.
Monseigneur! Monseigneur!
What is it?
The silverware basket! It's gone!
No, no, no, it's here!
Look, over there. Oh!
What about the silverware?
Ah. Now, there, I can't help you,
I'm afraid.
It's been stolen!
Lord save us! That man who was here
last night, he must have taken it!
Oh...
ungrateful beast!
After all your kindness!
Well, when you think about it,
was all that silver really ours
in the first place?
Yes, it was! Of course it was!
And, more to the point,
what are we to eat with now?
And, really, do we need even
a wooden fork or spoon
to dip a piece of bread
into a bowl of milk?
But to think what might have
happened last night!
Letting a wild beast like that
into your house,
we're lucky all he did was steal!
Come in.
Monseigneur.
This man was arrested ten miles away
with a quantity of silverware
in his knapsack,
which I believe to be
the property of the church.
Ah, thank you, Sergeant,
for bringing him back to me.
Welcome back, I'm glad to see you.
You forgot to take the candlesticks,
didn't you?
What?
Well, didn't he tell you that
I said he could have the silverware?
He refused to answer when
questioned, Monseigneur.
Well, that was his right.
But no harm done.
Of course you were doing your duty.
So all is well, you can go now.
Let him go free?
That's right.
And thank you for your trouble.
You may go now.
If you say so, Monseigneur.
I do. Good day to you.
Here you are.
Put them in your knapsack.
Monseigneur, what does this man
want with our candlesticks?
I assume he's going to sell them
for as much as he can get.
Don't forget, don't ever forget,
you promised to use the proceeds
to become an honest man.
I don't remember that.
Nevertheless, it's what you want,
isn't it?
To lead a good life?
No.
I don't know.
Jean Valjean, my brother,
you do not belong to evil any more.
You belong to good.
I have bought your soul with that
silverware and these candlesticks.
No!
Nothing to be done about it,
I'm afraid.
You belong to God now, Jean Valjean.
Go in peace.
God be with you.
Well, that's that.
I've done all I can.
It's up to Jean Valjean now.
# Amor me llama... #
A little higher, please!
# Toda mi alma es en mi ojos
# Porque ensenas... #
No cheating! Come on!
Go on! Run! Faster, faster, faster!
Run!
Faster, faster, faster! Come on!
We have a winner! We have a winner!
You said there would be a surprise!
The surprise comes later!
So do you love me, Favorite?
Of course I do, Blachevelle,
darling!
I adore you!
So what would you do
if I stopped loving you?
Oh, no, don't say that,
even as a joke!
I'd run after you and
scratch your eyes out.
What you said just then
about Blachevelle,
you don't really mean it, do you?
I detest him.
He's too full of himself.
And he's stingy.
There's a boy down my street
that I'm in love with.
Thing is,
he only makes 20 sou a day,
so... what are you going to do?
Don't look at me like that, Fantine!
I know you love your Felix.
And he's not stingy,
I will give you that,
setting you up in your own place.
All done?
Waiter! Waiter!
Waiter, another bottle, please!
Two! Two!
Two more! Two! Two more!
Toast, toast!
Ladies and gentlemen!
A little decorum, if you please!
Decorum!
Shh! Let's bring some dignity
to the banquet.
Oh, leave us alone, Felix!
Down with the tyrant!
Bombarda, Bombance, and Bamboche!
Friends, I appeal to you!
There must be a limit, even to
a meal such as this one has been!
Gluttony punishes the glutton.
And remember,
all our passions, even love,
can die through over-indulgence.
Moderation is the watchword.
Moderation in all things. Yes!
Hear, hear!
Hear, hear! Good speech.
Now sit down and shut up.
I haven't finished,
I haven't finished!
A toast to merriment!
To merriment!
Life is good!
Everything is beautiful!
I'm surrounded by beauty!
Awww!
That's better.
Now come and sit down,
and be sensible, please.
No.  Please. the moment has come.
It's time for the surprise!
Surprise! Gentlemen.
The surprise.
Don't be long!
Make it a good one.
This is the surprise!
Shh! Shh!
At last, the surprise!
What's it going to be?
I don't know, but
I hope it's pretty.
Gold necklaces!
No.
What's that?
Where are the gentlemen?
The gentlemen have
left a letter for you.
Give it here.
It says, "This is the surprise."
Well, go on, then. Open it!
Good job one of us can read.
Right, here we go.
"O loving mistresses!
"At last it is time to remind you
that we have parents.
"We have estates far away
in the country,
"and we have duties to perform.
"Our fathers are calling
their prodigal sons home,
"and killing fatted calves for us.
"By the time you read this,
"three galloping horses
will be carrying us home
"to our mamas and papas.
"We are leaving.
"We have left.
"Lament us briefly,
"and replace us rapidly.
"Signed, Felix,
Blachevelle and Fameuil.
"PS, the meal is paid for."
# Que direz-vous d'Cadet Rousselle?
Ah! Ah! Ah! Oui, vraiment
# Cadet Rousselle est bon enfant
# Cadet Rousselle a trois maisons
Cadet Rousselle a trois maisons
# Qui n'ont ni poutres ni chevrons
Qui n'ont ni poutres ni chevrons
# C'est pour loger les hirondelles
# Que direz-vous d'Cadet Rousselle?
# Ah! Ah! Ah! Oui, vraiment
# Cadet Rousselle est bon enfant
# Cadet Rousselle a trois maisons
# Qui n'ont ni poutres ni chevrons
# Cadet Rousselle a trois maisons. #
Did you see my 40 sou, monsieur?
No.
Will you move your foot, monsieur?
What's your name?
Petit-Gervais.
Will you move your foot now?
Go on, get out of here.
Get lost! Go on!
You've got it, haven't you?
You've got my money!
You're a dirty thief!
A curse on you!
Petit-Gervais! Petit-Gervais!
Petit-Gervais!
Here's Maman!
Was she a good girl?
Good as gold.
I hope you were, too, mademoiselle!
Aren't I always?
Shhh, shhh.
Shhh.
Oh, Cosette.
Whatever are we going to do now?