A man called Thenardier saved my life.
If you meet him, do the best you can.
All we need now is a spark
to set off the powder keg,
and all Paris could go up in flames!
We must make this city ungovernable!
And defend this barricade to the death!
I want that man found,
arrested and brought to justice.
Where is he?!
- Who?
- Jean Valjean.
We're moving to a secret address.
But how would anyone know how to find us?
Is there someone you wish to be found by?
My beloved Marius,
please come or send word tonight.
I got a letter for you.
Let me go!
I can't let you go!
There's fighting all over Paris!
I hate you!
In her heart, she's gone.
Got a letter for number seven.
My darling, I am now
on the barricades with my friends...
If I die, I die loving you.
Attention!
So, what did you see?
It's all over, comrade.
Hundreds of soldiers
are getting ready to attack.
And most of the barricades
have been destroyed.
Are you all right?
Me?
Never better.
Everybody outside, now.
You need to hear this.
Marius. Courfeyrac.
Wake up!
For God's sake!
Citizens!
This... is the endgame.
Every man and woman who stays here
and fights today will die.
History will remember us and one day
the people will prevail.
But, for now, the whole Paris army is out
and within an hour they will be upon us.
You have nothing to expect.
Nothing to hope for.
So be it!
Let's raise the barrier higher,
and fight till the last man!
Friends, consider!
Some of you have wives, husbands,
sons, daughters.
Think of them.
A heroic death will do nothing for them.
You get yourself killed, they starve.
Or worse.
For you, it is a braver thing
to live, for your family's sake!
Enjolras is right!
There's no shame on you
living to fight another day.
Every married man and woman,
every breadwinner, come forward,
shake our hands, and leave!
I command you!
I entreat you!
Comrade.
Live well, comrade.
You'll be building a better world.
A world we won't be seeing.
Are you quite sure you want to be here?
Yes.
Papa?
Bonjour, mademoiselle.
Have you seen Papa?
No.
Mademoiselle, come back!
Prepare yourselves.
Mademoiselle! Mademoiselle!
- Get back! Get back!
- Marius!
- Get back off the street!
Marius!
Look! Positions!
Prepare yourselves!
Brace yourselves!
Cannon fire!
Fire!
Get down!
Stay down!
Move! Move!
Allez! Allez!
Fall back!
They're falling back!
Citizen, the Republic thanks you.
I don't know who you are,
or why you are here,
but I'm glad to have you with us.
Comrades!
This is a grim moment in our history...
...but a glorious one!
Our sacrifice is going to help
build a better world.
This barricade is made of more than
just cobblestones and bedsteads.
It is made of hopes,
of ideals,
of love of our fellow men.
We fight for the wretched of the Earth!
And if we go to our deaths,
we go to our deaths with joy!
Long live the Republic!
Vive la revolution!
Marius! Marius.
We've bought ourselves some time.
The trouble is,
we're running out of bullets.
Leave that to me.
Gavroche! Gavroche!
Come back here!
Gavroche, come back!
Gavroche!
You'll get yourself killed.
Hey! The corpses!
Gavroche!
Bad luck, try again.
Good shot...
Don't be a fool!
Quickly, Marius!
Come on...
We got them.
It was good sport...
...wasn't it?
Poor little squirt.
What did he say?
He said...
He said it was good sport.
And...
Enjolras!
- Get him inside, quickly.
- Get him up.
Dress his wound.
Come here. Come on.
Marius. Marius!
Open your eyes.
This is our last refuge.
When they take the barricade,
those left alive can fight on here.
What about him?
The police spy?
The last man alive
can put a bullet in his head.
May I claim that honour? As a favour?
I don't see why not.
He's yours.
Fire!
Come on, comrades. Go.
Just so.
Go on, then.
Take your revenge.
Oh, yeah.
A blade would be more your style.
Aaaargh!
Shut your mouth.
There.
You're free. Now go.
What is this?
If I come through this alive,
which isn't very likely...
...you can find me
at Rue de I'Homme-Arme.
Number seven.
- I shan't resist arrest.
- What are you doing?
I've no reason to take your life.
Now go, before I change my mind.
What, you're not going to
take your opportunity?
Do you wish to die?
It would make a hell of
a lot more sense than this.
Yeah, well, you'll have to
arrange it yourself. Now go. Go.
Just go!
Get back! Get back!
Get back!
Courfeyrac!
Come on, come on...
This is history. This is history.
Come on!
What the hell's going on?
Hey! Find your own boozer!
Oh... Bugger, that hurt!
He's the leader.
- Shoot him where he stands.
- Wait a minute!
Me too.
Long live the Republic.
Line up, lads.
You're entitled to be blindfolded.
- Do you want the blindfold?
- I piss on your blindfold.
Take aim.
Fire!
24601.
This man is a criminal,
a liar and a thief.
The scum of the Earth!
You're a dirty thief!
It's all his fault.
You see this monster?! Monster!
- It's all his fault.
- ..criminal, liar and a thief...
- Dirty thief!
- Monster!
Scum of the Earth!
- Dirty thief!
- Scum of the Earth!
- I hate you!
- Monster!
Forgive me.
Forgive me!
- Hold it there!
- Get back.
You're back, sir.
You all right?
As you see, Rivette.
Well, er...
...there was a report that
you'd been captured by the rebels.
Yet here I am.
Did you see him? The one
you're after, that man Valjean?
Yes, I saw him.
What happened? Is he in custody?
No.
He got away?
He allowed me to get away.
Must have a soft spot for you, sir.
Are you mocking me?
No, sir.
You know they were all killed,
the rebels.
- Was his body found with the others?
- Don't know, sir.
Then he's still at large.
And the other fella, Thenardier,
he's been sighted down by the river.
These riots seem to have brought
all the scum to the surface.
I was just on my way down there.
Do you wish to come, sir?
Got some of our best men
standing by, sir.
I think there's a chance we might
net the whole gang of them.
Good.
Well done, Rivette.
Just permit me, sir...
Take your hands off me.
Forgive me, sir.
Beg your pardon.
It's all right...
All right.
You're all right.
Stay alive. Stay alive!
Stay... Oh, God...
Marius Pontmercy.
So that's who you are.
If I die, take my body to my grandfather.
Monsieur Gillenormand,
number six, Rue des Filles-du-Calvaire...
Oh, you... you're really in the shit,
aren't you, eh?
The shit!
Forgive me. Ooh! The smell of you, eh?
You're really not at home here, are you?
You don't know your way around,
it's not your milieu.
What do you want?
Oh, I'm just wondering about
what you're going to do now.
How you're going to get out there.
You don't know, do you?
You're stuck.
Ah, shame.
We've not been friends in the past,
have we? But I could help you now.
You give me half of what you've
found in that man's pockets,
and I'll open up the gate for you.
What makes you think...
...he had anything in his pockets?
Well, you wouldn't have killed him
unless he had something
worth having, now, would you?
What do you say, 50/50?
All right.
Are you going to get this gate open?
Ah, no need to worry about that.
This is my territory down here, yeah?
Now let's see what you've got.
Come on. Let's trade.
There. Ye-e-e-es!
Is that all?
Not much for slitting a man's throat.
That's all.
Ten francs? Are you sure?
With your permission...
Arms out. Arms out!
Ahhh!
Hardly worth it these days, is it, eh?
The robbery game.
No-one's got nothing no more.
All right, mister, I'll let you out.
Take your friend with you.
Find a rope,
tie it around a big stone...
...when you dump him.
You don't want him bobbing up.
Come on!
Go on. Go on!
Oi.
Oi!
You ruined my life.
I was a respected man. I had money.
Now I live like a rat
in the shitty darkness!
It's him.
- It's Jean Valjean.
- Inspector Javert,
you can take me now,
but grant me one favour.
Help me take this man home
to his grandfather.
Who is he?
His name's Marius Pontmercy.
He's wounded.
- He looks dead.
- No, not yet.
Not yet.
Will you help me?
Please?
Monsieur Gillenormand!
Open up. Police! Open up!
Tell your master we've brought
his grandson's body home.
His grandson, you say?
Oh, my God, it's Monsieur Marius.
Gently! Careful.
It's Monsieur Marius!
Gently, gently. Careful.
Merci, monsieur.
Oh, oh...
Monsieur Marius,
what have they done to you?
Ahhhh, no need to tell me...
He's dead! He's dead!
He's got himself killed
on the barricades, just to defy me.
He knew very well I was waiting for him!
You... you had to do it, didn't you,
you had to break an old man's heart...
Wait! Monsieur! I can feel a pulse.
Pray God he'll live!
Serge! Serge! Quickly, get him upstairs.
Come on! Come on! Quickly! Quickly.
Hurry.
One more favour.
Let me go home.
Just for a few minutes.
Then you can do with me what you want.
Granted.
That young man.
Is he a...
...particular friend of yours?
Would you say he's... dear to you?
Quite the contrary.
If he lives, he intends to...
...rob me of... all my happiness.
And yet you...
Are you insane?
No, I don't think so.
Are you?
Go in.
I'll wait for you here.
You trust me?
Go in.
Forgive me.
Now you can find him.
Javert?
Javert?!
Yes, sir?
I've been making some recommendations
for the more efficient running
of the service.
I entrust you with the task
of bringing them
to the attention of the commissioners.
Very good, sir.
All well?
No.
Rivette...
...all is not well.
Prisoner Valjean.
He's no longer a prisoner.
I, er...
I let him go free.
May I ask why, sir?
I don't know.
As an act of clemency?
An act of madness.
That man...
That man!
Everything I've ever believed to be true.
Everything I lived my life by...
And he...
He...
No matter.
I shall, of course,
be resigning my commission.
Really, sir, one mistake...
If it is indeed a mistake, one
mistake against... a long career...
How can I continue? After this?
I have brought myself
and the police service into
disgrace and disrepute.
I need some fresh air.
I'm going for a walk.
Remember to bring those notes to the
attention of the Prefect Of Police.
Goodnight, Rivette.
I beg, Monsieur Le Prefet,
to consider these proposals
for improvements to the service.
First, that we end the practice
of prisoners
returning from interrogations
being made to remove their shoes
while they await transport
back to the prison.
Many are coughing
when they return to their cells.
This leads to hospital experiences.
Second, a prisoner who drops
a thread in the weaving room
loses 10 sous. This is an abuse of...
Third, special regulation of the...
Fourth, surveillance is generally...
Fifth, gendarmes...
Prisoners coming back from the...
Yah!
Argh!
Vive la revolution!
Ssh, Marius...
Oh, my!
My dear boy...
How did I end up here?
You were carried here by the police.
Not the police.
Somebody else. At the barricade.
I owe him my life.
Are they all dead?
Enjolras, Courfeyrac,
Grantaire, all my friends.
It... would seem so.
Was it all for nothing?
It brought you back to me,
my dearest boy.
I want to get married.
Do you indeed?
Did you hear that?
He wants to be married now!
All arranged.
What do you mean?
What I say. You shall have
your little sweetheart.
I've done some investigating,
and I find she's a jewel.
And she adores you.
So, no more to be said.
Cosette agreed.
Love agreed.
I couldn't... be happier.
My beloved child.
Father...
Did you hear that? "Father"!
Well, he loves me after all.
Now he's getting the girl he wants!
Well, why not?
- Ah, come in, monsieur.
- Marius!
You're very welcome.
- Cosette...
- Please, please, take a seat.
Thank you.
What happened to you?
It doesn't matter. Someone, I don't
know who, brought me back to you.
You're very lucky, my boy.
If I were 15 years younger,
we'd be drawing swords
to see which of us would have her!
Really, Father!
What's the matter?
Can't I be in love with her too?
It's only natural.
I'm joking, Mademoiselle. He's all yours.
You have a handsome husband
worth his salt.
No matter about money.
Your grandpapa will take care
of the pair of you.
No, my daughter has... has a dowry.
650,000 francs.
- 650,000 francs?!
- It's all there.
Well, you lucky devil!
Your little dove
turns out to be a millionairess!
They don't care, monsieur.
The only care about each other.
Ah, what it is to be young!
Well, I'll... take my leave, monsieur.
No, no, no. I won't hear of it.
We're all one happy family now.
- Stay for dinner.
- No, monsieur, thank you.
But with your permission,
I'll take my leave.
I'll see you later, Cosette.
No need for you to come now.
Very well, Papa. I'll see you later.
Thank you.
What can I do for you, monsieur?
I'm afraid I... I have to sit down.
I have something to tell you.
I am an ex-convict.
20 years in the prison hulks.
Escaped, recaptured.
Escaped again.
And presently I'm a wanted man.
I'm a thief.
I stole from a bishop,
the Bishop of Digne.
I even robbed a child.
You, Cosette's father!
No, I'm not her father.
She was an orphan.
I found her.
I am no-one.
I'm a peasant from Faverolles.
My first crime
was to steal a loaf of bread.
Do you see? I'm...
I'm a common criminal.
I knew there was something.
I remember, at the tavern.
You shot that police officer.
Is that why you came
to the barricade, to kill him?
What if I told you
I came to the barricades
with half a mind to kill you?
Yes, you see,
that's what you're dealing with.
For God's sake.
What am I to think of you now?
Think of me as you wish.
I wanted you to know the truth
so that I could take my leave
of her, and you, in peace.
I don't belong in the family of men,
monsieur.
I'm on the outside.
Poor Cosette! When she finds out...
No, I beg you, monsieur,
I beg you. Spare her that.
You can't ask me to keep this from her!
Monsieur...
...one day, when she was with me...
...she saw the chain gang go by.
And she couldn't bear to think...
...that such wicked men existed.
Men like me.
If you keep my secret, I promise,
that after the wedding I shall
get out of your lives forever.
Agreed.
Thank you, monsieur.
Good day, Baron Pontmercy.
I wish you a happy life.
Ah, elle est jolie!
- Papa?
- Yes, my dear?
Are you happy?
Course I'm happy. Happy for you.
Then why aren't you smiling?
I'm just... I'm going to miss you.
That's all.
Don't be silly, Papa.
The honeymoon will be over
before we know it,
and I'll be back in six weeks.
And... then we will see each other
all of the time.
- Thank you. I'm glad to be home.
- Thank you, gentlemen.
I still think we should go
and see Papa first.
He'll be wanting to know
all about our wedding journey.
- Maybe later. Come on, darling.
- Nicolette!
Madame!
Monsieur!
- Merci.
- Merci, monsieur.
Oh, welcome home!
Ah. There's a visitor to see you.
Very important, the gentleman said.
- I put him in the drawing-room.
- Very well.
Oh.
Bonjour, Monsieur Le Baron.
What are you doing here?
Monsieur, I just thought
I'd congratulate you
on your wedding day.
And, Madame, you look so beautiful.
But I remember when you were
a skinny little guttersnipe
we picked up at Montfermeil.
Thenardier.
That's me.
Marius, this man is evil.
My father saved me from him
when I was a little girl.
Your father...
Let me tell you something
about your father.
Cosette, go upstairs,
I'll deal with this.
What do you want here?
I've got some information for you
that'll make your hair stand on end.
What information?
I want a little something in exchange.
I want to set up a business.
In La Jolla. The New World.
There's money to be made there,
slaves to trade.
- And your information is?
- Cosette.
That old fella, your so-called father,
is a thief and an assassin.
I wouldn't have him in the house
if I was you. Not safe.
I know all this.
He told me so himself.
Oh, yeah?
Who did he kill, then?
He killed the police spy, Javert.
I'm sorry, Cosette.
Well, I... It's not true.
How could you believe such a thing?
She's right. Cos he didn't.
Javert did himself in.
I saw it with my own eyes.
Threw himself off a bridge, he did.
Nah, the one that the old fella
killed was a young chap.
I met him in the sewers
just after he'd done it.
He was going to dump the young chap
in the river.
What did he look like, this young chap?
About his size. I don't know.
What are you saying?
You've got it all wrong, you old fool.
He was saving your life!
He must have been the man
that carried you home.
He saved my life.
He saved your life.
What about me?!
Eh?
- You?
- Yeah.
You came here to ruin a man...
...and you crowned him with glory.
You're a liar, and a stupid one at that.
And you're the thief,
you're the murderer.
I saw what you did in that squalid slum.
I could have you chained up
for the rest of your life.
Now get out before I change my mind.
Wait.
Take this with you.
1,000 francs.
I understand you saved
my father's life at Waterloo.
The Colonel...
...Baron Pontmercy.
Monsieur and Madame Pontmercy, er...
...once in a lifetime,
virtue is rewarded, eh?
My eternal gratitude.
Papa? Papa!
Cosette?
He's gone away.
The candlesticks -
they're gone.
I'm sorry I kept the truth
from you, Cosette.
I made a promise to your father.
Marius...
...I think I know where he might be.
Papa?
Papa.
It's you.
You've come?
You took the candlesticks.
I thought we might find you in Digne.
You saved my life, and never told me.
Oh, monsieur...
I thought I'd never see her again.
Cosette.
Oh, Papa.
Didn't you know,
I'm not worthy of your love?
- I'm not worthy of anybody's love.
- Don't speak like that.
I know everything.
Why did you run away and hide?
Oh... Oh, Papa! Papa...
Papa, your hands, they're so cold.
That's because I'm going to die soon.
No.
No, you're not.
You won't, because...
Because I won't let you.
You're coming home with us.
I'm going to kidnap you.
Do you really love me?
Oh, Papa. Papa.
Are you still there?
Yes, Papa.
I had... things to tell you.
Never mind.
Thank you.
Love each other.
Monsieur!
- Monsieur!
- No.
Monsieur!