Something terrible
happened last summer
and I have no memory of what
or who hurt me.
No one in my family
will tell me...
...if they even speak to me
at all.
Maybe they're afraid
the truth will destroy me,
or maybe
it will destroy them first.
When you're left for dead,
you want answers.
I'm determined to get mine.
My name is
Cadence Sinclair Eastman.
I was once strength
and promise and spun gold.
The photographer's due
in an hour.
On it.
Thanks.
Your grandmother
wants us to wear...
Ocean hues and neutrals.
I already know.
I saw the Ralph Lauren bag
on my bed.
Oh, uh, Aunt Carrie's wondering
if you know where Johnny is?
My cousin Johnny.
Salt, swagger,
and reckless abandon.
Police escort.
It's definitely a vibe.
It was actually awesome.
These two vineyard bros,
they bet me
that I couldn't corner
a golf cart at top speed.
And...well, they were right,
obviously.
But when I tell you
I literally took flight...
Yeah, right through
the pro shop window?
- Yeah, and not a scratch on me.
- I got that phone call. Ugh.
What did the cops say about
your aeronautical adventure?
I don't know.
They were cool.
Also, they got me here
just in time, yeah?
Can't have Gran and Grandad
mad at me for being late, hey?
What, mad at the eldest boy?
Come on.
Get your smiles on, William.
Male heirs need to represent.
I'll give you a head start.
Go.
♪ That train has
left the station ♪
♪ But our love will grow ♪
♪ Oh ♪
♪ Oh, oh, oh ♪
♪ Oh, oh, oh... ♪
My cousin Mirren.
Sugar, effort,
and constant curiosity.
They're gathering.
Now, see,
you look iconic in that outfit
and I look like a golf caddy.
No, you don't.
But...
My mom's gonna fillet me.
What do I do?
Oh, I...
Switch with me.
- Are you sure?
- Yeah.
I won't get in trouble.
I'm Cadence the First.
I have plenty of "get out
of jail free" cards to spare.
OK, fine.
Let me see your paintbrush.
Really?
You said ocean hues
and neutrals.
Just stand behind someone tall
in the group shot.
A straight line, please.
Liberty, can you move
an inch that way, please?
Just an inch.
That's not an inch, Liberty.
The shirt I laid out for you
hid your bony shoulders.
Smile.
I'm over it.
When are Ed and Gat
getting here?
Uh, Gat's
on the afternoon ferry
and Ed's got some business
on the vineyard.
Ed always has business
on family photo day.
Why is he never in the picture?
'Cause they're living in sin.
Stop it!
We'll take a selfie later.
♪ To try to get up and go ♪
♪ Oh, na-na, na-na-na, na-now,
can't you see... ♪
Real smiles, please.
♪ To have your way... ♪
Cadence.
Welcome to
the beautiful Sinclair family.
Yes, we are those Sinclairs.
Some people call us
American royalty.
We live,
at least in the summer,
on Beechwood Island,
a landmark
of the Martha's Vineyard Sound
where we gather every year
to swim and sun
and tell the tallest of tales.
♪ If you say the word,
then I'll say goodbye ♪
♪ Forever I see
you and me... ♪
Oh, hi, Mom. Hi, Dad.
And there's our William.
And that hair.
Oh, here you go. Yeah.
A true Sinclair boy.
Mom, we brought
Ed's nephew, Gat.
- Oh.
- I know.
His father passed this year,
so it's a big help
to Ed's sister-in-law.
Cady, Mirren,
I brought Gat!
What's a Gat? Wait!
This was the year
my story truly began,
the summer my cousins and I
were eight years old...
Summer 8, we called it...
when we met the boy
who would change everything.
Poor kid stowed away
behind the captain's chair
the whole time
we were on the water.
Aww.
He's probably found
somewhere small to hide.
Are you real?
I think so.
I'm Cadence.
I'm Gat.
Tag. You're it.
Johnny, Mirren, come on!
I'm gonna get you!
On Beechwood,
Johnny, Mirren, Gat, and I
were wild and fearless.
Our island was a fairy tale
filled with kings and queens
and castles.
On it, we could be anything.
Johnny!
♪ We're only young
and naive still... ♪
♪ We require certain skills ♪
♪ The mood,
it changes like the wind... ♪
Our antics led
to our family calling us
the Liars.
We probably deserved it.
Come on, stay still.
Liars forever!
Gat grew to love
Beechwood as much as I did.
And now, I can't imagine
summers without him.
My best friend,
my favorite thing
about my favorite place.
♪ Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah... ♪
Honestly, Cadence,
would a genuine smile kill you?
- Come on.
- Gat!
Come on,
everybody settle down.
Gat was once
fireflies, mischief,
and old books.
But in Summer 16, he would
turn to something new.
Gat!
Tag. You're it.
This was how it all began.
We were happy.
We wanted for nothing.
No one was an addict.
No one was a criminal.
No one was needy.
No one was a failure.
We swore
things would never change.
Cannonball!
♪ Fall back in love
eventually ♪
We had no idea
how wrong we were.
♪ Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah ♪♪
Thank you.
Oh, I have for you...
Tell me about your adventures.
God, life is boring
when I'm not here.
That can't possibly be true.
Beautiful people
don't get bored.
- Mm. That's a fact.
- Yeah, right?
Gat, tell Cady beautiful people
don't get bored.
I hear women can be
anything they want these days.
Two things at once, even.
Mom, will you have Amira
send some fabric swatches?
I want to redecorate
Windemere this summer.
Cuddledown is way overdue.
Next year.
Right now, Windemere needs
a full divorce cleanse.
You OK?
Yeah, we're putting an offer
on a perfect space in Tribeca
that goes on the market
in August.
It's right by my gallery.
There's room for a nursery
for when...
There's also this great store
right on the corner
that I've almost convinced
to carry my jewelry line.
Oh, Carrie, that's fantastic.
- What is that?
- Yeah.
That, right there.
What is that?
What?
Party boat? Sick!
It's obstructing the view.
That looks awesome.
It's gauche.
Cady,
sorry about the divorce.
The universe sucks sometimes,
but I'm glad you're in it.
From Gat.
PS, found a lucky penny
on the ferry.
♪ I pretend
that you don't understand ♪
♪ I sure as hell
don't know you well... ♪
Gat got...
- taller.
- Yeah.
And he joined
the swim team too.
Decided I'm getting us on that
party boat this weekend.
Why?
It's just a bunch
of drunk, trashy tourists
looking to hook up.
Exactly.
Come on, dude.
OK.
Two truths and a lie
about your off-island time.
Uh...Mirren.
Fine. Um...
I've been sexting
with an older guy...
I got a flower tattoo
on my bum,
and I met Taylor Swift.
No way sweet little Mirren
is sexting.
- That's the lie.
- What kind of flower?
- A daisy.
- OK, that's the lie.
Who's the sexter?
He's a senior I met
in the debate semis,
and he's incredible.
It's a disaster.
Does he use the splash emoji?
Ew, no, he just...
his family's coming out
in August to the Vineyard
and he's gonna want
to actually have sex,
which is impossible, so...
You don't want to?
I have been texting
like I'm an OnlyFans girl.
I have no idea how to do
any of that stuff, and...
I don't do anything
that I'm not excellent at.
So I need to make sure
that the time is right,
the place is right,
the vibes are good,
and that there's, you know,
nothing awkward or weird
or, like, sticky.
Yeah, good luck with that.
Cadence, your turn.
OK, fine.
I crashed the Beemer
that my mom got me,
I got a short story published
in Write City Magazine,
and I kissed
three unimportant boys.
Yeah, you didn't wreck the car.
You just know her too well.
We can't play this game
with the two of you.
She has tells.
Plus I, uh...
I read that short story.
I liked it.
- Thanks.
- Your turn, Gat.
Let's see.
Uh, OK.
I got busted for stealing
a six-pack from the bodega,
I got my junior
motorcycle license,
and...
I pulled a fire alarm
and ended up
in Saturday detention with
a bunch of other delinquents
who actually, I don't know,
turned out to be pretty cool.
Lie.
I've seen that movie.
You have a motorcycle?
OK, it's just a written test
in New York.
Anybody want an ice pop?
Ooh, ice pop.
I'm coming with.
Wait, wait, Johnny.
You skipped your turn.
What?
You couldn't handle my truths.
I can't believe
you read that story.
It was kind of weird.
No, it wasn't.
It was beautiful.
I mean, when the narrator
turned out to be
inside the mind
of the princess?
Such a good plot twist.
It was kind of sad too.
Genuinely.
I mean, I was torn apart after.
What?
No, it's, uh, nothing.
It's just...
my other friends didn't get it.
So robbing a bodega.
That's a level up for you.
Yeah,
I don't know why I did that.
You know, I knew the owner,
like, my whole life.
They used to give me free M&Ms.
Didn't call the cops, though.
Just my mom.
That's why she sent me
to India over the break.
She thought time
with my grandparents
would somehow teach me
how to respect my elders.
Tell me more about your trip.
It was...
it was honestly amazing.
And hard too.
So I hadn't been there
since I was a baby,
so it was all pretty new.
Cady, there is so much art,
so much culture there.
It did change me.
My nana, she took me out
to the rural area and...
Something changed that day.
I looked at him
and he wasn't just Gat.
He was contemplation,
enthusiasm,
ambition, and strong coffee.
He seemed like he was mine.
I don't believe in soulmates
or the supernatural,
but in that moment,
the world felt magical.
That's what you need.
A distraction.
No, I don't need a distraction.
I need a decorator.
Well, I'm not sure
what's harder,
wrangling three girls
for a five-minute FaceTime
with their father,
or keeping him on the line
long enough to talk
to his wife.
I mean, at a certain point,
are you even really married?
My marriage is just fine.
So was mine, until it wasn't.
To be fair, Penny, you are
emotionally unavailable.
And, Bess, you are...
She is a Beacon Hill tradwife.
I don't know what that is.
It's rude is what it is.
Brody is able
to build his empire
because I run our household
like a Fortune 500 CEO,
keep three gremlins
out of trouble,
and still manage
to make it to Sunday dinners
at Mom and Dad's every week,
whereas you breed dogs
and sit back at an arm's length
while your brilliant daughter
overachieves.
Did I miss anything?
No.
Nailed it.
Bess, tell Penny it's all right
to get naked with Salty Dan.
- With who?
- Salty Dan, the...
- hello?
- The harbor service guy?
He's a cowboy.
A cowboy of the sea.
Gotta get back on that horse.
Gimme.
Harris?
Sorry. Have you got a minute?
I wanted to ask you...
It's there again.
You're...
talking about the boat.
The whole sound
at his disposal,
parks his ass in my view.
You're an industrious
young man.
See what you can do about it.
Show us what you're made of,
Sinclairs.
Winner gets my eternal respect.
Winner gets a pound of fudge
from Murdick's.
Whoo!
And who is the judge?
Who do you think?
Excellent foundational
structure, Littles.
You need more decoration.
Unfair, Liars.
You're stacking the deck
with a professional.
As reigning champion,
I'm allowed to sprinkle
my magic anywhere I want.
How about right here?
Yes. Mm.
Carrie, this needs more water.
No. Water will make it drip.
Yeah, that's the point.
I need the drips, all right?
Otherwise,
it's just a block of dirt.
I'm going for, like,
carpenter's gothic.
All right? Like, icing trim.
OK. Yes.
I see the vision.
You know, I'm not sure
you're gonna be able
to top last year's
architectural spectacle.
The tide charts
were misleading.
I love how stressed out
you get about this every year.
I curate art collections
for a living.
I can't attach my name
to anything less
than a masterpiece.
All right, so...
party boat.
Ugh.
- Just let it go, bruh.
- Let the party boat go.
- So annoying.
- What?
Look, we have everything
that we need right here.
That's the problem.
Our sexual prime
is passing us by
while we build
fucking sandcastles.
- What is that?
- It's for the fudge, man.
- I need it.
- No, fine.
- It's the best fudge.
- The best fudge.
You need the fudge.
Cool.
Johnny, come on.
Your dad is burning
a party-boat-sized hole
in the back of my head.
Just ignore it.
It's 'cause he's used to bossing
around entire corporations.
He's not gonna fire you.
I won't let him.
- Oh.
- I promise.
I'm trying to build.
♪ But that don't
make it real ♪
♪ Real love takes
and cops that feel ♪
- Oh!
- Come on!
Hey, hey, hey. Hey.
Hey, hey, hey.
And the Littles
are the winners.
- I knew it!
- Yes!
♪ Same days,
same days forever ♪
same days forever ♪♪
Cady.
You guys coming or what?
You know,
I think that's the mousse
Harris requested
Lydia make for tonight.
Well, there's always pie.
Hey, so do you want
to take the boat out with me?
You're finally ready
to drive the boat?
No, no, no, no.
Why?
You know why.
It's a Sinclair boat.
Well,
you're an honorary Sinclair.
Doesn't give me the freedom
to drive it, does it?
Fine.
Where do you want to go?
♪ Darling,
won't you take me home? ♪
♪ Send me shivers
somewhere I used to go ♪
♪ Wrap my name
across your mouth ♪
♪ When I let
my feelings down ♪
♪ Darling,
won't you take me... ♪
On the count of three?
Three...
Two, one.
♪ Home ♪
♪ Send me shivers
somewhere I used to go ♪
♪ Wrap my name
across your mouth ♪
♪ When I let
my feelings down ♪
♪ Darling,
won't you take me ♪♪
It's cold. It's cold.
It's cold.
What were we thinking,
jumping in the water?
I mean, everyone knows
there's practically
a shark infestation
off the coast.
Suck it up, swim team.
Fine, fine, but when I get
murdered by a shark,
I expect you to write
a really excellent eulogy.
It's not murder. You're prey.
Come on.
OK, fine.
- Better?
- Better.
Why are you looking at me
like that?
I'm not.
OK.
You...
Why are you looking at me?
I don't know.
You just...
you seem different.
In a good way?
In a new way.
You have this,
like, confidence.
Do you sometimes feel like
everything is changing?
In the real world, yeah.
But not on Beechwood.
That's what I love about it.
It feels different
without your dad, though.
I guess.
But I'm not supposed
to talk about him, so...
That's weird.
- That's my mother.
- Oh.
You OK with everything?
We got a new couch.
That is a very Penny
response.
It's a really nice couch.
Right.
- Right.
Did you take me out here
'cause you think
I need therapy?
Because Sinclairs
do not do therapy.
Right, right.
Sinclairs believe
in outdoor exercise,
stiff upper lips
and, what, cocktail hour?
- Yeah.
- Right, right.
I-I brought you out here
'cause I thought
you might need a friend.
I didn't understand
what I was feeling.
But then I saw him
writing me a letter
with a beech flower
he had dried and pressed.
The porch light.
The piece of hair
falling across his face.
I thought, "Gat.
My Gat."
And then I knew.
I knew how I felt.
♪ Honey, I'm spiraling ♪
♪ The web that I'm tangled in ♪
♪ Just isn't built for two ♪
♪ So before I let you in ♪
♪ Tread lightly,
just tread lightly ♪
♪ I've made enough mistakes ♪
♪ To fill up the oceans, babe ♪
♪ And when it rains,
it pours, so if you're... ♪
Do you want to watch
the meteor shower
with me tonight?
I don't think Johnny has
the attention span
for stargazing.
What about just us?
♪ Dive in ♪
♪ Baby, dive ♪
♪ Oh, baby, dive... ♪
Sure. Yeah.
Just us.
♪ Baby, dive ♪♪
Don't even think about it.
Oh, come on.
I need to be entertained.
Here.
Have at it.
A bookmark.
I'm sure you and I have
different meanings of the word.
Should we play
some tennis?
- Yeah.
- Uh, no offense.
You three are not
up to my standards.
- Oh, that's ridiculous.
- No.
- Come on.
- Come on. We're not that bad.
I am terrible.
I'll admit it.
Turns out I need a new
doubles partner this year.
The Eastern
Connecticut Championship
will never be the same.
Yeah, well, things got messy
when we started losing.
Messy how?
Well, we had
all these travel matches.
You know how it goes.
Hotel rooms and chaperones
who don't actually chaperone.
Wait.
We're talking about Jackson,
right?
Not your mixed doubles partner.
Wait, is this a big
coming out moment?
- Dude, congrats.
- Whatever.
Don't throw a parade
or anything.
Still figuring it out.
Look, the point is, one night,
we just sort of went for it.
And it got weird.
Everything changed.
Like, ruined our vibe.
No rhythm on the court.
We're not even, like,
friends anymore.
It blows.
I'm sure it kind of messed up
the whole team too.
Mm. 100%.
Well, we should
watch a movie.
Back to the Future 2
or Romeo and Juliet?
Uh, I think I'm gonna
finish my book tonight.
Yeah, same.
Did you borrow
Johnny's cologne?
No.
That is potent.
What are you doing?
Reading up on
Vineyard maritime ordinances.
Harris and I are
in a chess match.
Unfortunately,
even if I win, I lose.
- House rules.
- Why do you play at all?
When you fall in love
with a Sinclair girl,
you agree to participate in
the family mindfuck Olympics.
Yeah, greater men have crumbled
under pressure, but I remain.
Ooh, by the way,
you got a letter in the mail.
I thought your generation
only communicated via texts
with no punctuation.
Gat, bro, I've done it.
I've bested
even my greatest achievements.
OK.
Do I want to know?
Do I?
You do not.
You, my friend,
you're coming with me.
What?
Yeah, and you're not
wearing that.
- Wait, why?
- See ya, Ed!
Cady.
It's on.
The party boat.
My guy came through.
We're in.
Not driving.
What are you doing up here?
I thought you were
reading tonight.
Meteor shower.
OK.
Party boat!
Whoo-hoo!
♪ Waiting for the night
to come ♪
♪ 'Cause I've been hiding
from the sun ♪
♪ Every time
I hear the wind ♪
♪ Yeah, I can feel it
rolling in ♪
♪ Tell me what you wanna do ♪
♪ 'Cause I've been thinking
me and you could... ♪
Ooh, sorry, taken. Sorry.
♪ Won't you say
what's on your mind? ♪
OK. Tequila, anybody?
♪ 'Cause I've been
running out of time... ♪
Gat?
Dude, what's your deal?
What?
You're staring at Cadence.
I'm not staring at her.
- What do you mean?
- So what are you looking at?
N-nothing.
I'm not looking at anything.
Cadence does look
extra pretty tonight.
Can I borrow
some of that lipstick?
Since when do you wear
lipstick on Beechwood?
Enough about the lipstick,
please.
Did you notice
the lipstick, Gat?
Is that why
you were looking at her?
'Cause she looks
extra pretty tonight?
I wasn't...
look, she looks the same
as always, OK?
What are you guys doing?
Fine, Gat.
OK.
Let's find a bar, yeah?
Mirren, shot.
We're gonna do a shot.
- Come on, Gat.
- No. Come on.
All right!
Come on,
we're at a party.
Mwah!
Well, I have to go
and get ready.
Brody is coming in
on the last flight.
Oh, honey, that's lovely.
How did you manage
to convince him?
I simply reminded him
that marriage is about
more than just providing.
Ah.
You bartered in blowjobs, eh?
Girls, show some class.
At least we still have sex.
Oh, if I was
offended by that,
I would still be married.
The divorce jokes. Pen.
I know, I know.
The Sinclair way is
to never mention it at all.
That's not fair.
Obviously, I am here for you
if you want to share.
You don't have
to worry about me.
I'm fine.
Honestly.
I don't miss Sam. I...
18 years of marriage, and I
don't even think about him.
What does that say about me?
Well, Sinclairs face forward.
I imagine the divorce
must be draining, though.
Mostly on my bank account.
He's coming after me
for everything.
The Burlington house
and what's left of the trust.
He leaves you
for another woman,
and he thinks he deserves that?
The nerve.
It's not...
it's not that simple.
He's hired
a private investigator.
- I'll just...
- No.
Hey, where are the other Liars?
They're just, uh,
doing their own thing.
Surprisingly off-brand.
- Where?
- What?
The booze cruise, obviously.
No, we weren't there.
Oh, you kids.
You think I have no idea?
As if I didn't get my fake ID
from the exact same
shitty backdoor bar in Edgartown
when I was your age.
Then why didn't you tell him
he couldn't go?
Because then he would
want to go even more.
I mean, people always want
what they can't have.
Wait.
Were any of you served alcohol?
We're underage.
Yeah.
Yeah, you guys are.
Perfect. Thank you.
I'm off to threaten
a small business owner.
Hey.
What?
We can't all stay
trapped in amber
on Beechwood forever,
as much as we would like to.
Why don't you come
watch the meteors
with me and the kids?
We're having s'mores.
OK?
Once upon a time,
long, long ago...
there was an enchanted island
with four beautiful castles.
And it was on that island
that a young maiden met
a gallant prince.
But...
she had no need
for such trivial things.
For that smart
young maiden knew
that princes would come and go.
Whoa.
Hmm?
A meteor, William?
Nope. Shark.
There are no sharks here.
It's probably a whale.
- Night vision.
- Cady?
- Wait, I wanna see the shark.
- Where is everybody going?
Why are you in the water?
I was swimming.
But you're wearing clothes.
I know.
I just really wanted
to be here with you guys.
Instead of where I was.
Tag.
You're it.
OK.
Why'd you run?
To see if you'd still chase me.
I've been chasing you
my whole life.
I'll always chase you.
You made me feel
so stupid tonight.
I know.
I'm sorry.
Johnny was so intent
on us all going,
and I got scared.
Of what?
Cannonball!
Get your asses in here
right now, you ditchers!
Get in!
Cannonball!
Where's the taxi?
My husband was due in
on the last flight.
Well, whoever's on that flight
got to where they needed to be
already.
I'm the one who's running late.
Hey, tell your mom
I'll load her up
on those clams she likes.
Can you tell me
what's wrong with me?
I've had three kids, sure,
but...
I maintain myself.
I write thank-you notes
on time.
I don't lose my temper.
I am sexually generous.
I am prettier
than both of my sisters.
Yes, Carrie's got
the stronger chin,
but that's only because
my father bought it for her.
All told, I can't see
a single thing wrong with me,
except for the fact
that I married a man
who can't seem to make it
on the last fucking flight
of the day.
Do you have any cigarettes?
- You need a light?
- Yes.
These things will kill you,
you know.
Well, since you asked,
the answer is,
there's not a thing
wrong with you.
Not from where I'm standing.
Look, there's another one.
You guys could have
just told us
you wanted to be somewhere else
tonight, you know?
Instead of ditching us.
I'm sorry.
Yeah. I'm sorry too.
OK.
All is forgiven.
And I'm freezing.
You guys want to play a round
of Code Names at Red Gate?
Ooh, yes.
Yeah.
Right behind you.
Be right there.
I'll grab my stuff.
Am I forgiven too?
'Cause I wanted to hang out
with you, just us.
I did, but I...
I got nervous.
And Johnny was
so set on the party,
and I didn't know
how to explain.
I'm just really, really sorry.
Well...
you might be forgiven.
But...
you're gonna have to learn
how to drive the boat first.
I think that has to wait
until I can afford to fix it
if I break it.
And you're gonna have to stop
looking at me like that.
I'm not looking at you.
That was a lie.
And back on the boat,
I lied then too.
That's why I swam back.
To tell you I was...
I was looking.
Of course I was.
♪ Getting through still has
a cost... ♪
I do you think you're pretty.
So pretty, it's distracting.
♪ It slips through
your fingers, love ♪
♪ Falling from you... ♪
I don't want to lie anymore.
♪ Drop by drop ♪
♪ What I had left here ♪
♪ I just held it tight ♪
♪ So someone with your eyes ♪
♪ Might come in time ♪
♪ To hold me like water ♪
♪ Or Christ,
hold me like a knife ♪
♪ We're born at night ♪
♪ So much of our lives ♪
♪ Is just carving
through the dark... ♪
When we kissed,
it was like
all the stars in the sky
banged loose
from their moorings.
For a long time,
that night was the last thing
I remembered of summer 16.
Gat and me,
caught in the idyll
of our own perfect fairy tale
on Beechwood Island
with summers with sandcastles
and lemonade.
And no one was a criminal.
♪ Darling, we sacrificed ♪
♪ We gave our time ♪
♪ To something undefined... ♪
No one was an addict.
♪ This phantom life ♪
♪ Sharpens like an image ♪
♪ But it sharpens
like a knife ♪
♪ We're born at night... ♪
No one was needy.
♪ So much of our lives ♪
♪ Is just carving
through the dark ♪
♪ Yeah... ♪
And no one was a failure.
We were happy.
We wanted for nothing.
♪ Yeah... ♪
But it's important
to remember...
...we were liars.
This season
on We Were Liars...
Remember who you are.
Oh, Cady.
All year long, you didn't come
to the hospital or call.
Why did you forbid everyone
from talking to me
about my own fucking life?
The doctors,
they said it was best
if you remember on your own.
Ugh, we had a moment.
I knew there was a vibe.
Watch yourself, young man.
You could get hurt.
When two families merge,
someone always feels
like an intruder.
Everything feels messed up.
- No, fuck you!
- Stop!
You know, maybe I'm wrong
about how perfect it felt.
But not every fable
ends happily.
Some stories have no hero
at all.
Sometimes,
the castle crumbles.
Johnny!
You think I'm a fucking idiot.
Don't you dare try
to gaslight me.
You chose to be a mother.
I didn't ask for you
to waste your life on me.
Let's be real.
None of us is gonna be
his favorite daughter.
I have always believed
that women are entitled
to our secrets.
Wanna know the truth,
Cadence?
Maybe I'm a terrible person.
You wanna believe that?
I need answers.
I need to see
if all the lies
lead to me on that beach
alone.
What did you do?
♪ Once upon a time,
there was a princess ♪
♪ Waiting for a boy
to give back her shoe ♪
♪ Suck it in, suck it in,
be a wife in a blue dress ♪
♪ The prettiest piece of
property the land ever knew ♪
♪ She waited and she waited
for the guy to show ♪
♪ But she didn't know
that after midnight ♪
♪ He was busy
in her stepsister's bed ♪
♪ So Cinderelly said ♪
♪ Plot twist ♪
♪ I don't need no prince
to save me ♪
♪ I'm a goddamn CEO ♪
♪ Don't call me "baby,"
equal pay me ♪
♪ Snow White said
you tried to kiss her ♪
♪ So I'll just buy
a new glass slipper ♪
♪ And burn your castle down ♪
♪ And kids, that's how
Cinderella snapped ♪
♪ When the smoke cleared,
every girl in the whole land ♪
♪ Woke the fuck up
and started making demands ♪
♪ Rapunzel shaved her head ♪
♪ So there was nothing
to climb on ♪
♪ Jasmine made out
with Mulan ♪
♪ Sleeping Beauty sued
the dude who kissed her ♪
♪ While she was asleep ♪
♪ And Ariel was confident
without any feet ♪
♪ Tiana went and got
her biomedical degree ♪
♪ And Beauty realized
that she was the Beast ♪
♪ I don't need no prince
to save me ♪
♪ I'm a goddamn C ♪
♪ Your castle down ♪
♪ And kids, that's how
Cinderella snapped ♪♪