[theme music playing]
[Dani] He's awake!
He's awake.
- [Hannah] Oh, thank God.
- [Dani] He's awake. He's awake.
[Dani breathes heavily]
[menacing music playing]
["Tainted Love" by Cell Soft playing]
♪ Sometimes I feel I've got to ♪
♪ Run away
I've got to ♪
♪ Get away ♪
♪ From the pain
You drive into the heart of me ♪
♪ The love we share ♪
♪ Seems to go nowhere ♪
♪ And I've lost my light ♪
♪ For I toss and turn
I can't sleep at night ♪
- ♪ Once I ran to you ♪
- ♪ I ran ♪
♪ Now, I'll run from you ♪
♪ This tainted love you've given ♪
♪ I give you all a boy could give you ♪
- ♪ Take my tears ♪
- Good morning.
♪ And that's not nearly all ♪
- ♪ Tainted love ♪
- ♪ Oh, oh ♪
- ♪ Oh, oh… ♪
Good morning.
[Henry moans]
Most certainly isn't.
[man] Little hair of the dog…
- [Henry sighs heavily]
- …and your ten o'clock.
[groans]
No one before noon.
[chuckling] Oh, no you don't.
You insisted.
Even if you begged, you said,
we had to get this one done.
Ugh. Christ. [sniffs]
[sighs] The nanny.
Au pair. Here.
Au pair.
[sighs]
[gentle piano music plays]
Miss Jessel.
I'm Peter Quint. I work with Henry.
Mr. Quint.
Uh, no… [chuckles]
So... so, uh, you have a stain.
Right there.
Oh.
Do... do you need a minute?
No.
Good now.
He will notice, you know.
Okay.
- [Peter] Please.
- Thank you.
Mr. Wingrave,
this is Rebecca Jessel.
I just read about your win
in the Baker case,
and my hat's off.
Read where?
The Telegraph, of course.
Mm.
You have a stain on your blouse.
The children are, what?
Seven and nine?
Mm.
I expect being precious about blouses
won't serve me well.
Quite.
The agency has told you
about our circumstances, I trust?
Yes, and I'm dreadfully sorry
about your loss. I…
can only imagine
what those poor children have been...
- I don't have my reading glasses, Peter.
- Of course.
[Peter] Your references are impeccable.
University of London,
School of Oriental and African Studies.
You went to SOAS?
Mm.
Just for a Russian poetry course.
And your time
at London School of Economics.
That's hardly a bastion
of Russian or bards.
Finding my way through Public Law.
Mm.
The surprises continue.
So…
why apply for a nanny job
if your ambitions lie elsewhere?
I suppose I don't look at this that way.
I've always been good at it, to be honest.
I have an inquiring mind.
I ask questions of myself
and of the world around me every day,
and that's what I love to nurture
in children.
I trust that won't be a problem,
Mr. Quint.
So, what do you think?
Au pair.
Um, that's correct.
That was the primary focus for today.
You called it a nanny job.
Did I?
That was my mistake.
[Henry sighs]
Nonsense, Peter.
We both know you don't make mistakes.
[ominous music playing]
[rumbling sound crescendos jarringly]
[man] You're sure this is him?
Oh, absolutely.
I also saw him yesterday, on the parapet.
Hannah says his name is Peter Quint.
- They know who he is.
- Oh, I remember Quint, all right.
Figured he'd be half a world away,
on a beach somewhere.
Uh, children, why don't you
go upstairs, please?
- But...
- No, no arguments. Up you go.
[Dani whispers] Go on.
Quint drained one of Mr. Wingrave's
bank accounts last year.
Over 200,000 pounds.
Hard to believe he'd come back
to steal the silverware.
Anyone else see him?
Well, no, I-I didn't, but…
I'm sure she's right.
The children?
[Hannah] No, they didn't either.
[policeman] Well, I did a sweep,
and I didn't see anything.
I suppose my lights scared him off.
Whomever he was.
Lock your doors, lock your windows,
and give us a call if you see him again.
Not much else we can do for now,
I'm afraid.
So, um, that's it?
I did a sweep.
I'm not sure
what else you'd like me to do.
Um…
Anything, really.
- Look…
- [rain pattering]
I did a sweep.
- Peter's a bit of a shit…
- [chuckles]
…but he's not dangerous.
He's a thief.
Just don't give him access
to your bank accounts,
and you're probably all right.
[Hannah] I'll call Mr. Wingrave as well.
Uh, see if he can offer any other advice.
He expected rather a lot from the police,
if memory serves me correctly.
And he's probably still in touch
with your superior.
I'll take another drive
around the property…
…on my way out.
Ma'am.
[car door shuts]
[engine turns over]
- Are you really gonna call Henry?
- I am, but he's two hours away.
I'm calling Owen, and Jamie.
Where are you going with that?
I'm gonna do my own sweep.
[light classical music playing]
Mr. Quint.
Lovely to see you again.
The pleasure's mine, Miss Jessel.
[radio tuning]
There's not many stations that come in
along this stretch, I'm afraid.
Off then, if you don't mind.
[radio clicks off]
So…
were you for or against me?
Oh, you think that matters?
[Rebecca] Well…
you said you work with Mr. Wingrave,
but it certainly felt like your interview.
Well, I had to hire you.
I mean, I'm already the gofer,
the chauffeur, and the nursemaid.
If I didn't hire you,
I'd be the nanny, too.
Sir Henry's a bit of a mess, then?
He's a good man.
He's having a bad stretch, that's all.
What have I gotten myself into, exactly?
Well, the children are clever,
- if a bit strange.
- Mm-hm.
Boy is a bit of a dark horse,
and the girl, she talks to the wallpaper.
I mean, more…
how are they coping?
I mean, after all they've been through.
You know, it's…
[sighs]
I mean, their parents didn't come home.
That's all.
They don't comprehend much beyond that.
[gentle piano music plays]
Why, hello there.
What a gorgeous flower you are.
What's your name?
I'm Flora.
That means flower. Latin.
[Rebecca chuckles]
Of course it does.
- And you must be Miles.
- Hi there.
Let me guess,
you ought to be our very own Mary Poppins.
[Rebecca chuckles]
Well, I'm not practically perfect,
but I am…
perfectly splendid.
- Hannah Grose.
- Rebecca.
- It's lovely to meet you.
- Lovely to meet you too.
Ah, this is Owen.
- Lovely to meet you, Owen.
- And our...
- Jamie.
- Hello.
You shouldn't be smoking.
Ay, you're right.
Do you like that?
Just flip…
…and click.
- There.
- [Flora] I'll show you everything.
- You must see the statue garden.
- [Rebecca chuckling]
- Let Miss Jessel settle in before you...
- [Rebecca] It's all right.
[Hannah] All right.
The statue garden is my favorite.
There are flowers, of course.
And much more.
And they're all…
perfectly splendid.
[storyteller] Miss Jessel found herself,
as she walked the grounds of Bly
for the first time,
wishing that she might never leave.
And it turned out…
- …she never would.
- [owl hoots]
[nocturnal chirping]
- [screams] Jesus!
- Jesus!
[pants]
Shot plenty of rats with it.
More than happy to add
Peter fucking Quint to the tally.
- Not a fan, I take it.
- You don't know the half.
I'm learning.
You got the right idea.
I think it's a teachable moment for him.
You looked down there yet?
[door creaks open]
[Jamie sighs]
[Jamie]
Hannah must have left 'em burning.
She's always lighting and forgetting 'em.
The place will burn down
one of these days.
[Jamie sighs]
Let's go.
No sign of Parapet Pete.
Do you want hot chocolate?
My skin's crawling
thinking he might be out there.
How about we stay here tonight?
Just in case.
- Yes! A sleepover.
- [Miles] That would be fun.
- [Flora] That would be splendid.
- A sleepover. That would be fun.
What about your mum?
It's just for one night.
She's already fast asleep.
It's better I'm here.
- Just in case you-know-who shows up.
- That would be great.
You haven't touched your hot chocolate,
Mrs. Grose.
Can I have it?
- Uh, no, you'll be up all night.
- [Flora] Yes!
- Let's stay up all night!
- [Dani] Flora.
[Flora] This is all so exciting!
We're going to stay up all night long,
and it's going to be perfectly...
[fire crackling]
What on earth would possess him
to show his face around here again?
It can't be for more money, surely.
He can't have got through
what he stole already.
Oh, no, thanks, love.
One of us needs to be sober enough
to take him on.
You want the poker or the shotgun?
Mm. Candlestick in the library.
[Owen sighs]
Here you go.
[Owen] What if he's the one
who's been ringing here…
then hanging up? Hm?
I thought those were prank calls.
Well, maybe not.
Who would he be trying to call?
Maybe Becca.
- Why would he call a dead woman?
- He might not know she's dead. [sighs]
She certainly wasn't big news
outside the county.
He might not know a thing.
Or maybe he spent all the money, or…
had second thoughts.
Or maybe he misses her.
So…
he calls the house now and then,
hoping she'll pick up, which…
…she never does.
So…
he comes on back…
to find out why.
Well, that doesn't bode well for anyone.
I wouldn't fancy being there
when Peter Quint
finds out Rebecca Jessel is dead.
- [Rebecca] So, are these two friends?
- [Flora] Yeah.
- They're friends.
- [Rebecca chuckles]
- Best friends.
- Mm-hm.
Dolls are ridiculous.
Dolls are wonderful.
You get to make up all kinds of people
and tell stories with them.
Hello, my name is Flora.
But they're not made up.
I'll make one of you, Miss Jessel.
What's your favorite color?
Hmm.
I don't have a favorite.
I like all the colors.
Then I'll make you one
with all the colors.
Thank you. [laughs]
[knocking on door]
Come in!
Am I interrupting?
Ah, I'm here on an errand
for Sir Henry, and…
…well, I found these,
and I thought flowers this beautiful
deserve a beautiful woman.
So, these are for you, Flora.
[gasps] Thank you so much.
They're perfectly splendid.
No one's ever given me flowers before.
And I thought they were for Miss Jessel.
And now you're so dreadfully jealous.
Well, we can share, can't we, Flora?
Of course.
Have a flower, please.
Aww.
Well, thank you, Flora.
Let's go and put these
in some water, okay?
Be right back.
You didn't rip up Jamie's garden, did you?
She'll be cross if you did.
Ah, that one was born cross.
I don't know why Flora gets so silly
about a few stupid flowers.
Do you know what life
is really all about, Miles?
- Not flowers.
- No.
Keys.
See…
people are like locked rooms.
They've all got different locks,
and you've got to guess the shape
of their key.
Like how there are…
keys to all the doors in this pointlessly,
excessively large house.
Different keys for different doors.
So, if you want someone to open a door,
you have to try out different keys
until you find the one that works.
Like…
for people like your uncle…
His key is money.
Or flattery.
For horses, it's carrots.
And for women, most of them…
[sighs] …it's flowers.
Then why did you give the flowers
to Flora?
I didn't.
[thunder rumbling]
[wind whistling]
- Still at it?
- [Peter chuckles]
- I'm just about done.
- Mm-hm.
Not looking forward to going out in that.
Uh, then don't.
Have some tea while it blows over.
Okay.
[thunder rumbling]
So, how are you finding it?
It's a fine job, really.
Uh, yes.
The kids are very sweet,
even if I'm mopping up
their muddy footprints sometimes.
Twice now they've snuck out
in the middle of the night.
No, I mean, how are you finding all this?
I mean, living in a mansion,
the statue gardens,
ordering servants about,
this ridiculousness.
I mean, I'm…
hardly lady of the manor.
Uh, I spent the morning
cleaning vomit off the boy's jumper.
[giggles]
I'm sorry, that's not funny.
One like you, as smart as you are.
Well, it's offensive even.
It's fine.
Um, Miles is a sweetheart.
Surely, that's not what you wanted.
I mean, I can't imagine
a young Rebecca Jessel
looking out her window,
dreaming up at the sky that someday,
someday, she'd be scrubbing up
some rich kid's puke
while his guardian drinks himself
into a coma.
You're too good for that.
Too good.
And too smart.
I don't care if Henry can't see it, I can.
I saw it the day you walked in.
I said to him,
"One day, I might be working for her."
[thunder rumbling]
Tell me what you want.
I mean, everybody wants something in life,
and somehow our betters
have convinced us that's a bad thing.
So, what do you want, Rebecca?
I want to be a barrister.
Now you're talking.
Not a solicitor.
A proper barrister, like Mr. Wingrave.
But, first, I need a pupilage.
Three other women from my year
managed to get one,
and all left within the first year.
A sea of old men
trying to run a hand up your skirt
every day for six months
while you try to persuade them
that your brain isn't between your legs.
So, you took a different route?
I mean, your references,
they're impeccable.
Astor's, Bryce's, Gray's of Norfolk.
People like that get to know you,
see the brain power and ingenuity
just taking care of their heirs.
But now…
…now you have their wife or child
fetching for you.
And you remain focused,
you keep on impressing…
…you leap right over
all those grabbing hands
and find someone of worth to mentor you.
[thunder rumbling]
Henry is a QC
and a master in trade legislation,
but you knew that
when you applied, didn't you?
I see you, Rebecca.
I see you.
- [thunder rumbling]
- [Rebecca sighs]
So…
…why are you here?
Why am I here, uh…
on this Earth?
Why am I here in this job
working for Henry, or, uh…
why am I here with you
when I was meant
to be back in London an hour ago?
Let's take them one at a time.
Why am I here on this Earth?
Uh, to make sure I leave behind
more than I took.
Why am I here in this job
working for Henry?
Because you may not know it
to look at me, but…
there is a ceiling that I, too,
cannot break through.
Growing up where I did,
I'm quite simply not part
of the fucking club.
So…
…why am I here?
I don't know.
But I feel…
…hopeful.
And that doesn't happen often, not to me.
I should go. I'm sorry. Uh…
- Are you sure? It... it's still...
- No, it-it's fine.
The worst has passed.
But thank you, uh, for the drink,
and the company.
You're welcome.
Thank you…
for the conversation.
It's been a long time
since I've had a real one.
Good night, Rebecca Jessel.
Good night, Peter Quint.
[sighs]
[eerie music playing]
[jarring crescendo]
[gentle music plays]
Hey, you all right?
Hm?
Oh, God, I'm so sorry.
[sighs]
If truth be told,
I haven't slept well for days.
Well, Mrs. Grose, it is too late now.
Come on.
Tuck in and relax for a bit.
[sighs]
[chuckles]
Rather that was you curled up there?
[Owen clears throat]
Every girl in the village is mad for him.
He doesn't even know it,
which makes it even worse.
[chuckles softly]
[Dani] They look like Bonnie and Clyde.
[Jamie] Yeah…
if Clyde fucked Bonnie over.
He got away.
She paid the price.
So, what? He's stalking a dead woman?
Risking prison for someone
he didn't even bother to bring along?
That doesn't make sense.
The wrong kind of love can fuck you up.
Follow you.
Make you do some really stupid shit.
[sighs heavily]
And those two…
…believe me,
that was the wrong kind of love.
[Dani] We've all been in the wrong kind
of love for one reason or...
Mm-hm. But I saw
how he twisted himself into her.
Burrowed in deep.
I know why so many people
mix up love and possession…
But guess what that means?
He didn't just trap her.
He trapped himself.
And I hope she haunts that fucker forever.
[melancholy music playing]
People do, don't they?
Mix up love and possession.
Yeah, they do.
I don't think that should be possible.
I mean, they're opposites, really.
Love and ownership.
Yeah.
[Hannah] They really ought to be in bed.
Oh, yes.
Yes, yes. [chuckles]
- I'll take them.
- [Hannah] Okay.
Up you go.
Thank you.
You're the coolest.
[Jamie chuckles]
- I had a bad dream.
- Oh.
I hurt you.
- And it made you feel sad.
- Oh, you never make me sad, poppet.
[kisses]
[rain pattering]
[frightening orchestral swell]
[Dani whimpering]
[panicked breathing]
[ominous music intensifying]
[music abruptly stops]
[rain pattering]
[eerie music playing]
[birds chirping]
Do you have any hearts?
[Flora] No.
What a liar you are!
I can see two of them, right there!
Stop peeking at my cards, Miles!
Miss Jessel, he's cheating!
- You're lying, and that's cheating!
- It's not!
[Peter] Stop cheating, Miles.
[Flora giggles] Peter!
What are you doing here?
And, more importantly,
have you brought me any more flowers?
Uh, no. Uh…
I've got some errands
to do for your uncle,
so he sent me here
for at least a few days.
- Days? [giggles]
- That's right.
Mrs. Grose is making up a room for me
as we speak.
Will Uncle Henry come over soon?
I don't know.
What's with the face?
Nothing.
You know, I lost my dad too.
I was a bit older than you.
And he was pretty crap
most of the time, but…
You've seen this, right?
This belonged to my dad.
It's a little piece of him.
One of the only nice bits, really.
Why don't you…
hold on to it for me?
Would you like that?
Just don't burn the house down, please.
[Rebecca chuckles]
Let's play some cards!
[clears throat]
[Flora] You just need to watch out,
because Miles is a filthy cheater.
- [Peter] Is that right?
- [Flora] But otherwise…
- it's perfectly splendid.
- [Peter sighs]
[Miles] Yes, and you're perfectly mental.
[Flora] Stop it, Miles!
[sighs]
[floorboard creaks]
[creaking]
[Peter] Sorry, I shouldn't have. Uh…
I-I couldn't sleep, and, uh…
[Rebecca gasps]
[both moaning softly]
[door locks]
[praying indistinctly]
[Owen] Good morning.
Oh… good morning.
A-Any sign of him?
Oh, uh, no, not a thing.
Did a quick sweep.
- Safe as houses.
- Oh.
But you know what?
I think Mr. McQueeny next door
could look in on Mum today.
I can call him and, uh, stick around here,
just in case.
No, no, really.
[inhales sharply] I'd feel just awful.
Oh, it's only one day.
And I'm sure she can use a day without me.
It might make all the difference, really.
[chuckles]
Well, thank you for coming to our rescue.
Well, you always come to mine.
[Owen clears throat]
[footsteps receding]
Good morning, it's time to wake…
Oh, you're already up.
How are you feeling?
Capital. Wonderful, in fact.
Can we have a picnic, do you think?
It's a marvelous day for it.
Once we find Flora,
let's make a day of it.
What do you mean, find Flora?
Isn't she in her room?
[music box playing "O Willow Waly"]
Flora?
- [music box continues playing]
- [flies buzzing]
I'm all finished.
And I wanted to show you something.
- Here you are.
- Thank you.
You said your favorite color
was all the colors,
and Miles says
if you mix all the colors
in the world together,
you get black.
Well, it's beautiful. I love it.
You're beautiful.
Peter was even saying so himself
this morning.
He stayed the night, you know.
Well, it is fun to have him here.
[frightening music playing]
[Dani] Flora.
- Flora.
- No!
- Flora!
- [screaming] No!
No!
No! No!
- No!
- [screams fading]
[music intensifying jarringly]
[man] No sign of fever.
Tell you what, sweetheart.
You're gonna spend
the rest of the day in bed.
[Dani] She was inconsolable.
I'm afraid this isn't unprecedented.
Well… not surprising
given what they've been through.
[Hannah] Well, yes.
Well, when you talk to Henry,
you can tell him I said they're all right.
Are they all right?
Well, there's nothing
physically wrong with them,
and that's all I can speak to, I'm afraid.
I'll see myself out.
- Always nice to see you, Hannah.
- And you.
[footsteps recede]
I can't believe he didn't show up.
I told him I'd called a goddamned doctor.
He said, "Keep me posted."
Tell him you called a coroner,
and then maybe.
No, nothing short of that
would get Henry Wingrave back to Bly.
Said the same thing when I told him
about Quint. "Keep me posted."
I still don't understand, though.
She was by the lake.
But she hates the lake.
Yeah.
Miles, darling. Um…
Why don't you go help Owen
with breakfast, hm?
[Miles] She doesn't hate it there.
Why should anyone hate a lake?
She talks about it all the time.
Sure.
But Flora lies.
[Hannah sighs]
[Rebecca moans gently]
[kiss]
- Good morning.
- Mm.
Yes, it is.
[Rebecca moans]
[chuckles softly]
Oh, my gosh, I need to get up.
- No, in a minute.
- No, no, stop. Seriously.
I'm serious, Pete.
- Come back.
- [chuckling]
Look, just hold that thought, okay?
I have to go.
- [sighs]
- But they can wait.
Please.
You're here another night, right?
Right?
At least.
I'll tell Henry the house will blow up
if I don't stay the week.
[chuckles softly]
Then hold that thought.
Just till tonight.
[exhales]
Come back to bed.
Please.
[chuckles softly]
Patience.
[footstep recede]
Owen, apparently, you're cooking
for seven again tonight.
- Oh, he... he's staying tonight as well?
- Mm. Apparently.
Although I'm not sure for how long.
[Peter whistling "O Willow Waly"]
What is that?
That is a very specific Bordeaux,
and it would knock
your knickers off, Hannah.
Do you want a glass?
Have you been in the wine cellar?
Yeah, it's fine.
Henry's blessed it.
I'll save you a glass if you'd like.
It is a lovely year.
[giggling] I can't. I have to get back!
I know, I know.
Just a few minutes, please. Please.
They've been at it again.
- Why do they keep tracking mud in here?
- Well, make them clean it up.
Well... They shouldn't be in here at all.
We shouldn't be in here...
It's fine.
We've got permission from the top.
- The children...
- They're set.
I've seen to it, okay?
Okay.
[sighs]
Do you trust me?
Yes, I trust you.
- What?
- Wait.
- What are you doing?
- It's a surprise.
Oh, my gosh.
- Okay, a few more steps.
- Mm-hm.
- I don't have long.
- I know, I know, I know.
- [Rebecca sighs]
- Okay.
Open your eyes.
Whose is that?
It's yours.
I don't understand.
It's one of my projects,
inventory for this wing.
There's a few things
going to auction, but…
Henry said this was yours,
if you want it.
- He didn't.
- He did.
I mean, took a lot of convincing.
But…
I'm persuasive when I need to be.
- this belonged to...
- She never wore it.
He was adamant about that.
She never wore it, so…
don't feel bad.
Try it on.
Go on, try it on!
[chuckles]
[music box playing "O Willow Waly"]
No. No, no, no.
See, fur like that…
…you have to feel it on your skin.
At least once in your life.
There's nothing like it.
[song continues playing hauntingly]
[sinister music plays quietly]
[sighs]
[Rebecca moans]
Let me show you…
just how beautiful you are.
[chuckles softly]
- [giggling]
- [camera shutter clicks]
- Let me see, then.
- No.
Not till the end.
[moans softly]
- [Hannah] Excuse me.
- [gasps]
[both breathing heavily]
The children, Rebecca, are on the lawn.
- By themselves.
- [Rebecca] Yes, of course.
- I'm so sorry.
- [Peter] They're fine. They're fine.
The blouse, perhaps.
Oh, gosh.
I'm so sorry.
- This wing is off limits.
- [Peter scoffs]
Careful, Hannah.
- You know that I can have...
- What? Have me fired?
[scoffs]
Oh, yes, I know that very well, Peter.
You've got his ear.
You could have the lot of us out of here
if you truly wanted. Do you know what?
Right now, I do not care.
You see, if I ever…
ever find you in here again,
in Charlotte's things, ever again,
so help me God,
I will drag you out of this house
by your bloody ear
and throw you into that dirty lake.
Do you understand me?
[music box continues playing softly]
Good.
Now, clean this up.
It's almost supper.
[Owen] Oh, my God, this is divine!
This is going to be an absurd cake.
It needs something. Strawberry or lemon?
- Me first because I'm older.
- I want to try the batter!
I mean, I've made some good cakes
in my day,
but this one is batter.
[chuckles softly]
Oh, a lot of long faces tonight.
We might need a bigger cake.
- Let me try!
- All right, there you go.
Go on.
Mmm.
- Divine.
- Hm.
- But you should add more strawberry.
- [Miles] My turn.
Hm. More lemon.
It needs more lemon.
You all must try this. It's amazing!
You'll agree.
- It needs more strawberry.
- [Miles] Lemon.
- [Jamie] All right, let me try.
- [Owen] Oh, no, not Jamie.
There needs to be enough left
for an actual cake.
[Jamie] Move over.
[clears throat]
- Strawberry.
- Ooh.
Ha!
[Owen] All right, love.
A taste, then a smile.
- Oh, no…
- Oh, come on, come on.
Please, I'll be offended.
There you go.
[gasps] Ooh!
[children laughing]
- Oh.
- Now I've done it.
Oh, don't.
- You're…
- No, no, no.
…a battered woman.
- [Hannah] For God's sakes.
- [children giggling]
Mm.
It's divine. Perfect just the way it is.
[Owen] Well, that's useless! Hm.
Come on, Rebecca.
- [Rebecca scoffs]
- [Owen] Chin up. Mm-mm.
[Hannah] Thank you.
[Rebecca smacks lips]
Mmm. Delicious.
I say…
lemon.
Oh, we have a proper batter royale.
Come on, Pete, you're the tiebreaker.
Oh, no, the pressure.
[Owen] Hm.
[smacks lips]
Oh, God, that's amazing.
I'm going to say…
…strawberry.
[Flora] Ha! In your face, Miles!
[laughing] They're finally asleep.
I swear, Flora's wearing
a cake's worth of batter.
What's going on?
I'm going back to London.
- Oh, I-I… I thought...
- Yeah, well,
we both had a disappointing evening,
haven't we, Rebecca?
Um…
When are you coming back?
I don't know.
Will it be long?
I'm not sure.
But you'll be fine, won't you?
What do you mean?
I mean…
if you're gonna flirt with him
right in front of me,
- why would I stay for that?
- [zips up bag abruptly]
If you're hungry while I'm gone,
see if Owen can find something
to stuff into your mouth,
since you're okay with that, apparently.
Have you gone mad?
- What are you talking...
- I'm talking about that man
who you opened wide for not two hours ago.
Mad!
You wanted people to take you seriously.
You said you took this job
'cause you didn't want old men
looking up your skirt or down your blouse,
but age 'em down and dumb 'em up,
and you just open up
when you're told, is that it?
Do you have any idea what you look like?
He... he just…
- He... he asked me to taste his batter.
- God, fuck!
[groans]
You're naive when you want to be.
That's good to know.
It's good to know that when a man asks you
to put something in your mouth,
he doesn't have to ask twice.
He... he… He didn't. You misunderstand.
You'll be fine.
[door slams]
[indistinct conversations in distance]
- [Hannah] I'll let you know.
- [Owen] Hannah, don't insult me.
- [Hannah] It was only in my mouth.
- [Owen chuckles]
[phone ringing]
Hello?
Peter?
[line hangs up]
Attention, please!
[Dani] Flora!
[Miles] Welcome to story time.
How are you feeling?
Oh, my God, you've gone into the makeup.
It's story time.
- Oh, God, story time.
- Oh, good, story time.
[Miles] Come along.
Like it never happened.
They bounce back fast, these two.
They've had to.
That's right, it's your first story time.
- Yeah.
- They do this a lot.
- Oh! Uh…
- [Hannah] Yeah.
- Let's get this over with.
- …exciting.
[Owen]
Uh… Story time is a Flora special.
- [Dani] Mm-hm.
- It's like therapy for them.
Means she's processed
whatever she's been chewing on.
- Right.
- [Flora] Attention.
Welcome to story time.
Go, Flora!
That's not my name.
That's not her name.
[Flora] My name is Tales.
And what are you, Tales?
I'm a cat, of course.
A cat named Tales.
I've seen it all.
As a kitten, I fell off an apple cart
and had nowhere to live.
I wandered and mewed,
and always followed the smell of apples
because maybe that meant I'd find my mum.
My mum was an apple cat.
[Miles] And what did you do?
I found a giant jumper in the forest
and pulled on the yarn.
And pulled it all out.
It took oh so long.
Yarn of a tale.
[adults chuckling]
A tale of a yarn.
But once it was done,
it was so nice and warm.
I wrapped myself tight.
It was warm, it was right.
In fact, don't react,
like my strange little friend did.
Because, once it was done,
it was purr-fectly splendid.
Yay!
And what is your name?
I'm Poppet…
the puppet.
And what are you, puppet?
A puppet named Poppet.
My maker was Claude.
He made puppets aplenty.
He loved them so much… [chuckles]
…even though he had 20.
One was too silly,
and one was too stupid.
One laughed too much,
and the other…
…too little.
Claude went away…
on a journey one day,
and left the puppets at home.
And as time went on…
…soon…
- they forgot they had strings.
- [ominous music building quietly]
And later…
they forgot they were even puppets at all.
And then…
[ominous music intensifying]
…Claude came back…
…so excited.
But they had forgotten him, you see.
And their strings.
They laughed when he said he'd made them.
They laughed at him.
And he was…
so sad.
But they kept laughing.
[yells] These stupid puppets!
These stupid puppets
who had forgotten!
So, he pulled on their strings.
And it hurt.
[phone ringing]
Thank Christ, Peter Quint to the rescue.
[clears throat]
[phone ringing]
Sorry, Pete. Bad news, but she's dead.
Oh, God.
Uh…
Yeah, no. Yeah, he is. Just…
Just one… one moment.
I-It's your neighbor,
Mr. McQueeny.
Look, I am so sorry, Owen.
I'm so sorry.
[whispering indistinctly]
[Owen sniffles]
[engine turns over]
I'm going to light a candle.
[footsteps receding]
[Dani clears throat]
I'm so glad…
you stayed.
I am too.
[melancholy orchestral music playing]
Who the hell knew?
[door closes]
[engine turns over]
[echoing breaths]
[frightening orchestral swell]
[distorted sob]
- [abrupt scraping sound]
- [Dani screams]
[scream echoes and fades]
[closing music playing]