[theme music playing]
[music fades to silence]
[water sloshes]
[storyteller] The housekeeper
was no stranger to muddy footprints.
A few times a year, it seemed,
she started her days with a mop.
Always the same path.
From the door to the forbidden wing,
and back again.
The door got stuck.
It was stuck,
and we couldn't get it open.
Honest.
And the mess in the hall?
It's just a bit of mud.
[Dani] Hm.
Well, I forgive you.
But I'm afraid I…
I don't believe you.
That's the issue.
[Flora grunts]
[Dani] Miles!
[Hannah exclaims]
Miles, I just mopped that bit!
[Miles breathing heavily]
[chute bangs shut]
[Dani] Can I have that, please?
- What are you...
- [Dani] Not me.
You.
That was entirely unacceptable,
and now you are going to finish mopping.
- But that's not fair!
- [Dani] Hey.
It's just a bit of mud.
[Miles sighs]
Now, you'll finish mopping
while Flora and I go get her doll back.
A-Assuming…
[inhales deeply]
…that's all right with you, Mrs. Grose?
Oh, n-no, it's... fine by me.
In fact,
we've had this conversation before,
haven't we, Miles? Hm?
Every few weeks, it feels like these two
are off on a midnight run,
and muggins here
is left to mop up their mud.
[sighs]
[cheerful whistling]
[Owen] Good morning.
[Dani] Excuse us, Owen.
- Hi, Owen.
- Flora.
Come on.
I don't like the cellar.
It's perfectly dreadful down there.
Can I stay and have a glass
of orange juice with Owen, please?
- [Dani chuckles]
- [Flora] I'm sorry, I'm not being cheeky.
It's just… I quite hate the cellar.
It's perfectly dreadful.
[Dani chuckles] Is that all right?
I'll just be a sec.
Somebody's brother threw their doll
down the laundry chute.
Oh… of course.
Thank you.
[Owen] Hmm.
[switch clicks]
[clicking]
Brothers can be
perfectly dreadful sometimes, can't they?
He isn't, though.
He really isn't.
You have a fine heart, miss.
[light fitting creaking]
[footsteps ascend quickly]
[door creaks]
[door slams shut]
[Dani] Look who I found.
What's her name?
She can't remember.
Are you gonna hang it in your room?
For protection?
No, I took it down.
- [Dani] Why?
- [Flora] Because it doesn't work.
[Dani] Miles?
Miles?
You can go get dressed.
[creaking sound]
Miles?
[echoing] Miles, are you okay?
[school bell ringing]
[door opens]
[students chattering]
[man] All right, boys.
Let's settle down.
Let's find our seats, shall we?
[student] Hello.
Welcome.
Good morning, gentlemen.
[students] Good morning, Father Stack.
[sighs] I trust you all had
a very festive Christmas.
- [students] Yes.
- [Father Stack] Excellent.
I think we have a majority.
Well, then…
spring term.
Congratulations. Seems like you've made it
through the winter,
though not without a few casualties.
I'm afraid Brian Duncan
won't be joining us for a bit.
- Yes?
- Is he ill?
No, Mr. Hooper. Nothing quite so serious.
He took a bit of a tumble.
He is on the mend
and will be back with us shortly.
So…
shall we begin?
Bibles.
"Now, there on the hillside,
a great herd of swine was feeding."
"And the unclean spirits begged him,
'Send us into the swine.'
'Let us enter them.'"
"So, he gave them permission."
"And the unclean spirits came out
and entered the swine."
"And the herd rushed down the deep slope
into the lake and were drowned there."
So…
…there we have it.
Three Gospels,
three slightly different accounts
of the same event.
Three different places
that it could have happened.
But the broad strokes remain the same.
Jesus cast the demons,
known as "Legion" in Luke and Mark,
unnamed in Matthew,
out of a single man,
according to Luke and Mark,
two men according to Matthew, into…
and on this they all agree,
- a herd of pigs.
- [boy 1] That then go jump in the lake.
That then go jump in the lake, exactly.
[boy 2] Um, but why was Matthew
being so contrarian?
- [boy 3] What's contrarian?
- It means he was being a tit.
- [students giggling]
- Hey, language, Obermann. Final warning.
Miller, excellent question.
Why do the Gospel accounts differ?
Well…
because man is fallible.
Even the men who wrote these Gospels.
Even me, which I'll have to remind
some of your parents, no doubt,
once they get wind of this conversation.
They needed permission?
The demons?
- Permission to…
- [Miles] To enter the pigs.
Ah! Yes, they did.
Did they need it for him, though?
Did they need it for the man?
Ah… Excellent question, Wingrave.
And that, actually,
is the… the big takeaway here,
so thank you for asking that.
We are, all of us,
free to make our own choices.
It's one of the most important gifts
that God has given us.
A gift that not even the demons
in this story could usurp.
See, evil exists,
and we are tempted.
But we are not compelled.
So, yes.
They did need his permission.
[school bell rings]
As they need ours!
All right, gentlemen.
Wingrave.
Uh, quick word.
The headmaster passed this onto me
this morning.
It's not often that a... a student
gets any post on the first day.
And judging by the writing
on the envelope,
- I assume it's from...
- My sister.
Very thoughtful of her
to have it waiting for you.
Something to make you feel
a bit more at home, no doubt.
You asked some excellent questions today,
by the way.
Thank you, sir.
You are most welcome.
And, Wingrave…
I want you to know that this room
is a... a safe place for questions.
Not just about your studies.
About anything you like.
I am here,
as are the other members of the staff,
so if you feel the need to talk,
we'll listen.
You're in none of this alone,
is what I'm driving at.
Thank you, sir.
Well, I won't keep you.
Oh…
John 16:22.
It's brief, I promise, but it's helped me
on more than one occasion.
John 16:22.
[Miles] Hm.
"So also you now indeed have sorrow,
but I will see you again,
and your heart shall rejoice,
and your joy, no man shall take from you."
- [book shuts]
- [sighs]
[bell tolling]
[grunting]
Wingrave!
[grunting continues]
It's nearly time!
Shall we go down?
[grunts]
[Hooper] Wingrave!
Wingrave!
[bell continues tolling]
[storyteller]
The trouble began as trouble often does.
With an accident.
Or so it would be called.
- [bell ringing]
- [students chattering]
[ominous music playing]
[Miles grunts]
Wingrave!
[Hooper] Miles!
[disquieting swells of white noise]
Wingrave!
[music intensifying]
You can have the bottom bunk.
Thanks.
[theme music plays softly]
[sighs]
- I'm glad you're all right.
- Yeah.
Why'd you do it?
Do what?
Why'd you jump?
Just looking for the right key.
What was that?
I didn't jump.
I fell.
- [Hooper] I saw you jump.
- I fell.
[sighs] Yeah, well…
…if you ever need anything,
I'm here for you, mate, okay?
Good night, Miles.
- [footsteps running]
- [students yelling]
Father Stack!
What is it, Mr. Banks?
[students shouting]
[chanting] Fight, fight, fight, fight!
[Miles and Hooper grunting]
[chanting continues]
[Father Stack] Hey, break it up!
Break it up!
Wingrave!
Hooper!
[weakly] Here.
- Are you okay? Can you breathe?
- Yes.
Okay, let me get you up.
Thank God.
- [Hooper coughs]
- Loosen your tie. There you go.
Okay, everybody back to class, now.
Go on, all of you.
- [bird coos]
- [Father Stack] So, you started it?
Had he wronged you in some way?
Said something to you?
Something to set you off?
Look, Miles…
I wanna help you,
but I need you to help me,
to understand this.
And not only me, Hooper's parents.
They could push for a suspension.
And the headmaster
will want to mollify them. But…
…I put myself ahead of that.
The headmaster and I have already spoken…
…and I have made it clear
that your well-being is my responsibility,
and priority…
moving forward.
But, Wingrave…
…this isn't the way.
Look, I understand
what you're going through.
Or, you know what? Maybe I don't.
Maybe I don't, so…
So, tell me.
Be my teacher.
Hm?
We all do terrible things sometimes.
That's expected.
It's... it's baked into us from the start.
But it's that feeling of remorse,
that guilt, that terrible guilt,
burning inside your chest, that's…
that's what distinguishes us
in God's eyes.
None of us are blameless.
Except the soul that's not yet conceived
and the animals.
Like Pidge over there.
They're the only innocents.
Then it wasn't fair, was it?
What wasn't?
What Jesus did to the pigs.
In the demon story.
Maybe not.
The Lord works in mysterious ways.
A cliché, I know, but…
…true.
And death is something to mourn,
not fear.
And you've had to deal with death…
…far, far more
than a child your age should.
Far more.
[sighs]
They're in a better place, Miles.
I don't know everything, but…
I do know that much.
They're in a better place.
They're not coming back.
I'm afraid not.
That's not fair either.
No, it isn't.
Why do the bad ones get to come back,
and not them?
[bell tolling in distance]
- [door opens]
- [chilling strings play suddenly]
[floorboard creaks]
[unsettling music plays]
[ominous music playing]
[music intensifying]
[man, sternly] Master Wingrave…
is there anything you'd like to say?
Anything at all?
I have a mind to expel you, young man.
I truly have.
But Father Stack…
Well, Father, I'll let you say it.
[Father Stack sighs]
Wingrave…
Miles.
What you've done,
it… it can't be minimized, it…
can't be avoided by not talking about it
or by you being sent home.
It follows you.
Do you understand? It…
It stays.
But remorse,
or demonstrating remorse,
won't make all of this go away,
I'm not gonna lie to you,
but it is the first step
towards some kind of absolution.
Hm… Towards grace.
Look, I-I know
that you have been through a lot.
Do not feel sorry for me.
Your parents… and your au pair.
- More than we could hope to understand.
- Don't.
And the weight of all that
could cause one, anyone,
to do terrible things,
even if they didn't mean to.
It could press one,
- drive one to commit acts that...
- We are not compelled.
What our chaplain is saying
is that we're going to start
with an apology and go from there.
He is correct
about your special circumstances…
…but I at least have to insist
on the apology.
For God's sake,
we at least have to have that.
[raises voice] Speak!
That animal is dead
because of you, Wingrave.
Dead doesn't mean gone.
[headmaster] What did you say?
I'm sorry.
I know you are, Miles.
I know that, and I also know that…
- together, you and I...
- I'm sorry I didn't do worse.
Cut off its head, spread out the insides,
or burn it.
I'm sorry I didn't do worse.
- [headmaster] Ahem.
- [Father Stack sighs]
[headmaster] Right, then.
Get Master Wingrave's uncle
on the telephone, please.
[Miles] I'm sorry, Father.
I…
I needed to find your key.
That's all.
[storyteller]
And so the reason for Miles's expulsion
was difficult to pin down.
He was expelled, it turned out,
for an injury,
an accident, a crime,
a fight,
and, finally,
an affront.
Why he'd done any of these things,
no one would understand.
Only the letter from Flora,
delivered when he arrived,
forgotten in the dormitory,
would offer a possible clue
as to why he tried so, so hard
to be sent home.
[whispering] "Come home."
[sighs]
I'm finished.
Okay, I'll be with you in just a sec.
- Are they gonna go back in their house?
- [Flora] Later.
Okay.
Spick and span!
- I imagine you learned that at...
- Boarding school.
Yeah. Professional, I'd say.
[chuckles] Why don't you come
teach your sister how to do it?
She'll think it's just splendid.
- Oh... But...
- Just splendid.
[footsteps receding]
[cup clatters]
What are you up to?
Hannah's got the day off, it seems.
Mm. The new missus put the children to it.
Yeah.
For real?
- [Miles] Mm.
- [Hannah] Mm-hmm.
[Dani chuckles]
Nice.
How are they doing?
Perfectly. [chuckles]
I could get used to this.
[Hannah] Oh, I don't know, I feel lazy.
Like some sort of lazy layabout.
Go on, admit it.
- You're loving having this wee break.
- Oh, I suppose.
I just don't like seeing them punished,
is all.
They're not the first to track mud
through the halls. You should know.
Every time I see you
marching towards the house,
I find my hand drifting towards the mop.
Firstly…
I always wipe my feet, I'll have you know.
And, secondly…
what about when
they locked her in a closet?
Oh, now, you can't blame them for that.
Given what they've lost,
strangeness is expected.
You can't give them a pass forever.
Look, you clean up after them,
Owen feeds them, Rebecca…
Rebecca coddled them.
But this one…
- This one's got them doing hard labor.
- Oh, come on, now.
[Jamie laughing] What?
That shite works.
Well, it worked on me.
Look at me now.
I'm a shining beacon of reform.
[both laugh]
[Jamie] Ah, thank God. You're a star.
- Cheers.
- Hannah?
[Hannah] Hm?
- G and T?
- Oh, no.
No, thank you. Not for me.
Gin is a sad drink.
[Owen groans]
- [Jamie] So, Owen…
- Hm?
Thoughts on the new au pair.
- Gossip.
- What?
It's just Christian concern, Hannah.
All right, fine.
On a scale of zero to American,
how would you rate her?
- [Hannah and Owen] American.
- [all laugh]
[Jamie] There we have it.
Though, maybe a bit too pretty.
Do you think she's pretty, Owen?
Jamie!
- [Jamie laughs]
- Uh…
[Jamie] Look at him!
He's tongue-tied.
- He can't answer.
- [Owen clears throat]
It's just romances don't fare well at Bly,
do they?
- [Jamie] We're just having a laugh.
- [Hannah] I know.
But then that's how it starts.
Don't worry.
I only have eyes for you, Hannah.
- Oh.
- Enjoy your break, ladies.
Oh, I almost forgot.
Um, in the kitchen,
there's a crack in the ceiling.
Would you mind popping in
to have a look?
Where exactly?
Uh, by the stove,
high up towards the ceiling.
You can't miss it.
I'll get round to it.
Great work, you lot! Keep it up!
[footsteps approaching]
[door creaks]
[Dani] Flora, you cleaned!
Well, how sweet of you.
You're welcome.
I put all your things into the wardrobe
and chest of drawers.
[suspenseful music plays]
Are you cross with me?
I-I found these, too.
I didn't break them. I promise.
- They were like this already.
- It's fine.
It's fine.
[gasping softly]
Excuse me a minute.
[panicked breathing]
[gasping, sobbing]
You all right?
Kids.
Run you ragged.
[Dani] Yeah.
[Jamie] Well, people really.
- All of them.
- Mm-hmm.
That's why I prefer plants.
Easy to get along with.
And I find if I don't like one,
one looks at me kind of funny,
I can always just…
you know…
[makes choking sound]
[Dani sniffles]
So, if it's child-rearing advice
you're after, I'd just…
[Dani laughs]
…start there, maybe.
There we are.
It's not so bad, right?
Yeah.
I cry three, maybe four times a day
around here.
Five, if I'm really being honest
with myself.
How else do you think
I keep all these fucking plants watered?
With my endless well of deep,
inconsolable tears.
That's how.
It's what got me the job
in the first place.
Look, you're doing great.
You're doing great.
Thank you.
Anytime.
[Dani sighs]
Right. [clears throat]
Well, back to it, then.
Chin up, Poppins.
[door opens]
[door closes]
[footsteps approaching]
Uh, where are you off to?
Heading back to the garden.
I have a few more weeds to pull.
Trying to earn time off
for good behavior, then?
Have a lovely afternoon, Jamie darling.
"Darling?"
[sighs]
[water running]
[echoing bang]
[cabinet door squeaks]
[water turns off]
[exhales heavily]
[clears throat]
[birds chirping, insects chittering]
No, no, no, no, not too much,
or they'll come to take you away.
Who will?
The food police.
For a salt and buttery.
[Flora giggles]
Oh, my God.
You're such a lovely man, Owen.
Why must you speak?
- [Dani laughs]
- [Miles] Miss Clayton?
Might I have a word?
Yeah, sure thing.
In private.
[phone ringing]
- [Owen] We've got this, right?
- Right.
Wingrave residence.
[Flora in distance] Hello? Hello?
Hello?
So?
I'd like to apologize.
For all of it.
For locking you in the wardrobe closet,
for the mess in the hall.
All of it.
But, most importantly,
for being such a child about it.
Being around Flora,
I sometimes forget myself.
Wow.
That's, um…
I think
Flora just misses Miss Jessel terribly.
So, we play little games
to keep her from feeling sad.
Mm.
Such a draining thing.
Dealing with children.
[Miles whistling]
Little shit.
Hey.
Little fucking shit.
Hey, he's just a kid.
I'm gonna kill him.
- I swear to God...
- No. Hey, they're just a few flowers.
Oh! Sure. Well, that's fine, then.
A little boy cut a few flowers.
- What's the big deal?
- They weren't ready to be cut!
[Jamie sighs]
Look, I just…
I have a way of doing things,
and I don't like people
- messing about in my garden.
- No, you're right.
You're right.
I'll talk to him.
[sighs] 'Course.
[sighs] Look, could we just go back
to the bit
where, uh, you were acting mental
- and I had to talk you down?
- [Dani laughs]
[crickets chirping]
Ten minutes, okay?
I wanna see teeth brushed,
hands washed, and pajamas on!
Good day?
- Great day.
- Aw.
- [Dani] Now…
- Mm.
I've got a little surprise set up
for the kiddos,
if you wanna join.
Oh… Oh, uh…
No, I couldn't.
- Are you all right?
- Yeah, fine.
I just, well…
I haven't been sleeping very well.
I think I'll turn in for the night.
- Okay.
- Good night, darling.
- Good night.
[Dani] All right, you two, line up!
[Dani giggles]
Hmm.
Pajamas seem to be in order.
[chuckles]
Let's see those hands.
Good, good.
Sure. Teeth!
[teeth clack]
Ahh.
[Dani giggles]
You did so well…
that, as a reward,
we can play a game.
Hm?
Any game you like.
We'll be back in our beds
before too long, right?
We can't be out of our rooms too late.
[Dani] We won't.
Hide-and-seek!
Okay, hide-and-seek, sure.
- Is that all right with you, Miles?
- [Flora] Please?
[crickets chirping]
- [Dani] Ten, nine, eight…
- [footsteps running]
…seven, six…
five, four…
three…
two, one.
Ready or not, here I come!
- [clock ticking quietly]
- [door creaks]
[wind whistling softly]
[Dani] You aren't down here, are you?
This wing is off limits, game or not.
Okay?
[thud]
[music box playing "O Willow Waly" softly]
[door creaks open]
[music box tune grows louder]
[Flora humming "O Willow Waly"]
[reedy voice joins Flora
humming "O Willow Waly"]
[music box continues playing]
[Flora and voice continue humming]
[Flora stops humming]
[other voice grows loud and strangled]
Shh!
[voice stops]
[Flora resumes humming]
[music box continues playing]
- Got you!
- Jesus, Miles!
- Got you.
- I'm supposed to be looking for you,
- and this wing is off...
- I'm going to start counting,
and it'll be your turn to run and hide.
I'll find you.
[strained] Ease up!
Ease up!
[Miles, yelling] One! Two! Three!
- Four!
- Miles!
- Five…
- No, game over!
- [Miles in distance] Seven! Eight!
- Miles!
[Miles] Nine!
[Dani] Miles.
[rapid steps]
Flora!
Olly, olly, oxen free!
Hm.
[creaking sound]
[wind whistling]
Hey.
[sighs]
[wind howling eerily]
[door creaking]
Shit. [breathes shakily]
[gasps softly] Oh.
[echoing gasps]
[wind resumes whistling]
[eerie music building]
[frightened gasp]
[panting]
[softly] I'm gonna call
the fucking police. I'm... I'm gonna…
[yells] I'm gonna call the fucking police!
Dani.
I-I don't feel so good.
- [thuds]
- [Dani gasps]
- Oh, God.
- [Dani] I saw him.
I swear to God.
In the window.
Same guy. Same guy as yesterday.
I-I'll lock the doors.
Hey! Hey, hey!
It's okay! You're okay, you're okay!
He's awake!
[sinister clashing sound]
- [Hannah] Oh, thank goodness.
- [Dani] He's awake.
- [Hannah] Thank God.
He's awake.
[frightening music building
to final close]
[closing music playing]