You can come for me if you want to.
But if you take me down,
I'm going to take you down
twice as hard and twice as fast.
You've got to make
a full statement, on the record, today.
- I need a deal.
- That can't happen, Justin.
I'm won't lose me job for anyone.
Not him, not you.
So, I'll call you.
And that makes you think
coming here is a good idea?
No, but this does.
Dd Luther has never,
to my knowledge, broken any laws,
either in pursuit of his duty
or otherwise.
I've been honoured to work with him.
I don't want to play games.
You know, I'm too old for that.
- I'm not a game-player.
- Good.
‘Cause neither am I.
Ohh!
Okay, ready?
Take care. All right, see you later.
- See you later.
- Bye-bye!
I was going to say, er,
- do you want a lift?
- Uh, yeah. That would be lovely, yeah.
Yeah, okay.
Well, I'm just parked round here.
- Okay, cool.
- Cool.
Right.
So...
You took your time.
I was just picking my moment.
For three years?
But, you know, this thing...
me and you, it's not just...
Get down!
- Smash it in!
- We're gonna do you now!
- Start the car.
- It's gonna be all right.
- Come on!
- Get him out!
Leave her alone!
Get off me!
What?
Hey, boys!
Hey, boys, help me deal with this.
Ah, nah, nah, stay there. Stay there.
All right, pass me it.
How can I help you?
What is it, fam?
You're looking for something, yeah?
What? What are you, deaf?
Hey, deal with him, man.
Oh, he's fully loaded! Run! Run!
- Go, go, go!
- Stop!
Put your hoods down!
Hoods down!
Run, run, run! Let's go!
Please, please.
Please just wait, Callum.
Please, Callum.
♪ Love is like a sin, my love
♪ For the ones that feel it the most
♪ Look at her with her eyes like a flame
♪ She will love you
like a fly will never love you
♪ Again ♪
How old were you when you got together?
21, 227?
You've, um, still got love
in your voice.
Well, you don't
stop loving someone, do you?
Is that a problem?
It's, um...
It's the opposite of a problem.
- She was very beautiful.
- She was.
Yeah.
- Duty calls.
- Mmm.
Justin! Come in.
Sorry?
Come in.
Why?
- What do you mean, why?
- Well, you never ask me in. Not ever.
Mmm.
Mary? Oh, sorry.
Uh, this is my mate Justin.
- Hey there.
- Hey.
Justin, this is Mary.
- All right, Mary?
- Hi.
He's my mate. And I love him.
Right. Work!
You gonna be all right?
- Fine.
- Yeah?
- Fine, yeah.
- Make yourself at home.
Will do. Totally.
Well, come on, then, Justin.
Nice to meet you, Mary.
- Briefly.
- Yeah.
All right, boss?
Victims are Steven Meredith
and Shaun Butler.
This is Meredith.
Murdered a young solicitor
six years ago.
It's in the file.
- Eyewitnesses?
- Dozens.
White male, 25 to 40.
Lightish to darkish hair,
short, possibly longish.
Nondescript clothes.
May ride a motorcycle.
Possibly a scooter.
Or a car.
- Where's the other one?
- Over here.
Shooter walks up during the affray,
puts the sawn-off to Butler's chest.
- Doesn't hesitate?
- Apparently not.
It's not an easy thing, that.
To put a sawn-off to someone's chest
and pull the trigger.
Even if you hate 'em.
Let alone make this mess.
- So who's Caitlin?
- Oh, we turned up no Caitlin
in Meredith and Butler's ambit.
No family or known associates.
There's no Caitlin connection
to the solicitor.
That rules out a revenge attack.
And this is way too heavy
for a gang beef.
- So what's up with the website?
- Goes live in two hours.
Well, can't we just pull it down
or trace it to the source
or whatever you do with websites?
Apparently not.
It's being hosted from Uzbekistan.
Or Kazakhstan.
One of the Stans, anyway.
The upshot is, is that there's no way
we can pull it down in time.
Apparently there's hundreds
of these leaflets already in the wild.
People have been tweeting
the address since about 5:00 a.m.
So the chances of containing this,
essentially, are...
three-eighths of sod all.
Hello, Mary.
Maxine, I'm DCI John Luther.
You all right?
This man, the killer.
He spoke to you?
- He did, yeah.
- What did he say?
He, um...
He told me not to be afraid.
Do you remember anything
about his voice?
- Maybe he had an accent?
- Um...
Uh...
It was nice.
In what way?
Kind. He, um...
he had a very kind voice.
He had a kind voice?
And then?
He...
He sat and he held Callum's hand
until the ambulance arrived.
Can you describe him?
- I'm sorry?
- Describe him.
The killer of these men.
Why?
Maxine, they're dead.
Now, I know he seemed kind...
- but that doesn't give him the right...
- What,
give him the right
to save Callum's life?
Stop me from being gang-raped?
The way I see it, two people
were going to die last night.
Thanks to this man,
and no thanks to the police, by the way,
it wasn't me and it wasn't Callum.
And now you're asking me
to help you send him to prison?
I would rather go to prison myself.
So how did you and John meet?
Sorry, I'm just not very comfortable
having this conversation.
How much do you actually know
about John Luther?
Um...
I'm not actually sure what that means.
Look, why don't...
Why don't we just give him a ring?
Put it this way. Try, if you like.
Does he ever talk about her?
Well, he doesn't not talk about her.
Okay, um, I've actually got to go.
Sit down.
I'm late for work.
Did John ever mention how she died?
Um...
I'm not actually sure that
that's any of your business.
She left him.
Shacked up with another man.
And not long after she was killed.
- Did he mention that?
- I'm sorry.
I'm not sure what's
supposed to be going on here, um...
I'm completely lost.
That's why we're here.
To help you understand
how lost you really are.
Oh...
You all right?
Yeah. Got it down to about 14 possibles.
It's just weird
seeing all these terrible things
happening to women with the same name.
Caitlin raped. Caitlin stabbed.
Caitlin drowned. It just seems...
I don't know.
Justin...
I think it's time you move on, mate.
I mean, you should be doing my job,
having little Ripleys of your own.
Been meaning to tell you that for...
You need to get to Hamlyn Woods.
All right, guv.
Couple of dog walkers
found him, apparently.
- Do we know who he is?
- Yeah, Liam Glass.
Why does that name sound familiar?
For a few months he was
the tabloid's favourite bogeyman.
Because?
He lived in the spare room of the flat
where Lucinda King died.
Ah! The little girl.
Yeah, four years old.
Mr Glass was her stepfather's cousin.
Crack cocaine addict,
arsonist, career burglar.
He sat by and took no action
while her mother and stepfather
- starved and beat her to death.
- Yeah, what did he get?
Five years?
Four, with time served.
Four for four.
Our boy's killing predators, isn't he?
People the justice system spat out.
He's on a mission.
We'd better find him.
And find him fast.
It's going live now, boss.
By now, many of you
will be wondering who Caitlin is.
She was my wife.
This is Caitlin.
Four years ago...
she was raped and murdered
by a man called Milan Knizac.
Mr Knizac had been classified
as "medium risk" by probation staff
when he was released from prison
less than halfway through
a nine-year sentence
for robbery with violence.
Caitlin wasn't just taken from me.
She was taken from her friends.
She was taken
from her mother and father.
She was taken from the children
she will never have.
The criminal justice system
was created to protect us
from people who would do us harm.
But time and again,
it fails in that purpose.
For all the Caitlins
and for all their families,
it's time for that failure to end.
Okay.
I think we've got a big problem.
For all their families,
it's time for that failure to end.
Come on in.
Tom Marwood. Architect.
Pretty good one, apparently.
Caitlin dies, he's depressed.
Spends a bit of time in hospital.
Then, all of a sudden, boom.
He's energised.
Joins a gun club,
takes lessons in Krav Maga,
urban survival courses.
It's like he's training
for the zombie apocalypse.
Wow.
So before this all kicked off,
who was he talking to?
Who was his confidant?
Uh, Alan Ramsey. Caitlin's brother.
- This one?
- Yeah.
Ramsey. All right, find him.
We've got to talk to him.
Guv, Marwood's been planning this
for a long time.
He's well prepared, he's off the grid
and we're not gonna find him
where he's at.
We've gotta find him
where he's gonna be next.
And how are we gonna do that?
Well, he's making a play
for public sympathy.
Meaning he'll keep targeting
offenders that people hate the most.
- The worst of the worst.
- So?
So...
say we find the ten
most debased scumbags in London,
put a surveillance team on 'em,
see if we can't get to Marwood
before he gets to them.
Yeah, well, how do we
narrow down the possibles?
I mean, depravity is
hardly in short supply in this city.
We collate nature of offence
against the volume of press coverage.
It can definitely be done, boss.
All right. Let's do it.
Hey. Can we meet?
Yeah. You all right?
Yep. I just... really need to talk.
Okay. Seriously, are you all right?
Some people came round
after you'd gone.
What people?
A man and a woman.
Police.
I can't talk about this
on the phone. I can't.
- I need to see you.
- Mary, all right, listen.
Just tell me where you are right now.
- At work.
- At work?
- All right, good. I'll just come now.
- No, no, don't do that.
Mary?
Hey.
Should we get a cup of coffee
or something?
Yeah. In a minute.
- Um...
- You all right?
Yeah, um...
How did your wife die?
Zoe?
Uh, that's a long...
It's a long story.
She was, um...
taken...
by a friend of mine, someone I knew.
And if I'd asked you that question
this morning...
before that...
Glaswegian dick
had done his dirty business,
would you have given me
the same answer?
- Of course.
- Why?
Because it's the truth.
Hey, listen.
- Whatever they said, they were lying.
- They had a file on you.
- What did you do?
- Nothing. I did nothing.
Whatever they told you,
they were lying.
I... I think you should
stay away from me.
- Mary! Come on.
- Please!
Mary!
They were lying!
Justin. What?
We're down to 263 potentials.
Well, you'd better move faster
than that then, eh?
We'll get there. Where will you be?
Oh, I'll be checking out
the brother-in-law.
Okay.
- Hello.
- George.
John Luther!
How the devil are you?
I'm fair to middling.
Have you got two minutes for me?
I'll put the kettle on.
What?
What are you scared of, Erin?
I'm scared of what
this is turning into.
:::::: www.hiqve.com ::::::
- So0?
- So here's the thing.
You come for me, I'm fine with that.
I'll match you bite for bite
and, in the end,
we'll see who's still standing, right?
But you need to keep away from Mary.
She's off limits.
But what's the point
of knowing your weak spot...
if I don't get a chance to...
poke it a bit?
See, here's the thing, John.
This isn't some pre-match symposium.
There are no rules of play.
- George, if you sow these seeds...
- Then what?
I reap the whirlwind?
Is that right?
You know your problem?
You've spent your life
thinking you're the whirlwind.
Well, you're not.
Because I'm the whirlwind, John.
I'm the whirlwind.
We'll see.
A big police search
is underway in London,
trying to find vigilante suspect
Tom Marwood,
after he posted an online video...
Who is it?
It's Lee from downstairs.
Um, courier dropped
something off for you.
I signed for it.
What is it?
Uh, it's... I don't know,
a book or something?
Please.
Hello?
Alan Ramsey?
- Speaking.
- It's DCI John Luther.
This'll be about Tom, I take it?
Yes, it is. Do you have
a couple of minutes to spare for me?
Sure.
I'll see you there.
Alan Ramsey?
Alan? DCI John Luther.
Don't move!
All right.
Stop, stop, stop!
Stop!
Do me a favour.
And throw me
your phone and wallet, please.
One out of five murders
are committed by men on bail.
- You know that?
- Every copper knows that.
Then why does nobody
do anything about it?
Because it's complicated.
No, it's not.
You've got me there.
Listen...
Detective Chief Inspector John Luther.
All I want is what you want.
To have these people locked up
so they can't do any more harm
to anyone else.
Now, look me in the eye
and tell me you disagree with that.
Not the motive, maybe.
But I seriously dispute the means.
What, you've never been tempted?
To administer
a bit of personal justice?
I don't have the right to do that.
Nobody does.
Two days.
Give me two days. That's all I need.
- For what?
- To make things better.
- You know I can't do that, Tom.
- Yes, you can.
If you chose to.
Tom...
you know they're going to kill you.
This is how all these things end.
I died the day I came home
and found my wife's corpse
stuffed into the airing cupboard.
Don't make me your enemy, John.
We're on the same side.
I'm sorry you think that.
Tom, listen to me.
Tom!
Um, DCI Luther?
- He's not here, ma'am.
- Oh, okay.
Then, um, I wonder if you
could spare me a minute, DS Ripley?
Thank you.
So what is this,
like a Derren Brown thing?
- Who?
- Mindreader. Mentalist. Reads minds.
Oh, right.
No, you don't
want to read my mind right now.
Full of scorpions.
Right.
He's long gone.
I didn't know he'd be here.
Swear to God.
I didn't call him or anything.
He cloned your SIM.
He's a clever boy, your brother-in-law.
I'm beginning to like him.
- You all right?
- Yeah.
Yeah, I think so.
Justin, I think
I might have taken a wrong turn
- somewhere along the way.
- Surely not.
Well, that wasn't exactly
the disarmingly gallant reaction
I was hoping for
- in my heart of hearts.
- What were you hoping for?
In your heart of hearts?
DS Ripley.
Boss.
Yeah, on my way.
Got to go.
- And fight the good fight?
- Listen, we'll... we'll put it right
- but I really do need to go.
- Sure.
Do you want to talk
about this properly?
That's why I'm here.
No, I mean... properly.
As actual human beings.
- Like a drink or something?
- Oh...
- Okay.
- All right, well, I'll give you a bell.
Okay.
- This got my numbers on it?
- All six of them, yeah.
Who needs more
than six numbers? Marwood?
Had it on his toes. Long gone.
So, I had a visitor. Erin Gray.
Oh, yeah? She had problems
parking her broomstick?
She wasn't a happy flower.
- This about Stark?
- I think so.
- I get the impression...
- He's not playing with a straight bat?
Yeah. I get that impression, too.
Why, what's happened?
Nothing.
Listen, I've got to go. Cover for me!
You have one saved message.
Wow, you were right
by your phone. So, anyway,
it's me. Hi.
That's Mary.
Mary Day from last night?
So, yeah, anyway, cool.
Speak soon!
I know, I know you said
to leave you alone, don't talk to you
and I will, I'll just...
I just wanted to say one thing.
And then I'm gone.
Say it.
I'm really sorry
that you saw what you saw.
I can only imagine
how it made you feel.
It made me want to throw up
is how it made me feel.
It made me want to...
vomit.
- I didn't do those things.
- So,
why did they say that you did?
Was it for a laugh?
Look, I'm not gonna say
I haven't done stupid things,
I have. I've done stupid things.
Really stupid...
But I was trying to help people.
And I... You know, it just got...
It's kind of like
when your car goes into a skid.
And they tell you, you know...
Turn into the skid and then
you'll find yourself coasting.
Trying to hang on
and hoping that somehow
you'll straighten out before you...
get to the edge. I...
None of what they said was true.
None of it.
So you need to tell me what is.
I don't know if that's a good idea.
Oh, well, how am I supposed to
trust you if you don't trust me?
I need to know, John.
Okay.
All of it?
All of it.
Every last drop.
I've got to take this. I'm sorry.
I've got to take...
Yeah.
- Boss?
- Good news.
The proactive strategy
seems to be working, in principle.
In principle? Wow.
A sex offender, Terence Corran,
was abducted from his flat
a little more than two hours ago.
He's on the list
- but we were too late.
- Oh, I had him, I had him!
I had my hands on him.
I just let him go.
Well, he had a gun to your head
so I think it's more a case
of him letting you go.
All right, look, just have Benny
send me the, um...
address.
All right.
- I'm having a horrible day.
- It's okay.
But, um...
I'm gonna be back late tonight.
But later than usual, I mean.
I will be back.
You know where everything is.
Yeah, I think so.
- I'll be there.
- All right.
You all right?
Corran's a paedophile.
Did 15 years
for false imprisonment and rape.
Bit of a tabloid nightmare.
Went on to self-publish
poems and essays
about inter-generational love.
Sees himself as a champion of freedom.
Ungoverned by religion or law.
Yeah, I've heard that one before.
Lack of conscience
dressed up as philosophy.
- It's not right, is it?
- What's not?
Well, Marwood
walks up to Butler and Meredith...
Blam.
Doesn't do the same with Corran.
Why is that?
You find any keys?
Not that I'm aware of, no. Why?
That's what you do, you know?
You walk in,
big bag of books in one hand,
plop 'em down,
put your keys on the table,
fish out your wallet and your phone.
Yeah, okay.
So who took his keys and why?
- My name is Terence Corran.
- Boss!
I'm a paedophile.
I spent 15 years in prison for
the heinous violation of young children.
I've shown no contrition
because I don't believe sex between
adults and children to be wrong.
Statistics suggest that,
having been released,
I'll go on to commit
many further offences
against many other children.
But still,
the criminal justice system set me free.
So what should be done with me?
No...
- Do you understand social networking?
- No.
Good. Then I'm not alone.
Apparently, people are climbing
over each other
to incite Terence Corran's execution.
Bread and circuses.
Nothing new under the sun.
If Tom Marwood gets his wish, and people
vote to hang the paedophile -
and they will, for who would
suffer a paedophile to live? -
then there's no telling
where this is going to end.
Riots, copycat murders,
lynchings, pogroms.
Gangs of vigilantes kicking to death
people whose faces don't fit.
Where's your head at?
Well, we're not gonna find
Tom Marwood before midnight.
But if you're right,
if he executes Corran
this all gets very ugly very quickly.
But we know
he's monitoring the media.
And you're right. There's nothing more
potent than private pain made public.
Please.
Upstairs has signed off.
Having made it perfectly clear that,
if this goes lopsided,
it's you and me
who will swing from the gibbet.
It won't go lopsided.
Benny?
If this goes lopsided I need you
to find every bit of intel on Corran.
Haunts, associates, anything
that makes your nose twitch, all right?
- Come on.
- Go, Blue Leader.
- Cheers, Ben.
- Cheers, Justin. Look after yourself.
- Excuse me, mate, Kiera Mills?
- Over there.
Kiera?
Kiera Mills?
Do you know what that man did to me?
Terence Corran?
I say "man".
Do you know what he did?
Yes.
I was a little girl. I was 11.
- And he...
- Kiera, I should explain to you
that I have no sympathy
for Terence Corran.
All right? Not one bit.
And I don't get to choose who
should live and who should die.
Even if I hate them myself.
This is the hardest thing
I've ever had to ask someone to do.
What do you want?
I want you to plead
for Terence Corran's life.
- Benny Boy?
- So I've been trawling the list
of Corran's known associates.
Nothing solid.
But about a month back,
a parole officer got a tip-off
that a nonce, a Gordon Murray,
was in breach of his parole,
associating with known sex-offenders.
Corran's not been named but him
and Murray were known to be BFFs.
Right, and where do we find Murray?
All right, Gordon?
We're the filth.
Which is funny, really,
considering who we're talking to.
Shall we try that again?
I'll have a lemonade, please.
What do you want?
7hey say Marwood
could be unpredictable and dangerous.
Everyone wants him dead.
Your mate, Terence Corran.
King Nonce.
He's got less than an hour.
- I think you know where he is.
- How could I?
I think Marwood's been following you.
I think he's taken Terence
back to your... clubhouse,
where you and your dirty little mates
have your social gatherings.
So where is it? Back of someone's pub?
Dirty little shop somewhere?
- Come on.
- No, you've got it wrong, mate.
I'm not your mate.
I'm far from your mate.
The sight of you makes me
want to wash my skin with Domestos.
The terms of my parole
forbid me from using the internet
or mixing with other sex offenders.
- Is that right?
- Boss...
Can you turn that up, please, love?
Thank you very much,
ladies and gentlemen.
I know you're all aware
of how urgent this situation is.
So Kiera will now make
a short statement.
My name is Kiera Mills.
You don't know me,
because I was never named in the press.
But 18 years ago,
when I was a little girl,
Terence Corran stole me
from the back of my mum's car.
She'd just popped to the shops
to get some milk.
Terence Corran kidnapped me
and raped me.
He ruined my life.
This morning, a man
kidnapped Terence Corran
and threatened to kill him
for all the terrible things he has done.
Not just to me
but to other little boys and girls.
So I have come here today...
to send a message to the man
who has Terence Corran in his keeping.
And that message...
That message is kill him!
Right, you tell me where he is
or when they come for you,
I'll let you just hang.
- Don't look at me, mate.
- Come on!
- All right! There's a lock-up.
- A lock-up? Where is it?
We use it for meeting, socialising...
- You disgust me! Come on.
- If I tell you,
you might find some materials.
- Shut up, shut up! Where is it?
- None of it's mine!
- Where is it? Tell me now!
- I want it in writing.
Horsemonger Lane, the railway arches.
You just... All you do
is cross the estate.
Benny. Corran's got a lock-up.
Railway arches, Horsemonger Lane.
Scramble ARV now.
Don't! Don't! Please.
Please, no!
Please just let me go.
Oh, God. Oh, God!
Shh, shh, shh.
CO19 are en route. ETA 13 minutes.
Local units should be there in nine.
Wait, boys, he's tweeting the address!
We're on our way.
We'll be there in two, three minutes.
Watch out!
Move, move, move!
Stop right now!
Thomas Marwood! Enough!
Move!
Come on, move!
Come on!
Let go! Let go!
- Get back, get back!
- Get Marwood!
Get him off!
He's still alive. Grab them!
Tom Marwood! Stop!
Okay, enough.
We're done, Tom. All right?
- What's your name?
- DS Ripley.
- Justin.
- What I need you to do, Justin,
I need you to back away.
I can't do it.
Of course you can.
No, I can't. Sorry.
You've already done enough tonight.
I saw how you waded into that mob.
That was brave.
Nobody could ask any more of you.
So just...
back off.
Let me go.
Let's say I did that,
yeah, and all this carries on.
Someone innocent gets hurt.
- How am I supposed to live with that?
- It won't happen.
It'll happen.
You've made your point, Tom.
People are talking.
You're all over the internet.
All over TV.
- You've done what you needed to do.
- I don't want to do this.
I'm a copper.
We're on the same side.
I don't think you're going to shoot me.
Now, please.
- Just back off.
- I'd love to.
Please!
No.
Justin! Justin!
Wait a minute! Wait...
Hey? No! Don't you...
Don't you... Hey!
Get up!
Justin!
No, get up!
Get up!
Come on, mate, get up! Get up!
police officers being hurt
after a crowd in East London
turned violent.
The police had intervened
in what vigilante Tom Marwood...
It's John.
Leave a message.
I asked you nicely.
Now look. Now look what happened.
This is your fault.
This is on your head.
I warned you
not to make me your enemy.
I warned you!
The public execution of sex offender
Terence Corran.
His whereabouts are currently unknown.
He's thought to be armed
and extremely dangerous.
♪ Satan, your kingdom must come down
♪ I heard the voice of Jesus say
♪ Satan, your kingdom must come down ♪
:::::: www.hiqve.com ::::::