Spill. Have they shagged yet?
Yeah. I think so. No!
And he wants her to leave her husband
and just go away with him.
What, leave everything?
I would shag Gary
if it'd get me out of this place.
Would you?!
No!
Of course not!
But anywhere is better than this place.
When you two
have finished gossiping, Jayne,
need you on the tills.
Detective was looking for you
on the breakfast shift.
For me?
Why?
Hi... Hey. Can I help you?
I'm here for DS Francis?
Over there.
Hi. I'm Alison Brooks.
Apparently, you were asking for me?
Yeah, I was. Alison, yeah.
Thank you for coming up.
I got your name
from the Community Skills Database.
You signed up when you started
working for the canteen.
You read lips, right? Yeah.
Good. OK. All of our usual
lip-readers are busy on other jobs.
One sec.
Hello.
This is Alison.
Alison works in the canteen.
She's a lip-reader.
This is Detective Inspector Marsh.
James.
- James.
- James, hi.
And this is DC Lawford. Ben. Hello.
So, you lip-read?
Did you have lessons, or...?
I just picked it up.
And how much of a conversation
can you read?
Well, it depends.
You know, some people are easy.
It depends on the situation.
OK. Can we just have one moment?
Is that all right? Have a sit-down.
Sir, all our usual terps
are tied up on other jobs.
I-I can do it if you tell me what it is.
OK. That was impressive.
OK... She got that.
Well, we're all watching
a gang who are planning a robbery.
A big robbery.
And we have reason to believe
they're meeting tomorrow,
but they're always careful to meet
in places where we can't bug them.
That's why we need a lip-reader,
so we can understand what's being said.
Exactly.
Well, with lip-reading,
it's not just about seeing words.
It's who's talking
and what you know of them,
cos you kind of need context.
But we've also got to be
very careful about what we tell you,
for your own protection.
Alison
do you need an interpreter
or anything like that?
Well, I don't have one now.
You can't talk about anything
that we've spoken about today.
No, OK.
You need to check me out.
Make sure you all can trust me?
We'll let you know.
DS Francis will be in touch.
Hi!
You're on tonight? What?
Why aren't those in the fridge?
Well, I'll take them now.
Can I get a non-alcoholic beer?
Non-alcoholic beer?
You would like some beer?
Non-alcoholic beer? OK. I'll get you that.
Good. I've negotiated an extra hour,
which means we now have surveillance
until 11:30.
And then the team
is due on a job in Dover,
which gives us a fighting chance
to figure out what Helen Redman
is cooking up this time.
We picked up another text.
The meeting place is a picnic bench
on the south side of the park.
Alison, come through.
Went to three numbers.
One unknown,
one we think is Braden Moore,
and the other, you'll like this -
Joseph Holhurst.
Christ, really? Yeah.
OK, so Helen's getting
the old gang back together.
Well, minus Rob Byron, I guess.
Isn't Danny Heath still inside?
For the ransomware attack
on the insurance firm.
He's got eight months.
OK. So Helen's recruiting.
Alison. Hey. Hey.
Hey. You all right?
Nice to see you. You all right?
Come through.
This gang that we're watching,
they target jewellery stores, workshops.
Not afraid to use violence.
We can't arrest them
until we have enough evidence
to secure a conviction, but that's
like trying to do a jigsaw
without the picture on the box.
And, what, you want me
to find that piece of the jigsaw?
Exactly. You know,
we're doing what we can.
We've got the live feeds, we're...
I need to see you.
OK. Sorry.
We have surveillance teams in the park,
and we're watching the live feeds
whenever we can.
But today, we need you to just sit
and watch the monitors
and tell us what you see. OK?
Alison. Hi.
These are the people
we'll be watching, OK?
We call her Cruella.
We call him Hulk.
And that's Wolf.
What, like a code name? Yeah.
We need you to tell us
if you know any of these people.
No. No?
Here we go. Here we go. Nia?
Have a seat.
OK.
'Someone's approaching
the rendezvous.'
Unknown IC1 male,
grey jeans, brown hoodie.
Who is that? No idea.
'Awaiting orders. Shall I move him on?'
Nia, anything?
Not yet. Nothing.
He looks really nervous.
Like he's waiting for someone.
Hold on. Ben, he might be part of this.
Hulk's here.
New contact with Cruella.
Entering east gate.
'Contact with Wolf, central path.'
Full house.
Nia, do we have an ID
on the IC1 male in the brown hoodie?
Not yet. OK, keep trying.
There's not much to go on.
I'm looking back through the messages.
OK, what about this one?
What about this one?
What can you see there?
Here, anything you can see.
Anything at all.
James, just give her...
Liam. Liam?
That's his name. His name's Liam.
Nia, check for any associates
of the gang called Liam.
If we play the surveillance feeds back,
are you OK to try again?
To get any information
we might have missed.
So, if I play this back...
Right. Anything you can get from this.
Wait. Can you just go back a bit?
Yeah, well, if I...
Well, here. You do it. OK.
She's introducing man in a hoodie
to Wolf.
He said his last name. I missed it before.
So, Hoodie says his name's Liam.
And then I think his second name
is something like
like Barlow or Marlow.
But P and a B and an M,
they all look the same.
OK. What else?
Keep watching. What else?
Hulk said,
"I think he can help us."
Yeah. So, Hoodie is telling Wolf
about himself.
He's not from Canterbury.
He's moved around a lot.
Yeah, it's like it's
some sort of interview.
Liam Barlow, 29.
No previous convictions.
I have an address in Manchester, but...
They found him. Yeah.
OK, I need a full profile on him.
As quick as you can, yeah?
Very good work today.
Very, very good.
You need to fill in this form
if you wanna be paid.
OK. Alison? Alison?
Very important
that you don't look up anything
that you've seen in this office today, OK?
For your own safety.
OK. OK.
'Fantastic, well done, John.
'He knows his sport, this lad, doesn't he?
'So, Christine, over to you...'
Today, the footage is from CCTV,
so it won't be as good quality,
but we need a date and location
for the robbery.
Morning, Sir. How are we doing?
Good. Do you wanna roll the tapes?
Sir.
Anything?
No, it's not really clear.
I can barely see the face. OK.
Well, you use this,
and you take as long as you need.
What's she saying? Here.
What's she saying?
Cruella is saying something
about Belmarsh?
Is someone in prison there?
Yeah. We know. Yeah. What else?
Keep looking.
I think she's saying a date.
Let me go back a bit.
Actually...
Actually two dates, 7th and 17th.
Could it be 7th or 17th? Alternate dates?
7th AND 17th. 7th and...
Maybe the robbery might happen
between those dates.
I mean, it's very hard to see, but...
She says "big, risky".
"Keep an eye on him."
What's he saying here?
This guy, what's he saying there?
"Putting him in a flat..."
Putting him in a flat.
Good. Near the app.
Could it be The Tap?
It's the name of a pub.
Yeah. Yeah, yeah. Yeah, it could be "tap".
- Are they talking about Hoodie?
- Ashleigh.
Shit. Sorry, I'm gonna have to go.
What?
Load of nonsense...
Excuse me. Hello. What is happening?
Our landlord's selling our estate
to this management company.
Sorry, does that mean
our rent's gonna go up?
Someone's got to pay
for her expensive suits.
No, no, no, no.
We've got intel
that the gang are meeting
in a bar not far from here.
We can watch on my tablet.
Saves us going to the station.
How do you know
they're gonna meet at the bar?
Someone got lazy.
We're monitoring their messages.
But that's why we need to be quick,
because they could change
their passwords at any time.
Yeah.
They're having technical problems
with the camera.
Would you be up for going into the bar?
Into the bar?
We'd just be friends having a drink.
We won't get too close to them.
OK. Yeah?
But you're buying. OK.
Wolf, Hulk and Hoodie
are at a table to the left.
On the left?
Yeah. Our team will be in there.
And we can just take their place
as they leave. OK.
I'm just gonna talk to you
like we're friends,
and you can just ignore me,
and you watch them, OK?
OK. You ready? OK.
What do you want?
Can I have an Aperol spritz, please?
Two Aperol spritz, please. Thank you.
Thank you.
OK. We gotta go.
OK, I'm just gonna... chat,
while you get what you can.
Take your time. OK? Yeah.
Wolf is here.
Are you OK?
I need to get closer.
The angle's really bad.
It's too dangerous.
Keep trying from here.
You'll not get everything straight away.
Are you OK?
I can't see anything from here. OK.
Drink up. Why?
What are you...? Wait!
Alison!
Hi. Can I have an Aperol spritz?
On her tab. Thank you.
Can I get some napkins?
Jesus Christ.
'You shouldn't have got so close.
They could've seen you.'
'Do you wanna know what I saw?'
'What did you see?'
This isn't about the jewellery shop.
Yeah, I think they were talking
about something like metric
like a bio-metric...
'Biometrics? Are you sure?'
'I can't think what else it can be.
It's such a clear shape.'
'Biometrics?
'That sounds like
they're going for a vault.
'That is a step up for this gang.'
'Hoodie thinks he can break in.
'I think he's a computer hacker.'
Did you see anything else
about the venue?
No. I think Hoodie needs something.
I don't know what,
but I think Cruella
is gonna get him information.
'You did well. You got loads this time.'
'It's so much easier
when you're in the room with them.'
'These people are dangerous.
'You don't want to get close to them.'
Can I get you something?
No, thanks.
Alison. Hi.
We should, er... It's a live feed today.
See you. See you around.
'They're meeting in the play area.'
What, you got that
from the phone messages?
How do you know about that?
I saw you say something about phones.
Thank you.
We're looking for
a potential high-security facility.
Somewhere that uses biometrics,
which is new territory for this gang.
Did you find out
what they're planning to steal?
Look, just stick to lip-reading.
Leave the detection to us.
Contact with Hulk.
Cruella, south side with Driver.
That's a shit angle, isn't it?
'And we have Wolf.'
Hoodie's joining the party.
OK, we've got them,
we just need to see them.
I can't see anything. She...
Can I get... Can I get closer?
You can't? Nothing at all?
You can't see anything?
I can't lip-read the back of a head.
They won't like anyone closer.
Bad idea.
Just get a little bit closer.
She's got a point.
They're right there
talking about it. Right there.
OK. Ask her to move in.
7-0-6, move closer, with caution.
OK. No.
Er, this isn't gonna work, is it?
Shit. Yeah. This isn't gonna work.
Fuck's sake. Great. OK.
Stand her down. Yeah? Yeah.
7-0-6, stand down. All units, stand down.
They were right there talking about it.
They were right under our noses.
Right there.
I'm really sorry, I...
OK, well... Right, listen. Listen!
I wanna know where they've gone to
after that, OK?
I wanna know where they've gone,
who they've spoken to,
what tasks they were given.
Ben, a list of all high-security facilities
that use this biometric data.
Let's try and pinpoint a venue,
can we, please?
Let's try to make sure today wasn't
a complete fucking waste of time.
Can I just...? What?
Sorry, I need... I
need to go to the toilet.
Alison?!
Ashleigh?
Can we talk? Yeah.
Look, I'm really sorry
that I didn't get anything earlier.
Don't worry.
We were asking too much.
No, and James...
James wasn't angry with you.
This isn't just about stopping
a robbery. There's
Cruella, her husband
is in Belmarsh Prison for ten years,
for manslaughter.
A member of the public died
during their last armed robbery,
and James blames himself
for not stopping it.
That's why we're pushing really hard.
Was it... Was it James' fault?
No. The investigation cleared him,
but a man died.
And, you know, he had a wife.
So... sometimes,
the IOPC's blessing isn't enough.
Well... I could see a lot more
if you just get me closer.
I mean, I got a lot more in the wine bar.
I don't think that's a good idea.
OK. But The Tap is a pub, right?
The Canterbury Tap.
And they've put Liam in a flat nearby,
so maybe he might go in there.
Have you been researching the case?
No...
You really, really need to leave
the investigating to us.
But...
Hello. Cinnamon roll and a pastry.
My coffee?
Enjoy...
Did you use nut milk? No.
No. I'll get you another one.
Night. Alison!
Can we have a chat before you go?
OK.
I'm... really sorry, but Karl thinks
this isn't working out.
But he didn't ask for the nut milk.
And even if he did,
he waited till I turned away.
Look, I'm sorry.
No, I really need this job. I know.
And I don't wanna lose you.
You're gonna find something else. No!
Samira!
Alison... You could've told me yourself.
Hello again.
Hi. Can I have
a half of Cold Zombie, please?
You know your craft beer, then?
I like the names. Cold Zombie.
Dead Pig Ditch. Bobby's Biscuit.
It makes it easier to lip-read
when people order them.
You work in a bar? Yeah, I used to.
But I'm currently looking for a job
at the moment.
We can never hold on to staff.
Wait, so are you looking?
Er... I know you're probably thinking,
"I don't wanna hire a deaf barmaid."...
But I will learn all your menu
before the first shift.
I don't get people's orders wrong.
I've got a day job,
but I could work any evening.
All right, OK. So what you're saying is...?
I'm saying give me a chance
and I'll show you.
I'm gonna try it around there.
Got it, thank you.
Hi.
What can I get for you?
Just a pint of IPA.
Are you, like, a regular here?
No, I just moved in around the corner.
I'd better remember your order, then.
Do you find it hard, with the music?
Sorry.
You're deaf, aren't you?
Or hard of hearing. Is that what you say?
I'm deaf. What did you say?
Does the music make it difficult for you?
Yeah, sometimes.
But I like the beat.
Yeah. This is a good one.
Bad day?
Just work.
Can I tell you a secret?
It's my first day,
and I pretended
I know everything about craft beer,
but I actually don't.
I just got a new job too.
What do you do?
It's too boring to explain.
That'll be 6.99.
What's your name?
I'm Alison.
Liam.
Have a good day. And you.
Hey, don't worry, I'll close up here.
You did good tonight.
Come back tomorrow?
What do you think?
Yeah?
All right, yes.
You going? Closing, aren't you?
Gotta go to work. Night.
Good night.
Fuck! Are you OK?
Alison?! I'm fine. I'm OK.
I'll just get a bruised
arse in the morning.
Have you got a death wish?
I-I'm sorry. I forgot my lights.
Don't get up.
Don't get up! I'll be... I'll be fine.
I'll be fine, I'll be fine.
OK. You need a hospital.
I'll drive you.
You OK? Get in.
Sorry.
You were on your way somewhere.
I missed my meeting.
Besides...
This is more important.
I can't run you over
and then abandon you.
It's supposed to relieve stress.
That is weirdly effective.
Do you do this often?
Just throw yourself in front of cars?
It's my first time.
Well, I'm honoured you chose me.
Are you from Manchester?
I don't always get the accent.
Yeah. Yeah, I am.
Just got here,
and I barely know anyone, so...
Well, now I know you.
Now you know me.
- Is this happening now?
- Yeah.
We picked up a text. We know
they're meeting this morning,
but we don't have a location.
6-0-2.
New contact with Hoodie.
All right.
Let's go. Nia?
We've got a text coming in.
Bright, walker, roast.
OK. Ben. Ben. Where is that?
There, it's by the splash park
in Vale Gardens.
OK. We've got a What3words location.
The gang are meeting
by the splash park in Vale Gardens.
Can we get officers there? '6-0-2.
'Hoodie is diverting. He's entering
the electronic shop on Beem Street.'
Wait, wait, wait.
Nothing on phones, Sir.
Why... Why the change of location?
I dunno.
OK, there's a back alley
down the back of the shop.
Maybe he's trying to shake us?
Nothing on phones? What is he doing?
What is he doing?
Contact with Hoodie.
He's carrying a bag.
Subject continuing east on foot
along Beem Street.
What is in that bag?
Can we see what he's bought?
Negative.
'Subject continuing on foot.
'Taking west turn into Vale Gardens.'
'6-0-1. New contact with Hoodie.
'Entering Vale Gardens,
headed toward the splash park.
'6-0-1.
'Hulk on site.'
Here we go.
He's saying he's sorry. OK.
If we set up a meeting, you turn up.
There's no fucking discussion!
Hulk is getting really angry.
Something about a meeting.
Alison. There.
What is he saying?
And... there, what's that?
There, what's he saying there?
We need to know what he's saying.
He's explaining something. What...?
Have you made contact
with Liam Barlow?
You've risked
the entire fucking operation.
Good morning, Mr Stanford.
I have an appointment.
I've got information.
We were so clear to you about
the dangers of getting involved.
I didn't tell him I was
lip-reading for you.
You understand how dangerous
this is, being an informant?
I'll have to keep my eye on you.
Subtitles by accessibility@itv.com