The gang's last robbery was a jeweller's.
Innocent member of the public got shot.
Door whirring
how did you find out that
they're meeting at the ice rink?
Well, I saw a text on Liam's phone.
'Do you talk a lot with Liam?'
yeah. Because how else
can I get close to him?
Anything you can get on that
woman there in the Navy blazer.
She's chandra baskhi. She works
for the steel millionaire Amir joshi.
I'm getting you through the tech.
Those are nothing to do with me.
You're in this now.
There is something about
this I don't feel comfortable with.
We don't wanna park too close.
Please be careful around Liam.
Seat belt clicks
Alison, spit it out.
Ok. If we...
If you got Liam on, er, conspiracy...
Conspiracy, yeah.
How long would he be looking at?
Put it this way - if you help us get him,
before they go in with guns,
then he... he might have a life.
Right. Ok.
Alison, if you have feelings
for this guy, there's...
You... No, Liam likes me.
I'm just playing along.
Yeah. There's a fine line...
Look, I know what I'm doing.
Knock on door, keyboard clacking
he exhales
so...
One kiss, and then you just ran away?
He sighs.
I'm sorry.
He chuckles softly do you wanna...?
I, er... I've been away a
couple of days, that's all.
Visiting a mate.
And moving to a new place?
Er, yeah. Braden
needed his old place back.
So just like that? Yeah, it was urgent.
Is this all about your job?
Are you trying to protect me from...
Whatever it is that you're doing?
I can't tell you anything more.
And I completely understand
if that's not enough for you.
Ok.
No more questions.
Except one more.
Chuckles softly
are people gonna get hurt?
Look, I know what sort of
guy Braden is, but brains.
Trumps brawn.
Always.
I wanna see you again.
I wanna see you every
day, if you'll let me.
But I can't tell you what I'm doing.
Ben, walk us through what we know.
Ok. Chandra baskhi. Oversees
transport for Amir joshi.
Could've been chandra who
alerted the gang to the jewels.
And we have a confirmed location
on where the jewels are right now?
Yeah. The family have an account
with croesus international vaults.
Their London branch is in Mayfair.
And we've finally found
the mysterious "Sammy".
Genius used his credit card at the bar.
Sammy Turner, software engineer at...
Croesus international.
And we've contacted the
company or the auctioneers?
No, we don't wanna spook anyone,
but the auctioneers have confirmed
the jewels are going on sale in five days.
Which is promising, but the
gang stopped communicating.
You're not getting around
weight-sensitive vaults
without some kind of rehearsal.
Yeah, exactly. So
where are they practising?
Because unless we gather
evidence for a conspiracy charge,
we've got to move in on them at
the vault, and then we risk bodies.
So... James sighs
let's keep all eyes and ears
open. Let's look at lock-ups.
Let's find out where
they're working from,
where they're keeping their weapons.
Let's dig. Quietly.
Dogs barking.
Footsteps descending.
Door opens door closes.
Thanks. Cheers.
Door opens.
What can I get for you?
You're a friend of Liam's.
Yeah.
How did you...?
I'm Helen. He must've mentioned me.
I learned not to ask.
Good.
Liam's asked to take you on a work trip.
As I'll be paying, I thought I'd
better get a proper look at you.
And...?
Where did you work before the tap?
At the orchard house cafe.
Have you been? No.
Liquid pouring.
Liam says that you live with your mum.
Yeah. No dad around?
Bottle cap unscrewing he left.
Is that everything?
Yeah.
I reckon so.
Are we going away?
At the tap, a woman came by,
and she said that she was your boss.
Really?
She gave me a right grilling.
I'm sorry.
So, where is Helen taking us?
Fancy hotel.
Separate rooms, obviously.
So, Liam has invited me away.
Overnight?
A day trip.
Is it mostly work, or is it mostly fun?
Healthy mix... I hope.
So...?
I need to find something to wear.
'London again?'
he didn't say. Must've
said something. I mean
I mean, did he tell you
what the trip was for?
Sorry I'm late. Traffic was awful.
Liam is talking to Alison again.
He did tell me...
That he has a plan to make
sure no-one gets hurt on this job.
So he's starting to trust you.
I suppose he must.
Ok.
Thoughts, ash?
Yeah, I think you should
go. I think she should go.
Ok. Anything you can get
from Liam, anything... Yeah.
Could be essential.
Wow.
Thanks.
Thank you.
He exhales, chuckles.
I was worried that
you'd change your mind.
I nearly did.
But then I haven't been
to a five-star hotel before,
and I'm about to become homeless, so...
He sighs
how about we leave Liam
and Alison at home today?
Yeah, that's fine by me.
Good. Because when
we get to the front desk,
they'll call me by another name.
Just play along, yeah?
Ok.
She chuckles softly, engine starts
engine revs.
Sir?
We found out where the joshi
family are staying in London.
Good. Mayfair regency hotel.
It's just down the road
from the auctioneers.
Great. We heard from Alison?
No, not yet. Ok.
Guv, can I ask you a question?
Why so obsessed with the
rookie when it's Helen's op?
Because he's not a rookie.
I mean, skills like his, you
hone them. Takes years.
So... who is he?
What's his link to the gang?
Why's he suddenly taken
Danny Heath's position?
And why is it we don't
know anything about this lad
from before five years ago?
Guests chatter
welcome.
Thank you.
Bags in the back. Thank
you. Sure. No problem.
A room under "Jack standford", please.
Of course.
Welcome to the hawthorne
estate hotel, mr and mrs standford.
They chuckle softly
not sure how I feel
about taking your name.
Who says I didn't take yours?
Your lucky day, sir.
Looks like management's
upgraded you to the Milton suite.
Really?
Amazing. Thank you. Can
I show you to your room?
No, no. I think we'll manage. Yeah?
Liam chuckles softly
clock chimes.
It really was our lucky day.
No. That was the day that you
got yourself a hacker for a husband.
Wait, you did this?
Yeah. I had to get in and bump us up.
The suite's only room with two beds...
She chuckles softly
ok. Yeah.
He chuckles
so, what's the plan?
Taking you to dinner.
Hotel's restaurant.
Tiny portions, big bill.
You ever been to a place
like that? No. Have you?
Yeah, care home took us every week
come here.
Liam exhales.
I probably got this all wrong.
I... I tried to keep it simple.
No obligation to wear it.
It's perfect.
But that's, what, two months' rent?
Only the best for mrs standford.
Liam, I... I-I can't accept that. Why not?
I'm getting a big pay-out soon.
Who better to spend it on?
So what you're doing, it's soon?
Phone buzzes.
Footsteps approach
wow.
Thank you. He chuckles
wait, do I have time to have a bath?
Course. I need a bit of time to
get some work done, anyway. So...
Downstairs at seven, yeah?
Don't stand me up this time.
No.
Looking for the spa, madam?
Chuckles softly
'nocturnes, op. 9' by chop in he exhales.
He gasps softly.
She chuckles softly
do I look the part?
More than.
Can I just hold you there
for a moment, please?
Good evening. Nice to see you again, sir.
It's good to be back.
We've taken the Liberty of
preparing some welcome drinks.
Diners chatter.
The maitre'd has arranged
the private dining room for you.
Fine.
Muffled conversation.
So, can you tell me... What
she is saying to him right now?
It's probably not that
interesting. Let's find out.
Muffled chatter.
I think they might be
talking about their grandson.
She chuckles ok.
He just said, "I'm not changing
the nappies for anyone."
Liam laughs charming both chuckle
yeah, she thinks so, too.
How do you do it?
If you don't mind me
asking. How do I do it?
Well, you just watch very carefully.
You sort of imagine the sound
coming out of their mouth.
But it's also all the other stuff, too.
So hard work, then?
Yeah. It's like... it's like a
great big puzzle, you know?
You're piecing things together.
And you've got body language, too.
Like, I'd, like... You lean
forward to ask a question.
Or you lean back cos
you're kind of a bit pissed off.
He chuckles
it's a proper talent, that.
He chuckles well, you've
got one too, haven't you?
Yeah.
How did you get into hacking?
No laptop in the home. Obviously.
So I'd go and use this
old PC in the library.
Ended up on these hacking
forums. Made a bit of mischief.
So you didn't go stealing the
pensioners' money, have you?
Cos that's a bit of a red flag.
Dunno. Those two have it coming.
Both chuckle
so, how did you get from that to...?
This?
I was doing some coding
work in London last year. Legit.
Legit? Pay, not great.
But I had this boss, Danny.
He was in with Helen and that lot.
Inhales sharply
but he couldn't do this
job, so... He put me up for it.
What, he put you up for it?
He sort of... had to quit.
So...
Have you never been tempted
to bend the rules a little bit?
Like your dad? My dad?
How do you...?
Helen made me do a
little bit of background.
Well, then...
You probably know my dad's
been breaking the rules all his life.
Yeah. Didn't get him very far.
And I knew that was not the path for me.
Sorry.
Did you have any foster
families that you really like?
There was one couple. They
really put up with all my shit.
We were happy families for a bit.
For a bit?
What happened?
Turned 18. Moved out.
He died.
His wife gave me this, actually.
Really?
It belonged to him.
I'm really sorry. Don't be.
Do you ever... see your foster mum?
Yeah. Well, I try to.
Door closes thank you.
Am I going mad, or is this
tidier than when we left?
He chuckles two cleans a day.
The rich are just that filthy.
Night.
Well, it'll be a shame
to mess up two beds.
Wouldn't it?
Speech muted.
I've been wearing them all my life.
I feel a bit naked not wearing them.
When you're with people who can sign,
it's quite freeing, not needing to wear it.
You must miss that.
Being with someone
who knows what it's like.
Yeah. I... I guess so.
Give me time. I'm sure I can learn bsl.
So, after your job.
Do you get to go back to your old life?
No.
Guess that's the point.
Ok, see you later.
Ok, took some leaning
on the Mayfair regency
to bend their discretion policy,
but they told me that the
joshi family are out of town now.
She sighs what about the jewels?
The auction house are continuing
with the sale. Nothing's changed.
Ok. There's more.
The vault wouldn't divulge
anything about the joshis' deposit.
However, when I pushed them
and sent them an image of Liam,
they did confirm he had
visited the vault last week,
under the name... "Jack standford".
Alison causing headaches again?
You're always so hard on her.
Don't think I don't know why.
She told you, then.
She didn't have to.
Look, me and Sara, it's not just some...
It's the real deal.
My ex left me for "the real deal".
They split a year later. Funny.
She chuckles I'm sorry.
It's not any of my business.
No. It's not.
Alison... I'm right, aren't I?
Yeah. Totally off-grid. Radio silence.
Then we need to run a
trace, for her own safety.
Phone buzzes.
Chuckles awkwardly how
about brunch in the bar?
Mum's trying to video-call me.
I... I think she's really
worried about the eviction.
I'll meet you down there. Ok.
Door opens, closes
thank you so much.
You're very welcome.
A hotel?
Why didn't you tell us?
Well, you wouldn't let me go.
Alison, you cannot just disappear.
You... you can't ignore my messages.
The more you text me,
the more exposed I get.
Do you know, me meeting
you is a massive risk right now.
I know. Yeah, I get that.
But if you don't reply to
me, then obviously, I worry.
Liam has a really nice smile,
but it doesn't mean he's not a criminal.
Liam was watching
some people in the hotel.
I saw them. Yeah, I'm
pretty sure it's the joshis.
This is Amir joshi. Did you see him?
Yeah, I saw him. Last night.
Ok.
So, joshi's trying to buy a place
for his daughter in Knightsbridge.
He's... Inhales deeply
he's trying to teach her
a lesson in prudence,
so he's selling her favourite
necklace to pay for it.
So Liam must be here
to spy on him. Yeah.
He hacked into the hotel's cctv.
Well, let's hope he's not watching you.
I don't think... Alison... Phone buzzes
is that him?
Alison, I don't... no, no, I
don't feel right about this.
I'm gonna have to call James. Just let...
No. No. I'm gonna have to go. I just
I really hope you're not doing anything
that would make this difficult.
I'm doing exactly as you asked.
Phone camera clicking.
Papa? Come here. Light's better.
Hi.
Where have you been?
Well, mum was really
upset about her eviction.
What?
You have your alone time, so do I.
Thank you.
It's a bit early for that.
Shall we play our game again?
Ok.
Who shall we spy on, then?
How about Princess over there?
Indistinct chatter.
She really loves the spa.
But... she really wanted the suite,
and she's asking him for an upgrade.
Beat her to it, didn't I?
Muffled chatter
body language says she's
not happy. Phone ringing
that one's easy.
Ok. What's he saying now?
Bidding.
Something about bidding.
He said it has to reach 5 million,
or he'll pull the item.
She's not happy that he's selling it.
She really is not happy. Liam chuckles.
A pistachio Mac... A pistachio...
Macaron? Yeah, that's it, she said.
He asked for two boxes
to be sent up to her asap.
Wonder she's not spoilt
are you watching them?
Is there a reason?
Look at them.
Think they'd even notice
if they lost something?
He exhales that was... special.
Yeah. It was.
But...?
I just... I wish you weren't
doing whatever you're doing.
I wish I could live
in that hotel forever...
And just forget the rest, like, all of it.
Me too.
Yeah.
Liam must have known the
joshis were at the hotel, yeah?
He's tracking them.
So you saw Liam watching
Amir and his daughter, reshmi?
Yeah. Liam asked me to lip-read them.
'I saw them talking about bidding.
'I think they were talking
about the necklace.'
'he probably wanted to check
they're going ahead with the auction.'
'do you think Liam was harvesting
pass codes from the joshis?'
like clone their devices, maybe?
Well, I did see Liam do
something on his laptop
when they was in the bar.
'He could've connected to their phones.'
it would explain how they hope
to get past the vault's safeguards.
Exactly. Did Liam mention
anything about his past?
Well, he did mention a guy called Danny.
And Danny was his old boss at
this coding company in London.
And Danny used to work for Helen.
But then he had to quit,
so he put Liam up for a job.
That's brilliant. Brilliant.
Ok. Get onto the met.
Get them to give you any intel
that they can on Danny's old case.
You get anything
else? Anything else? No.
No, not much, no.
Ok. That's great. Come
on, I'll give you a lift.
See you later.
Seat belt clicks Alison.
I never asked you to stay
in a hotel room with Liam.
No.
You didn't. But you did
ask me to get information.
You didn't really think of
where that might lead to.
I think I... I think I've become so hung up
on putting these bastards
away, you know, that, er...
That's on me.
But whatever you've started
with Liam, I need it to stop.
Please.
Yeah, ok.
So, all that damage to
my credit card's borne fruit?
Confirmed everything chandra told us.
Got everything we need
for our new approach.
Course you're happy. It's
all about you now, innit?
So what? Your cut's the same.
When are you collecting the piece?
Tonight.
Speak then.
Marky-Mark, the girl in?
Alison? Er... No. No, she's
not working today, bray.
You ever wonder what she's
up to when she's not here?
What you getting at?
I don't trust her.
I ran background on her. She's clean.
Right.
I'm really starting to regret
letting you in on this job.
First...
You shit your pants so
badly about my little toy
that we had to relocate you.
Now your throb-on for that girl
is starving your brain of oxygen.
Well, this job... It's my ticket out.
Nothing is gonna fuck that up for me.
Especially not some girl
that I'm passing the time with.
Understand?
Phone buzzes.
'Liam?'
I think... we need to talk.
Me first. Please?
What's this?
This is what we're taking.
Wait, is this from the family
that you were sitting
next to at the hotel bar?
That's right. I had to
do some recon on them.
I need you to keep it
secret until we're done.
We're gonna take it from an
ultra-secure vault in London.
Replace it with a replica.
No-one will even
notice until it's too late.
And I... I swear to you.
No-one will be hurt.
How am I supposed to believe that?
You have to trust me on that.
Is that enough?
He exhales.
She chuckles.
I'm sorry... You nearly finished it.
But if you don't like Brazil.
We can go anywhere you like.
And not just for one night.
Forever.
I'm trusting you because I
want you to go away with me.
You're asking me to...? Alison.
In 48 hours, I am gonna have.
A lot of money.
But I'm gonna have to leave the country.
And I want you and your mum.
To come with me.
What? You want us to go...?
Look at them at the top.
They've got houses on every continent,
and you don't get to keep your home?
You deserve a real life.
I don't know.
What to say.
Say yes.
You cannot see Liam
again. He's dangerous.
If you walk into that vault,
you're gonna get caught.
I know that. How do you know that?
'It's just way too risky.'
unlocking now. Go on through.
She needs to stay out of this.
Go, go!
You'll appreciate it's important
for us to understand the
events that led up to today.
Now.
Subtitles by accessibility@itv.Com