It's Alison.
She says the robbery's happening
at the hawthorne estate hotel.
'Back straight, smile wide.'
whatever you do, do not be yourself.
'Just open the door.'
she's at the hotel. Tell her to leave.
She needs to stay out of this.
'Necklace has changed
hands. Two bodyguards.'
now. Device beeps
alarm ringing Alison!
Liam... Braden. Stop! Argh!
You know where Liam is now?
Did you not arrest him at the hotel?
Exhales.
Any news on Ben yet, Nia?
I'll call again, sir. Thanks.
Yeah.
Monitor beeping, ventilator hissing.
Braden can't be in Glasgow and
Plymouth at the same time, can he?
So can we just try and work out
which is the more credible sighting?
Thank you.
Ashleigh sighs
you should go home. Get some sleep.
No, I'm fine. I'm ok. I
wanna... I really wanna be here.
How are you?
Spoke to the bodyguard's
family. You know.
It's not your fault. You did
everything that you could.
Any leads on the phones?
No, we've had, hundreds
of calls since the appeal,
but it's just wishful thinking.
And the joshi team have been
on the phone, asking for updates.
Again. You?
I spoke to Interpol, europol. Nothing.
Should've listened to you
about Alison, shouldn't I?
She was over-involved.
What's Antony saying? Anything yet?
No, Antony is saying no
comment, all through the night.
It's really fun. Helen
has coached him well.
Yeah. Sure she has.
She'd have paid him off
to keep quiet, do his time.
Just got off the phone with
Sara. She's at the hospital.
Ben's out of surgery.
He's not conscious yet, and we
won't know anything for a few hours.
My god.
Ok.
Ok, everyone.
Er.
DC lawford put himself on
the line for the job yesterday.
Put the safety of
others ahead of himself.
Let's make sure that wasn't for nothing.
Let's put all our efforts into
finding Braden and Liam.
We're not gonna let
them walk away this time.
God, Alison's mum is still
here. She's wants to see her.
Sure.
Alison sobs gently.
Hello.
This is Julie, my mum.
Hi, Julie. I'm James. Hi.
Ashleigh. Hi.
Ashleigh is gonna help find
you somewhere safe to stay
while we find Braden.
Does that mean we're
not going home? No. No.
Not yet. Not yet, ok?
But I can send someone to collect
anything you need, if that helps?
Can I... Can I have a
quick word with Alison?
Got a favour to ask. Is
there any news on Ben?
Yeah. Yes, yeah. Ben...
Ben's out of surgery.
He's still unconscious, but he's stable.
Ok, I can't give you your phone back,
but we were wondering...
If you might be able to
send Liam a message.
Ok, it's not like he's gonna reply,
but if he checks his messages,
that might help us to locate where he is.
Is that ok?
And what should I say?
Just keep it simple.
Just ask him to let
you know he's ok. Yeah.
Ok.
That?
Great. Yeah, that's great.
Thanks, Alison. Thank you. Thank you.
The... the information I gave you,
is it enough to arrest Helen and Joseph?
We're bringing Helen and
Joseph in for questioning.
One step at a time.
So you're interviewing them? Yeah.
Can I be with mum? Yeah.
Knock on door
rapid knocking
Braden? Yeah.
Braden, what are you doing
here? You're all over the news.
Look, Danny would want you to help me.
If the police come here, I'm
telling 'em you threatened me.
He sighs what a mess.
Yeah.
It was the kid. He exhales
Liam Barlow. Liam?
What'd he do?
He convinced me we were
gonna stitch up the police,
but it was me that got played.
Exhales sharply your
Danny recommended him.
Well, someone informed on
Danny for that ransomware gig.
And you think it was Liam?
It opened up a vacancy, innit?
For some slippery little
mancunian fucker to step into.
You sure no-one followed you?
So, Oliver's gonna stay with you.
There's stuff in the kitchen,
but if there's anything
you need, just let him know.
Yeah.
Ok.
No, thank you. No, I'm fine. Thank you.
Alison? I should get back.
I'll check the back doors. Ok.
You should get some rest. You
must be completely exhausted.
Have you spoken to Mark?
Because Helen and
Joseph came to the pub,
so he might know something.
We are speaking to him, but just
I know that it's hard, but you
do need to let us do our jobs, ok?
Can... can I go and see Ben?
I don't think that's a good idea.
He's only just got out of surgery.
It's just... I need to do something.
Please.
Sara?
How are you doing?
You brought her?
We're just here to drop
off some flowers, that's all.
Sara, I'm... I'm sorry.
Do you honestly think that you can just...
Show up with flowers
and everything'll be ok?
You shouldn't be here. It's...
It's already way too complicated.
I... I was trying to help. I was
I was trying to stop the robbery.
You slept with one of the suspects!
Was that... Was that part of your plan?
Ok.
We should go. Come on.
If you had just done what you were told.
And waited outside, Ben would've...
He'd have waited for armed response.
He wouldn't be in there.
I know.
Any more activity, let us know.
Sir. Yeah?
Liam's phone was switched
on. It pinged a tower in Budapest.
In Budapest?
You don't buy it?
He scoffs
why is someone as tech savvy as Liam
letting us track where he is?
Keyboard clacking.
Computer chirps, beeps.
Ready? Let's do it.
Device beeps
interview commences at 11:17am.
My client would like to make a statement.
Right, well, we've got some
questions we wanna ask you, Helen.
I've advised my client not to
answer any questions at this stage.
I want to start by saying that I'm shocked
by what happened at the hotel.
My heart goes out to the
family of the bodyguard who died
and to the police officer who was injured.
Braden Moore is an associate
of my estranged husband.
He got in contact with
me, wanting to get involved
in some property deals that I'm planning.
I made it clear that I did not
want to associate with him.
'I've known Helen red man for years.'
we reconnected recently
when she expressed an interest
in investing in one of my
property developments.
And I introduced her to
another business associate,
chandra bakshi.
Why are... Why are you
protecting her, Joseph?
I was introduced to
Braden Moore at the ice rink.
If I'd had any knowledge
of what he was planning,
of course, I would've reported it
to my employer and to the police.
If Braden somehow got
the idea to take the necklace
when he met miss bakshi, it
was wholly without my knowledge.
Paper rustles
that's all I've got to say.
Should we wrap up there?
Unless you have evidence to charge?
Not yet. But, er...
You spoken to Liam's girlfriend, Alison?
Why do you ask?
Lovely girl. Thought she
might know something.
But then, of course, juries
might not rate her as a witness...
On account of her being deaf.
So easy for her to misunderstand.
And you know what
barristers can be like.
Ruthless.
Door opens, closes
all our evidence for conspiracy
is on a hit for the vault, not the hotel.
They've covered every angle.
They've got all their stories lined up.
Phone buzzes better
to let them run for now.
Gives us time to build
a stronger case, no?
Yes?
Is that confirmed?
Ok. Thanks.
We just had a confirmed
sighting of Braden.
He is still in Kent.
He's somewhere near
faversham, apparently.
He could be at Danny
Heath's place. Danny Heath's.
Let's get an armed unit down there,
and let's get you down there too.
Alison sighs.
Yeah.
That's the records you asked for.
Fostering records
from Manchester. Right.
Not many match the
criteria you gave me.
I think this is him. Thanks, Nia.
Inhales sharply.
'He's not here.'
the team have been
through the whole house.
But Molly does admit
that Braden was here.
Any idea which way he was headed?
'No. She claims to have no idea.
'Says that he threatened to kill her.'
said that she was too shaken
up to call it in after he left.
'Ok. Bring her in.'
I'll be back soon, ok?
Let's go.
We've had to release Helen and Joseph.
You can't charge them?
They're blaming it all
on Liam and Braden,
saying they planned it alone.
But what about the evidence
that I have given to you?
The information you
gave us was very helpful,
but it wouldn't stand up in court.
Lawyers would just exploit
how you came to be on the case.
And, of course, your
relationship with Liam.
Which would undermine
all your evidence.
So everything that I did
and all the risks that I took,
what, they're all for nothing?
What did Mark say?
I bet he knows something.
Mark's not said anything.
Frankly, I think he's a bit scared.
Did Liam ever talk to you
about his time in foster care?
In foster care? Yeah. What did he say?
There was just one
family that he really liked.
Go on. But the man died
a couple of years ago.
Right. That's what he said?
Yeah. Why do want...?
We've been trying to
find out who that man is.
We know that Liam
came from Manchester
and he came from foster care.
Yeah.
But we can find no trace of
Liam Barlow before five years ago.
We did, however, find a Liam gray.
Fostered by a family in Manchester.
He's the right age,
matches Liam's description.
So he changed his name?
Alison, did Liam ever show
you a picture of this man?
His name's Charlie Fletcher.
That's the man that Alfie killed.
That is Liam's ring.
He said that he actually got
that ring from his foster dad.
Charlie was Liam's foster father.
And none of this is a coincidence.
Are you saying that
Liam took the necklace
for revenge for Charlie?
Car beeps, unlocks.
Door closes, she sighs
you hungry again? This
was dropped off for you.
No, I didn't order that.
You didn't order this?
Actually, yeah, I did. Sorry, I forgot.
I ordered that for mum. I'll take it.
Ok. Thank you.
Inhales sharply.
Breathes shakily.
Alison. How did you find me?
I put a tracker on that
cop's car, ds Francis.
You lied to me.
You told me that no-one
was gonna get hurt.
That wasn't supposed to
happen. Braden promised me.
And you believed Braden?
He sighs I know.
Did you use my hearing
aids to spy on me
and listen in to my conversations?
I'm sorry.
Do you not know how fucked
up that is? How invasive?
My hearing aid is like a part of
me. I thought you understood that.
Alison, you slept with me so
that you could inform on me.
That's fucked up.
No, I slept with you because I liked you.
No. No, no, no, no. You betrayed me!
Did you engineer our first meeting? No!
The crash on your bike?
That was an accident. I didn't know you!
But you got to know me,
and you didn't stop informing.
He sighs it made you feel important.
Yeah.
I was, because somebody
was listening to me
for the first time ever!
I know Charlie was your foster dad.
Is that why you took the necklace?
Money's the only thing that
Helen and Braden care about.
That was the only way to hurt them.
You really care about Charlie?
He sniffs yeah.
And I care about you.
That's why I came back.
Come away with me. We can still do it.
I've got a buyer for the
necklace in Panama.
He's gonna pay $5 million in cash.
No! What kind of life have you got here?
You're about to be
kicked out of your house,
and I meant everything that I
said about bringing your mum.
You could go to the police,
and you could testify
against Helen and Joseph.
We've still got a chance
to make things right.
No.
I'll go to prison for a very long time.
And I've got a plan.
A private plane will take us to Belgium,
and then we'll catch a plane to Brazil.
And no-one will find us there.
I like you. I really do.
But I don't
I'm not really sure if I know who you are.
You know me.
When we were in my flat, at the hotel.
That was real.
It could've been real.
But you completely fucked it up.
No. We both did stuff wrong.
And I am sorry. I am so sorry.
But we're on the same side.
We both wanted the same
thing - to stop Helen and Braden.
No. If you wanted to stop
them, you'd go to the police.
He sighs I can't.
And by the time you
call them, I'll be gone.
I can't go with you.
And if you're going, then.
Then maybe we should say goodbye.
So that's it?
We just walk away? No.
Good luck. No.
He sighs.
Doorbell rings
hi, dawn.
James.
Can I come in?
Yeah.
I've got a little boy arriving tomorrow.
Five years old.
Mum's in rehab, dad's
never been around.
Liam Barlow. Sound familiar to you?
Er, no. I was...
It's just he was one of your foster kids.
I think he was with you in 2012.
Changed his name since
then, I think. Nothing?
I've got a... a picture of him.
He chuckles that's him.
Have a look at that.
Honestly don't recognise
him. No, nothing?
There were so many kids over the years.
And I was working back then, so
Charlie did most of the foster care.
He sighs
we're friends, aren't we, dawn?
Yeah. Of course.
I mean, I could get a warrant
to search the place, if you like.
Or you can just tell me what you know.
Clock's ticking.
Liam was Charlie's favourite.
The only one he stayed in
touch with right up until he died.
But he's a good lad, James.
Is he? Is he? He's a good
kid, is he? Right, yeah.
Why don't you tell that to my colleague
who's just spent four hours in surgery,
having a bullet removed from his spleen?
Liam didn't pull the trigger.
Did he not?
So that makes everything ok, does it?
You think the same about Braden
not pulling the trigger on Charlie?
Does that make him
blame-free as well? I mean...
Or is this some kind
of rough-justice thing
against Braden and Helen?
I didn't know what he was planning.
I would've stopped
him. Of course I would!
I don't know where he is.
Dawn...
Dawn exhales James sighs
'you got anything?'
Liam's definitely been here.
I'll fill you in on the details later,
but dawn's not giving him up. 'Ok.'
we've just had a report of a
carjacking just outside ashford.
Description matches Braden.
We tracing that car?
'It pinged the anpr just outside
canterbury. Nothing since then.'
I think he's probably
staying off main roads.
Tyres screech.
Everything ok?
Gone. Gone.
'You really shouldn't be here, Alison.'
I know, but have you
spoken to the police?
Yeah. I don't think I was much help.
I have been working with them.
I came here because you're
the only one who can help now.
The detectives think I
don't have enough evidence,
and I need someone
else to stand up to them.
They would protect
you. No, I'm sorry, Alison.
You don't cross people like Braden.
I really am sorry, Alison.
Footsteps approach slowly hello, Alison.
Phone buzzes.
Alison sobbing 'hey, hey, manc.
'Look who I ran into.'
Alison whimpers, cries
breathes heavily.
Mrs Brooks.
Thank you.
Keys jingle.
Dawn gasps Liam.
Alison grunts
come here!
Braden grunts
now...
We're gonna see how much your
boyfriend really cares about you.
The police will find you.
They will be looking for you right now.
He chuckles.
I knew there was something about you.
You're always watching.
How long you been ratting?
Since the very start.
Well...
You don't feel so clever now, do you?
How could you be so stupid?
Alfie's gonna be out in a few years.
That's not justice.
I did this for Charlie... For you.
I never meant for you to do this.
I wanted to take something from them,
the way they took Charlie from us.
Braden contacted me. He's got Alison.
I'm gonna get her back.
Helen's gonna meet
me... Take me to Alison.
I just got to give them the necklace.
Then what?
Then when... once Alison's
safe, I'll get on the plane.
I'll manage somehow.
I just wanted to see you.
Say goodbye.
So you'll spend your life on the run?
I don't have a choice.
You could still do the
right thing. Go to the police!
No. Just promise me
you won't call them.
Braden'll kill her.
He's got nothing to lose now. He'll do it.
How do you know he won't kill you?
Come here.
She sobs gently
ok, everyone, I want us to circulate
descriptions of Liam and Alison
to bus stations, train stations.
Let's go ports, airports. Let's
check private airfields, too.
They're likely to be more noticeable
as a couple than they are alone.
Ok? Let's get on it.
Where's Liam? Where could he be?
Liam. Can't say it's good to see you.
I'm alone, like you said.
Where's Alison?
Have you got the necklace?
I wanna see her first.
We'll go in my car.
Inside.
Braden?
Braden!
Gun clicks whoa.
No sudden moves, ok?
He come on his own? He did.
And he's got the necklace.
Where's Alison?
I need to know that she's safe.
He chuckles see, I... I
always knew you were soft.
Here's your little police snitch.
Get up! Alison whimpers whoa, whoa.
Liam. Don't trust him.
Shut up!
He's not gonna let us go. Alison cries.
Danny Heath. Can
we just get on with this?
I tracked Danny down.
Got him to let me in
on the ransomware gig.
And I got him sent to prison for it.
All so I could meet Helen
red man and Braden Moore,
cos you killed Charlie.
That's what this is about?
You fucked up my gig
for Charlie Fletcher?
He might be nothing to
you... But he meant a lot to me.
Hey, hey, hey, hey.
Easy. I'm getting the necklace.
Let me see it.
I'm gonna need you to
put that gun down first.
No chance, manc.
Now get out.
Alison yelps on your knees.
But you've got the necklace.
Why not let him go? Not your concern.
On... your... knees.
No, no, no, no, no!
No, no, please, no... Do what he says.
Please, don't do this,
please! Do what he says.
Just go. But you got what you wanted.
Get out! Alison, do what he says.
You got what you wanted.
Please don't hurt him.
Get out! Alison!
Please, go!
What you sticking around for?
You'll be next! Get out!
Please, go.
Officer, muffled: Armed
police! On your knees!
Stay where you are!
Officers clamouring.
Putting it down!
Clamouring continues
don't... don't shoot!
I'm putting it down!
- I got nothing!
- Stop resisting!
Stop resisting! Stay where you are!
Braden grunting, panting
Braden Moore... I'm
arresting you for murder,
armed robbery and attempted murder.
You don't have to say anything,
but it may harm your defence
if you do not mention when questioned
anything which you
may later rely on in court.
Officers chatter
got the suspect secured.
Get him in the car.
You ok?
We got Helen's admission
on tape, which is...
Thanks for getting in
contact. You did the right thing.
He was a good man,
was Charlie, wasn't he?
Liam clears throat, chuckles
is that why you did it? Was it all for him?
It was.
I'd believe you if you hadn't
run off with a £5 million necklace.
Look, Alison was just wondering
if she could have a word with him.
Yeah, she can have a minute. Yeah.
Thank you.
Are you ok?
Yeah.
You gave yourself up for me.
It was worth it.
Just so you know, I was
really tempted by your offer.
Next time?
I'm so sorry.
Just... I actually like working hard.
And all I ever wanted is for
people to give me a chance,
the same chance as anyone else.
All right, it's time to go.
Car door opens I'm sorry.
Engine starts.
She inhales, sighs
hi.
It's nice to see you. Yeah, you too.
Courtroom chatter
courtroom chatter.
All rise.
Case of Liam Barlow.
Are you Liam Barlow? Yes.
Liam Barlow, you are
charged with conspiracy to Rob
in that on or before 17th
September of this year,
together with Helen red man,
Braden Moore, Antony bates,
chandra bakshi and persons unknown,
you conspired to Rob
Amir joshi and others.
How do you plead?
Guilty or not guilty?
Guilty.
Footsteps approach
hello. James.
Sorry, the... the door was open.
Yeah.
Moving out? Yeah. We're
moving into a new flat.
New start. Well, I hope
I hope you don't mind me coming round.
I just wanted to give you some
news. We've arrested Joseph holhurst.
Not connected to the
robbery, we couldn't do that.
But we had a good look
through his accounts,
and we managed to charge
him with money laundering.
So Hollis and byrne
have suspended him.
So it's not gonna make any difference
to us getting kicked out of here?
We also got news back
from the review board.
I didn't wanna say too much
until we knew the outcome,
but, you know, payments to
informants are based on results.
And thanks to you, we
made some pretty big arrests.
And it was your information that
led to the recovery of the necklace.
So...
Paper rustling
£50,000?
Is this for me?
It is.
Thank you.
Well, don't thank me.
It was your hard work.
It's gonna really help.
Well, if you have anything left over.
You might wanna think about this.
With your skills.
I'm sure you'll be in demand.
Subtitles by accessibility@itv.Com