Detective looked for
you on the breakfast shift.
This is detective inspector marsh.
James. James.
I-I can do it if you tell me what it is.
'We're all watching a gang
who are planning a robbery.'
they're careful to meet in
places where we can't bug them.
That's why we need a lip-reader, so
we can understand what's being said.
Who is that?
No idea. Liam.
Liam Barlow, 29.
'Look, these people are dangerous.
You don't wanna get close to them.'
'the tap is a pub, right? And
they put Liam in a flat nearby.'
I could see a lot more
if you just get me closer.
You really, really need to
leave the investigating to us.
Are you, like, a regular here? No,
just moved in around the corner.
Tyres screech Alison?!
There. What's that?
What did he say there?
Muffled conversation
speech muted
missing this. What is this? Yeah.
Sorry.
He didn't turn up for a meeting.
And he's asking Cruella to reschedule it.
Why? Why did he not
turn up for the meeting?
I-I don't know. It's not clear. Radio beeps
'6-0-1.' what's he doing?
Hoodie is taking items
out of the carrier bag.
Saying something like "phone".
And "switching".
And the driver's not
really happy about that.
Driver's phone just went off.
What? Wh-what happened?
They're switching the sim cards.
So you've been getting the
messages from the driver. Shit!
Yeah, we were
intercepting his messages.
Radio beeps all units, stand down.
Phone buzzes muffled chatter.
You should get to your shift.
But... if you can't read
their phone messages,
then you're not gonna know
when they're gonna meet.
So... what you gonna do?
We'll find another way. Thanks, Alison.
'Yeah, pull up the recordings, will you?'
right. There. Now,
who's...? Ok, so, hoodie.
'Hoodie's not gonna give us anything.
'I mean, why would he? So
we need something, anything.
'Agreed? Anything that
vaguely resembles a lead.'
I'm sorry. Sorry.
Liam's new to the gang, isn't he? Yeah.
'So he could be our way
in. What do we think?'
"phone buzzes
'ok, they're gonna reschedule
this meeting, aren't they?
'So we need to find a
way to be there, yeah?'
'yeah.'
and we stay focused on Liam.
Antony, mate?
Everything ok? Yeah.
You... you have been changing
your sim card once every three days,
like we told you?
Yeah, course I have, bray.
It's just Liam thinks
we're weak on security.
I've been doing everything
you told me to, bray.
Did you... or did you not
follow the rules we gave you?
Sarah doesn't like
me changing numbers.
She's nearly nine months.
She could drop any day.
Sarah.
Antony groans.
Machine beeps.
Hi.
I, er... didn't know
you'd be working today.
Is this a bad time?
I'm... I'm fine. Can we talk later?
No, I... I just... I was
hoping to see Braden.
Yeah, later's good.
Sorry. She chuckles
I didn't see you there.
You are...? I'm Alison. I work here.
Alison, this is Braden. Our owner.
Hiring anyone these days. I'll take that.
Just stay out of his way, you know?
He chuckles
hum of conversation.
Glass clinking
hello. Hey.
I... just wanted to see how you are.
Yeah, I'm fine...
The owner, Braden, do you know him?
He put in a word in
for me for this new job.
The guy you were
speaking to, is that your...?
Yeah, he's my ex. Yeah.
I got major bad vibes.
She chuckles I'm sorry, I
didn't mean to be so rude.
It's ok.
When you two were, like,
signing, it made me think,
that's how it must be for you all the time.
Around, you know, people who can hear.
Yeah. It... It can be like that sometimes.
I was wondering...
Do you wanna come
out for a drink sometime?
Chuckles nervously yeah.
Er, yeah, maybe.
Er, thank you for taking me to
hospital and for driving me home.
You didn't have to do that.
Yeah, I did. I knocked you off your bike.
I better go back to work.
See you later. Door opens
door closes.
Hairdryer whirrs.
Mum!
Sighs.
Thank you.
Yeah. Yeah, I'll give you that.
Ok. Yeah, I'll see you then.
I've gotta go. All right. Bye.
Alison. Is everything all right?
Yeah. Have you got a minute?
Yeah. Yeah, come... come this way.
'What's up?'
who was James talking to?
Er... James is with the
assistant chief constable.
He's trying to get more
funding for surveillance.
But we'd never be able to
watch them around the clock, so...
So you need someone closer
to them, like an informant.
Yeah, but that's easier said than done.
But I've been
I've been doing some bar
work, and it's near Liam's flat.
Have you been working
at the canterbury tap?
Have you made contact
with Liam Barlow?
Er... Have a think.
I believe you've been working at the tap.
I... I went in cos I just wanted
to see if he was there, and...
But they needed the staff,
and I just really need a job.
I mean, of all the places
Braden Moore owns
the tap. You know that?
Yeah, I... I know.
Was that the only time you
made contact with them both?
At the bar.
It's a simple question. Just have a think.
That was the only time?
Wh-what?
Ben has been tracing Liam's movements
over the last couple of days,
and it seems Liam made a
surprise trip to the hospital
night before last.
It was an accident, and
he knocked me off my bike.
And then he drove you to the hospital?
Well, I think he was just worried.
He just didn't want me
calling the police, so...
You were the reason why
Liam didn't go to that meeting.
It was you.
You've risked the
entire fucking operation.
I'm sorry, but...
You wouldn't have known
anything if it wasn't for me.
You were paid, Alison. You
only paid me minimum wage, so
I should arrest you for misconduct.
But I could actually help!
You know, Liam and Braden,
they're actually meeting.
I saw them talking.
And the meeting's back on.
I don't want your help.
I don't want anything from you.
It is not safe for you to be
anywhere near this station.
You're a security risk.
Ashleigh, tell the canteen
we're letting Alison go, yeah?
I had to push James to use you.
This looks bad on me,
too. No, I know. I'm sorry.
Am I gonna get paid?
Don't push your luck.
May I...? I should explain to Gary, then.
I'll talk to Gary. Max, could you...?
If you could just come
this way? This way.
Hi.
So, did you fix my bike?
Yeah, yeah.
You need your wheels for work,
and the crash was my fault too.
Your mum offered me a cup of tea.
Thank you. That's very nice.
We've been chatting.
Chatting?
About what?
You, mainly.
Me?
Sorry, she's just winding me up...
Shall we go outside?
'You made a big impression on my mum.'
I like her. She's cool.
Seriously, thank you.
I didn't know how I was
gonna get my bike fixed.
It was a little bit selfish.
See, I was hoping that maybe
you'd have that drink with me.
Maybe. If you ask again.
He chuckles
can I take you to
London tomorrow night?
I'm meeting some friends, and I
thought maybe you could come along.
Ok. Yeah.
Tomorrow. Tomorrow.
Well, the acc was charmingly
blunt in his assessment of our case.
We are not getting
any more surveillance.
Liam Barlow. Any news on him?
He's been working as
a software developer.
Yeah? He's moved around.
Previous addresses in
London and Manchester.
Couple of parking tickets.
'To be honest, I'm not getting much.'
people don't usually evade
your levels of research skills.
'Without access to their messages,
we need another way in, don't we?
'So keep looking.'
Have you got two phones?
He chuckles softly one's for work.
What do you do?
I am a software engineer.
Who do you work for?
I am doing some... digital security
work for a local businesswoman.
But she made me sign an nda,
so I shouldn't really be talking about it.
Well, that sounds more
interesting than pulling a pint.
It's not, believe me.
So, where exactly are
we meeting your friends?
They are going to a
bar down by the river.
We'll drop in and see
them, take it from there? Ok.
Ok.
Animated chatter, music plays
can I squeeze through, is that ok?
Thank you. There we go.
Oof, busy! What do you want?
Can I have a vodka, lime and
soda? Yeah, yeah, no worries.
Hiya.
Chatter and music muffled.
Phone buzzes.
Dance music blares
faint chatter
chatter and music muffled.
This is my fiancee, Maya. Hey!
Hi. Liam. Hey. Nice to meet you.
Er, this... this is Alison. Hey!
This is Sammy and Maya. Hi.
Hi! It's lovely to meet you.
Lovely to meet you, too.
Are you engaged? Yeah.
When are you getting married?
Don't ask. It's not for ages.
Back in a second.
Have you met Liam before?
No. We just met.
Sammy wanted to come here.
Said we might run into a friend.
So, how did you and Sammy meet?
Well, I'm a dental nurse.
He just kept... Speech fades
conversation muted
eventually, I was like, "are
you gonna ask me out or what?"
That's very cute. Yes.
So, what does he do for work?
He works for a security
storage company.
They look after valuable
things for very rich people.
Whereabouts is he based?
They've got buildings all over.
Sammy's mostly based in
Mayfair. He's quite junior.
Low hum of chatter and music
very cute.
It's not a real diamond, but I don't mind.
You know, Sammy keeps saying
he's gonna get me a real one,
like he'll get a big pay rise or something.
Hey. We should get
going. But we just got here.
What, you're going now?
We'll go somewhere else.
Maya scoffs one more drink.
Four! Four... Dance music blares
want me to get some
more? Yeah, definitely.
Should go get more, for sure.
Yeah. Machine beeps
get four more? Four.
Cheers! Whoo!
Well, you definitely cannot drive. I know.
I'm back in town tomorrow,
so I'll grab the car then.
Let's get a taxi. But how
much is that gonna cost?
Don't worry, I'm paying...
Are you hungry? Am I what?
Are you... are you hungry? Hungry?
Yeah. Yeah, I'm hungry.
I am. Come on. I know a place.
Do you know what, I used
to come to London a lot
when I was little with my dad.
He used to take me to the flower market.
It was different back then.
Actually, it was the only time
I remember going anywhere
on my own with him.
Yeah, he was away a lot.
It was mostly was just
me and mum, growing up.
He doesn't live with you now?
Thank you. What did you say?
Your dad, he doesn't live with you now?
He went off wandering.
Is... is he deaf too?
No. My mum is deaf,
but my dad is hearing.
Are things tough without him? Tough?
Yeah, my mum's been made redundant,
so financially, it's a bit difficult.
And my dad just didn't really deal with it.
Or, actually, he just didn't want to.
I was let go, two jobs. Two jobs.
So, yeah, things are a little bit tough.
So, what do you wanna
do? What's your dream?
Dream?
Do you know what, I used to be
really good at gymnastics at school.
Really? I actually thought
I could win a gold medal.
She chuckles
but I need a bit more
realistic dream than that.
No, no, no, don't do
that. Don't be realistic.
What... you're not realistic?
Definitely not. No way.
So what is your unrealistic plan? Mine?
You know...
This place does the
best sticky toffee pudding.
Sticky toffee pudding?
Ok.
Er, sticky toffee pudding, please.
Thanks.
You left it open.
You could lose anything in it.
Thanks.
Hey, that looks nice.
Could you see what I was saying
when I was talking to Sammy?
Not much, no.
You seemed to be
asking a lot of questions.
I have to pay attention, otherwise
I'd never know what's going on.
So you're always
watching? It's like a habit?
Well... yeah. Why?
What, you got something to hide?
He chuckles
I'll have to keep my eye on you.
I had a good night.
Really good. Yeah. It was good.
I... I can see you again, right?
To be honest, it's complicated.
"Complicated".
With your ex?
Just complicated.
I should go.
I'll text you.
We were so clear to you about
the dangers of getting involved.
Yeah, but I didn't tell him
I was lip-reading for you.
I didn't tell him anything. Yeah
I've got information.
Liam met up with a guy called Sammy.
I think he works for a
high-security storage company.
I didn't get his last name,
but I think Liam brought me
along to keep his girlfriend busy.
They talked about Mayfair.
I think, Sammy showed
something to Liam.
I think it was a floor plan.
They talked about a
family vault in a basement.
Family - what family?
I don't know, but Sammy's fiancee
thinks he's coming into some money.
I think they're paying him for information.
What do you want?
What do I want? Yeah.
Well, I want to help.
They're not suspicious of me.
They underestimate me.
Most people do.
We can't risk you being seen
here while you're working at the tap,
but, yes, your information
backs up what we know.
We're checking the description of
Sammy against employees of vaults
and high-net-worth
storage facilities in Mayfair.
It's allowed us to
narrow down our search.
You understand how dangerous this is?
Becoming an informant.
Dangerous? Yeah.
And you're already working at the bar,
and you have no intention of leaving.
Correct? Correct.
I mean...
If you happen to see
anything related to this case
while you are working at that bar.
I would really appreciate
it if you would let me know.
Ok?
Alison, for your safety,
we'll set up protocols,
and I'll be your contact, ok?
But just so we're clear,
I am not asking you
to put yourself in any
danger to get this information.
Ok? Do not go out of your
way to watch these people.
Yeah, yeah. No, I understand.
You can end up with a
lot of regrets in this job.
Alison, I don't want
you to be one of mine.
For us to foster that digital awareness.
I can tell by some of your faces
that it's time for me to shut
up so we can go for lunch.
Thanks for listening.
Ben, any news on venues?
Working with Alison's information,
we've narrowed it down to three
high-security storage facilities
and vaults that use biometrics.
'But I can't find out more
about specific security systems,
'as the facilities are
understandably reluctant
'to give out that information.'
Nia, you were looking at
the driver, Antony bates?
Anpr shows he's been
checking out warehouse space.
'Warehouse space?'
ok. Maybe using this as a rehearsal
space if they're looking at vaults.
'We need to get three down to one.'
good morning. I have an appointment.
Your credentials, if I may?
Passport, and letter of
recommendation from my bank.
Thank you, mr standford.
I need a box. Doesn't need to be big.
Just absolutely bulletproof.
Follow me, sir.
I'm told you're the best.
We have all the usual safeguards
motion sensors, weight-sensitive vaults
and a few innovations of our own.
Glad to hear it.
Retina scanner. Still the most
secure biometric safeguard.
Indistinct chatter, machine beeps.
That'll be 5.60. Machine
beeps customers chatter.
Cobweb.
Do you want another one? Later, yeah.
Door opens, closes
hey. Hi.
How's it going?
Terrible.
I met this girl, we went
out, had a really nice time,
but then she didn't reply to my texts.
Sorry. I've just been really busy.
Yeah. Me too.
Well, I'm sorry, I just
turned all the taps off.
I, er, come to see Braden.
I can get him for you.
You go. I'll lock up.
I will text you.
Ok.
What are you doing? What?
You were texting... And
then you looked at the monitor.
I didn't know if I should
turn the screen off.
Mark didn't say. Whoa,
whoa, whoa. What's goin' on?
Who were you texting?
I wasn't texting.
You know her? Yeah. I...
How well do you know her?
Give me your phone. What?
No. I didn't do anything. Open it.
It's from earlier. There's nothing since.
You should get going.
Go.
Alison, it's my responsibility
to keep you safe,
and if you're not gonna play by
the rules, this isn't gonna work.
This meeting is significant.
What are they planning?
To second chances?
This is way beyond anything
we could've asked for.
This is... brilliant. Thank you.
You're in this now, and I'm
gonna tell you how we do things.
Subtitles by accessibility@itv.Com