Roman emperors
were the real punks.
Don't say "punk." It's cliché.
Whatever. Let me tell you
about these dinner parties.
Nero loved a good poisoning.
- At a dinner party?
- He'd arrange one right at the table...
I don't feel like
going on tonight.
Too bad, 'cause that's what
makes the club feel like paying us.
Titus, this was
all in the book.
Titus would ply
his guests with wine,
then bind their privates
with a chord.
Hey! Did you get a new guitar?
A '64 teardrop reissue.
Not a mark on it.
All right.
Can I see it?
Oh, it's nice.
Hey! Hey! Hey!
Hey, cut it out, man! Hey!
You stupid son of a...
You're gonna pay!
It's a hunk of wood, bro.
It should look
like a hunk of wood.
We're not the philharmonic.
See, look, man.
It's better already.
Hey! It's 10:45.
How about taking that onstage?
Now I feel like going on.
You're my child,
and so arethose quadruplets,
and I'm not gonna
give any of you up.
Don't you dare talk to meas a mother.
Sign on the door
says "closed for private event."
You're alone.
How much more
private can you get?
Will you pass me a tissue?
Who are you keeping?
You owed me a decision 10 days ago.
Total amnesia.
You're my whole life, you.
And Luisa Maria can't decide
if she's gonna keep the quadruplets.
Then how can you...
She keeps them.
I read it online.
You happy now?
I ruined it for you.
- I want two names by Friday.
- Fine.
I'll arrange for a patient
with a mysterious illness
to come in on Thursday.
Yes. You need more tests.
It's only been two months.
Who knows how they'll react
to freak weather patterns?
They all did fine
in the wind tunnel.
Two names by Friday or the pay overruns
come out of your salary.
I can hurt you.
I know that now.
And I move
your parking space to the E lot.
Don't ever leave me, Mom!
Hey.
Who's the sickest patient
you got?
I've got a guy who'll be dead
in the next 10 minutes.
Oh. You mean someone who might actually
survive a diagnosis.
There's nothing here.
Just the usual cracked heads,
gunshots, false alarms.
Who would you pick to fill your
narrow little flats?
So, you can fire them
off my recommendation?
Nice try.
Hey, who do I have to grope to get
some turndown service in here?
Jimmy Quidd.
He's a punk rock singer.
Punk rock star to you.
Repeated trauma,
self-cutting, fever,
arthralgia, hyper-inflated chest,
fatigue, anemia,
blood in the stool and urine.
I've died and gone
to diagnostic heaven.
His blood results show booze, cocaine,
amphetamines, opiates.
The only mystery here
is how he made it to be 38.
I'm 28.
And he lies.
And he's a pain in the ass.
- Hey, come on.
- No.
Wrap him up.
I'll take him to go.
Dizzying array of symptoms,
any of which could be caused by drugs,
trauma, being a loser.
The guy's a walking pharmacy,
could be anything.
Oh, forgot to mention.
Final case.
Get it right, you're hired.
Runner-up will be decided strictly
on some definition of merit.
- Endocarditis.
- Hemorrhagic lesions
on the lungs and gut.
Bronchiolitis obliterans,
he smoked his airways into oblivion.
- Endocarditis.
- I already said that.
I heard of it
before you mentioned it.
Speed counts.
Find something else.
Could be bacterial meningitis.
- You already picked.
- I'll take meningitis.
Too late. Go run your tests.
No. He's sick
'cause he's a drug addict.
No. He has every symptom
you'd expect from a drug addict.
So, you think
it's all too perfect?
Some other disease
is trying to throw us off its trail?
If he had four out
of 20 possible symptoms,
he'd be
a garden-variety druggie.
Twenty out of 20,
there's an underlying disease.
Run your tests.
No!
He's weak, in withdrawal,
just spewed blood.
They're gonna rip off
a piece of his lung,
ram instruments
down his throat,
and Rota-Rooter his intestines.
It'd be nice
if we didn't kill him
trying to figure out
what's killing him.
One diagnosis,
one test at a time.
O2 sats are low,
hyper-inflated chest.
I need a bronchoscopy to...
- You just lost two points.
- What for?
For thinking
it makes a difference who goes first.
- Only one person can be right.
- What points?
Can't have an objective system
of measurement without numbers.
You lose three
for not knowing that.
From now on, only the person
holding this can treat or run tests.
Wanted to give you the serpent staff
with the poison axe-head,
but I left it in my car.
Don't need you.
It's one thing to hire based on a game.
Don't need your lecture.
It's insane to treat
based on a game.
You're not
taking the long view.
The one where
we stuff another patient in a body bag?
No, if we're wrong,
that'll come pretty fast.
The long view is the one where
we pick the best team,
that way we can use all the bags
we save for grocery shopping.
You're not buying
that argument, are you?
No.
In which case,
I'm back to my original position.
Don't need you.
What do you think of Amber?
I screwed up a diagnosis.
You don't seem
that upset by it.
I diagnosed a guy with adenocarcinoma
three months ago.
Told him he had six months.
So, now you gotta tell him that he's way
behind on his Christmas shopping?
He didn't get worse.
I rechecked everything.
Biopsy was a false positive.
Harmless lesions
caused by talc inhalation.
Medical clemency.
Interesting.
Why would you use that word?
Because I'm interested.
When I'm interested,
I describe the things
that make me interested
as interesting.
Most people would say
good, possibly great.
Why aren't you
able to just enjoy...
Why aren't other people
able to just be interested?
- Is he in there?
- Yeah.
Why'd you go right
for the drug theories?
If he had a history
of shoving cancer into his veins,
I'd have guessed cancer.
Okay. You're an idiot.
Either that or you've decided
you can trust a smoking addict
alone in a bathroom
with an oxygen tank.
I got your
new test results back.
Sorry I'm late.
Who's your colleague?
Dr. House.
Yes, Dr. Wilson.
I really don't
need the consult.
I know the prognosis.
Apparently not.
Mr. McKenna,
I can't believe I'm able to say this,
but you're cancer-free.
The biopsy looked
like adenocarcinoma, but it wasn't.
Harmless lesions
on your lungs. You're fine.
I don't get it.
- Cool.
- No, it's...
I know this must
come as a shock,
but I've
double-checked the labs.
I just accepted
an offer on my house.
I've had three goodbye parties.
I'm buying
plane tickets to Venice.
You can still use those
if you're alive.
I have to pay a $6,000 broker commission
on a house I'm not selling.
Money I don't have.
Thank you for letting me know.
I would have thought the living
would mean more than the expenses.
It's not about the money.
I have 17 points?
I started you all out on 100.
Then you blew up
part of the building.
Where's Foreman?
He 9011 paged.
- By who? Is it about our...
- Me.
I needed him right away,
somewhere else.
We're hiding from Foreman?
Foreman accused me
of playing games with patient care.
Who gets the eyeball next?
I haven't run my test yet.
It still might be a lung issue.
You can't run your test. The patient
had massive smoke inhalation.
Do a bronchoscopy,
it'll set off a laryngospasm.
I'll do
an open-lung biopsy instead.
You want an invasive surgery
because you screwed up?
The patient snuck a cigarette.
The patient is an addict.
It's not his fault he's jonesing
for whatever
he can get his hands on.
Not his fault he's jonesing?
In what universe does
that make any sense?
Get him on a nicotine patch.
That'll keep up
with his joneses.
Do your biopsy.
How's the new us's
final case going?
It's a moving target. House keeps moving
it, so I can't find it.
So, you decided to focus on solving
the problem in Darfur?
Taub is in there
prepping the patient for a biopsy.
Stay close to Taub,
I stay close to House.
And stay close to the game.
I'm trying to stop the game.
That's your role in the game.
Did you wander
over here to annoy me?
You're not wearing a lab coat.
House doesn't
wear one, does he?
Damn!
Now when I walk away,
it's gonna look like
I have a reason other
than just annoyance.
He won't let us
finish prepping him for the biopsy.
Try the other arm.
The problem's not the arm,
it's the entire patient.
Hi.
He let you check his chest.
He let you do anything
except check that arm.
He wallpapered himself
with nicotine patches.
Real rebellion has a point,
it's not just
juvenile and purposeless.
Maybe purposelessness
is my purpose.
Mission accomplished.
Amber, it's not the patches.
He's got blood clots
moving through his body.
Means I was wrong.
Oh!
If the clot reaches his lungs
or his heart, it'll kill him.
It's true!
We all know it's true.
You just wasted our time.
And what you're doing?
I'm not competing.
- Where's Taub?
- Foreman was following him.
So, you paged Taub.
Didn't see that
I had much choice.
He has schistocytes
on his blood smear
which means DIC's
causing the clotting.
What's causing the DIC?
- Drug impurities.
- You lost your round.
New symptom, new round.
This has to be drug related.
This is how doctors kill patients,
by seeing the stereotypes...
Drug addicts use drugs
is a stereotype?
Drugs are bad is a stereotype?
- Losers lose is...
- Malaria.
He hasn't left
the country in years.
Malaria's relapsing-recurring.
For all we know,
he could have been sick for years.
It explains not just the DIC and
the bleeding, but the tiredness, fever,
everything
we attributed to drugs.
Oh, yeah. It's much more likely
that this ass punk rocker
was exposed to
malaria than drugs?
If you were always right,
then you wouldn't have just been wrong.
Or let the patient
mainline nicotine.
Or ravaged my anatomical model,
which Grandma House bought me
when I aced my MCATs.
A pharmaceutical rep
left that here on Tuesday.
Grandma does
some part-time work.
The rep was
a 30-something babe.
Thank you. I got her hips.
Carry it with pride.
Manipulative bitch,
you're wanted in the laser's circle.
Why do you hate drug addicts?
Your situation is different.
You're taking
a necessary prescription...
I know. I'm fabulous.
And I'm not the patient.
I'm not allowed to have
a problem with junkies?
You're allowed.
There's gotta be a reason.
He's the patient. You don't know him.
Why do you hate him?
He's throwing his life away.
'Cause he's
setting his own terms,
not living in fear
of every pop quiz?
I thought we were
talking about him.
We were never
Why are you afraid to lose?
Are you gonna fire me
because I like to win?
Just wanna know the reason.
I watched this football game once,
and I noticed something odd.
The winning team
was the happy one.
I did the math.
Our patient's happy.
He's an idiot.
He's a happy idiot.
That screws
with your worldview.
There's something freeing
about being a loser, isn't there?
Why are you afraid to...
Mommy didn't love me enough.
Daddy expected too much from me.
Something.
Let's assume that's true. I get how
that can make me a screwed up person.
But how is my willingness
to do anything to get the right answer
bad for my patients?
Or put in terms you can understand,
how is it bad for you?
I didn't ask you
to pick up the meds.
I'm trying to be
a good colleague.
You're trying
to boost your score
by prescribing drugs for House.
Why else
would you have a second bag?
Didn't say good
colleague to you.
You realize
we still have a patient.
Don't care about the patient.
You care about this job more
than you care about his life?
I care about my wallpaper more
than I care about his life.
Okay. You're jerking me around.
There's no reason
to be a doctor if you don't care.
I care about life.
I just don't care about his.
He doesn't care, why should I?
My time is better spent...
Kissing up to your boss?
Average doctor cuts off a patient
18 seconds into a history,
because that's all
the time he's got.
Meanwhile, six of us are administering
to a guy with a death wish.
So, why do you want the job?
Not because I'm maximizing
my service to mankind.
Good for you.
Where is he?
We're gonna spend the next hour
looking for a guy
who doesn't wanna be found.
Jimmy Quidd's
greatest stiff. 1989.
A profit-seeking
entity released this?
He put it out himself.
He wanted people to
listen, but apparently
didn't want people
to enjoy listening.
- Now, why would someone...
- Truly a mystery.
Why would anyone do something
just to aggravate people?
Why would you have
a blank liability release form
plus your checkbook
on top of your desk?
Probably because
they were in the second drawer,
in a manila envelope,
under a book,
and you put them
on top of my desk.
You usually keep
your checkbook at home.
It's your go-to excuse
for why you can't lend me money.
You're gonna pay
the guy the six grand, aren't you?
There are other people
I write checks to. I do have cable.
There's no negligence
without injury.
I handed the guy
a death sentence.
He's not distressed
with the death sentence.
He's distressed
with the life sentence.
I gave him
three months of misery.
You gave him three months
of being someone special.
You're paying the guy
because he used to be boring,
and without you,
he's gonna be boring again.
Hi.
Results of
the malaria tests already?
Well, no.
But we were wondering if you'd sent
the patient for any additional tests?
You lost the patient.
Taub, you check lost and found.
Thirteen, come with me.
Why do you love drug addicts?
I won't pigeonhole the patient,
so that means I'm...
Perfectly capable
of drawing my own conclusions.
Are you capable of
answering a question?
I think there's more
to him than the drugs.
Admirable, why?
I need a reason
for doing something admirable?
There's always a reason.
He's a patient.
You don't know him. Why do you like him?
Alcoholic parent?
Druggie youth?
There's no such thing
as a saint without a past.
Or a sinner without a future.
What makes you so sure that drugs
are a mask for something else?
Drugs are always
a mask for something else.
That's the dumbest thing
I've heard in my life.
You really want this job?
Why, you think
you can talk me into leaving?
You're a person
who likes her privacy,
working for a man
who needs to know everything.
You're a person
who cares about her patients,
working for a man
who cares about games.
I hear him.
Neither sleet, nor mail,
nor dread of night.
Hold on.
Malaria's not contagious.
Children, I bid you good night.
Which one of you guys
sapped my powers?
Was it you?
Did you take my powers?
Or maybe it was you.
Well, no matter. See, I'm feeling
stronger already.
It's okay. It's okay.
He's okay.
Respiration's good.
Pulse is solid.
We need a lot of
nurses in here!
Dr. Cuddy, the face
that launched a thousand long faces.
Get control of your patient.
Strap him to the bed
if you have to.
I wanna keep all four.
You can have two.
You don't get
negotiation, do you?
I say four, you say three.
We finally settle on three-and-a-half,
which would be
good news for Taub.
You don't want four.
You don't want three.
But if I say three,
you get to keep playing your game.
Who would you pick?
Are you asking my opinion?
If you have any absolute truths,
that would be even better.
You never want my advice.
You spend your life
trying to avoid my advice.
You're
a bureaucratic nightmare,
you're a chronic
pain in the ass,
and you're
a second-rate doctor at best.
Am I blushing?
But you do know this stuff.
Can we get this over with?
Taub and Kutner.
Taub will stand up to you. You won't
like him, but you'll respect him.
Kutner shares
your philosophy of medicine.
God knows I don't
need two of you,
but he will actually help you.
It's not malaria,
the blood work is negative.
But we did find the reason for the DIC.
Bad blood fragments.
So if we can figure
out how they got there...
Blood exposure during sex?
Haemolysis
from the malaria meds?
Stop guessing,
you'll spoil the surprise.
If you're looking
to get information out of the guy,
he's not exactly
the bare-your-soul type.
Hey, I was wondering if you guys know
The Girl from Ipanema?
- What are you doing?
- Nothing. What are you doing?
That's mine, man.
You're gonna be
denying that in a second.
Next time make sure you bring enough
for the whole class.
He's been sharing
needles with this guy.
Means he injected this guy's blood,
his own blood attacked it,
chewed it up,
those were the fragments we found.
So, DIC was nothing?
We're back to bloody vomit,
and his two dozen other drug
or non-drug symptoms.
Re-check everything.
Throw these guys out
and strap the patient down.
House!
Respiratory failure.
Good news for you, Thirteen.
'Cause that is
definitely not drugs.
The blood clots
were drug related.
Coughing up blood and the respiratory
arrests are still on the table.
Inhalants?
If I wanted or needed
your drug diagnosis,
I would have told
Foreman where we are.
He knows where we are.
'Cause he followed you!
- I followed Taub.
- I followed her.
He had a bleeding problem.
That could cause respiratory arrest.
Again, if I wanted to forgive
his Drano drinking ways,
I wouldn't ignore
what you just said.
Could be an infection.
- No, lumbar puncture's clear.
- What lumbar puncture?
You didn't authorize that test.
True, and yet here
I am with the results.
Thirteen thought it was
bacterial meningitis.
And I had the eyeball.
It was a harmless test.
Patient's welfare still counts
for something, doesn't it?
Yep. Minus 50.
Chronic pulmonary embolisms
would explain the breathing problem
and the blood
coming from his lungs.
- I'll run an ultrasound...
- You're not running any tests.
He knows it's not PEs,
the guy's d-dimer's normal.
That doesn't always rule out...
You go in to run one test,
run eight more like she did,
find out which one's right,
then comes back with a brilliant guess.
- Is this true?
- No.
That's too bad, 'cause that would have
earned you 40 points for cleverness.
Points go to Amber.
Foreman, you run the test.
Sure, anything I can do
to help your game.
- He's not gonna run the tests.
- No. I don't think so.
So, what's wrong with me?
You mean, besides your music?
Oh, sure. Just because I don't play
your kind of music,
it's not music, right?
Yeah, I resent you
'cause you're not Perry Como.
Look I don't play
for an audience, okay?
Well, then, that stage
you stand on is an odd choice.
I just... I do it for me, okay?
I don't do it for you.
There are three choices
in this life.
Be good, get good or give up.
You've gone for column D. Why?
Simple answer is if you don't try,
you can't fail.
Are you really that simple?
Look, yeah, some people,
they like my music.
Most people can't stand it.
But they just sort of
just shrug and ignore me.
But a few, they feel
like they have to tell me
what I'm screwing up,
you know, what I'm wasting.
Why do they care?
You have some peculiar masses
near your heart.
Peculiar, how?
Well, unlike your music, they elicit
some emotional response.
That's odd.
You care
if I appreciate your music,
but you don't care
if you live or die.
Maybe the answer
is that simple.
I can't apologize
enough, to you, to your family.
There may not be any technical
liability here but...
You're ripping it up
because you think
it would be wrong
to take money from me?
I think it would be wrong
to take so little money from you.
You're out $6,000...
You ruined my life.
I ruined three months.
For the first time in my life,
I was living in the present,
'cause that's all there was.
You're suing me, not for the wrong
diagnosis, but for the right one?
Have you spoken to a lawyer?
You gave me happiness,
and then you took it away.
Definitely no emboli.
It's pretty fuzzy.
Hey, for point and shoot,
I thought I did okay.
It's fuzzy
'cause he was still shaking,
'cause he was coming down
from the heroin.
Where is everybody else?
Clinic's been quarantined.
Patient came in with
avian flu-like symptoms,
and 50 extra dollars
in spending money.
Can you do this echo again?
Okay, minus five
for ingratitude.
No "Thank you, Dr. House."
No "Here's a bottle of Codeine"
"for your troubles,
Dr. House." Oh, no.
I was asking
if you could do it again
after giving him
a sedative to keep him still.
I could. We'd definitely
get the answer,
but since the opiates would decrease
his respiratory drive,
and he already
can barely breathe,
minus 10 for asking me
to kill the patient.
What if it's
a congenital defect,
an anomalous
vessel on his heart?
You know that the heart
does the blood stuff, right?
And the lungs do the breathing?
If the vessel wrapped
around his trachea.
What do you want me to do?
MRA.
So you can get a clear picture
of that vessel.
What? Wait, what? What? Why?
You said the picture sucked
because the patient was shaking.
MRA will be worse.
We have to get a picture.
You were doing better
before you had a good idea.
How can we see it
if we don't take a picture?
You can see me, right?
We wanna look at his heart
with our eyes.
So, I kill the patient
on my operating table,
you get to keep
testing your team,
and I take the heat from Cuddy.
If it goes that way, yeah,
that'd be excellent.
His respiratory status
is through the floor.
If there's a vessel
and we don't remove it fast,
best case,
he's on a ventilator for life.
Granted, it'll be a short one.
Who do you think I should hire?
You want me to tell you
in front of him?
Well, it'd be rude
to ask him to leave now.
If you don't do the surgery,
the patient will die.
You'll have had
nothing to do with it,
and everyone will know
that you had nothing to do with it.
And everyone will know
that it's because
you were pissed off
at House for firing you.
You know that's not
why I'm saying no.
Yeah, but that's how
it's gonna play out.
Keep him and Amber.
You'll get stuff done.
Prep him for surgery.
This isn't an anomalous vessel.
Look at these lymph nodes.
Way too big.
They're the masses you saw.
70 over 40. He's crashing.
Two units of PRBCs.
Starting dopamine.
We're losing him!
So, how's your game going?
It's not whether
you win or lose.
Respiratory failure
and large lymph nodes.
Whatever this is, he's not gonna be
breathing much longer.
Does Foreman being here
means the game's over?
It means the patient's life
is almost over.
You can call it what you want.
We're done, people. Come on!
I need ideas. I don't care
who they come from.
Of course you do.
This is still a game.
You're still gonna reward whoever gets
the right idea, punish whoever's wrong.
Hire who you want.
Get this over with.
Thirteen, Kutner.
I'm sorry. Go home.
- Why?
- It doesn't matter.
He just told me that I gotta...
Lungs are stiff, could be ARDS.
You fluid overloaded him.
Anyone's lungs would leak
after that surgery.
- Goodbye.
- Anaphylactic shock.
No sign of bronchospasm.
What if the lymph nodes
are caused by
chronic stimulation
of his immune system?
Impurities in his drugs
could've...
Street drugs are laced
with all kinds of things.
An immune overreaction
would explain everything.
Drug diagnosis.
That's what you're going with?
That firing thing,
it was all a dream.
Go find where he gets his drugs
and what's in them.
And put him on dimercaprol
for heavy metal poisoning.
Competition works.
So, you're not
gonna tell me who sells you drugs?
What does it matter?
You're dying. Does that matter?
Not really.
I'm not an adult.
Never wanted to be.
So, if the choice
is running out
the clock with a walker,
and a bedpan...
You don't regret anything?
Well, there was a lot of drugs,
a lot of drinking,
a lot of fights.
I regret everything else.
You hate me, don't you?
Yeah.
I don't care.
What's it like?
It means you have no regrets.
Kind of
sticks in your head, doesn't it?
This guy's amazing.
There's not one redeeming note.
What sort of a lawyer
tells his client
he's got a case because
he's going to live?
I've heard that not all lawyers
are as ethical as
the ones we see on TV.
I don't think this guy
even has a law degree.
Well, the guys on TV
don't, either.
I think he has
a medical degree.
It directly affects
my bottom line.
If you have less
money to lend...
I'm trying to take
responsibility.
And I'm trying to teach you
that everyone is out for theirs.
You might as well keep yours.
And lend it to you?
You have to control everything.
How come you're going around asking
everyone who you should fire?
I'm asking for input!
I thought you would have
admired the humility.
You like games because
you can control them.
God, I'm gonna put
the record back on.
You like what's interesting,
never mind if it's real or good.
You wanna know
why you offered that guy six grand?
Life just happens,
and that scares the hell out of you.
You think you can cure pain.
You think you can avoid pain.
You think you're responsible
for every failure,
every patient's boring life,
every friend's screwed-up...
You don't wanna
face it any more than my patient does.
Dying's easy. Living's hard.
That can't possibly be
as poignant as it sounded.
Still can't find
the drug source,
but I don't think
that's the problem.
The dimercaprol isn't working,
and Quidd volunteers
at a home for abandoned kids.
Why are you telling me this?
Because his
bass player told me.
Is it medically relevant?
I don't know.
Well, then, why are you...
Stop playing games and do your job.
No.
This time I'm firing
Taub and Amber.
This is a joke, right?
It's only a joke if you come up
with the answer.
It's not really funny
if you don't.
Thirteen and Kutner,
you're fired, too.
- Foreman?
- He's a druggie.
I was never sure
there was a disease in the first place.
So, all we know
is that he's dying.
Who wants to tell the patient?
Fine, I'll get some kid
to go talk to him.
It's the only people
he gets along with anyway.
Are we still fired?
He works with abandoned kids.
Is it medically relevant?
I think so.
I need a brain biopsy.
For the patient.
You two switch.
You wanna drill into
the skull of a patient
who almost died
on the operating table yesterday?
Why are they here?
Because I wouldn't have gotten
the answer without each of them.
You could have just told me.
I want you to feel guilty.
She thinks
the patient's a loser.
the patient's a winner,
just a regular guy
with a regular problem.
He thinks he's gonna be great
once he's all grown up,
and he thinks...
What did you think?
- Autoimmune.
- Right.
Less interesting
but just as important.
- We can't all be right.
- You're all wrong.
My mom always said that two wrongs
don't make a right.
She never said anything
about four wrongs.
I always found that suspicious.
Plain old measles,
constant exposure from
hanging out with
Oliver Twist and his lot.
I assume he's been vaccinated.
Patient's immune system
was shredded with years of drugs.
Early markers of rash and fever
would have been lost
on a druggie.
His immune system overreacted,
which is why
his body went haywire.
That's clever.
You're not doing a biopsy
without neurological symptoms.
If I'm right,
the virus is in his brain.
Wrong course of treatment
could be his last course.
I need a neurological...
He kept swallowing.
Could be neurological,
could be a complex partial seizure.
What did it look like?
Good God, woman,
how much more proof do you need?
If you can induce a seizure,
you can have your biopsy.
Hoes, hum!
We're gonna use
flashing lights.
Noxious stimulation,
it'll irritate your brain.
If there's damage
to your neurons,
it'll trigger a seizure.
That way we can...
I got something
much more noxious.
It's not as commonly used, but sound
can be just as big an irritant.
Now remind me
of your influences here!
'Cause I'm gonna
say Thelonious Monk
and the sound a trash compactor
makes when you crawl inside it.
I don't do it for you.
I do it for me.
What do you think?
Is he seizing or dancing?
Seizing.
Play him the B side,
it's even worse.
Schedule an OR for the biopsy.
See you in the lecture hall.
A little mood music,
build the suspense.
Sounds more folky.
You seriously have no idea
when to shut up, do you?
Amber, please stand.
You didn't call me bitch.
Is that bad?
You played the game
better than anybody else here,
but for the wrong reasons.
Reasons don't matter.
Results are the only thing...
You were wrong.
Twenty years ago, this was recorded
by Jim Moskowitz,
who later became
known as Jimmy Quidd.
Loves kids, apparently has a heart,
perhaps even a soul.
If you're gonna work for me,
you have to be
willing to be wrong, willing to lose.
Because you just did.
You're fired.
Thirteen, please stand.
You just said
I was right about...
He was a drug addict.
Four applicants, two spots.
If I had three, I'd keep you.
Game over.
You're gonna
have to grow old after all.
You've got measles. We're blasting you
with corticosteroids.
What's wrong with you?
I got fired.
Well, what are you doing here?
Trying not to care.
Yeah?
That's not easy.
What the hell did you do?
You told me to hire
Kutner and Taub.
Because I knew you wouldn't.
Oops.
I can't let you hire two men.
Now, that is sexist.
You've already got Foreman.
Is he a dude?
Hire a woman, too.
Hire two women?
You can have the one that
gives a crap about people.
- They both do.
- Right.
Hire Thirteen.
This was your plan all along.
Well, at least
the games are over.
How long have you known me?