The Chinese Water Torture Cell
was invented in 1911 by Harry Houdini.
Nothing like new material.
He was lowered
head-first into the water.
His ankles were locked
and bolted to the top of the tank.
I'm going to need a volunteer.
Ooh! Ooh!
The guy dislocating
his shoulder, right there.
Could you tell the guy
next to you to come up?
Come on, get up there, man.
Get up there, man! Come on!
Come on!
- Hi, have we met before?
- No.
See, if you'd said, "Yes,"
you could've gone back to your seat.
Now, can you vouch for this audience
that this is a glass tank full of water?
- Yeah.
- No, you can't.
You haven't done
anything yet. Come on.
Knock on the glass.
Solid glass. Knock on it.
It's real water, too.
Ilana, splash the guy.
- Does that feel wet to you?
- Yeah.
And you think that proves it's water?
I think we have met.
Do you know the public washroom behind
the truck stop east of Omaha?
- No.
- See, if you'd said, "Yes,"
that would have been so funny.
Hold out your arms for me.
- You've done this before, right?
- No.
Again, two choices
and you went for the unfunny one.
Now, remember. There's only one thing
you've got to be able to do.
Drag a screaming, crying shackled man
out of a tank of water.
Up!
Hey, you can swim, right?
Tell me you can swim!
Yeah.
Two answers, man. Two answers!
Is that part of the act?
I'm new. I think so.
Maybe not.
Get up here!
Aw.
Five eager doctors,
and no sick people.
Let us try and fill
our spare time with a new challenge.
The winner gets immunity...
I've a sick guy.
I saw this magician last night...
The girl's fine.
He didn't really cut her in half.
His heart stopped while he was hanging
upside down in a water tank.
A drowning man's heart stopped?
That is a mystery.
Along with immunity,
the winner gets to nominate two...
He lost consciousness
almost as soon as he hit the water.
You have to leave work at 6:00 p.m.,
but you make time for man dates?
What's the challenge?
Are we not allowed
to be friends?
I'm just hurt. When I asked you
to come see Mamma Mia...
No history of heart disease,
no angina, no...
He's lying.-
About his history?
ER confirmed...
About everything. He's a magician.
That's what they do.
He screwed up the trick, started
drowning and he got a cardiac arrest.
You were talking
about a challenge?
The winner nominates
two of your competitors.
I will fire one of them.
Even if he was drowning,
it would have taken longer to set off
a cardiac incident
without some
underlying problem...
Fine. Go run your tests.
If you're wrong, you're fired.
If I'm right, do I stay?
If I say no, are you going
to let your patient die?
What's the challenge?
We can all applaud the doctor who's
willing to break all the rules.
But the real hero
is the unsung doctor,
toiling in anonymity, because he broke
the rules without getting caught.
I need to know
you have these skills.
I need you
to bring me
the thong of Lisa Cuddy.
Not kidding.
Thong, Cuddy, go-
It's how I got hired.
You're actually
considering this?
If you want to stand on principle,
I really respect you for that.
It's childish, unprofessional
and inappropriate.
The job is not worth it.
We should all beg off, tell him
we failed, no winners, no losers.
Fine.
You're going to do it,
aren't you?
Of course I'm going to do it.
No valvular regurgitation,
no wall motion abnormalities,
no other structural defects.
If you didn't sound so despondent,
I'd say that was good news.
It is for you, not for him.
Notice any heaviness in your legs
the last couple days?
Why isn't it good news for you?
Because if there's nothing wrong
with you, he gets fired.
- Seriously?
- Somewhat seriously. Your legs?
Haven't noticed anything
out of the ordinary.
- Shortness of breath?
- Would it help if I puked?
Pick a card.
- Any tightness in your chest or arms?
- Pick a card.
You don't seem too worried.
Would you please pick a card?
Our boss thinks your cardiac arrest
was just a result
of you accidentally drowning.
Your boss is an idiot.
Put it back. Shuffle them up.
So, then,
why aren't you worried?
Either I'm dying or I'm not.
I mean, I don't want
the ride to be over,
but unless worrying is some new form
of treatment...
- Your card.
- No.
I'm going to prep you
for a transesophageal echo.
You sure you shuffled these?
And I'm going to
need to sedate you.
Might wanna check
your wallet first.
Would you check your wallet?
It's part of the trick.
That's my card.
How did you do that?
Do it again?
- Thought you weren't playing.
- I'm not.
She'll fire you
if she catches you.
I don't think she can fire me
for not trying to steal her panties.
You trying to will them off?
If I had a plan,
the first part would be
not telling you what the plan was.
You haven't touched
that coffee.
Yes, I have.
She can't keep her panties on
if they're wet. We work together.
One wins, protects the other.
Or, I win by myself, and then you try
desperately to convince me to spare you.
Dr. Cuddy!
Dr. Taub, are you okay?
I just tripped. I'm so sorry.
I have some extra time.
Do you need any help in the clinic?
Okay-
We found no apparent cause for the
arrest. TTE and TEE revealed no...
Send the patient home.
You can give him a lift.
We checked for clots,
we checked for...
You're reporting to me because
you're scared to report to House,
because you found nothing,
because this isn't a case.
And you thought
I'd save your ass.
Yeah.
I thought he was sick.
What was I supposed to do?
What about his lungs? Decreased oxygen
saturation leads to heart failure.
- ER didn't find anything.
- ER wasn't looking.
Too busy trying
to keep him alive. Get an MRI.
Clinic.
Yes, can you ask Dr. Cuddy to come
to the nurses' station? Stat.
Right away.
I asked you to get Dr. Cuddy.
Dr. Taub said
she'd be right out.
A fungus in my lungs? How would I even
get something like that?
Well, right now it's just a theory.
We don't even know if...
God, I knew I shouldn't
have done those mushrooms in college.
I'm sure there's no connection.
It was a joke.
You really lose your sense of humor
when your job's on the line.
Sorry. Most dying people
don't really like to...
Not that you're dying.
But a little sick
would be perfect?
Yeah.
My stomach!
Stabbing or throbbing?
Grey Turner's sign.
He's got internal bleeding.
I'll call surgery.
The surgeons have transfused
three units AB positive,
but they're still
looking for the source of the bleed.
No trauma. Could be liver disease,
vitamin K deficiency.
Only thing we know
for sure it's not, nothing.
And we would've noticed
something chronic like liver disease.
It's probably an
intestinal infarct.
No, I got it!
Eau de Cuddy.
No way. How did you get them?
Only one way.
These are not Cuddy's panties.
You don't think that I...
No.
Also, she's wearing
a red bra today.
Like I'm the only
one who noticed.
Means that
the downstairs will match.
Do your research, people.
An intestinal infarct could be linked
to the cardiac arrest.
Hike up your skirt.
That's rude, even for you.
Hike it down then. You're wearing a
black bra. Let's see the underwear.
No!
You two cut a deal.
If you're not cheating,
you're not trying hard enough.
So, you're not
wearing any underwear?
There's a guy bleeding...
Foreman, she's not wearing any
underwear. You used to be more fun.
She's not wearing
any underwear, big deal.
When she stops wearing clothes, then we
can drop the medical stuff.
Let me see the MRI film.
We didn't get any images.
He started screaming
as soon as I turned it on.
Define soon.
I didn't even get
a chance to sit down.
You guys ever wonder
how he was going
to get out of that water tank?
You, come.
Lacerations in his digestive tract
and his spleen is shredded.
Ladies and gentlemen,
I have nothing in my hands,
nothing up my sleeve.
I do have something
in my pants,
but it's not going to help
with this particular trick.
Watch closely.
- How you been?
- Fine, 'til now.
Ta-da!
Now, you disappear.
Look familiar?
The MRI's magnet ripped this through
your intestine into your spleen.
Forgot about that,
on account of almost dying.
Where's Dr. Kutner?
He's no longer on your case.
'Cause there's nothing
wrong with you.
I didn't screw up that trick.
Everything that's happened
can be explained
by you being forgetful
and incompetent.
You screwed up,
you passed out...
Know my favorite time to lie?
When my life hangs in the balance.
Your life doesn't
hang in the balance.
You know your life
doesn't hang in the balance.
Your reputation might hang...
You ever do magic as a kid?
You seem like the type.
Lonely, obsessive...
I outgrew it. You?
Pick a card?
Too much trouble.
Can I just pick my nose?
I am not a hack.
I tell you how it's done,
will you go home?
Guess you're going to
make it magically appear in my wallet...
You are a hack.
I don't screw up.
Nosebleed that major
means he's actually sick.
Means the cardiac arrest
was a symptom.
Stop gloating.
I'm not gloating.
Then what's that smirk?
No smirk, it's just how I look.
What about
the underwear challenge?
I declare it
officially on hold.
Not really fair, but I get it.
It's Cuddy's.
Pull down your pants.
You think I'm lying?
No, I want to give you a reward.
Yes, I think you're lying.
Cardiac arrest
plus nosebleed. Go.
Patient has no significant family
history, no angina, no prior attacks.
What if isn't his heart?
What if it's
the vessels around his heart?
Polyarteritis nodosa causes cardiac
symptoms and hypertension,
which makes his nose bleed.
You know what else makes your nose bleed
and your heart race? Cocaine.
Guy works in
a B-list nightclub in Atlantic City.
He's got to be taking
regular rolls in the snow.
You, take the gloater
to the patient's drug den.
Make sure you pat down
his pockets before you leave.
You and Big Love, biopsy a blood vessel
from around the heart.
Test for polyarteritis nodosa.
You, in my office.
Those aren't my panties.
I know.
Hypothetical.
A young woman does something
clumsy in public,
and instead of laughing it off, she gets
irrationally upset. Explain.
Maybe she's clumsy
'cause she's nervous
'cause she forgot
to do her spelling homework.
Well,
in my hypothetical, she's eight.
This girl's not insecure.
Seems more like she's afraid.
Do you have a point, or did you
just get a new book of riddles?
I think you're hiding
a medical condition.
I'm not.
I'm glad we had this talk.
Doctors often try to ignore
their symptoms,
because they
think they can't get sick.
If you've got something going on,
I need you to take care of it.
And I take your
compassion entirely at face value.
It's not compassion. It's self-interest.
I want my team healthy.
It's not
self-interest. It's curiosity.
I dropped a file, House.
I start bleeding from the eyes, I'll be
sure to make an appointment.
Okay-
- Well, found some pot.
- Bag it.
I'm not sure it really
fits the symptoms.
Of course not, but it'd be irresponsible
to leave it here.
- You have a quarter?
- No.
How did Cole get
those panties off Cuddy?
They were never on her.
No way those are hers.
Aha.
Tularemia.
No, he'd have to have rabbits.
True, maybe a tick
jumped from a rabbit
and landed on one of these white,
fluffy alligators.
Then it jumps onto our patient,
transfers the bacteria, causes
pericarditis, explains everything.
What are you giving me?
How'd you do the trick?
If I explain, it becomes mundane.
You lose the actual magic.
What do you mean,
"The actual magic"?
You think you're actually
sawing women in half?
You going to
tell me what's wrong with me or not?
Magic is cool.
Actual magic is oxymoronic.
Might not even be oxy.
You're not going
to tell me unless I tell you?
You got a nurse
to plant the card.
I can't get a nurse
to help me pee.
You got a buddy
to plant the card.
The fun is in not knowing.
The fun is in knowing.
My head.
Oh, I've got a headache.
How bad? Is it new?
It's not too bad.
I'll just take one
of these Vicodin.
You eat a lot of beets,
you have an electric toothbrush
and you sleep less
than six hours a night.
That's impressive.
The red betamine from the beets stains
the plaque deposits on your teeth,
which are then swirled
by your spinning toothbrush.
Your heavy lids and
your prematurely aging skin
tell me that you're
carrying a major sleep debt.
That was way cooler
before you explained it.
It was meaningless
until I explained it.
People come to my show
because they want a sense of wonder.
They want to experience
something that they can't explain.
If the wonder's gone
when the truth is known,
there never was any wonder.
You have tularemia from your rabbits.
I put you on antibiotics.
You'll be better
in a couple of days.
Sorry to spoil the mystery.
Thank you.
I'll get it.
Oh, my God!
- You're not wearing underwear.
- Of course, I'm...
A skirt that tight,
you got no secrets.
A skirt that tight
I can tell if you got an IUD.
Have you seen Dr. Cole?
No...
- You're blushing.
- I am not.
Look at me.
Oh, my God!
How'd you do it?
So I'm safe?
In this job, yeah. Your crotch,
on the other hand...
How'd you do it?
Prayer, mostly.
Just tell me.
Does Cuddy have her groove back?
It'd be rude of me to discuss.
You handed over her panties.
I don't think gallantry's really
an option at this point.
If I tell you,
then where is the magic?
He passed out. Ultrasound revealed
bleeding around his heart.
We drained 100 cc
before it stopped.
The antibiotics aren't working.
It's obviously not tularemia
or any other infection.
Excuse me, we were talking.
Bleeding around
the heart could mean botched biopsy.
When Cole was looking for...
Why would you accuse the man
who decides your fate
of screwing up?
Those really were her panties?
Cole has traveled
through the forest of crustaceans
and brought us a treasure.
He has earned his reward.
If I could just
get the immunity, I would...
No, Sophie. You can't.
Use whatever criteria you want.
Could be a clotting issue.
If he developed DIC after the surgery,
even a normal biopsy
bleeds out of control.
So, cardiac arrest and DIC.
What's the common denominator?
- Could be cancer.
- We've been looking at his chest
since he got here. It's clean.
So the main mass
is somewhere else.
Throws off a clot, blocks an artery
in his heart, causes the arrest.
Good. Go find out
where he's hiding his cancer.
If you swallowed any more metal
now would be a good time to tell us.
My hands feel kind of numb.
You lost a lot of blood.
I'm going to die.
Everybody gets scared
in the hospital.
You're sick, you feel awful...
No.
This time tomorrow,
I'll be dead.
So, who's going on the block?
He thinks he's dying.
He's probably right.
Tomorrow.
You decide to put me up,
I totally get it.
Nothing personal.
I haven't decided anything.
But you don't like me.
I like you.
There's some
fluid in the lungs.
No masses.
I'm manipulative.
I play the game.
I can be a bitch.
There's a dark spot.
Damage from where
the key ripped through.
You're probably expecting me
to bash the others.
Give examples of how they screwed up.
You know I can. I'm a good doctor.
As good as anybody around here.
Probably better.
And you know that's
the only thing that matters.
What's that?
It's not a tumor, it's another bleed.
This one's in his kidney.
And his thigh. He's bleeding
all over the place.
His timetable may be right on.
It was creepy.
The patient predicted his own death.
Would have been more impressive if he
predicted that he wasn't going to die.
- Of course, that takes longer to prove.
- Could be a symptom.
Sense of impending doom.
Yeah, could be adrenal gland disorders,
blood issues, anaphylaxis...
If you're going to
kiss his ass to protect your ass,
at least wait until
he's had a good idea.
It's a symptom
of him being a charlatan.
He's a second-rate magician
with a mysterious illness.
Why wouldn't
he predict his own death?
If he's wrong, we all forget it.
If he's right, he goes out a legend.
He got scared right
after a transfusion.
Tainted blood has been known
to cause a sense of impending doom.
It could also explain the DIC.
I predict all
your pagers go off right now.
But if it had happened...
Anyone bother looking at his panel?
His immunoglobulin levels are low.
That doesn't tell
us anything specific...
Are you acting stupid because
you know you're safe? Clever.
Low immunoglobulin plus failing heart,
plus fluid in the lungs,
plus internal bleeding
equals amyloidosis.
He's bleeding way
too much for amyloidosis.
Say anything about
his hands or feet feeling weak?
He said his hands felt numb,
but that's explained by the blood loss.
No!
Do not give me credit for that.
Close doesn't count. That's how people
get sucked into this stupidity.
He's seizing.
Somebody stabilize him.
The rest of you pull
his medical records. Go back 10 years.
Look for joint pain, fatigue,
anything associated with amyloidosis.
Mr. Finn,
nod if you can hear me.
You had a grand mal seizure.
We're giving you liquids
and an anticonvulsant.
Just try to rest.
Pulse is dropping.
He's stabilizing.
You're not going to
put me on the block, are you?
I haven't decided who
I'm going to pick.
It's cool.
His legs look swollen to you?
Slight swelling could be renal.
I baby-sat for you.
I decided I'm going to make my decision
based solely on who deserves to be here.
That's admirable,
though stupid.
You shouldn't save the strongest.
You should get rid of the strongest.
Eliminate your competition,
which is definitely not me.
And I'm your friend.
And how you going
to explain to your kid
that I can't take him to the zoo
next week because you got me fired?
Kutner,
he's going to seize again.
Flank pain, his kidneys are shutting
down. Also, Amber's a racist.
You knew they'd get paged?
I noticed a trend.
If nobody does anything,
sick people often gets sicker.
Do you think it's
remotely possible they had sex?
They're both single.
It's still legal in the blue states.
She barely knows him.
You know, in some cultures,
hiring people to steal someone's
underpants is considered wooing.
You should move there, because here
it's just, you know, creepy.
This was no woo.
This was an effective test!
This is beneath my skills.
Kidneys are shutting down.
Led to a sodium deficiency
and caused him to seize.
Kidney failure means
that I was right about amyloidosis.
Except that nothing in his medical
history remotely indicates amyloidosis.
So, kidney failure
proves I'm right about the bad blood.
Bad blood doesn't
explain the heart or the liver.
His major symptoms didn't start
until after we transfused him.
Is cardiac arrest
no longer considered a major symptom?
Not when it's
caused by drowning.
So your new theory is that you were
an idiot to take this case.
Yes. Can I go test
that theory now?
Waste of time. He needs a bone marrow
transplant for the amyloidosis.
You'd have to
irradiate him first.
If they're right
about the blood,
you'd be destroying
his immune system for nothing.
Which could be a good thing.
Does he have a really crappy life?
Go prove I'm right.
Do a subcutaneous fat biopsy.
At least let us eliminate
the bad blood theory.
Check the blood banks
for mismarks and contamination.
You got two hours.
That's completely arbitrary.
No, if I'd said that you've got
three lunar months,
that'd be completely arbitrary.
Two hours is how long
it's going to take Big Love
to finish the biopsy
that you guys can't do,
because you're wasting
two hours checking blood.
- Nine, three!
- Five, all!
Hey, brought you
something from the cafeteria.
It's not a bribe.
This is a bribe.
How much?
$1 million.
$5,000.
- This is so wrong.
- House specifically said
you can use whatever
criteria you want.
I've got money. You need money.
- Hand me that slide.
- Right now, you're earning
what I'm earning,
which is miserable.
I know what school your kid's at.
I know what it costs.
I've seen his picture.
He's going to need braces.
No RBC damage.
Nothing wrong with storage.
I'm going to double-check type
and start cultures.
We still got 32 minutes left.
Time flies.
What have you found?
You're checking up on them.
It means Cole's finished
with the biopsy and it was negative.
Inconclusive.
The fat doesn't always
give you the answer.
You need to biopsy his actual organs,
lungs, kidneys, liver.
We stick another
needle in him, he'll hemorrhage.
Unless we start
treatment for amyloidosis.
Unless it's not amyloidosis.
If he has an infection,
the radiation will kill him.
Show me evidence of infection.
We need more than two hours.
Some of these cultures
will take at least a day to grow.
- He'll be dead in a day.
- Like he predicted.
No, he'll be half a day off.
Would it make you guys feel any better
if I let you argue
with me for three minutes
before I order you
to treat for amyloidosis?
No. Just treat for amyloidosis.
No, don't.
You're playing the Cuddy card?
That's why I'm here.
Amyloidosis was your idea.
I was wrong.
Yeah, me, too.
You were never fun.
Give me the blood.
I'm type AB. Give me the blood.
Whatever's in there
could be killing him.
In where?
How much tainted blood
do you think they keep in here?
How many people
have gotten sick from...
It would have to have
been the first batch, the splenectomy.
That's when
the symptoms started.
Okay, let's transfuse blood
from those donors.
I'll be fine, we'll move on,
treat for amyloidosis.
Fill 'er up!
I have a new theory.
You're not stubborn.
You're not going to get checked because
you already know the answer.
I found an
old picture in your wallet.
Of course you did.
I wasn't snooping.
I needed lunch money.
I figure it's your mom,
except she looks about 32 years old.
Now, the only reason
not to update a photo in 20-odd years,
is she's not talking to you,
which would be interesting,
or she's dead, which would
also be interesting.
She's dead.
So is Grover Cleveland.
Pretty young to
have a dead mom.
Even younger 20 years ago.
I Googled her obituary.
Said she died at New Haven Presbyterian
after a long illness.
Parkinson's?
Huntington's chorea.
I'm sorry.
I'm leaving when
this case is over.
No, you're not.
You don't want
a doctor on your team
who's slowly losing
control of her body and mind.
Huntington's isn't
the only thing that causes tremors.
You think it's
just a coincidence?
I think you're the only
one on the team who drinks decaf.
I've been switching it out
with the regular
ever since you dropped that file.
You're trembling because
you're hopped up on caffeine.
The first file wasn't my fault.
Medical explanation for that is,
people drop things.
I've been walking around
thinking I'm dying.
You are.
You don't know that.
With Huntington's,
it's inevitable.
No, you don't know,
because I don't know.
How could you not get tested?
If your mom had it, it's a 50% chance
you're a bomb waiting to explode.
Not knowing makes me do things
I think I'm scared to do.
Take flying lessons, climb Kilimanjaro,
work for you.
Yeah, 'cause if you knew,
you couldn't do any of those things.
What?
You're sweating.
You're burning up.
House, you're sick.
Could be pneumococcus. That'd
cause chest pain and a stiff neck.
It's not pneumococcus.
Let me check your lymph nodes.
I'm not the patient!
The patient is
the one whose body is shutting down.
I'm having a benign
transfusion reaction.
Pseudomonas would present
as an armpit rash. Take off your shirt.
- You first.
- House, you gotta let us do this.
We can't biopsy him
without bleeding him to death.
You are not biopsying me.
How's your stomach?
Any diarrhea?
The more transfusions you have,
the greater the chance of you reacting.
I've had three in a decade. The fever
will be gone in a couple of hours.
I heard somewhere
that doctors ignore symptoms
because they think
they can't get sick.
You told us to give you the blood
so that you wouldn't...
I am not sick.
Fever is a symptom.
But not of what
the patient has.
My kidneys are working.
I'm not bleeding out of every organ.
Yet.
This is a waste of time,
and it's distracting you
from the actual case.
What's wrong?
The room's spinning.
You Okay?
Dizzy, my mouth just went dry.
Could be a symptom of a...
It's a symptom of narcotics.
Who spiked my...
What'd you drug him with?
Amber's nickname is "Cutthroat Bitch"
and you're pointing at me?
Got the kidney sample.
You're the only one
with nothing to lose.
Could have been you. You don't seem
to care if you get this job or not.
Yeah, I've been here for eight weeks
because my subscription
to Masochism Weekly ran out.
You're the only one who hasn't asked me
not to put them on the block.
You're either going
to pick me or you're not.
You're fair enough
to try to make the right decision,
and arrogant enough that
nothing I can say will change your mind.
I don't want it
to be over, but,
unless worrying about it
is going to make a difference...
I'm going to run some stains.
He'll be less of an ass to you.
Patient dead yet?
No.
It's a little much
for a first date.
Obviously,
you've never dated me.
Feels like you
already got the lung and kidney samples.
Now I just need
a piece of your liver.
Hey, you might want
to use a little bit of lidocaine.
Oh, yeah, I forgot.
Slight pinch!
You drugged me.
Stopped by the lab.
Your mutinous team is starting to worry
about life on Pitcairn Island.
All your biopsies are clean.
Because there's
nothing wrong with me.
Did Foreman finally okay
the amyloidosis treatment?
Patient's scheduled
for irradiation at 9:00.
You risked your life again.
You couldn't be sure
he had amyloidosis.
You can't be sure
that I couldn't be sure.
You did one test.
It was negative.
- Inconclusive.
- Well, then,
by all means, flood your body
with possibly lethal blood.
I usually like to give
the lethal blood to Foreman,
but I'm the only
one who's type AB.
Of course
you're type AB, universal recipient.
You take from everybody.
Of course,
you're type O. Universal donor.
No wonder you're
paying three alimonies.
How do you know
what blood type I am?
I don't.
It just seemed to fit the metaphor.
No, no, no, no.
Did you
test my blood for something?
Why would you
I didn't.
You must have told
me what you were.
Who the hell chats
about their blood type?
You had to have tested me.
There's no reason to ask anyone
their blood type.
You're about to run
out of here, aren't you?
Nurse,
can I have a moment with my patient?
He's due in radiation.
It's too late, he's dying.
Told you.
I'm sorry I doubted you.
It'd be a shame
if your secrets died with you.
Perhaps you've got
that trick written down somewhere.
Or maybe you want to
tell me and I'll write it down for you.
That way you can live on.
I'm taking it with me.
See, that way it stays magic.
You were wrong
about everything.
It was never magic,
and you're not dying.
What's your blood type?
Type A.
What?
Trust me,
it's way cooler to know.
Where's Finn?
Up my sleeve.
It's not amyloidosis.
And his blood's fine.
We just gave him
the wrong type.
Caused the DIC, explains the bleeding,
multi-system failures.
But we tested his blood.
That's because we don't test blood
for type. We test for antibodies.
Because your
body only makes those antibodies
when you actually
have that type of blood.
Well, apparently,
he has one more symptom.
His body's making
an extra antibody, type B.
Combine that with his natural
type A and, presto, change-o,
he magically pulls
blood type AB out of his hat.
- Would you stop that?
- God, yes.
Autoimmune diseases can make antibodies
go haywire, but, still...
It's happened. And apparently,
it's happened again.
I finally have a case of lupus.
Flush him with saline,
transfuse four units, type A
and start him on steroids.
He'll be back
hoodwinking idiots in no time.
Big Love, rise.
Use their power wisely,
my Lord.
I nominate Amber.
Cutthroat Bitch, rise.
You're surprised?
You're everyone's pick.
Next victim.
I nominate.
Kutner.
Now everyone's surprised. Why?
You said I don't
have to justify my picks.
No, I said you
could use whatever criteria you want.
Doesn't mean
I don't wanna know.
He was right about
this being a real case,
he was right about the botched
transfusion and he's your love nugget.
You got no reason to pick him.
But somebody else does.
Kutner's a liability.
He electrocuted himself,
lit a patient on fire,
it's only a matter of time
before he burns the hospital down.
You made a deal with Cuddy.
That's how you
got her underwear.
She sold it to you for the right
to put her choices on the block.
You said get
her underwear. I got it.
Your scheme was brilliant,
and you're fired.
You're all about
breaking the rules.
Her rules, not mine.
The whole point
of this was to subvert Cuddy.
You became her partner,
gave her power she didn't already have.
Let her greedy fingers
into my cookie jar,
which sadly
is not as dirty as it sounds.
Thanks for playing.
What the hell is this?
Looks like an envelope with
the results of a genetic test
for Huntington's inside.
Did you look?
I thought it'd be fun
to find out together.
I don't want to know.
No, you're afraid to know.
I might die. So could you.
You could get hit by a bus tomorrow.
The only difference is you don't have to
know about it today. So why should I?
I don't have to know
the lottery numbers,
but if someone offered them to me,
I'd take them.
You spend your whole life
looking for answers,
because you think the next answer
will change something.
Maybe make you
a little less miserable.
And you know that when you run out
of questions
you don't just
run out of answers,
you run out of hope.
Are you glad you know that?