Hi, I'm Chuck. Here's what's
been going on in my life lately.
I'm a little worried about our cover.
I think it's time for us to make love.
I own a deli in the mall and I often think
about meats and cheeses.
You do know we're just spending
the night together for cover, right?
By now, I'd say I'm pretty familiar
with the concept of faking it, so...
You're interested in that Lou girl,
aren't you?
Sarah is my...
- Girlfriend.
- Mm-hm.
You and me,
our thing under the undercover thing...
...is this ever going anywhere?
- No.
- We need to break up.
You know, like fake break up
our pretend relationship.
Hey!
Excuse me, can I get some help?
Four, three, two, one.
- Bingo.
- Hey.
I'm sorry. I'm on a break.
Great news, pal.
I am free this evening for a meal.
I'm thinking about surf and turf.
Half-meatball, half-tuna sub.
Then, boom!
"Call of Duty 4: Modern Warfare. "
- Oh.
- Me and you. Sniper.
On my back, watching me. Oscar Delta.
I would love to,
but I have plans tonight.
Don't sweat it, me too. Slammed.
- What are you and the lady doing?
- Uh, actually, the lady and I are no más.
It's over.
Ah, man, I knew this would happen.
I'm sorry.
Damn it! Women can be so cruel.
You know, as a matter of fact,
I'm the one who did the breaking up.
She just wasn't the right girl for me.
Right girl? Are you out of your mind?
She's the hottest piece we're gonna get.
Listen, I didn't really see a future
for Sarah and I, ultimately.
And so I didn't wanna waste
any more time.
Beg for her back, Charles.
Go.
- Yeah.
- Yeah?
What's going on in there?
Uh, just a little thing
I call Operation Devastation.
Explain.
Okay.
My boy is about to dump
the wiener chick.
- What? No way.
- What? Don't lie, you liar.
I'm not lying. All right, relax.
She wasn't the right girl.
- What?
- Yeah.
Right girl? What does that mean?
Look, Chuck.
I've been thinking about our breakup,
and I'm not so sure it's the best idea.
Miss me already, huh?
Well, just, you know, for the cover.
It makes things easier.
Then I guess your job's gonna be
a little bit harder.
Look, I'm sorry if you thought
there was something between us.
It's very common in these situations
to perceive a connection that isn't there.
Of course. I get it.
It's the old story, you know.
Guy gets supercomputer in his brain...
...beautiful CIA agent
is sent to protect him.
Then she tells him under truth serum
that she's not interested.
I get it. But for me, the emotional
rollercoaster is a little much.
So I think I'd rather find something
a little less common...
...like say, I don't know, a, uh...
A real relationship.
Okay, Chuck, if that's what you want,
then I'm gonna have to sell it.
You okay?
Sarah?
- Heart breaker.
Dream maker.
- Love taker.
- Don't you miss the aroma, Chuck?
Check this out.
Hey, buddy.
Heard about what happened.
Are you okay?
Yeah, I'm fine, Lester.
- Thanks for asking.
- No problem.
Now that you're done with Sarah,
mind if I take a crack at her?
Hey, swing away, champ.
You bet, brother.
Where you going? Don't run from me.
We need to talk about our emotions.
I'm sorry. You're gonna
have to weep without me.
- I got a date.
- What? Get out of here. Already?
Good for you, hot shot.
- With who?
- Just someone I met.
She makes sandwiches. Deli owner.
Okay, hold on a second. A pro?
Sixteen is up.
Yeah, right here.
- Who ordered the capicola?
Right here.
Seventeen.
Thank you.
Hi.
I don't
like the idea of this breakup at all.
- What the hell happened?
- She got dumped.
We decided that it would be best
for Chuck to date a civilian.
It will help secure his cover
in the event that someone IDs me.
- Because she got dumped.
- Let me get this straight.
Some woman comes in
and starts dating the asset...
...and this doesn't strike you
as suspicious?
It's not completely unfeasible.
He is a reasonably charming guy.
I've heard enough.
I wanna know everything about
this woman before she gets too close.
Wait, wait, wait.
Wow, it's, uh... It's been a while
since I've done that.
Ha, ha. Me too.
I think I tweaked my neck.
Well, it, uh, wouldn't be
an official Chuck Bartowski date...
...if the woman didn't leave injured
in some way.
I don't usually do this
on first dates...
...but do you wanna come inside?
Yeah.
I'm about to make you
a very happy man.
Oh, my God.
It's so good.
That is so amazing. Wow.
- Did you really like it?
- Oh.
Oh, like it? Yeah.
Yeah, I like it. I love it. L...
What's wrong?
You don't like it?
- It's the chopped liver, isn't it?
- Huh? What?
What? No, no, I...
No, it's amazing.
It's amazing. You're...
You're amazing. What is, uh...
What is that?
- What?
- The invite thing.
Oh, it's nothing.
Some invitation for a party
at, uh, Club Ares.
Who's Stavros Demetrios?
My ex, he owns the place.
- Why? Do you know him?
- No, not really, no.
Good. You don't want to.
He thought I was dating some guy
and he trashed his car.
- Threatened to kill him. Ha.
- Ha.
The last thing you want
is that lunatic in your head.
Stavros Demetrios.
A handsome playboy.
Owns and operates
a number of L.A. Clubs.
I don't think he's handsome.
He's the son of Yari Demetrios,
the shipping magnate.
What do you mean by playboy?
What kind of intel do we have on that?
What we have is information...
...that a volatile package
is coming to Los Angeles.
The cargo is time-sensitive, which
knowing the Demetrios family ties...
...to the Middle East
could mean a weapon.
Chuck, we need you
to get close to Stavros.
See if you flash on anything related
to the shipment.
What? You want me to get close
to my girlfriend's ex?
How do you want me to do that?
I don't wanna get her involved.
Why don't you
and your girlfriend hit Club Ares?
I hear it's supposed to be all the rage.
- How's my breath?
- Like the ocean.
Aye, aye, captain.
Are you kidding me?
Everybody in this place is scoring.
Chuck's onto his second lady.
What do we got? Nothing.
I don't know about you...
...but I intend to make the most
out of the seeds I've been planting.
What are you talking about?
I'm gonna tag Anna.
Are you kidding? You make me sick.
I'd rather get with Morgan.
- Hey, Larry. What can I get for you?
- Lester.
I wanted to say I was sorry
to hear about you and Chuck.
And if you needed someone to talk to,
I'm here for you.
That's very sweet. Thank you.
Wanna catch a movie? Grab a bite?
You're asking me out
a day after I broke up with your friend?
All's fair in love and war, Sarah.
- You know what you seem like to me?
- Mm?
A man who knows what he wants.
Sure, you know,
we could go through all the motions.
Coffee, movie, dinner.
Or we could just skip
all of that nonsense...
...and I could just devour you
right here.
Mm. This should hold us.
It's... It's an interesting, uh, thought.
Let me think
about that proposition. L... Oh!
Oops.
Your feet seemed to have slipped...
Is that Jeff, uh, calling me?
I will be right there, Jeff.
I'm just gonna...
What about that movie?
Hey, Lou!
Hi.
Hi. Nice to see you again.
You know, he's a great guy.
Yeah, um, I've had the same opinion
so far too.
It's not an opinion. It's a fact.
Don't hurt him.
Okay. Wasn't planning on it.
Thanks for the heads up, though.
Excuse me?
Hi, do you know
where I could find Chuck?
Ah, the sandwich maker.
- I have heard so much about you.
- Thank you. Ha.
- And I must be...?
- The guy who works at the Buy More?
Close. Morgan Grimes?
Chuck's best friend, soul mate.
- He hasn't mentioned me?
- Sorry.
Probably means he doesn't think
you're gonna be sticking around.
- Ha, ha!
- Hey, here you are.
- I'm glad you two finally met.
- Yeah.
- Hmm. I brought you some lunch.
- Oh, thank you.
Mm, I smell salami.
Black olive tapenade?
Okay. This might actually have a shot
at working out.
Well, Morgan-approval.
That's very big.
I seem to be getting that
from all angles today.
- Just had a moment with your ex.
- Did you?
Yeah, she's, uh... She can be
a little overprotective sometimes.
But speaking of exes, um...
...I was thinking maybe we could go
to that party thing at Ares tonight.
No. You know what?
Trust me, it's a bad plan.
Look, sooner or later
he's gonna find out about me...
...and I'd rather
just make the peace now.
Charming, handsome and brave.
That's a combination I'm not used to.
Yeah. Ha, ha.
It's a little... Little new for me too.
We're only on our second date
and already I'm lying to her.
Relax, it's dating in L.A.
Everyone lies.
We're gonna be tapped into the
club's surveillance. All we need is audio.
This has an RK-7 mini-mike
that works up to 20 feet.
I want you to keep it
as close to Stavros as possible.
Are you kidding?
Are you kidding me with this?
I can't wear this.
This looks ridiculous.
The alternative is
we join you on your date.
Fine.
- Earwig.
- It never stops with you people, does it?
Aren't you forgetting something,
Romeo?
Oh, of course.
Let me guess, this is equipped...
...with some kind of microscopic,
infrared tracking device...
...that determines
her mother's communist affiliations?
No, idiot. It's so you can get laid.
I usually... I'm sorry,
I get more respect at the door.
You know, I come here a lot.
Always here on Monday nights.
And then Tuesdays at Hyde.
I'm on the circuit.
You know, I do my thing. Heh.
- I can't hear a word that you're saying!
- Ha, ha. What's that?
I love this song. Do you wanna dance?
No, I normally, uh, require some social
lubricant before entering a dance floor.
Hello, sweetheart.
Stavros.
Uh, this is Chuck.
Chuck, Stavros.
- Hi.
- Cool pin.
I'd wear mine but I left it in the '80s.
- Ha-ha!
- It's just... Yeah, I kept mine.
Nice to see you.
Whoa, whoa, where are you going?
- Let me buy your new friend a drink.
- No, thanks.
- Um...
Have the drink, Chuck.
- Yeah, maybe... Maybe just one.
- Good, VIP on me.
Ha! Way to own the noobs, Morgan.
Use your deep impact perk.
Don't back-seat perk me.
I know when to use my perks.
I have to tell you...
...I think you're one of the best
"Call of Duty 4" players in the store.
Really?
You know,
I heard what you said to Jeff.
And I think
that you should not fight it anymore.
Just sort of, um, succumb to your
desire, you know, just...
Morgan, what are you doing?
- I thought you wanted me.
- Because I said I prefer you to Jeff?
I'd take Lester over Jeff.
Doesn't mean I'm into that loser.
But you'd take me over Lester, right?
Listen, can you keep this
between me and you, please?
You know, don't tell anybody?
Ah. That's aged 10 years in oak.
Can you taste it, Jack?
Chuck. And, uh, yes,
I think I did taste it.
Although that also could've been
a piece of my liver.
A piec... I love this guy.
He's a charmer.
- Hey, you.
- Hey.
Can I get you something?
Can I get some more wine?
Oh, don't do that, Jack.
You don't wanna get on her bad side.
- Fiery Italian.
- Stavros.
Think I'll tell him
about the trip to Meccano...
...where you threw a lamp at my head?
I still have the scar.
I thought you said
she threw it at your head?
She did.
The scar is from the makeup sex.
She's a tiger. Grr!
Get on with it, Chuck.
- Um...
...so Stavros, uh,
you're in the club game.
Don't worry about it.
- You seem nervous, relax.
- Oh. I'm not.
Ooh, you got a small neck, huh?
- Thank you very much.
- Like a chicken.
He does have a small neck.
Maybe I should go in.
Same bit with you, huh?
- What's that supposed to mean?
- You need me to spell it out?
All right.
You fall for the guys you work with.
First Bryce, now our boy Chuck.
Bryce was a mistake,
and I haven't fallen for Chuck.
Hmm. Yeah, whatever you say.
And just so we're clear, sister:
Not interested.
Have you ever snapped
a chicken's neck, Chuck?
- Can't say that I have.
- It's much easier than you would think.
- That's it, I'm going in.
- Hey.
No. Hey.
Walker!
Chuck...
...isn't that your ex-girlfriend?
Yes, it is. Yes.
Sorry. Uh, she's having
a hard time letting go.
It's happened to me before, a lot.
I better go talk to her.
I'll be right back. I'm so sorry.
I'm sorry. Excuse me. Excuse me.
Hey, what are you doing here?
I wanted to make sure you're okay.
I'm on a...
I'm on a date, okay?
It's just... You're ruining it right now.
I'm fine! I'm fine!
- Just... Just go.
- Okay, fine.
But your girlfriend is leaving.
Excuse me. I'm sorry.
Excuse me, excuse me.
Hey, where are you going?
You've spent the entire night
either with my ex or yours.
This date is over, okay?
I'm out of here.
- Lou, wait.
Excuse me.
No, no. Lou.
Don't go. Don't go. Don't go.
Excuse me.
Casey. Casey, Stavros' father, Yari,
just walked in.
He's heading towards his son.
Get the mike closer.
I need to hear what they're saying.
Chuck, get over there. Now.
Damn it, Chuck.
What are you waiting for?
Okay. Excuse me.
I beg your pardon.
I'm so sorry. Excuse me.
I literally was just in there.
Like, two seconds ago.
Okay, Chuck, this is it.
Get the mike closer.
Okay, you know what? I probably...
I was over there, so I'm gonna...
Thank you.
Four o'clock.
Tomorrow afternoon. San Pedro.
The package is time-sensitive,
so if it expires we are all dead.
Gotcha.
Excuse me. Excuse me. Excuse me.
Lou, wait! Wait, wait, wait!
Great. Great.
Nice work, Chuck.
We know when and where
the package is coming.
Mission accomplished.
How was the date?
Is it me or does our government
never want me to have sex again?
Charles Bartowski, second message.
Look, I totally screwed up.
I'm more than comfortable blaming it
on the alcohol or global warming...
...or my obscure allergy to neon.
But, hey, hopefully, I'll talk to you soon.
Okay, thanks. Bye-bye.
Damn it.
You made me gave her a "bye-bye. "
What? She won't talk to you?
Want us to cut her power?
- Smoke her out?
- Wow. That's very romantic.
Why don't you just club her over
the head and drag her out by her foot?
- I'll handle this one without the NSA.
- You did a good job.
We're going to the docks
to intercept the package.
You need me to go?
Yeah, you know, if crap hits the fan,
we could use you, chicken-neck.
Chuck. Chuck.
- What'd you hear about last night?
- I don't know what you're talking about.
I made a move on Anna,
and she shot me down, so I...
What, Anna? Really?
I didn't know you liked Anna.
What's like got to do with it?
You have a girl, I should have a girl.
Uh, occasionally, on planet Earth...
...men will consider their feelings
for a woman before jumping atop them.
Yeah, she's kind of cute in a freaky,
little tiger-ish kind of way, you know?
That's not my problem, dude.
What if she tells everyone?
I was starting to get some cred here.
Anna is very cool. I'm sure
that your rep is very secure, ese.
No, they're talking about me.
You see this?
I'm ruined, dude.
Okay, you got me. Ha-ha-ha!
Yeah, fun time at my expense.
Look, I tried to kiss Anna.
She dissed me, all right?
I feel like a fool.
Are you happy now?
Morgan, we were laughing about Chuck
getting dumped by the deli girl...
...after he dumped the wiener girl.
Kind of poetic?
You tried to kiss Anna?
- Why?
- Dude, how could you?
I got dibs on Anna.
I'm right here, you disgusting pig.
I realize that this is dangerously close
to bordering on stalker status, but, uh...
Look, I don't really care about that.
Oh, look,
maybe you're calling me right now.
I don't know. Maybe I should hang up
and just give you the chance to...
Okay, okay. Um, so you know,
if you get a sec, you can call me back.
Okay, bye-bye.
Won't call you back?
I, uh...
Yeah, I think her voicemail's broken.
It's very, very common.
I wanted to apologize for last night.
I suppose I jumped the gun a little and
I didn't mean to interfere with your date.
Not sure it qualifies as a date when
you're bugged with CIA microphones...
...and infiltrating an arms importer,
but, hey, I'm new at this.
Well, it's hard to have a real relationship
in this line of work.
Apparently it's hard
to have a fake one as well.
Well, if it's any consolation...
...I never felt like our time together
was work.
Oh, uh, gerber daisies. Lou's favorite.
- How do you know that?
- CIA.
I had them check flower deliveries
to her addresses from the last five years.
Good tip.
Excuse me. I'm so sorry.
Excuse me. I beg your pardon.
I'm so sorry.
Wait. Lou can I talk to you?
Just one second.
I'm busy.
- Who had the parm and proscuitto?
- Me.
There you go.
- Twenty-seven!
- Yo, yo right here.
You wanna talk?
Get a number like everybody else.
Who's got 28?
Twenty-eight. Twenty-eight.
Who's holding 29? Twenty-nine.
- Right here.
Twenty-nine!
- Federal agent! Down on the ground.
Don't move.
Get the bomb squad in here.
Let's go!
Number 43.
Right here.
What do you want?
Forty-four. Who's holding 44?
- Forty-four.
- I have 44. Yes, yes, yes.
Please, I'd like to speak to Lou,
please.
Buddy, it looks like you're gonna
have to take another number.
- Forty five. Who's got 45?
- Right here.
Forty-seven up.
You sure that's a good idea?
Yeah, why not?
Bomb in there, we're all gonna go.
Might as well enjoy a last smoke.
It's all clear.
Agent Casey,
you better take a look at this.
What the hell?
Someone knew we were coming.
Ninety-six? Anybody got 96?
I just wanted to apologize
about last night and explain...
I'm working. You want a sandwich?
- Yeah, I'll take a sandwich.
- Great. What will you have?
- You carry wheat bread?
- We do.
Why don't you grab
a couple slices of that?
Now toss them
and grab the seedless rye.
And while you're at it,
grab some pastrami.
End cut, none of that lean crap.
A man with high cholesterol. Sexy.
- Is that it?
- Oh, I'm just getting warmed up.
- Coleslaw.
- On the side?
- On the top, lather it on.
Swiss?
- Munster.
- Is that it?
After you shut it down and grill it.
This is a hot sandwich, sweetheart.
In the Reuben family.
These are for you.
They were alive at one point.
Gerber daisies, they're my favorite.
I'm sorry if I acted like a jerk
last night. I was really nervous.
Shut up, Chuck.
He had me at pastrami.
Who are these people? How did they
find out about the shipment?
I've no idea.
If anything goes wrong
with this shipment, we are dead.
These people will kill us.
What is coming in
that is so important?
I don't know!
And I don't wanna know.
Our job is to make the delivery,
not ask questions.
Now, you find out who this belongs to
and bring him to me.
Morning, handsome.
Nice work last night.
Hey, lover boy.
- Aah!
Hasn't that mirror suffered enough
already?
I am in the bathroom, okay?
Is there nothing sacred to you people?
Just the right to bear arms.
You two look terrible.
Well, we were up all night
explaining to our bosses...
...why we raided a cargo freighter filled
with air and a surveillance camera.
The tip you gave us
was compromised.
- Someone set us up.
- I think it was your sandwich maker.
Are you kidding me? Lou?
Please, come on.
You guys don't want me to date
for national security reasons, fine.
But I think this is pathetic.
And quite frankly, beneath you, Sarah.
This was taken at the docks
after your date.
I'm sure she has a perfectly reasonable
explanation for this.
Good. Can't wait to hear it.
Keep it. We have plenty more.
Everyone is talking about you
trying to hook up with Anna.
The guys at the Sbarro
even named a pizza after you.
No sauce, no toppings.
Nothing but pure cheese.
It's called "The Loser. "
Mm, let's grab a slice.
I'm ruined.
Chuck, our intel says Lou should
be meeting Stavros behind the club.
You guys are being paranoid.
There's no way Lou's showing up here.
Now you're miked.
Great.
Great. Thanks a lot.
And what will the sandwich police
be doing on this stakeout?
Here we go. We got company.
Oh, my.
Believe us now?
- No. As a matter of fact, I don't.
- Hey, Chuck, wait.
- No, damn it. I'm going after him.
- They have us on tape.
They recognize either one of us,
we blow the whole operation.
Thank you, Stavros.
Oh, my pleasure.
So your friend, Chuck,
where did you meet him?
He works at the Buy More
across from the deli.
I took my phone in to get fixed.
- Why?
- Nothing.
He just seems like a great guy.
I'll be back with the rest.
Well, hello, Lou.
If that is in fact your real name.
Chuck, what are you doing here?
- What are you doing here?
- None of your business.
Were you following me?
- Have you been spying on me?
- Hold on.
Don't try and turn this around on me.
I'm not the one smuggling, you know...
What is this?
Illegal things when my boyfriend...
Is that...? What is that?
Portuguese cured soprasetta.
What'd you think
was gonna be in there?
I, uh, didn't quite know. I just saw you
with Stavros and I suspected the worst.
Right. Well, congratulations,
your suspicions have been confirmed.
- I'm a smuggler. Ooh.
- Shh.
You should keep that down.
Someone will hear you.
I know it's illegal. There's
no additives or preservatives in it.
It takes 10 days to clear customs
and by then, it's gone bad.
Okay? Don't get me started
on that FDA crap.
- I can't hear. I'm going in.
- No, give him a minute.
- Can't go in every time he breaks a nail.
- Just cover the front.
I'm sorry, Lou.
I made a really big mistake.
Looks like I did too.
- Hey, what happened?
- I blew it.
- Again.
Yes, you did, Chuck.
You most definitely blew it.
Why did you come in?
I had the situation under control.
Yeah, I can see that.
Damn it.
So I assume you have a plan
to get us out?
Right now Casey's tracking
your GPS device in your watch.
A SWAT team will be here
any minute.
Yeah. About the watch...
Idiot.
Lou was incriminating herself.
I didn't want her in trouble.
Always the romantic, huh?
- Jealous?
- It was foolish.
Do you think the CIA is interested
in a deli-meat smuggler?
Well, excuse me
if I'm not Mr. Perfect Spy.
We can't all be Bryce Larkin,
now can we?
- Oh, who's jealous now?
- Jealous of you and Bryce? Never.
- Said everything?
- More or less.
Good. Now shut up.
You're sucking up all the air.
Sorry I jammed my tongue
down your throat.
No worries, Morgan.
Look at the lone wolf.
The wolf does it right.
You know, just jumps around
from mate to mate.
Never settles down.
This way, he never gets hurt.
Maybe, but lone wolves
are also lonely.
Food and Drug Administration.
How can I help you?
We know about the illegal meats
you've been importing, miss.
FDA's been running a task force
against the Demetrios family.
You're going down for 10 to 20
in a federal pen.
- For salami?
- For guns.
- Guns?
- Demetrios family's been shipping guns...
...which means, we can nail you
for aiding and abetting terrorists.
Or you can help us.
Uh, what would I have to do?
Give me the dock number where you're
receiving your shipments from Stavros.
Dock 14B, the northwest pier.
Thanks.
By the way, miss.
Your pastrami's delicious.
Time is of the essence,
so I will cut to the chase.
We've a very important delivery
that's about to be picked up.
We need to know
who else knows about it.
- Okay, I'll talk!
- No, Chuck.
We... We know all
about the imported salami.
And... And we're cool with it, man.
The real crime is that it's illegal
to begin with. Honestly.
- There's no need for torture, Yari.
- Ha, ha.
Mr. Bartowski,
I'm not gonna torture you.
Great. Great, we're on the same page.
- I'm gonna torture her.
No. No, no.
We're not on the same page anymore.
Not even the same chapter.
No, no. Please don't.
You killed a whole family
outside of Garava.
You stole their heirlooms.
You sold them except for that watch.
How you know that?
Your name is Vladimir Snell.
Last year you were paid $40,000
to kill a man named Leo Koloff.
You told me we were paid 20.
He's lying.
He'll say anything to get out.
He knows about everyone.
He knows everything.
And you owe me money.
Well, that settles that.
So if you will kindly tell me
who else knows about our shipment.
The package is here.
Berth 19. We got five minutes
until it expires, sir.
All right. Let's go.
We'll just have to kill them.
There's a weapon in the shipment.
Some kind of chemical bomb.
We have to get to it before it blows.
I'll hold the fort.
You go get the bomb, go!
The bomb's at Berth 19. Chuck,
I want you to get far away from here.
- I'm coming with you.
- You're not going near a live bomb.
Do you know how to defuse a bomb?
Do you have an Intersect in your head?
Hey, Chuck! Wait!
Dad, up the stairs. Go!
Go, Dad. Go.
Hey! It's over, Yari, drop the weapon.
Okay, you got me.
It's Tommy. We have a problem.
The package has been intercepted.
We're gonna have to clean things up.
Here, help me out.
Okay. Okay, Intersect.
Flash.
Show me how to do this.
- Did you flash?
- No, nothing.
Come on, come on, come on, baby.
Don't fail me now.
That's enough.
Run, I'll stay to defuse it.
- No, I'm not leaving you here.
- Go. That is an order.
No.
- I said go.
- Oh, I see.
You're gonna shoot me
to prevent me being blown up?
- Great plan.
- Why are you so stubborn?
I consider this a moment of courage.
Don't know where it's coming from.
- You just bring out the worst in me.
- And you in me.
It was nice knowing you.
Well, the good news is we're alive.
And the bad news is that this is kind
of an uncomfortable moment right now.
It's completely comfortable
on my end.
Just saying.
Hey.
Look, I know that you are so sick
of hearing this...
...but I am really sorry
if I've acted like a jerk.
Chuck, I know
who you really work for.
That you're an undercover agent.
How do you...?
Casey from the Food and Drug
Administration came to see me...
...explained that you were an informant.
Right. My cover has been blown.
I'm an agent for the FDA.
Can I ask you a question?
This whole time,
did you ever really like me?
- Honestly?
- Yeah.
Let's try that
for the first time since we met. Ha.
Lou, you are everything
that I'm looking for.
I just can't look right now.
Well, thank you for being honest.
The next time my phone breaks,
I'm going to Large Mart.
- Oh, that... That hurts.
- Ha.
- And the next time you're hungry...
- No, no.
Take it to the Wienerlicious.
I'm really gonna miss
the Chuck Bartowski.
So am I.
Hey, Lou.
Yeah?
- I'm sorry.
- Don't be.
Secret agent or not...
...that was the best kiss
I've had in a long time.
Hey, Morgan. Can I borrow a pen?
He is so whipped.
- Pathetic.
Ridiculous.
Whipped?
Oh, yeah.
I got a girlfriend now, Chuck.
Ha-ha-ha! Anna?
She couldn't resist
my animal magnetism.
I almost feel bad for the kid.
She never stood a chance, you know?
Anyway... Hey!
You and Lou, this Friday,
we'll double date.
- Lou and I broke up.
- What?
You're a free man?
Anna. Hey, listen, it's, uh...
It's Morgan. It's over.
We had a good run,
but the lone wolf has to run free. Okay?
Chuck and Morgan Train is on...
Chuga-chug.... Track. Ha, ha.
Yeah, not really though...
...because I'm gonna get back together
with Sarah, I think.
You couldn't say this
10 seconds ago, huh?
Anna? Honey? Sweetie?
Gotta go.
Whoever shot Yari
was here to pick up this package.
Someone who didn't want Yari
to talk.
It's all clear.
Looks mean, but it's non-lethal.
That timer wasn't a fuse,
it was measuring an oxygen supply.
Captain?
Captain? Decoding completed.
All systems stable...
This is Sarah. Please leave a message.
Hi, it's Chuck.
Of course it's me. It's me. It's Chuck.
Look, I was just wondering
if you wanna go out on a date tonight.
And by date, I mean no GPS,
and no mikes...
...and no chaperones.
It would just be us.
Oh, my God. Bryce.
Didn't I kill him?
I'm thinking
maybe we could hit up Sbarro.
They just named a new pizza
after Morgan, and, uh...
...you know,
I kind of wanted to support him.
So... Okay.
Bye.