Oh, boy. Wait.
Go back, go back, go back.
That is God and a surgeon
working in harmony.
Here comes the schwarma girl.
- Hey.
- Hey, hey, hey.
Here you guys go.
Be careful, it's hot. I don't want
for you to burn your tongue on it.
- Uh...
- Wow, 29 orders this month.
One more and you'll get
a free baba ghanoush.
I'm reaching in my pocket for money,
not for...
Hey, do you have change?
Oh, she's... Did you get it?
- Fellas.
- Oh, boy.
What are you guys doing?
Or have you forgotten about
Big Mike's policy on Mammary Cam?
I don't know what you're talking about,
Chuck.
He doesn't know? So you didn't remove
the offending video from the camcorder...
...and hand it to Lester,
who's now hiding it behind his back?
What? Wow, my feelings are hurt.
Charles, after all these years,
where's the trust, my friend?
In Jeff's sweaty palms,
along with the amateur consumer porn.
- Look...
- Hey, Chuck?
Uh, can I talk to you for a sec?
Move.
Awesome to see you, Devon.
- Yeah. Yeah. What's up?
- All right.
- So, what's on your mind?
- Chuck, I was...
- I was hoping to talk to you about Ellie.
- Yeah?
Yeah, yeah, of course.
Well, you know,
ever since, um, we've been dating...
...I've come to think of you
as that little brother I never had.
- Don't you have two younger brothers?
- Indeed. Indeed.
But you seem like someone who can offer
sage wisdom in confusing times...
...and this is one of those times
I am really confused, bro.
I don't know how to put this into words.
- That's a bug.
- What? What?
Spider? I hate those fuzzy bastards.
I think, uh, no, you got him. He was like:
"Rrr," and then: "Boo!" Gone.
Can you excuse me? I think
I just saw a kid crawling into an oven...
...over in Home Appliances.
Chuck. Chuck, I need you
to drop some knowledge, bro.
Keep moving, Bartowksi.
Nothing to see here.
Not even if I had the time.
You're getting sloppy, Casey. I understand
you have some perverse desire...
...to listen to everybody. But you
really need to be careful hiding your bugs.
What are you lip-smacking about?
I just found this on one of our
product displays...
...and not very well hidden, I might add.
Normally, I'm a fan of your craftsmanship,
if not your methods.
Look, all I'm saying is that something...
...discovered by someone
could spell trouble.
You worry about that supercomputer.
Let me worry about the spy stuff, huh?
Don't you have a hard drive
you can go fix?
Uh-huh, uh-huh. There's best buddy
of mine. Yeah. What's up?
Okay, saw an Infinity Ward
mail in the trash...
...and that means you got a pre-release
demo of the next "Call of Duty" game?
Ah. Yeah, but the last time
I lent you a game sampler...
...it ended up all over the Internet.
This one's gonna stay in my locker.
You can play it when you get
some adult supervision.
Adult sup...? I'm at the age where I should
get my prostate checked annually.
I could be trusted with an advance copy
of the next greatest game on the planet.
- Have you seen Awesome?
- Over by the Home Theater Room.
I think... That's... Really.
Hey. Hey. Sorry about that.
False alarm.
It turned out, anyway, the kid did not
end up defrosting himself as it turns out.
So, uh, what, uh...
What's going on?
This is one of those rare moments
when things are not kosher, Chuck.
Oh, man. This is harder than I thought.
Uh-huh.
Go... Go on. I'm listening.
Right. Well, I've been thinking a lot
about the way things are...
...between me and your sister.
And you're the man in Ellie's family,
so I was wondering...
...can I have your permission?
Can I marry Ellie?
Wow, that... That's quite...
Quite a rock you got there.
- Is that a yes? Dude?
- Yes. Yes. Sorry.
I ju... You kind of... Wah! You know,
you pulled the... Blang, just right in...
- Yes, you have my blessing.
- Thank you. Thank...
It's been in my family for years.
This was my great-grandmother's.
- Ha, ha. Uh, you think she'll like it?
- Like it? She'll... She'll love it.
I'm just not sure she'll be able
to lift her hand anymore.
Oh, one other thing.
Ellie is a bloodhound. If I keep this
in the apartment, she will smell diamond.
Can you hold onto this for a day or so?
Till I figure out how to pop the question.
- I don't think it's actually a good idea...
- Oh, thank you. Oh, ho-ho!
Thank you so much, bro.
Hey, pretty soon
I'm gonna mean that literally.
- There you go.
- All right.
- We have a problem.
- What do you mean?
Chuck found that in the Buy More.
We have a problem.
The bug Chuck found is a GLG-20,
one of the most advanced...
...counter-espionage listening devices
in the CIA arsenal.
- This is a CIA design?
- Ha. Figures.
The GLG-20 uses a low-power transmitter,
in order to avoid detection.
It has a maximum range
of about 20 yards.
Which means there's probably a receiver
hidden somewhere inside the Buy More.
We believe it's recently
become a favorite of the Fulcrum agents.
So you're telling us the secret government
cabal that abducted Bryce Larkin...
...and came within a hair of figuring out
that Chuck's the Intersect...
...is now skulking around the Buy More?
We need you to locate that receiver,
and find the person who planted it.
You have 48 hours.
If you cannot identify
the enemy operative in that time...
...we will have no choice
but to relocate Chuck...
...to a secure
government holding facility.
Bartowski's time as a civilian
may be coming to an end.
For their own safety,
his family may never see him again.
When are these ladies gonna learn?
They don't want someone taking a picture
of their business, put some drawers on.
- Hey, think we should make a run for it?
- You don't run from the cops.
- You look guilty or shot in the back.
- We are guilty.
Shh!
Bring me down and I will cut you.
- So no locks broken? No alarms set off?
- Nope. It's clean.
- Must be an inside job.
- Thought of that.
You think any of these dummies
can mastermind all this?
It's almost always someone
close to the operation.
When I find out who robbed my store
and stole my fish...
...I'm gonna break my foot off
in his behind.
- Oh, my God.
- Shh.
Hey.
What's with the, uh,
police presence outside?
They robbed the Buy More, man.
They took everything.
- They took everything?
- Everything.
Oh, please, God, no.
Please be there. Please be there.
Oh, God.
The ring. They took Ellie's ring.
Oh, my God.
Oh! Oh!
- Hey.
- Chuckles, what's up?
Listen, dude, I figured out
how I'm gonna pop the Q.
The Q? What... What Q? What's a Q?
You know, the Q, the big Q you only ask
once in a lifetime.
Can't say right now, Mom.
Is that your mom?
Tell her that I love that kittens playing
with the yarn sweater that she knitted.
You got it, babe. Ha-ha-ha.
- I'm gonna do it while we're skydiving.
- Really?
Do you think, uh...
Do you think that's a good idea?
Not the first time in the mile-high club,
if you know what I mean.
Yeah, uh...
Listen, skydiving is a little...
A little risky.
- Don't you think? You could drop the ring.
- Whoa, hot call, dude.
Hate to lose my great-granny's ring.
She gave it to me
right before she passed.
You know?
She knew Ellie was the one before I did.
Great, great, okay so...
Just let me know
when you figure something else out.
- Okay.
- But, Devon, um...
- Take your time.
- You got it, brother.
Detective Conway here is convinced
that this is an inside job.
And we intend
to get to the bottom of this.
Bartowski, get over here!
You're a suspect too. You all are.
When that pig talks to you,
look him in the eye and say nothing.
- Zip it.
- Nothing?
Come on, that's incredibly rude, Jeffrey.
- Dead men tell no tales.
- Ha. Stop it. Quit messing around.
Bartowski, where's Casey?
Don't you two usually carpool together?
Yes. Yes, sir, we absolutely do.
But, uh, not today.
Why don't you go find out why his ass
is so tardy?
Someone might find that suspicious.
Sure, I can... I can do that.
I'll just... I just have to make...
What?
- Where are you? Mike's looking for you.
He's gonna be looking for both of us.
Now get down here.
No. Listen to me. I need you, okay?
Someone cleaned out the Buy More.
They took everything,
my sister's ring...
...the one she's supposed to wear
forever.
Awesome is supposed to propose to her,
he trusted me and now it's gone.
Save it for your coffee klatch, Bartowski.
Get down here.
We got bigger fish to fry.
You robbed the Buy More?
We had no choice.
No choice? Out of your mind?
Do you have any idea
what's going on at the store?
That bug you found, it isn't one of ours.
- What bug? Who ours?
The one you found yesterday.
Casey only installed EM-50's.
The one you found was a GLG-20.
It requires a secondary recording device
nearby to collect the data.
- What are you talking about?
- Someone is spying on us.
- What?
- Okay, the bug you found was not ours.
It belongs to an enemy agent,
probably Fulcrum.
They planted it in the Buy More.
- Why?
- They're looking for the Intersect.
They're looking for you.
We found a total of 29 bugs just like it,
but we still haven't found the receiver.
Okay. Okay, well, wow.
Uh, extreme...
Extreme measures, but, uh,
decisive action had to be taken.
Good luck schlepping all this stuff
back to the Buy More.
Uh, I'm gonna get back there
and pretend I don't know.
Got any good tips
for beating a polygraph?
Chuck, wait.
- What?
Oh, duh, yeah. Ha-ha-ha.
Can I get my sister's ring back?
You guys are damn thorough.
You should be concerned
about not making...
Can I talk to you for a second? Hold on.
He can't hear it like that.
He won't process it.
How do you give a man a life sentence
just for being a good guy?
Okay, how about I give it a try, gently?
No, I don't wanna to hear your version
of it and neither does he.
It's a job. How come you gotta
get your lady feelings...?
- It has nothing to do...
- Agent Walker, Major Casey...
...you might wanna take a look at this.
This is a surveillance tape
taken during the robbery.
There's nothing there.
Bad guy disabled the security.
Wait.
Hey, that's Jeff and Lester.
- It's off.
And they are apparently drunk.
It appears they've mistakenly
turned the camera back on.
- Hang on a second, who's that?
That's the spy.
Who's the spy who spies on spies?
Why would a Fulcrum agent
want Big Mike's marlin?
Those two dilweeds interrupted
an actual robbery in progress.
- The receiver's in the fish.
- Marlin, actually.
- You would call it a marlin, right? Yeah.
- Look.
See? There you go. Done.
My job here is done.
So now I'm sure you super-agents
can figure out...
...where the two drunken pinheads
stashed the fish. Marlin. Four-foot marlin.
I'm gonna stick around here
and find my ring.
Hey, Chuck?
Chuck, no ring came up in our inventory.
What do you mean,
"No ring came up in your inventory"?
You robbed the Buy More, didn't you?
What happened to Awesome's ring?
We have some bigger-picture concerns
right now.
What could be possibly be bigger...
...than me ruining the chances
of my sister getting married?
The receiver may contain information
indicating that you're the Intersect.
Say it. Say what you're not saying.
If we don't locate the receiver
in the next 24 hours...
You'll be stored in an bunker for so long
you'll forget what fresh air smells like.
See? That was very gentle.
One, two, three, four.
I declare a thumb war!
Oh! Come on, Jeffrey.
Jeff, Lester,
we gotta talk, it's important.
Here's your problem, Charlie.
Why's your time more valuable than mine?
Oh, he is taking him over the top.
- All right. Okay.
Oh, my thumb.
- Narc.
- Narc, narc.
Narc. Narc. Narc.
- Easy on the shirt, narc.
- Where's the fish?
Fish? What fish?
Okay, we can do this the easy
or the hard way.
Easy way is I shove his foot up your ass.
- What's the hard way?
- I use my foot.
We've seen the surveillance
footage, guys. Okay?
- We know you were here.
- Yeah, right.
Yeah, you two geniuses thought
you were turning the cameras off...
...but instead, you turned them back on.
We won't say anything to Big Mike,
I promise.
Okay.
Whoa, what's happening?
Charles, would you give us
a few minutes, please?
Chuck?
- It was his idea.
- What?!
The whole reason we snuck in
was to get your ass another drink.
- You were getting the shakes.
- Not cool. It's a disease.
You're a disease and you've diseased
us all. Me, Chuck, this guy.
- Calm down. Calm down.
- Okay.
Look, Jeff,
I totally understand your plight.
We sympathize with you, okay?
And we don't judge.
Just tell us, what exactly happened?
We were across the street at Bennigan's
and I got cut off again...
Jeff. Ha, ha.
If you're gonna tell the story,
please, don't butcher it.
We were at Benni's,
enjoying the deep-fried sampler...
...and we decided
to come back to the store...
...for a nightcap
in the boss man's private stash.
It's off. Rock 'n' roll.
We have the store to ourselves.
We should take off all our clothes.
Don't make me uncomfortable
to be alone with you.
- Go get it.
- Bingo.
Yes.
No.
- No, no, no.
- Jeffrey.
This is a wasted mission now.
It's a wasted mission.
We've gotta do something exciting, man.
We can burn it down.
I was thinking more along the lines
of a fishing expedition.
And that, friends, is the story
of the missing marlin.
And where is the marlin now?
Ah, I'm afraid I'm going to need
a little compensation.
- At Chuck's. We took it to Chuck's pad.
- What? My apartment? Why?
We didn't want to get busted
with Big Mike's fish.
I'm gonna need lotion.
We're pursuing the receiver.
We've the location and it
shouldn't be long before recovery.
Stay with the receiver.
In the meantime,
we've decided to extract Chuck.
What? But we don't know
he's in danger.
There's a chance the identity
of the Intersect has been compromised.
We have to err on the side of caution.
But you promised we had 48 hours.
You know the game, Agent Walker.
The order has gone out.
Chuck is coming in.
Come on.
Chuck, you're looking for a marlin.
Hey, hey, whoa! Whoa, stop, stop.
I seriously doubt that these geniuses
had time to re-upholster the couch.
Well, it's gotta be here somewhere.
Chuck?
- Hey, sis.
- John.
- Hi.
- What are you two up to?
- What's going on?
- I'll clean it up later.
- We're looking for something.
- What is it?
Whatever you want to talk about is not
as important as what we're looking for.
Okay. What are you looking for?
- A stuffed fish.
- A fish?
Marlin, about four feet long,
got a spear-like nose.
- And a mouth.
- Yeah.
Okay, Chuck, I get it.
Besides, if anything really important
were going on...
...you have people in your life
you can talk to about it.
- Hey, Ellie, wait.
What?
Oh.
I love you. Just in case.
Just in case of what?
Uh...
Just in...
Just in case I can't find the fish.
I suppose you haven't talked to Morgan.
No. Why?
Because he left here last night
with a four-foot long marlin.
He's mine.
And you know nothing
about the stolen merchandise?
- No, sir. Officer. Detective.
- Where's my fish, Grimes?
- Mr. Tucker, please.
- The merchandise is insured.
That fish cost me 200 bucks on eBay.
Wait, you bought that fish?
Ha-ha-ha!
- That will be all, Mr. Grimes.
- What did you do for bait, PayPal?
Grimes, out.
- All right. Yes, sir.
- You cracked, didn't you?
You are so weak. So weak.
How am I weak?
I didn't say anything.
- How am I to believe that?
- Bartowski! You're up.
You go. I got the scraggly troll.
L... I did not rob the store.
Did I ask you that?
Already he's talking about stolen goods.
- Might as well admit you did it.
- Please.
Let me handle the investigation.
Now, Mr. Bartowski...
...we believe this was an inside job.
None of these imbeciles could tie shoes
without Bartowski's say-so.
If there's a ringleader, you're looking
at him. Where's my fish, Bartowski?
Okay, start talking.
- From the beginning.
- Okay.
Um, I was born a cesarean section.
I always felt robbed of that headlong
voyage through the uterine canal.
Where's the marlin, moron?
Ah, the elusive fish. Sure.
That's a tale for the ages.
Start talking, or I'll pull each one
of these hairs out of your face...
...one at a time, starting with this one.
Torture?
If you're trying to get me to talk,
you are using the wrong tactic, brother.
Really? What's the right tactic?
My own personal kryptonite: Grape soda.
On the rocks, please.
Conway.
- Excuse me, I have to take this.
- I got this.
Ah.
You don't wanna talk, Bartowski?
We'll just have to
turn the heat up on you.
Mm, mm.
There we go.
Ahh. Proper.
So it all started
with the next "Call of Duty" game.
I don't really consider it
stealing since I see Chuck and I...
...more as life partners,
and therefore community property.
Using my own personal entrance...
...I went into Chuck's room
to play the game.
Yes.
And when I reached into the bag,
I discovered...
I found a...
I can't go on.
- This is just getting a little personal.
- All right, new tactic.
Finish the story
or I put your head through the wall.
Okay, someone wasn't
hugged enough as a child.
Ugh.
- That's horrible.
- It's better on the rocks, that's why I...
Anyway, there I was...
...staring at the most horrific object
the world has ever seen.
No!
What? Morgan?
You scared me to death.
What is wrong with you?
No, no, no. No, it's Chuck.
- What is it? What happened?
- We've lost him, Ell.
We've lost him forever.
L... You better sit down.
Um...
I don't know how to say this.
He's gone.
Morgan, what are you talking about?
I'm talking about this.
Chuck's gonna propose to Sarah.
That's pretty much the whole story.
More or less.
Ellie and I bonded over the fact...
...that he didn't include us
in this life decision.
But, hey, who cares, you know?
He's got you now, so...
What does that have to do with the fish?
Fish? Who cares about the fish, John?
Chuck's getting married.
Pitas are here.
Hey, hey.
Hey. Hey.
You had 29 deliveries
so I dropped in...
...your free baba ghanoush.
- Really?
Twenty-nine deliveries, 29 bugs.
Wait a second.
Oh, lunch.
Thank you.
- Hey, buddy.
- I smell falafel.
- Of course you do.
Come on.
- Come on.
- I'm just gonna finish...
You're gonna finish the story.
Back to the story.
Whoa!
"Boobies. "
Jackpot.
Got you.
Good thing Jeff and Lester are pervs.
I can see you're sweating it.
So you ready to tell us
what happened here last night?
I'm telling you, guys, I have no idea.
Fine. There's other ways
to make you talk.
Time to send you back...
...to gen pop.
He sung like a canary.
Thanks for the info, Chuck.
- John Casey, you're next.
- One sec.
What, can't fit the police
into your social schedule?
Get in here now
or you and I are taking a trip downtown.
You have a second, Mr. Casey?
We'd appreciate it.
I can't believe you told Casey
you put the marlin in Chuck's room.
What?
Don't worry, I moved it to the freezer
at the Wienerlicious.
- Wow. I'm impressed.
Thank you.
- Bye.
Whoa. Where you going?
Where you going? Where you going,
Lizzie? Lizzie? Where is she going?
- Can I help you?
- Yeah.
I was wondering if I could get something
out of your freezer.
Oh, uh, I'm sorry.
It's a company policy.
The kitchen is usually off-limits
for non-employees.
Okay, then I'll have to use
my special pass.
You're not a hot-dog maker.
Bring it on, pita girl.
We're closed!
Where's the fish?
- We need to talk. It's an emergency.
- Listen, no. Hey.
Chuck. Chuck, it's okay, man.
I know about you and Sarah.
Man, and how she's more
than just your girlfriend.
What?
Morgan, stay.
Aah! Stay.
- Hello.
- After careful consideration...
...of all potential proposals,
I have made a decision.
Oh. Let me guess. Naked 2-K run?
Dinner, Chuck.
Romantic, candlelit dinner.
- Just the two of us.
- Wow, good.
The coup de grâce:
Molten lava cake
with a two-carat diamond ring filling.
Ellie will really love that.
Devon, just promise me you'll take care
of my sister if anything were to happen.
What's gonna happen?
Oh, hey. Cake hits the oven in two hours.
Don't be late.
What am I gonna do?
You can do nothing.
You didn't give Sarah the ring yet. Dude,
there's time to call this whole thing off.
Sarah, ring?
Yeah, the ring you got Sarah.
The one I kind of took out of your locker.
You mean...
...the ring that Awesome got for Ellie.
Oh, thank God, man. Are you kidding?
- I thought I lost you, pal. L...
- Morgan...
...where is the ring?
It's kind of complicated, but...
In the freezer at Wienerlicious. I put it in
Big Mike's marlin. Was gonna put it back.
Ow.
Slide it to me.
Now.
Hey.
No, no, no.
No, no, no!
Help! Help me!
Sarah?
Lizzie's the mole.
She got the receiver, Chuck.
Sarah, it's over.
They're gonna stick me in some cell.
Okay, Chuck, I need you to focus.
We can get Lizzie if you can get me out.
- How?
- I keep a backup piece...
...in the jar of horseradish sauce.
- Who puts horseradish on hot dogs?
- Chuck.
Got it, right. Hide it someplace
nobody would look. Good. Right. Okay.
Oh! Oh!
I got it. Okay.
Okay, now shoot the lock.
Um, look, Sarah,
I've never really fired a gun...
...and I've actually done this on purpose
to avoid shooting myself or others.
Just shoot the lock,
or I will shoot you when I get out of here.
Okay.
Get back. Ready? Get back.
One...
...two...
Take the safety off first.
One... One sec... Just a little problem.
Bartowski.
Big Mike told me I'd find you here.
- Drop the gun now!
No, no, no. No need to shoot.
That's not my gun. My girlfriend
is in the freezer. Let her out...
...she can explain.
- Let's go.
- She's right... Okay. Okay.
- Come on, move.
- Just look in the freezer.
Nice try.
Please, just look in the freezer.
She's right there.
Aren't you taking this a little seriously?
Where is Big Mike's fish?
What are you now, huh?
Big man's personal gestapo? Come on.
You can't break me, fool.
At the Wienerlicious.
Help!
- Casey.
- Sarah.
Stand back.
The delivery girl is the mole.
The detective took Chuck.
Where are you, Chuck? I need the ring.
This is not awesome.
I have the package, HQ.
This is Long Shore.
You're not a cop.
We've identified the enemy agent.
She was posing
as a Pita Parlor delivery girl.
Code name: Lizzie.
So she escaped with the receiver?
Yes, but she made a call.
We're tracing the cell signature
and we can triangulate her location.
- We just need more time.
- As soon as you locate her, take her out.
Uh, one of us needs to get Chuck
out of police custody.
- He was arrested just...
- The Intersect is no longer your concern.
L... I don't understand.
Detective Conway is CIA.
Chuck is on his way
to the extraction point right now.
We've decided to transfer him
to lockdown immediately.
Is there a problem?
Uh, no. No. I just thought
I would handle his transfer.
Forget about Chuck, Agent Walker.
Focus on catching that Fulcrum agent.
We're on it.
We, meaning I go get Lizzie
while you find Chuck.
Well, don't make me change my mind.
So...
...this is it, huh?
Gonna get my own padded cell.
Do I get a bed,
or is my whole room kind of like a bed?
It's not as bad as it sounds.
The underground complex you'll live in has
state-of-the-art security and amenities.
You'll even be allowed outside
to visit controlled locations.
I can't leave without telling Ellie,
a reason for going. What should I say?
Nothing.
It's safer for them if you just disappear.
The package is ready for extraction.
Send in the chopper.
Long Shore!
- Is there a problem?
- Thank God you're here.
I don't wanna go yet. I ca...
Agent Casey is tracking
the Fulcrum mole...
...he should have her in custody soon,
so we can hold off on the Chuck transfer.
If there was a change,
I would have been contacted.
- I have my orders.
- We don't have to. This is a judgment call.
We can hold Chuck here
until we know for sure.
- His cover was blown, he's gone.
- No.
I will take full responsibility.
Chuck is my asset. He's my guy.
Just give us more time, please.
I'd appreciate it. I really would.
Please don't do this.
Okay, you got one minute.
One minute.
- Sarah, I'm not ready to disappear.
- No, I know.
I need you to talk to Ellie...
...and to Morgan and my friends...
...and tell them...
I don't know. Look, if I'm supposed
to be dead, just say something...
...that will make it okay,
that will make them feel all right.
Just make sure they know
how much I love them.
You can do that, right?
Of course you can. You're Sarah.
You can do anything.
Hey, there's a silver lining to this too,
you know?
Because we're not working together
anymore, so we can go on a date.
You can come by my cell
and we can hang out.
And you can tell me
who the president is.
And maybe, uh...
Maybe we can see how we really feel.
Time's up.
Goodbye, Sarah.
Chuck?
I'll save you later.
- Oh!
- Get down.
I listened to the receiver.
She knows.
Do you know how many agents
are looking for Bryce Larkin?
And all this time, the Intersect was here.
Wait until my superiors find out.
Look, what if I surrender and you run?
I'll be in the cell. What's the difference?
- Torture.
- Okay, no surrender.
I only have one question, Chuck.
Who's the ring for?
- She has Ellie's ring.
- Chuck, distract her.
What? How?
Aah!
- Chuck, I'm not gonna go away.
- Okay.
Okay, look, look, look.
You really wanna take me in?
You're gonna have to sweeten the deal
a little for me.
Hey, hey, hey, uh, look.
Look, the CIA,
they're offering me a nice, padded cell...
...real cush. Can you beat that?
I'm a guy who enjoys a good steam.
Can you do...?
Can you do maybe a steam room?
I don't think you're really in a position
to bargain, Chuck. I have two guns.
What do you have?
Me.
Don't break the ring!
Hey! Bartowski, get out of the way.
There's really serious
spy fighting going on.
Get down, Chuck.
Sarah!
Oh!
- I had a feeling that girl was dirty.
Norman.
The power of positive thinking.
This was an amazing night...
...as it always is with...
But sometimes,
I know life isn't always awesome.
What I'm trying to say
is that when things get rough...
...I wanna face them together...
...the good times and the bad.
Oh, oh, oh!
Ladies' feminine products.
That's not good, that's not good.
Are you...? Are you sure
that Lizzie didn't have the ring on her?
When they took her away,
all she had was the receiver.
- Then it's gotta be here.
- You know...
...Chuck, if we can't find it,
we can just replace it.
It was Awesome's great-granny's ring
and it's gonna be my sister's.
Even if it's covered in coffee grounds
and miscellaneous DNA.
I have a ring
and I have the blessing of your brother.
Would you do me the honor of being
my wife, Eleanor Faye Bartowski?
Ah! Hey!
Ha-ha-ha! I found it!
Let's go.
I'm so sorry.
It might be a little dirty.
Wait to go, Chuck. I always knew
you could handle my family jewels.
So to speak.
Uh, when she's sleeping
really hard like that...
...sometimes if you pinch her nose
it'll wake...
Right. I'm gonna... Oh, okay.
Mission accomplished.
I can't believe you pulled it off.
Well, it'll make one hell of a story
at their wedding.
Which I'm never allowed to talk about
under fear of death.
Understood. I have other material.
You wanna?
What, spy? You?
- She looks so happy.
- Yeah, she does.
I couldn't leave them yet.
You don't have to worry about that.
You're safe.
Yeah, safe for now, though.
Right. I mean, they keep getting closer.
Eventually, they're gonna figure out
who I am.
Don't you think you should go in
and congratulate Ellie?
You wanna come in with me?
Oh, it's family time.
I know.
Well, good night.
We can only keep him here for so long.
You realize that, don't you?