There is nothing wrong,
nor will there ever be wrong,
with any Sabre printers.
Case closed.
Michael Scott,
as seen on TV.
I saw you on the news
and I want to pinch your tiny wiener.
Oh, my God.
It's Packer.
Oh! Pac-Man,
I thought you were a girl.
Apparently,
there are allegations
that Sabre printers
can cause a fire.
So, they asked me to give
a statement to the press.
I'm like,
"What? All right."
So, I do it.
It's on TV last night,
and it's in the paper today,
and it's online.
And then I call Froggy 98.7,
their request line.
I talked to the host
about it on the air.
It's like,
"Come on, people, enough."
Everybody,
we are at DEFCON 5.
I am officially the second
most watched clip of the day
on the WBRE news site.
What's number one?
Oh? That teacher who was wrongfully
accused of being a pedophile.
Now, we cannot let
the pedophile win again.
I would like you all to go to the
Web site and watch my clip 11 times.
So, instead of working, you want... Yes.
Okay.
Yes.
Come on.
Get it up. That's what... Let's do it.
Oh! Did you
see this report
that the zoo
got a baby otter?
It's on the same site.
Aw!
It's kissing its mommy.
Please. Michael,
you have to see this.
This is, like,
the cutest thing ever.
Really? A baby otter? Okay,
count me in as "Who cares?"
It's not even that
interesting, the baby otter.
It can't even stand up.
It's trying to stand up.
There he goes.
Howdy.
I hope I'm not
interrupting anything.
Jo, we were
not expecting you.
But you all no doubt
know why I'm here.
No. Turns out our printers are famous.
They're all over
the news.
It's an
interesting story.
Cheap, foreign printers
attacking
innocent Americans.
Well, actually the real
story isn't quite as racy.
But
let's give it a go.
Jo, I think that
I know what happened.
I'm not sure you do,
teddy bear.
Well, now I think
I might not.
Not long ago, we discovered a
defect in one of our printers.
So, we got a software
patch, fixed it right up.
Just like that.
I don't know
how it works.
Just as we
were about to
send out a letter to
our affected customers,
giving them free toner,
and we keep them happy.
But somebody here, they
liked that first story better.
The one where
we lose half our clients
For no damn good reason!
Whoever it was who talked to the
press, just come forward, please.
Jo,
I can assure you it was
no one in this office.
Can you, now?
Absolutely.
Anyone who talked to the
press, please raise your hand.
Put your hand up,
Norma Rae.
If you say anything,
so help me God,
I'll break off the
temples of your glasses
and stick them in
your eye sockets.
So unfair.
Even if I thought that our
printers killed baby seals,
I would not be
a whistleblower.
The Bernards, for generations,
have silenced whistleblowers.
It's how
we made all our money.
Woody Guthrie
wrote a song about us.
Old Mister Bernard
Who have you silenced today?
It's a little form.
Says, "I did not do it."
There is no reason for
anyone here to sign this
because I know everything there
is to know about these people.
I know when
their birthdays are,
I know what their
favorite kind of cake is,
I know what color
streamers they like.
All that's just birthday
information, Michael.
Yes, yes, but it
shows a bigger picture.
Why don't you
come with me?
We'll start out with the
honcho, what d'you say?
Okay.
When Mama was working
as a prison guard,
and something went missing,
she'd ask one question,
"What do we do when we
find the guilty party?"
And if they said,
"Come down on them
"with that swift hammer
of justice," innocent.
A clear conscience
don't need no mercy.
But if they said, "Officer Bessie,
well, they may have had a reason."
Blah, blah, blah, blah...
Well, nine times out of 10,
that's the anus they checked.
So, say we catch
this whistleblower.
What do you think
I should do with them?
We should give them a
one-way ticket to Montego Bay.
Where they keep
all the al-Qaeda.
Uh, that's Guantanamo Bay. Yes.
You put them in jail
for a long time,
you put them in jail
for as long as you can.
Well, I guess we're
all right, Michael.
I want these people to really
pay. I want them to suffer.
I'd prefer it
if they died.
Because it's not right.
Yeah.
Okay.
Hey, Dwight.
Hey, IT guy.
You mind if I get in
there for a second?
Oh, sure thing,
go ahead.
Just...
Dwight, what the hell?
Apache persuasion hold,
that's the hell.
What are you doing
to my computer?
The lawyers are searching our hard
drives for information on the leak.
Thanks a lot, Big Brother.
You're with Big Brother?
Okay, go ahead.
I got nothing to hide.
Wait, are they searching
all our computers?
Yeah.
I already
got to yours, Kev.
No, that's cool.
Sometimes I run.
I'm a runner.
Everybody knows
it was Andy,
and it is not fair for us all to take
the fall for his big, stupid mouth.
Ridiculous, Angela.
And like I'm going to believe
one of his spurned lovers.
Look, he's been complaining about
this for a while. It's not crazy.
Okay, Dwight.
Hold that thought.
I don't want to
waste your time
and I wouldn't
dare waste mine.
I didn't do it.
Now, I don't know
exactly who did it,
but I have a list
right here.
You should fire
the following people.
Well, I'm inclined
to believe you.
Why would I disparage
a company that has
made me rich beyond
my wildest dreams?
Yeah, I noticed
you've had a great year.
Good boy.
You turning that money
into more money?
Are you referring
to alchemy?
I don't like to tell a man
what to do with his money,
but if you ain't
investing in property,
then you're
dumber than a dummy.
I'm not dumb, I'm smart.
Well, buy property.
That's my advice.
Is there something
that you would like to say to me?
About talking to the
press? Uh, I do... No...
I didn't do that. Okay?
Didn't do it.
I don't believe you.
I swear on the graves of my
parents who aren't even dead yet.
That's a little much.
All right, all right.
I don't care.
That's how much, I swear.
Okay, I believe you.
I believe you.
How come no one's
giving Darryl any crap?
He was more bothered
about it than me.
Did you tell anyone
outside of this office
that the printers
were catching on fire?
Yeah, I did.
I was talking to
this girl at a bar.
Oh, no, no, no.
I think she could
sense my sadness.
And I found out too late that
she was a copyeditor at the Trib.
Oh, my God.
Was she cute?
No.
Oh, God, Darryl.
I basically swore up and down
that none of my employees did it.
And then I find out that
one of my best ones did.
And now he's probably
going to get fired for it.
And if that is not poetic
justice, I don't know what is.
Sounds like you were as
blind-sided by this as I was.
Yes.
And we didn't find anything
on your computer.
Good.
Except this.
Wow. This is just a mystery
novel that I've been working on.
I know what it is.
I skimmed the first chapter.
I'm just curious,
why would a man
who hates people
want to have
a relationship with a maid?
I don't know...
The way I look at it,
there's only one
of two reasons.
He knows a secret about her
that she doesn't know herself.
Or he wants to use her services
to mop up after a murder.
Yes.
Write your own damn novel.
It was me.
What was you?
You were the leak?
Okay,
I'm talking to this
woman at day care,
she's telling me all about her amazing
trip to Vietnam. I have nothing.
I tell her our printers
catch on fire spontaneously.
Why'd you do that? Her
husband's a reporter.
Yeah.
So, now everyone hates Andy,
and it's this whole mess,
and I don't know what
to do. Okay, just relax.
Just need to relax.
I could tell Jo,
or I could tell Michael.
This is a very good idea.
This is good.
Let's get all the bad ideas
out now. Flush them out.
You leaked it?
I don't know what to do.
Do I go tell Jo or...
I don't want everyone to
keep blaming the wrong person.
I don't know what
the best plan is, Pam.
Oh, God.
My mind is going
a mile an hour.
That fast?
Two whistleblowers. Two.
I always thought
Darryl and Pam
might get me fired
for something I said.
Yeah?
I weirdly know exactly
what you're saying to me.
So, I'll see you in
Meredith's van in five minutes.
Okay, you didn't need
to actually say that.
I have never seen
so many parking tickets.
All right,
this is just messed up.
No, you know
what's messed up?
This situation all up in
here is what's messed up.
We need to brainstorm,
we need to get out of this.
Brain-hurricane, come on.
Think. What have we got?
Um...
Hey, guys,
sorry I'm late.
We're not going
for yogurt.
It's okay, she's cool.
She also whistle-blew.
Guys, I couldn't help it. It
is so boring where we work.
I mean, it's as interesting
as a morgue.
It might be less interesting
than a morgue.
Hey, hey, it's as
interesting as a morgue.
Of course I'm the leak.
I think I tweeted it.
I can't control
what I say to people.
I spend
the whole day talking.
I mean, I video chat, I skype,
I text, I tweet, I phone, I woof.
Woof is a site that
I'm launching to be
the last word in
social networking.
For just $12.99 a month,
Woof links up
all your
communication portals,
so you are
always within reach.
It's part of the dog pack,
as I call it.
But look, why tell you,
when I can show you?
I just sent myself a woof.
Ryan,
you have a woof on line one.
Thank you, Erin.
Woof!
Okay, here's what we do. I say
we just smash all the computers.
We destroy the evidence.
No evidence, no case.
Wouldn't we get fired for
smashing all the computers?
No, okay, not all the
computers. Just our computers.
That idea sucks. PAM: I don't
think that's a good idea.
Just don't say no.
Mike, you know you don't
have to turn us all in.
All you need is
one scapegoat.
Uh, if you turn me in,
I'm turning in Darryl.
That's just what we need, another
black man in prison, you know?
Nobody's going
to prison. Okay?
All right, Michael, you need
to convince Jo to go easy on us.
And then we'll all confess
once we know our jobs are safe.
Okay, you can
count on me.
Let me give you
a hand.
Ready?
On three.
Oh, shoot. Got it?
Got it.
Dwight Schrute.
The property you're
looking at is in great shape.
By the way, it has a very
spacious basement office.
Basement office?
You mean like a lair?
Hey, Jo.
Michael.
I was thinking about
our little leak problem.
I was up all lunch
thinking about
what we should do
to this individual.
You know what I
think we should do?
We make them come to
work. And we work them,
and we make them sit next to
all the people they screwed over.
And we pay them,
but we make them feel like
they did something really wrong.
The one question I have is, "Do
we give them a Christmas bonus?"
I say yes, it's Christmas,
but right after, they're
back into the thick of it.
Michael Scott.
What do you know?
What?
It doesn't matter
what I know.
If it doesn't matter, then tell me. Why?
Because I wanna deal with it
the way I deal with it.
Well, deal with this.
Empathize with me
for a moment.
I came up here
with a big problem,
and now,
I've got a branch manager
who's giving me
the silent treatment.
Speak to me.
Speak.
Come with me.
What?
Are you leaving? Oh, my. Should
I continue with the investigation?
Are you gonna kill me?
I just need you to come
by later and sign a few forms.
Okay. What time works for you?
Mr. Schrute? What time works?
Cancel it. I want you to make
an offer at 1725 Slough Avenue.
Make them an offer
they can't refuse.
No, on second thought,
lowball them.
Don't call me
till you have it.
But...
Are we going
someplace far away?
I know you said
no questions,
but I have an early dinner
that I need to get to.
With the chief of police.
I'm very relieved
to learn it wasn't you.
All right.
Stan, you're up.
It wasn't me.
What a rich timbre
your voice has.
Okay, I am prepared to
conclude the investigation.
And?
You did it.
What? Based on what?
Just all the evidence. And it
really seems like it was you.
Can we all agree to say
that it was Andy for now
and sit with it,
see how it feels?
All right, sounds good. Okay.
Guys, I think that
seems a little unfair.
I mean, I feel like we don't
definitely know it was Andy.
Yeah, you know? I mean, for all
we know, it could have been Jim.
Really?
Michael.
I have rights.
Let's just talk.
I am not going to
tell you anything.
Honey, you don't seem
like your normal self.
Well, I'm going through a
little bit of a rough patch.
Mama Jo knew
there was something up.
The whole year, actually.
My favorite restaurant closed down. Oh.
I hate that.
And my new favorite
restaurant sucks.
I bought a video camera
last year
and I was looking
at the tapes,
and there were only, like, 12
minutes that I felt was worth taping.
The whole year.
And most of that was just
birds in my condo complex.
What is that?
And I miss Holly.
Who's Holly?
Holly Flax.
From the Nashua branch.
Best HR rep that Dunder
Mifflin has ever seen.
It has not been a blockbuster
year for me financially.
My Blockbuster
stock is down.
I think that
the real question is,
"Who is the whistleblower?"
Just...
I may have heard from an old
client and I may have immediately
started spreading the news to other
clients and potential clients, yeah.
But I'm not here
to talk about that.
I'm here to talk
about Suck it. Suck it...
Gabe, I told you all
about the printers.
I mean,
it could be you, Gabe.
Yes, it's totally obvious.
I mean, that's the point.
I think we all can agree
it's either Gabe or Angela.
It's Angela.
Get her, boys.
Hey, guys.
Sorry to interrupt.
I just wanted to say
goodbye to everyone.
Through Teach For America,
I'm going to go
down to Detroit
and teach inner-city kids
about computers.
Not now. NICK: Yeah,
it's just that my friends
are in the car waiting,
so I thought I'd...
Phyllis, what's
this guy's name again?
I don't know. Is it Shadow or
Garth? It's something weird, I...
My name is Nick.
Okay, well, "Nick,"
we're in a meeting.
Okay, look, I get it, people. I'm the
lame IT guy and everybody hates me.
Hey, listen, man, you
can't take it personally.
You call me "man"?
I just said my name,
just now. Did you
forget it already?
No,
sport.
You guys have 15 parties a
week. You can't learn my name?
Hey, hey, hey, IT guy.
Here's the story, champ.
None of us have spent a lot of
time getting to know you, okay?
We liked the last guy, Sadiq,
because he kept to himself.
And we also thought he
might have been a terrorist.
You know what? I'm going to
leave you with one other thought.
Inner-city kids use computers
for two things, games and porn.
So, good luck
wasting your life, Lurch.
Thank you so much for that.
I saw all of your hard
drives. And guess what?
You're not a photographer. And you
definitely can't fit into a size two.
Darryl, man,
you're on Facebook.
Why have you been telling
people you're not on Facebook?
- People want to be your friend, man.
- Hey.
All right?
And you... This guy.
You're the one
who told the press.
You wrote
an e-mail to the editor.
I saw it and I also
saw a Quicktime movie
of your little printer fire
test on your hard drive.
This guy's the snitch, he's the
snitch. So, that's it. Check it out.
We're going to
believe that guy?
When I was growing up,
there was nothing better than
being a big old business tycoon.
And I thought I'd
break that glass ceiling
and be a hero to all those
little girls out there.
And they'd make
a Barbie out of me.
I hate that
I sell cheap printers.
I do.
But if I have to go out
there in front of the press
and make one of them
public apology recalls,
I mean, that's all I'll
ever be remembered for.
Nobody will want to
play with my Barbie.
Well, you know,
I would be willing,
under the right
circumstances,
to do that for you.
Oh, honey, surely
you don't want that.
I surely do,
and don't call me honey.
Airplane II.
I'm about to buy
this building, you know?
You don't say.
I own a one-eighth share in a
rental property down in Pittston.
Well, I'm one-eighths
proud of you.
Enjoy that chair for now.
'Cause pretty soon you
will be on your feet.
Like Buckingham Palace.
Hey, Phyllis,
have you seen my bag?
You deserve it.
Look, I didn't want
houses and schools
to burn down
and children to die.
Does that make me a hero?
No, it does not.
Well, it doesn't make me the
worst guy in the world, either.
It does!
Andy?
Hey.
I wanted to say that I think it was
very brave of you to go to the press.
Thanks.
Yeah, you know.
Just seemed like
the right thing to do.
Yeah.
"We at Sabre have
betrayed the trust
"that we have built
with our customers.
"We regret our slow response and
our lapse in candor and judgment.
"At this time, we are issuing a full
recall of all Sabre GH400 printers.
"We will not rest until
this problem is solved.
"There will be no questions."
Are there any questions?
Hey, I appreciate you reading that
statement. You looked pretty up there.
That was fun.
I hope your rough patch
ends soon.
Thanks. Today helped.
Well, give a shout
if I can brighten your life.
Okay. Hey, you could transfer
Holly back from Nashua.
Let me see what I can do.