It's estimated
the observable universe
is 93 billion
light years across.
It's probably
more accurate to...
I'm gonna be so far away.
I don't care. I don't
wanna break up.
I'll come on the weekends.
Stanford's on the other
side of the country.
My dad has like 10 million
frequent flier miles.
He won't care.
We all right over there?
Yes, Mr. Damon, I just had
something caught in my throat.
Abby, you know
you're not supposed
to have any food
or drinks in here.
It's just water.
I have a cough,
I didn't want to
disturb anyone.
We can only observe
4% of the universe.
The rest of it
is unaccounted for.
I never knew you were
such a good liar.
Well, a little more vodka and you
might find out some more things
you didn't know about me.
Really?
Nicholas.
Yes, sir.
What conclusions can we draw from
the incredible number of stars?
That the movie's either gonna
be really good or really bad.
I was thinking more about the
implications for extraterrestrial life.
Well, I guess if there's an
infinite number of stars,
odds are there's
at least one galaxy
with life other than our own.
Or?
Or not?
Or our solar system
is somehow unique.
The question then
becomes, in what way?
The question then becomes, could you
possibly teach us anything more useless?
What're you looking at?
Abby?
Oh, my God. Something's wrong!
She's not breathing!
Call 911!
Would you mind at least putting a
napkin under your jelly toast?
Get a table and I won't
eat on the couch.
Yes, you will.
But I won't have a good excuse.
Why don't you go get a table?
It's not my condo.
You have my permission.
Pick out whatever you want.
Then it would be a
reflection of me, not you.
That wouldn't be right.
No, it would be a
reflection of the fact
that the guy who's been
mooching off of me
for as long as I can remember
isn't a complete ingrate.
You've never furnished a home.
I have furnished
a bunch of homes.
No, you've married
a bunch of women
who've furnished
a bunch of homes.
You want to eat off
something, fine,
move your piano in here
and eat off that.
You're afraid.
Of a dining table?
You know, they don't
actually come to life
when you put a knob
off your bedpost on them.
You are what you sit in.
Your friends, your job, your
furnishings, it all defines you.
You don't really believe that.
You just don't want
to do the shopping.
Buy some furniture
or admit that
you're empty inside.
Hmm.
X-rays confirm the fluid that
almost suffocated her to death
was from pulmonary edema.
Means the problem is either
in her heart or lungs.
Tox screen's clean for
everything except the alcohol,
and her BAC was barely .05.
Means she only had
one or two drinks, tops.
And there's no sign of trauma.
How did you know?
Because if there was,
Cuddy wouldn't have needed
me to take the case.
How'd you know Cuddy... Foreman's
the only one with the balls
to take a case without
checking with me
and he's still working on
breakfast, which means that
the 18, no, 17-year-old
honor student...
Cuddy has a soft spot
for smart girls,
and they don't start drinking
until second semester
senior year.
So, either you think that smart
women look out for each other,
which means you're an idiot,
or you think Cuddy's not
smart, which means...
Well, I guess it's
the same both ways.
Then how did you...
Picture fell out of the file.
She looks smart.
Where's Taub?
You don't already know?
Yeah, he's at home
in a fight with his wife.
I'm just curious what
he wanted me to know.
His car has a flat tire.
He's waiting for a tow truck.
What about rising blood
pressure from binge drinking?
It could set off a hypertensive
crisis, cause heart failure.
Two drinks is hardly a binge.
Certainly not if
you're an Aussie,
but when
an American school girl
has two drinks
before 10:00 a.m.,
it's a pretty sure bet that the
plan is to have a lot more.
It probably wasn't the first
time she had that plan.
We'll get a C-13 pyruvate MRI
to check for cardiac
lactic-acid levels.
Someone call Taub.
Tell him to cut the ball
and chain on his own time.
We're arguing
about couples yoga.
No. We're arguing over the fact
that we don't ever do
anything together anymore.
We don't ever do
anything together?
Chris, I love you, but I swear,
if you start talking to me
like I'm on the witness stand
again, I'm gonna break your neck.
Honey, we do stuff
together all the time.
Really? Like what?
And besides sleeping, watching
TV, going out to dinner,
what do we do together,
just the two of us?
We...
You don't like
going out to dinner?
All right, I'll do the yoga.
Forget it.
Now you don't want me to do it?
Just go to work. No.
I'm not leaving
until we work this out.
I'm fine. Please, just go.
Where's Abby Nash?
I'm Nick, her boyfriend.
This is my dad.
Hi.
You can wait in...
Where is she?
Is she okay?
She's having some tests run.
We think her drinking
may have damaged her heart.
Her heart?
No. She doesn't drink.
Not that much.
Just when she's at school?
Nick, what's he talking about?
It was a field trip. One
of the kids had a fake ID.
But, Dad, you know Abby.
Tell him.
I know what she's like when the
two of you are around me, but...
If you're right, the tests
will come back negative.
Can you give her a message?
I brought her homework.
And I love her.
Sorry I'm late.
Nick loves you.
House doesn't believe
you got a flat tire.
What does he think I was doing?
Fighting with the wife.
Why would I lie about that?
She wants me to do yoga.
We need thinner cuts.
When you and Cameron
had disagreements...
I'm probably not the best guy
to go to for marital advice.
Sorry.
It's just... What's that
in the mitral valve?
All right, I get the message.
No. No, I'm serious.
What is that?
Could be a fungus.
ER drew blood cultures.
All negative.
No parasites, no fungus.
Could be fastidious
enteric bacteria.
You think she's been eating
your wife's cooking?
Hey, I'm on your side, man.
I am not fighting with my wife.
I had a flat tire.
It's in my trunk. You can
go look at it if you want.
Don't need to. Face tells
me you're bluffing.
Not yours, Chase's.
If she was infected through
the intestinal tract,
she'd have intestinal symptoms.
There are other ways to get enteric
bacteria into the bloodstream.
She's not an intravenous
drug user, she has no tattoos,
and she doesn't have any scars
that would indicate
she's a cutter.
Transesophageal echo could give us a
better idea of what we're looking at.
If that valve is
about to dehisce,
echo could trigger
a heart attack.
So come up with a better idea,
or have a crash cart ready.
Why are you lying to House?
Chase told me.
What's the big deal?
Maybe we can talk about this
another time. Or never.
I really don't think
she's gonna tell anyone.
If I admit we were fighting,
he's gonna want
to know what about.
So tell him, or tell him
it's none of his business.
This is easier. Really?
Because it seems much harder.
What do I know? I'm not a guy.
Yes, if only I could be as open
about my emotional
life as you are.
It's not about the yoga.
Really? I thought it was, since we
spent an hour talking about yoga,
but what do I know?
I'm not a girl.
My guess is she thinks you don't
want to spend time with her
because you're spending it
with someone else.
If she thinks I'm
cheating, she would ask.
Because you'd tell the truth?
I'm not seeing anyone else.
Doesn't matter.
You have a history.
And that's not her fault.
So what am I supposed to do?
I can't prove a negative.
That is a problem.
There's the heart.
Valves look fine. No vegetations.
No myxomatous changes.
Can you give her
a little more sedative?
She's dissecting.
She's rupturing.
Get the scope out.
This doesn't make sense.
Her BP's normal,
and her heart rate
was controlled.
We'll figure it out later.
We've only got about 30
seconds to get her open.
No leakage from
the cannulation site.
Nice.
Let's see if she'll start up.
Cardiac paddles.
Charging.
And go.
Come on.
Again. Go.
Pushing five cc's adrenaline.
Zap her again. No.
It's not working. Clear.
Clear.
Normal sinus rhythm.
Thank God.
TEE and intra-operative
visualization
showed no vegetations
on the valves,
no structural abnormalities.
The dissection means
we were wrong
about alcohol causing
a hypertensive crisis.
And by "we" you
mean "you." Yeah.
You were the one who didn't
have any better ideas.
It's not my fault. I was
busy trying to judge Taub.
Since we already
ruled out trauma,
the dissection's
probably a genetic defect.
We're running the tests.
She's not marfanoid.
What about an allergy?
A severe enough one could set
off a systemic immune reaction,
cause fluid in the lungs and inflammation
that could weaken the aorta.
If it was an allergy, she'd be getting
better in the hospital, not worse.
Unless it was inside her.
Meaning?
You want my sperm?
We think a severe allergic reaction
could be causing a systemic breakdown.
To my son's sperm?
Actually, his semen is
more likely the problem,
which I realize is not
what you were reacting to.
When's the last time the two
of you had unprotected sex?
Never. I use a condom.
You always use a condom?
For everything?
Well, for most everything.
When?
The night before she collapsed.
I'm placing a drop of Nick's
semen protein onto the skin.
Then I'll abrade it
with a needle,
check for a rash
in an hour or so.
Mom, come on, we've been
dating for three years.
I'm not mad, sweetheart.
I'm just confused.
A systemic reaction can be
triggered by the protein in semen.
In most cases, the
reaction is fairly minor,
but in rare cases,
repeat exposure
can trigger a
hypersensitivity response.
"Repeat exposure"?
I know, I know, three years.
Is this supposed to hurt?
A reaction should
take longer than...
No, it's not that. Ow.
Abby, what's wrong?
My stomach.
Blood in the urine.
Help me!
No allergic reaction.
On the other hand, now
her kidneys are failing.
Could be some
kind of neuropathy.
Syphilitic lightning pains?
It's not syphilis.
VDRL and enzyme
immunoassays were negative.
What about a blood clot?
While she's on anticoagulants
for the aortic surgery?
Interstitial nephritis?
Wouldn't cause the
edema or dissection.
But cancer could.
Would you care to be a
little bit more specific?
If I could, I would've.
We could do a full body scan.
We hate full body scans.
And by "we" you mean "you."
We also hate when
a patient dies
before we figure out
what's wrong with them.
Do the scan.
How can you convince someone
you're not cheating on them?
Don't cheat. After a
while, they'll catch on.
What if I don't want
to wait that long?
Take them with you wherever
you go for 24 hours a day.
So your wife's a little insecure.
Is that so bad?
At least you know
she still cares.
I know she cares. What I
want is for her to be happy.
What? You don't think I
want my wife to be happy?
Sure. As long as
it makes you happy.
What do you think?
I think you work quickly.
Piece of cake. You give them
money, they give you furniture.
Not bad, huh?
Nope, it's not bad at all.
It's taking a really long time.
Just hang in there, and try not to
talk unless you really have to.
It can affect the images.
What was that? Hello,
are you still there?
I think there's something
wrong with the machine.
- It's not the machine.
- It's an earthquake.
Hold on, we'll get you out.
Get me out now.
Oh, my God! I can't hold on!
It's a black hole.
She's hallucinating.
I certainly hope so.
Hallucination
means brain problem.
Brain problems don't
split your aorta.
A vascular problem
could explain both.
Inflammation in
the blood vessel walls
leads to dissection
in the aorta
and could cause an
aneurysm in the brain
that could cause the visions.
It's a bit convoluted,
but brain and heart function
are susceptible, too.
If there was any sign of the
inflammation of the aorta,
that would make sense.
House! That's not funny.
I've got enough
problems already!
Trust me, this is gonna help.
An aneurysm explains
the hallucinations,
and it's the one thing we haven't
excluded from the differential.
Your texting does not
prove you're faithful.
It just proves you know she
thinks you're unfaithful.
You can't force trust.
What did she hallucinate?
The content of the
hallucination isn't relevant.
Not usually.
Not ever.
We know nothing,
brain knows all.
You get an ulcer,
you don't know it,
but the brain increases
mucin secretions.
It knows what the problem is,
it knows where the problem is.
It's a big logical jump
from a body's immune response
to the brain giving
subconscious diagnostic clues.
What about dreaming about
waterfalls, running streams
if you need to go
to the bathroom?
Sure. That's the same as the brain
shouting, "You have pancreatic cancer."
Her subconscious is trying
to tell her something.
We need to eavesdrop.
She was screaming she was being
sucked into a black hole.
So we should look for
a tumor in her anus.
We need the whole story.
A cognitive pattern
recognition program
might tell us what's
going on in her head.
Or we could act on something
based in science,
not science fiction.
Get an MRA with contrast to
see if she has an aneurysm.
Unless you think Cuddy's gonna
go for the mind reading.
Fine. Do the MRA.
When it comes back negative,
we can move on to the
crazy, but possible, ideas.
What did you do
with the furniture?
I returned it.
You told me to buy it.
But you didn't buy it.
You rented it.
You made one phone call
to Economy Furniture Supply.
"We get it done,
so you don't have to."
So what?
We had a table, chairs...
But no clue what
any of it meant.
Fine. I'll hire a decorator.
Perfect. Another woman
to tell you who you are.
I'll hire a male decorator.
Step inside one furniture store
and find one thing you like.
I like not doing this.
One.
Abby.
Hi.
Where's my mom?
She went down to get
some breakfast.
How are you feeling?
Well, besides the fact that I can
barely breathe and I ache all over,
not good.
Anything I can do?
Just don't go.
I'm not going anywhere.
Been a while since we've gone more
than a day without doing that.
I'm not going anywhere.
What'd you say?
I've been thinking...
Been a long time since we went more
than a day without doing that.
We have a secret.
Now, you don't need
to answer right now,
but, Abby, I want to marry you.
Tell him the secret. It's okay.
Something's wrong.
What? Abby, what
are you feeling?
I don't know.
Your secret is killing you.
I see... Maybe it's
all the medication.
I was just...
Abby, can you hear me?
You deserve to die.
I need four milligrams
lorazepam.
She seized for over a minute.
Inner-ictal EEG showed
no synchronous discharges.
And the MRA?
No aneurysms or arterial or venous
malformations in the brain.
As predicted.
What did we say
we'd move on to?
Out of body experiences
can be induced
by sensory overload in the
temporoparietal junction.
Temporoparietal junction
was clean on MRI,
MRA, and whole body scan.
Which just leaves us
with the question of
what happened during the
out of body experience?
If I say her blood pressure shot up
over 200 and she bit her tongue,
would that be
a satisfactory answer?
Sure. If you then went on
to answer the following,
did she float above her body?
Did she see Jesus?
Did she bathe in the Ganges?
No, no and no. Can we get
back to the medical science?
No.
She claims she emerged
from her body
as a younger version of
herself and started talking.
She couldn't remember
what was discussed.
But I'm sure
it wasn't a differential.
House, cognitive
pattern recognition
is 50 years from being
a useful diagnostic tool.
Even if we can get the equipment, it
takes hours for the initial mapping.
If she has another seizure,
she could stroke out.
Coincidentally, she could also
have a stroke if we do nothing.
I'm not telling a mother
who's scared out of her mind
that our best shot
is a magic trick.
It's not magical,
it's experimental.
Just like washing your hands
after pooping once was.
And technically,
it's not our best shot.
I'm pretty sure
it's our only shot.
Perfect. So, Foreman,
go get her consent.
The rest of you, go down
to the cog-sci lab.
The equipment
should already be there.
I'll catch up.
Thanks for the invite.
I am not sure I'm up
for the hospital food.
Good, 'cause I wasn't
planning on lunch.
While you watch video clips,
a computer maps how your
brain processes the images.
How long will it take?
Six hours. But that's
really just the prep.
Once the computer maps how she
processes the information,
we'll put her under
twilight sedation,
use the same equipment to monitor
her unconscious thoughts.
Hopefully, it'll spit
out a very basic video
of whatever's
going on in her head.
And what will that tell you?
Hopefully, it'll give us a clue
as to where your brain
thinks the problem is.
A lot of "hopefullys."
Could it hurt her?
We're at a diagnostic dead end.
We've got to try something.
This is much better than lunch.
I agree.
What made you think of this?
I missed you.
No, I mean this. The car
in the parking lot.
I just don't like feeling like
maybe this isn't the first
time you've done this.
It's the first. I love you.
You know that, right?
Yes.
I want you to be
able to trust me.
And I want to, but...
Inspiration Point doesn't
open till after dark.
Got a real cool magic
show about to start.
Also, I'm gonna need
to check your spare.
Abby, can you think
of something specific?
Like what?
Doesn't matter. Just
make it a single image.
What are you thinking?
About Nick playing baseball.
Holy crap.
That's amazing.
Yeah.
Now all we have to do
is read her subconscious
and hope that it's completely
rational and went to med school.
Does anything get you excited?
Can I help you with something?
Yes.
I was wondering if
you could tell me
a little bit about
this dining table.
It's made of wood
and you eat off it.
So you're paid by commission?
It's furniture.
Find something you like,
let me know, I'll ring it up.
Thank you so much.
Okay, that's... That's not...
That is a remarkable collection,
if I can show it to you.
I'm Gabriella.
I'm really just looking for
a nice dining room table.
I see. You're daring.
Yes, I do that sometimes.
But right now, why am I daring?
You're not
constrained by rules.
What else attracts you
in the patio section?
Wait. This is a patio table?
For outside?
Well, it's taken us
just over an hour
to prove that she has a
very boring subconscious.
Anyone ever tell you you
can be a real buzzkill?
Yes.
Stars. Maybe that's a stripe.
It's the sky.
She's thinking about the moon
and the stars in the sky.
She's going to Stanford
to study physics.
It's not a big revelation that
she'd think about the sky.
Or a star could be a white blood cell.
Leukemia?
Who's that?
Her dad? He died
when she was eight.
What did Daddy die of?
Private plane crash.
No connection.
Stars, moon, sky, white
blood cells, heart valves,
black holes, or anus,
or a million other circular
passageways into the body,
and her dad.
What do you think it means?
She likes school and
she has daddy issues.
Neither of which helps us.
So now what do we do?
Start over?
We obviously missed something.
What about the liver?
What about her left toe?
Oh, sorry,
I thought we were randomly
picking out body parts
that had nothing to
do with her symptoms.
Liver's responsible
for proteins,
immunological effects,
production of red blood cells.
Might be able to explains the
lungs, the hallucinations...
Not the aortic dissection.
Her kidneys are also failing.
Polycystic disease could
explain the dissection.
So, that's one imperfect theory
plus a rare complication
of a second theory,
which gives us a
complete explanation.
Don't polish
the notion, Foreman.
Pineal gland is calcified.
It's supposed to be calcified.
Happens after puberty.
What if it's obscuring a tumor?
It's the only place we
couldn't look inside.
Get a better look
at her pineal gland
with three Tesla
fast-spin echo MRI.
You're pacing my office 'cause
you're buying furniture?
No. I'm pacing your office
because I'm physically
incapable of buying furniture.
For Amber's old place?
Yeah. It needs some new...
I know you bought
the place I wanted.
You're a jerk, let's move on.
Hire a decorator.
I'm supposed to find me.
Backpack through Europe.
I know it's hard to believe,
but you know
what says even more
about who you are
than your furniture?
The fact that
you are letting House
tell you how to buy furniture.
Call Beatrice.
MRI revealed no remarkable
features on her pineal gland,
but there were
slightly elevated levels
of lactate dehydrogenase
isoenzymes.
Which we would expect to see
if there was an allergic
reaction happening.
There's definitely no allergy.
Parasite? There's this
Middle Eastern parasite...
How exactly do you
want to be shot down?
On the basis of the fact
that she's never
been within 6,000 miles
of the Middle East.
Or on the basis of the fact
that all our scans
and urine samples
came back clean.
And yet she's still failing.
System after system.
So, either we find
the answer at autopsy or...
What?
I got nothing.
I was gonna head out. If there's any
change, I assume you'll page me.
Are you having an affair?
Does it bother you that your
wife doesn't have the guts
to actually ask
that question and I do?
On both ends, yes.
Difference is, I'm not
afraid of the answer.
And I might believe you.
I'm not having an affair.
But you want to.
No, I don't.
I'm through living like that.
Why?
What, you finally
got to the point
where half your age plus seven
just isn't young enough?
Talk to you later, House.
Or is it because you now really
are old enough to be their...
The dad.
Does he travel for work?
What do you mean, does he?
He died almost 10 years ago.
Not hers. Her boyfriend's.
He's the one in her visions.
I'm your son's
girlfriend's doctor.
Oh!
It's a mouthful, but probably
not as tricky as your title.
Okay. Is Abby
gonna be all right?
Do you travel a lot?
Yeah, I have a food
import business. Why?
Where do you go?
All over. France, Italy,
the Mediterranean? Why?
I think you exposed her
to a parasite.
Oh!
I thought the scans
didn't show any.
Because she doesn't have any.
But you just said... It's cool.
My theory is that her body was
able to kill off the parasite,
but what it couldn't do
was get rid of the shell,
which doesn't
show up on the scans.
That little piece of
microscopic garbage
set off an allergic reaction
called Cerebellar Schistosomiasis
delayed Hypersensitivity
Allergy or "CSDHA."
Risky, unpleasant treatment,
but completely curable.
Well, that's fantastic.
You'd think so, wouldn't you?
Only thing is,
did you ever have sex with
your son's girlfriend?
Where the hell
do you get off...
Shut up.
See, I can't treat this
unless I can confirm it.
The only way she could
have been exposed
to this parasite is sexually,
which means she's
gonna die very soon
unless you admit
that you slept with her.
Dad. What's going on?
Gee, this is bad,
because you now have
to choose between
her living and the
truth becoming public,
and frankly, given what the
truth is, it's a tough call.
You'd broken up.
She was crying...
Your girlfriend is not
allergic to your semen.
She's allergic to
the Egyptian parasites
swimming around
in your dad's semen.
You slept with Abby?
I was drunk. We both...
No need to explain.
Technically, she was legal.
Wait, wait! Wait!
Hey, all things considered,
it's actually great news.
So, what do you think?
You wussed out
and used a decorator.
Why can't that be me?
A wuss who loves decorators.
Because it's not.
Okay, it's not.
But don't return it.
I can't keep doing this.
You have to. You can't keep
letting other people define you.
Not another elephant.
The decorator didn't pick this.
You're gonna have
to buy your own cape.
I like what this says
about you, Wilson.
Wait, I don't remember him
at the wedding, do you?
I don't remember most of the
people who were at our wedding.
Which is why
I thought I'd ask the love
of my life to marry me.
We're already married.
I want to be better at it.
Well, that's beautiful.
What did you tell him?
That it doesn't mean
she doesn't love him.
And he bought it?
It's true.
Your wife say yes?
How did you know...
Monkey see, monkey do.
At least he has the
"young and stupid" excuse.
She said yes.
Good for you.
Thank you.