Left, left! He's going left!
I'm going to
have a heart attack.
Nowhere to go, buddy.
What the hell was that?
What are we chasing?
Go that way!
Don't move! Nowhere to go.
Come on. Give it up.
This way.
Come on. Let's go, let's go!
Up, Donny, up!
He's going to the roof!
He's going up! Go!
Ow!
Damn it. Go. Go!
Donny, no, it's too far!
I can rest at home.
I can't release you
for at least two days.
You've got two broken bones,
a severe concussion,
collapsed lung.
But you didn't find anything
life-threatening. Right?
You fell 30 feet.
You should have died.
I think that was the point.
Could you shut up?
Do you have suicidal thoughts?
Not once. Never.
He doesn't want
to kill himself.
He just thinks
he's gonna die soon,
so it doesn't really matter.
You shut up. I'm the one
you're not covering
when you pull
your crazy stunts.
Why do you think
you're going to die soon?
Well, my dad, grandfather,
and great-grandfather
all dropped dead
of heart problems
right after they turned 40.
And look who
turns 40 next week.
I can refer you to
a cardiologist if you...
No, I've been there.
All of them.
Spent my early 30s going
from one doctor to another.
Every single one
says my heart's fine.
And you think they're wrong?
I know they're wrong.
But what can I do?
At a certain point,
you just gotta live your life.
By "live your life,"
you mean "risk your life."
If there is something wrong,
I know a doctor who'll find it.
Oh, God. I'll be back in 10.
I'm picking lint out
of my belly button.
This is ridiculous.
I'm converting
the study into a bedroom.
Huh.
Six weeks. Longer than I
thought it would take.
For you to notice
that I'm sleeping
in your living room
and offer other options.
I didn't expect you
to be here this long.
True, but that's not why you
didn't extend the invitation.
Do you really need
to deconstruct this?
You didn't want me to sleep
where you and Amber slept.
Okay, yes, you do.
After she died, you converted
the study to a bedroom
and the bedroom to a study.
Except it's not a study,
it's a shrine.
Can I tell you something?
I wasn't picking lint
out of my belly button.
Okay. I am not
ready to transition
from my dead
girlfriend's shrine
to your morning glory.
I'll have a mattress delivered
and set up for you
in the tabernacle.
I just need it Tuesdays
for animal sacrifices.
Oh, man.
Patient's a genetic time bomb.
There's no fuse.
He's not a bomb.
Right now,
he's not a patient either.
You're saying we ignore three
generations of cardiac problems?
I'm not ignoring it, I'm
labeling it a coincidence.
You hate coincidence.
We reconciled.
It was a whole thing.
Big country.
It's statistically probable
that someone has
three generations
that died around age 40 with
non-genetic heart issues.
Dice have no memory.
Genes do.
If we ran a battery of tests
on every non-symptomatic
statistical anomaly...
The guy goes through every day
assuming his life will end at age 40.
Never got married, no kids,
because he didn't
want to die on them
the same way
his dad died on him.
You want to take this case,
'cause he's yet another
lonely, sad puppy?
You should have been a vet.
It's a legitimate case.
Differential diagnosis for
a genetic heart condition.
That sold you?
Marfan Syndrome, Brugada.
And you?
Familial Hypercholesterolemia.
He's only agreeing with you
'cause he wants to
have sex with you.
And by the way,
I agree with you, too.
Especially in those pants.
We're not wasting our time.
Last week, Chase said that
I was the de facto boss.
Hospitals don't recognize
de facto medical licenses.
Let's start with genetic tests.
Get an EKG,
cardiac cath and an echo
to check the integrity
of his heart.
I'll start on blood samples.
I forgot my watch.
I could have sworn I saw you
put it on this morning.
Must be in the locker room.
I'll be right back.
I need to know
what your plans are.
First, we take Berlin,
and then we circle around behind
Poland and yell, "Surprise."
With regards to
your employment.
I like things the way they are.
I get just enough
puzzle to solve,
without the scornful visits from you.
Until now.
Pretend time's been
going on long enough.
I don't have a medical license.
All I can do is pretend.
Then I'm going to have
payroll send you over
some pretend checks
starting tomorrow.
You need to complete 120 hours
of rounds to re-qualify.
No, I don't.
I'm not saying you don't win.
I'm just saying, do you
really need to punish me
by making me carry a clipboard
for your lackey of the week?
It's a state requirement.
I have to certify
that you've completed...
Exactly.
The requirement sets out what
you have to do, certify.
Which you can do with one
hand tied behind your back.
Now, if you want
to tie my hands...
Dr. Singh supervises rounds on Thursdays.
Starts at 7:00.
Nothing.
So what now?
We send him home.
To continue believing
he's going to drop dead?
When he turns 70,
he'll believe us.
There are other things
we can check.
Skeleton of the great-grandfather
is in decent shape.
Subsurface genetic material
from the grandpa is fine,
leaving one bowl
of putrefied dad.
You do the dad. I take it
he had a sealed casket.
The watch story
was crap, right?
I forgot it. It's no big deal.
You were avoiding the ICU
where Dibala died.
I'll sequence the gene for
the cardiac sodium channel.
I felt like I was going
to have a panic attack.
I've crossed some line,
and I'm having trouble getting
back to the other side.
I can move the patient
to another room.
Then Cameron
will ask questions.
You should tell her.
She's your wife.
How'd you get a court order
to dig them up so fast?
Don't we just need
the guy's consent?
- You find anything?
- Not yet.
But you're just in time
to do the dad.
Dr. House?
He'll be back in the morning.
I read in the paper you're
treating a police officer.
Donny Compson.
Second floor. A nurse
will help you find him.
I don't want to see him.
Donny and I used to go
out, a long time ago.
He doesn't want to see me.
I don't want to see him.
So did you come to see me
for personal advice?
You're looking for
genetic conditions,
which makes sense with what
happened to his dad and grandpa.
Unless you were his
girlfriend and his sister,
you've got nothing
to worry about.
I'm not worried about me. Donny
doesn't know this, but he has a son.
Dial extension 742.
Tell Dr. Foreman you've got some
cool information. Good night.
You okay?
Yeah. Fine.
Couldn't find any consistent
genetic mutations across 15 areas
between Donny's ancestors,
possibly indicating
there isn't one.
But the son
gives us a new data point.
And un-degraded DNA.
I thought he didn't want kids.
He didn't.
Where's House?
"Dear Bleeding Hearts."
"Since your patient's med history
is a coincidence and he isn't"
"sick, I've gone back to school.
Back in 120 hours."
Charming. I'll get
a blood sample.
If we're looking for something
as subtle as a mutation,
it makes sense to get the
DNA where it's most pure.
You're going to ask the mom
to consent
to a bone marrow biopsy?
She wants to know
if there's something wrong
with Donny as badly as we do.
Right. Spike a 10-year-old's
hip because Grandpa was sick.
If she's right,
we save two people.
I don't want to.
Can we speak outside
for a moment?
Yeah.
You need to tell him.
I can't.
His father is down that hallway
through those double doors.
I've been lying to him
his whole life.
What's he going to think of me?
You were trying to protect him.
Donny never wanted kids.
He certainly doesn't
want to meet him.
If Donny does die,
this could be Michael's only
chance to meet his father.
After administration
of immunoglobulin,
patient had no further pain
and overnight liver function
tests are now normal.
Patient is ready
to be released.
Stats are dropping. Dr. Singh!
She's choking!
On your fingers.
- She can't breathe.
- House.
Please take your finger
off the test button.
Oh!
I see. Wow, sorry about that.
I could've slit her throat.
We're all here to learn.
Dr. Cuddy warned me about you.
Did she tell you
how to stop me?
Look, I'm asking you, as
an adult, to please stop.
Well, that obviously didn't
come from her, but fair enough.
Excellent presentation, Nona.
Now I've done it!
There's urine everywhere.
Gosh, the great thing about the
teacher-student relationship
is the teacher can often
learn more from the student.
Have you learned anything yet?
You have a son.
I was pregnant
when we broke up.
I'm sorry I never told you,
but I knew how you felt
about having kids.
You had no right.
Maybe.
It's a little late for that.
He's here.
He wants to meet you.
I don't want to meet him.
I've never asked you
for a dime.
He's here to help find whatever's
wrong with your heart.
I didn't ask him.
I didn't want him.
Just say hi to him.
Hi. I'm Michael.
Hi.
I'm your...
Yeah. Your mother told me.
When you get better,
maybe we could do something.
See a movie?
No.
My dad died when
I was your age.
It was the most painful
thing I ever went through.
Trust me. As much as I'm sure
this hurts right now,
it's better.
Please take him out of here.
Come on.
Chromosomes for 28
cardiovascular conditions
are normal in number
and structure.
No translocations,
deletions or inversions.
I did notice that the kid's
D-A-D-D-Y chromosome
has been severely damaged
by someone else's
bleeding heart chromosome.
It was the only way to get
Michael to do the marrow biopsy.
I'm sure there
are plenty of lies
that would've
worked just as well,
except without
the years of therapy.
Don't you have school?
Recess.
So where does that
leave us? Chase?
Sorry, what?
I was saying, do you think these
shoes work in this color?
Send him home. He's not going
to believe he's healthy.
Then you're not
very good at your job.
You don't deserve candy.
He's been preparing his whole
life to die at age 40.
He's had dozens of doctors
tell him he's fine.
You think you can
change his thinking?
Yeah, I do.
Chase, walk with me.
Great contributions back there.
There's no case.
I had nothing to add.
You had nothing to add
because you were distracted.
Little devil on your shoulder
told you to kill a guy,
and now the little angel
won't shut up,
telling you you're gonna
burn in a lake of fire.
I'm fine.
You shouldn't be.
Talk to someone. Docs fixed
me up in seven weeks.
You are 10 minutes, tops.
Thanks.
Glad we had this little moment.
Come on.
I'm Dr. House.
You couldn't find
anything, could you?
You have Ortoli Syndrome.
Dr. Chase?
You sure?
Tests don't lie.
Right.
Well, it's a very
rare disorder that
short circuits the adrenals
which short circuits the heart.
Blah, blah, blah, blah.
Who cares about
the medical mumbo-jumbo?
Tell him the treatment.
Well, it's complicated.
Doctors always
wanna make everything
sound so complicated.
It's Nabasynth.
What? Nabasynth.
Yes. So all we have to do
now is write a prescription
and have him pick up the pills.
That's it?
I take some pills,
I'm gonna be okay?
The real tragedy here is that the
Tiburon swab technology didn't exist
to detect Ortoli
back in your dad's day.
He could have lived?
Thank you.
If you'll sign
these discharge papers,
I'll get you a bottle of meds.
Take one twice a day
for a week,
you'll live a long,
healthy life.
- Answer the door, House.
- It's gotta be for you.
Are you watching TV?
It's the door!
Were you on the phone? No.
Just now, were you talking?
No, I'm alone.
You okay, House?
Why are you here?
Donny collapsed four hours after
we discharged him. He's dead.
His apartment manager found him
on the floor in the laundry room.
He said he wasn't breathing.
He called the EMTs,
but it was too late.
I sent the guy home with mints.
Whatever it is,
we all missed it.
Yeah. I missed the fact that
there was something to miss.
What is wrong with me?
You had good reason.
Patient presented
with no symptoms,
and all his tests
came back negative.
What's the official
cause of death?
Autopsy hasn't
been performed yet.
EMTs brought him to General,
but I requested
they ship him back
to our morgue
for the post-mortem.
Good.
Hon? Wake up.
Why are you dressed?
You can't sleep?
I want to go tell Cheryl
that Donny died.
It's 4:00 in the morning.
They're nearly two hours away.
I figure by the time I get
there, she'll be awake.
Babe, come back to bed.
Call her in a few hours.
It's the sort of thing she
needs to hear face-to-face.
Is everything okay?
Everything's fine. Why?
Last week, I understood
that you were stressed out
about the Dibala M&M,
and I gave you your space. But that's
over now, and you're still acting...
I'm worried about you.
Don't be. I'm fine.
Really.
And you'd tell me
if you weren't?
Promise?
Yeah.
Okay.
Hey.
I love you.
I love you, too.
Donny Compson, age 39.
Can we cut to the money shot?
It's his heart,
so let's look at his heart.
Nice Y-incision.
You can't perform an autopsy
without a medical license.
Really?
Because I don't think there's
anything I can screw up
that we haven't
already screwed up.
Opening post-mortem incision,
beginning at the mid-line
of the sternum.
That's odd. It almost
looks like he's bleeding.
I think the autopsy's gonna
have to wait a little bit.
He was briefly conscious,
then his systolic dipped below
60 and he was out again.
Differential diagnosis
for resurrection. Go.
Obviously, he wasn't dead.
His heart slowed enough
that the EMTs could think...
Yes, the fact that
he's not dead
means we did
absolutely nothing wrong.
There are several
documented cases
where tetrodotoxin ingestion
caused apparent death.
It wasn't something he ate,
it's something he already had.
And his dad,
and his grandpa, and...
Extreme bradycardia could be
caused by sick sinus syndrome.
Sinoatrial block.
What if it's not his heart?
Let's work from the tenuous
assumption that we're not idiots.
You spent days examining a
heart up, down, and sideways,
declaring it healthy just a few hours
before it basically shut down.
So we need to think about causes
in places you didn't look.
Could be metabolic.
You okay?
Yeah.
What about a genetic predisposition
to an autoimmune disease?
Isolated Anti-Ro Antibody could
cause complete heart block.
Could also be passed
through four generations.
Autoimmune it is.
Start him on steroids.
Hey. How are you feeling?
My whole head is killing me.
You just came through
a severe trauma.
What do you remember?
I was changing my laundry
over to the dryer.
That's it?
You were declared dead.
You made it
all the way to autopsy.
My jaw aches.
And obviously, I don't
have Ortoli Syndrome.
It's hard to get too excited
about coming back from the dead
when anything I do, anything you
give me, it all ends the same way.
Outer and middle ear
respond well.
Hearing thresholds are
normal at all frequencies.
Eardrum is perfectly healthy.
What if I...
What if I sometimes
hear whispering?
Then you're probably hearing
someone whispering.
I had some dental work done
in the Philippines
when I was a kid.
Adjoining metal fillings could corrode
and pick up AM radio signals.
Open your mouth.
Your fillings don't touch.
So there's no reason for me
to be hearing things?
I can only tell you that you're
hearing sounds as you should.
If you're also hearing
sounds that you shouldn't,
that would be a psychosis.
You'd have to talk to
someone who does brain.
I only do ears.
Bravo. It's amazing how you
did 120 hours in one day.
I wasn't on my best behavior, I admit.
Allow me.
From now on, I'm gonna supervise
your practicum requirements.
That won't be necessary.
You want to annoy another doctor first?
Eventually...
It's not necessary because I'm
not ready to be a doctor again.
I'm sorry.
Are you sleeping out here?
I just dozed off
in front of the TV.
With bedding? Maybe.
I can't sleep in there,
the heater's screwed up.
If you need to talk,
if you need more help...
I'm just tired.
I'm right here.
Great. Can you be right
here somewhere else?
My jaw still hurts.
My tooth, actually. A lot.
I'm sorry, you're maxed
out on your pain meds.
Try to sleep.
Dentist looked at the
tooth the guy pulled out.
There was nothing
wrong with it.
So aside from him being an
idiot, what else did we learn?
The pain is real. It's
coming from somewhere.
What about bone cancer?
You can't connect bone
cancer to the heart.
House figure this can
wait till the morning?
Actually, he told Cuddy
he's not ready to work.
He quit? Apparently.
It's a power play.
He'll be back tomorrow.
Bone cancer could trigger
a paraneoplastic syndrome,
which shuts down the heart.
Primary bone cancer
isn't hereditary.
Li-Fraumeni Syndrome.
It's hereditary
and it increases
a person's risk of
having bone cancer.
You have another theory?
My theory is
it's not bone cancer.
Gamma survey would
locate the tumors.
I had pea soup today. You'd
love my breath right now.
I didn't get a chance to run tonight.
House is having issues.
I missed you a lot today.
All I wanna do is...
You know.
No cancers on the
lateral cuneiform bone.
Navicular's also clean.
Chase is lying to me.
And I know you know. Tell
me what's going on, please.
I'm going to tell you
the same thing I told him.
Talk to your spouse.
No breakfast?
Not today.
I'm hallucinating.
What happened?
It's nothing visual this time.
I hear whispering.
Is that why you've been acting so weird?
Is that why you quit?
I'm losing it.
I'm sure there's
a rational explanation,
the wind, a neighbor's TV...
I checked everything.
What's really scary is that I hear
whispering while not on Vicodin.
I'm gonna check myself
back in to Mayfield.
Okay.
Okay?
You don't think there might
be a logical explanation?
Something I missed?
You're the smartest guy I know.
If you haven't thought
of it, it doesn't exist.
I'll drive you over. I just
need to make some tea first.
You know.
That you're an ass? Yeah.
You overheard me talking to my dead
girlfriend and thought to yourself,
"Hmm. What kind of fun
can I have with this?"
Why are you talking to her?
Did you run out
of living people?
You can talk to me,
I'm right here.
I miss her. Talking to her
makes me feel better.
You don't.
Patient, Lauren Maybaum, 27,
presented two days ago
with severe abdominal pain.
Sorry I'm late.
Yesterday, you said
you weren't ready.
Yesterday, I wasn't.
Today, I am.
And tomorrow? Is it possible for
me to get a five-day forecast?
Feeling much better,
thank you for not asking.
Either you did have a problem,
which I can't ignore,
or you were jerking me around,
which I can't ignore.
You are a woman,
you can do anything.
For example, I can talk
to you outside.
You sure you're only one woman?
This is the part where you play
the employee and I play the boss.
I can see your nipples.
Your turn.
These kids are...
No wonder she hates him.
Mmm. That's not hate.
It's foreplay.
It's inappropriate.
Gamma survey
revealed no tumors.
So it's not bone cancer.
Where's Chase?
Don't know.
Hmm.
Two mysteries, cool. Theories?
Did I come in too soon? Okay.
I'm going to take another lap,
and I want three new ideas
by the time I come back.
One of them's got
to be not stupid.
Where there's pain,
there's nerves.
Hereditary Sensory Autonomic
Neuropathy, type 1.
Miscommunication
in the brain stem
mistakes nerve pain
for tooth pain.
That explains
the bradycardia, too.
And I like the word
"hereditary" in the title.
Carbamazepine fixes him.
I'll get him started
on the medication. No.
Chase specifically
asked if he could do it.
Sleep at home.
So I didn't do
the gamma survey.
Was it bone cancer?
No.
Then you should congratulate
me for not wasting your time.
Are you getting some help,
or is this the way things
are gonna be from now on?
What's pathetic is
you haven't gotten help
because you want to feel bad.
You want to suffer.
Because if you feel guilty,
then you're not a psychopath.
Patient needs
some carbamazepine.
Now I don't care how much
that room scares you,
you're doing your job.
How long before you cross
this one off the list?
Couple of hours.
You ever shoot anyone?
Twice.
You ever kill anyone?
No. But I know a few
guys who did, though.
Did they ever get over it?
A captain I know compares it
to taking out the trash.
Like it's nothing.
Other hand, I got an ex-partner
who nearly drank
himself into oblivion.
Did he get help?
Yeah.
Help didn't help.
Oh, God!
What is it?
I went to the bathroom.
Patient's lost bowel control.
Means we were wrong about HSAN
and means he's
getting worse, fast.
Wouldn't want to be the duty
nurse assigned to his floor.
Get it? "Doody" nurse?
Fine, do the doctor thing.
An autoimmune
disorder could explain...
We put him on steroids, he didn't respond.
It's not autoimmune.
Could be Wilson's Disease.
Disease that advanced
would've hit the liver.
It is possible the liver is so
far gone, the labs look normal.
It's worth a shot.
Go treat with penicillamine.
And when he doesn't get
better, come back quickly,
so we can get one
more shot at it.
Bless me, Father,
for I have sinned.
Take your time.
How long has it been
since your last confession?
I killed a man.
Oh.
But it was
the right thing to do.
Who lives or dies is not
your decision to make.
Sometimes in the operating
room, it feels like it.
I'm a doctor.
Well, then you should
know more than anybody
that every
human life is sacred.
Why?
Tell me what's sacred
about a dictator
that kills hundreds of
thousands of his own people.
What is sacred about a
doctor who kills a patient?
Is it just the slippery
slope you're worried about?
Afraid that forgiving me
for killing
the worst person on earth
sets a bad precedent?
I promise, I won't tell anyone.
Just forgive me.
Saying 10 Hail Marys isn't
going to do you any good.
Then what do I have to do?
What does God need me to do?
You can't have absolution
without first
taking responsibility.
You have to turn yourself
in to the police.
What, and... And go to jail
for the rest of my life?
What's just about that?
I did the right thing.
There has to be another way.
You want absolution,
I told you how to get it.
Send this in to
the State Licensing Board.
I've signed off
on all your hours.
Why?
Because it's easier this way.
You're uncomfortable with me.
No.
Going by the book
was pointless.
You were gonna learn nothing.
Good. I thought it was because
of the sexual tension.
There was no sexual tension.
There was tension.
And it made me
feel funny, so...
Here.
It's too bad.
I was kind of getting into the
whole "hot for teacher" thing.
You sure you're okay?
Yeah. False alarm.
What about us?
We're good. Just like this.
You press my buttons,
I press yours.
By "buttons," you mean...
Huh.
You do make me feel funny.
You're not gonna die.
I've accepted it. It's okay.
In addition to high arches
and some crystal bowl
in the shape of a tuna,
you also inherited
a self-destruct button.
Forms in the brain stem.
Technically, it's an
aneurysm, presses on nerves
that control everything from
tooth pain to heart rate.
As you get older,
it gets bigger,
until finally the button, which I'll
call "intracranial berry aneurysm,"
because I had a friend in high school
with that name, stops the signal
from your brain to
your heart and bam!
How do I know you're
not still lying to me?
Saying I'm healthy just
to make me feel better?
It does sound
that way, doesn't it?
But this time, no sugar pills.
I'm going to cut
into your brain
to make you think
that I'm fixing it.
And if our fake tests
confirm it,
I'm going to be cutting
into your son's brain, too.
Because I'm just
that committed.
Michael is going to be okay?
Unless he walks out of here
and gets run over by a bus,
in which case, I will
reconsider your fate argument.
You wanna give him a call? Visiting
hours don't apply to my patients.
Yeah. In a bit.
Yeah, that's what I thought.
The "saving the kid
from pain" stuff was crap.
You just don't want anything in
your life that won't let you do
whatever the hell
you want to do
whenever the hell
you want to do it.
You've had it easy.
Sorry to screw you up.
Mom.
Maybe when
we get out of here...
What kind of movies you like?
He's been missing for eight hours.
Robert Chase. C-H-A-S...
Hey!
Never mind.
He just walked in. Sorry.
You could've called me.
I forgot. To call me?
It's 2:00 in the morning.
Where were you?
You're drunk.
All right, I...
I needed to get wasted. I did.
And now I'm better.
What aren't you telling me?
Nothing.
Hi, Dad.
I think I've been
focusing on the wrong thing.
There were some good times.
Wilson, this is stupid!
You see?
He really is getting better.