Hey.
Hi!
Car's full of gas.
You sure?
And if I'm not?
You'll be paying me back
for those damn invitations.
Oh. Well, then never mind.
Ted is a wonderful man, Dad.
He's the second
greatest guy I ever met.
Guess that's us.
Mmm-hmm.
Into this holy estate, these two
persons present now come to be joined.
And so, if any person
may show just cause
why they may not
be joined together,
let them speak now or
forever hold their peace.
That's what I like to hear.
Do you, Theodore Philip Taylor,
take Nicole Margaret Murray
to be your wife,
and promise before God
and these witnesses
to be her loving
and faithful husband,
in plenty and in want, in joy and in
sorrow, in sickness and in health,
so long as you both shall live?
This isn't funny, Ted. Ted?
Are you all right? Teddy?
Teddy! Ted.
Hey.
What time is it?
Happy time.
I'm still asleep.
Just think of this as a dream.
What about House?
I said a dream,
not a nightmare.
He's in the next room.
Sound asleep.
Esteban,
hope you're getting ready.
Hmm.
I met the neighbors.
Sir, do you know this man?
I don't need a temporary.
I need a permanent.
Yesterday.
Please do.
Good morning. Hardly.
One of my PAs quit an hour ago,
and I have to reshuffle
next month's schedule.
That's nothing. I woke up in
the wrong bed this morning.
Any bed you're in
is the wrong one.
That's not what your mama said.
Oh, snap.
I'll be going now.
To human resources.
He started it.
I was in
the neighbors' kid's bed.
Luckily, Esteban still
likes sleeping with Mommy.
How drunk were you?
About yay drunk.
Are you okay? You shouldn't be
drinking at all, much less...
You sound just
like Esteban's mom.
I need you in the clinic.
Sorry, I'm busy.
Tell me you have a case.
You know, even if you don't.
I have a case.
Sounds interesting.
I'll take it.
I owe you one. Now tell
me you don't have a case.
I really do have a case.
We're even.
You guys know how to honeymoon.
This is Dr. House.
Aphasia and syncope.
He can't speak.
"Aphasia" is Greek
for "loss of voice."
We've ruled out infection,
vocal cord damage and stroke.
A lot of guys syncope
at the altar.
It's Greek for
"having the vapors."
We ruled out all the
common causes of fainting,
low blood pressure,
hypoglycemia, dehydration.
Don't say "ah."
Do you know what it is?
Roll on your side
and lift up your gown.
There's one thing
they didn't test for.
A test for what?
Faking.
Ow!
Test was positive.
I can talk.
I wasn't faking. My voice
just came back right now.
Hey, I'm not the one
you have to convince.
I know he wasn't faking.
Boy, if she's buying that,
she might just be a keeper.
What about the syncope?
Well, that...
She buying this, too?
Why would he fake anything?
Kryo podia.
It's Greek for "duh."
So, you get to keep
the engagement ring.
I don't think he was faking.
That's because you're
more gullible than I am.
For instance, I don't believe
that you called off
your open marriage.
I believe your wife
called it off,
and you called off telling her
that you weren't calling it off.
Guy doesn't throw a golden
ticket in the trash.
Same way a guy doesn't give up
a lucrative medical practice
to come work for you?
That's exactly why you dabble.
You're compensating for your
professional conquests with sexual ones.
I'm not that predictable.
For example, you're
probably not expecting me
to ask you out
for dinner tonight.
No, thanks.
You won't even consider it?
I did, just very quickly.
Truth is, since I
called this thing off,
my wife has been very grateful,
and I could do
with a down night.
If I go out with the boss,
nobody can blame me.
Okay.
If you bring your wife.
No, that's the point.
I need a little...
You're lying.
I'm not lying!
Then I'm not going.
Okay. Fontina at 8:30.
You believe me, right?
Of course, I believe you.
Then let's do it.
We'll tell the cab to take us to
AC right now and get it done.
You're serious? You just walked
out of the emergency room.
Exactly, I walked out.
I feel great.
Well, we do have
the clothes for it.
Ted? What's wrong?
Are you... What's wrong?
Oh, my God.
Can somebody help us?
Please! Please, hurry.
Just breathe. Oh, my God.
There's gotta be a better
way to call off a wedding.
A tweet, for example.
Pleural effusion.
You think his lung
is faking it?
There's at least 200 cc's
of fluid in there.
Okay, let's say all his
symptoms are real.
Explain how one of them
suddenly went away
without using the words
"virgin" or "Mary."
If the pleural effusion's
caused by something systemic,
it could explain
his other two symptoms.
So whether
you believe him or not,
all we have to figure out
is what caused the PE.
ER ruled out infection. Eosinophil
count ruled out parasites.
And medication he's
not telling us about.
You really don't trust
this guy, do you?
I don't even trust the ER.
Let's rule out
infections ourselves.
Tap his lung, send cultures,
run cytology for cancer,
and check his blood pressure.
We already...
This time, talk about
nuptials while you do it.
Check his home
for everything else.
He just moved in with his
fiancée three months ago.
Toxic exposure could take
longer than that to manifest.
You check his love nest.
You two check his
swinging bachelor pad.
That somebody else
now lives in?
I assume so.
Not the glass!
Place looks like 1960s?
Could have lead paint.
You think
a 27-year-old has pica?
If it gets us out of here before
the owner comes back, yes.
What did you tell
that cute physio?
That I changed my mind.
No, you didn't.
You're more nervous than usual.
Because this B&E has actual B.
What...
That's a suspended ceiling.
What are you doing?
I want to see what's above it.
More ceiling.
Made of
40-year-old acoustic tile.
Asbestosis, I like it.
I'll be in the car.
What the hell?
It's okay. We're doctors.
Nobody was home, so we...
Well, I'm calling the police.
Do you know Ted Taylor?
He used to live here.
Yeah, what about him?
He's our patient
at Princeton-Plainsboro.
Is he okay?
We think he may have asbestosis
from your ceiling tiles.
They're not asbestos. I had
them checked when I moved in.
How sick is he?
Is he a friend of yours?
He was.
Actually, he was my
boyfriend for three years.
- I'm not gay.
- Really?
'Cause it would certainly
explain the cold feet.
Oh, and the boyfriend.
So you're bisexual?
No, I'm straight.
Cotter, the guy you met,
he's gay.
He had a crush on me. I left.
After three years?
It's possible.
Doesn't mean you're gay just because
the guy you're sleeping with is.
We weren't sleeping together...
What's this got to
do with anything?
Lung tap turned up
mononucleosis.
ER doesn't
routinely test for it.
It explains the PE and can
be virtually asymptomatic.
We got to wondering, how
does a 27-year-old get mono?
You're a little old
for the kissing disease
unless your immune system
is compromised.
If there's been
any unprotected sex,
we'll need to test for H IV.
There's been
no sex of any kind.
Okay.
I'll go test your fiancée for H IV.
She the curious sort?
Wait.
There may have been some contact.
But I'm not gay.
Sodomy, one of the top 10 most
common household accidents.
I did a lot of stupid things,
but I turned my life around.
I'm as straight as any of you.
You don't have to believe me.
I'm just saying
you can test me as long
as you don't tell Nicole.
What business is it of hers?
I don't see anything wrong with
him marrying a straight woman.
How about it'll make
them both miserable?
Just like most
straight marriages.
He's got the right to life, liberty
and unhappiness like the rest of us.
Absolutely no reason
to look at me.
I'm not saying
it's a great choice.
Just saying it's his choice.
But it has to be hers as
well, which it can't be
as long as she
doesn't know he's gay.
Which is how it's gonna stay
since we have
no right to tell her.
Like you've never
bent the rules.
You date guys. You date girls.
I assume, at some point,
you're gonna make a choice.
I don't lie about who I am.
Patients lying never
bothered you before.
Patients weren't lying about
their sexual orientation before.
So you're only judgmental
when it gets personal?
Does it bother me
that people hurt others
because they're too weak
to face the truth?
Yeah. Sorry about that.
Tell me she's
not looking at me.
He's negative? Yep.
Looks like being gay
didn't make him sick.
So maybe being straight did.
Test was negative, no H IV.
Told you.
What you didn't tell us is how
you turned your life around.
That can be pretty hard.
It was.
Downright impossible
on your own.
I talked to some people.
It was more than
just talk, wasn't it?
I know this is personal stuff.
I'm here to help you,
not out you.
I had therapy.
Conversion therapy.
Went to a camp for three weeks
of intensive rehabilitation.
They injected him with emetics
while he watched gay porn.
Apomorphine?
Or lithium chloride, or cyclophosphamide.
He doesn't know.
And when that didn't work, they
shot him up with male hormones.
A chemical assault like that
could explain the PE.
And the ECT explains the rest.
They gave him electroconvulsive
therapy to make him straight?
To zap the fabulous
right out of him.
Neural damage accounts
for the aphasia.
ECT doesn't cause
neural damage.
Unless it was done at Dr. Liberace's
He-man Quackery Camp.
Run an EEG. See if they straightened
him or just scrambled him.
Sorry, I completely forgot.
My wife just started a ceramics
class Tuesdays at 8:00.
It's a half-hour
drive from here.
She won't be back till 10:30.
She's taking it with
her girlfriend, Marly.
She hopes to make
a tea service.
You want to call her?
No need.
I already texted her.
And here she is now.
I think you're still
seeing the physio.
You got a backup suit
in your car.
Don't wanna be
bringing home da stank.
Okay, yes. You're right.
About everything.
But please, House,
don't tell her.
Hi, Rachel.
Hi, Dr. House. I didn't
know you'd be here.
Hi, honey.
Got your text, obviously.
I'm just leaving.
I got a ceramics class.
Really? I love it.
Even managed to talk Chris
into signing up for one.
Of course, he's in
the beginners' class.
You're in a ceramics class?
Friday nights, right?
Friday nights.
Sounded like fun.
You should join Chris's.
You know, I should.
Well, gotta go.
Making a tea service.
Hi. I must've fallen
asleep in the lounge.
- What are they doing?
- An EEG.
What's it for?
We're looking for
neurological damage
that could've
caused his symptoms.
Damage from what?
A head trauma.
He had an accident?
It wasn't an accident.
It was before he met you.
What happened?
Was he hospitalized?
You should ask him about it.
They have the results.
Everything looks normal.
Look at this.
Beta waves are spiking.
What's that mean?
I'm not sure.
He's coding! Crash cart!
What's happening to him?
He's having a heart attack.
Charging. Clear.
EKG showed no abnormalities.
So what caused the arrest?
Four ways to stop a heart.
Electrical problems, restricted blood
flow, blood where it shouldn't be.
Shocks, blocks or bleeds.
I think that's three things.
And cheating.
No, sorry, that's
how you break a heart.
I found a ceramics class in Trenton
on Friday nights that was full,
so my wife couldn't join me.
EP study ruled out shocks.
Now you just have to find
some Pottery by Taub.
The lamer it looks, the better.
So we'll do an angio to see
if it's blocks or bleeds.
You should be a doctor.
I'm going to check out
this new lesbian bar tonight.
Your life is awesome.
You wanna come?
I was telling a 33-year-old woman
that she has breast cancer.
No, you weren't.
How do you know?
Because if you were,
you'd need to see
the pain in her eyes
so she can see
the concern in yours.
Why are you setting me up
on dates with my team?
Taub asking me out was quirky,
but Thirteen doing it
is a barking cat.
I'm doing it to help you.
By setting me up with a hottie
that I can't sleep with?
And Thirteen?
I've been spending
more time with Sam.
I know it's been hard on you.
I figured if you
had some company...
I don't need your help.
Then consider it helping our
neighbor's four-year-old.
I gave him a dollar.
How much did you have to pay?
Nothing.
I just told them
you might be feeling down,
and it was in their self-interest
to keep you company.
A hundred bucks.
Foreman held out for 200.
House, I'm worried about you.
You could've ended up
in jail or worse.
Racking you with guilt.
So I do something really
stupid, and you reward me.
Read any parenting manual.
That's not helping me.
That's helping you.
Fine, I did it for me, for my
relationship, out of pure self-interest.
Okay.
You'll do it?
For you.
Thank you.
It's not gonna work, though.
Maybe. But how bad can a night
out at a lesbian bar be?
Hey.
How are you doing?
Heart attack at 27.
They said you had
a head trauma?
I fell off a stepladder and hit my head.
It was a stupid accident.
An accident.
We need to prep you
for your angio.
Valium will help you relax.
We're gonna run a line
through your femoral artery.
Ted? He's having
another heart attack?
I don't think so. His
heart rate seems normal.
Mmm.
Are you okay?
You weren't discussing
wedding plans, were you?
No. I guess I just...
Fainted.
POTS. Postural Orthostatic
Tachycardia Syndrome.
BP plummets when he's upright,
reverts to normal
when he's lying down.
He was lying down both times
we took his blood pressure.
Protracted hypotension could
have induced his heart attack.
Also explains his syncope.
And his aphasia.
He was upright, then you laid him
down on the bed to test him.
BP reverted to normal,
voice came back.
Jabbing him with the needle
had nothing to do with it.
POTS can be brought on by viral or
bacterial infection such as mono.
So load him up
with fludrocortisone.
You didn't read your ceramics
course description, did you?
Yeah. You did?
As I'm sure your wife did.
So we all know they're doing
a Fourth of July theme.
She'll be expecting
something star-spangled.
Nicole?
Yes.
Cotter Macklin.
I'm an old friend of Ted's.
Hi.
How's he doing?
He had a heart attack.
Oh, my God.
They have him on some new
meds, really knocked him out.
Well, how are you holding up?
I'm okay. Thanks.
I brought this for him.
That's his favorite thing
in the whole world.
I know.
You weren't at the
wedding, were you?
No, I wasn't invited.
Ted and I had a falling out.
How did you know each other?
We met senior year of college.
Yeah, we shared a house
for a while.
You were roommates.
For three years.
I'm sorry. I just miss him.
I think you should leave.
I shouldn't have done that. Now.
Please?
I hope he gets better.
Hey. How are you feeling?
Mmm. Don't know yet.
Your numbers look good. We're
gonna keep you on these meds.
You had a visitor
while you were asleep.
Oh, yeah? Who?
Cotter. Who is he?
I shared a house
with him after college.
I don't know why
he would show up.
That's it? Yeah.
Why? What did he say?
I need to hear it
from you, Ted.
One night, I got really
drunk and I went to bed.
And he came into my room,
and one thing led to another.
The whole thing was a mistake.
Are you saying
you had sex with him?
I was drunk and confused...
You're gay?
No.
I thought I was.
I even made up my mind
to tell my family.
I stood in front of the bathroom
mirror, psyching myself up.
But all I could see
was disgust.
And that's when I realized
I didn't hate the thought of admitting
I was gay because I was ashamed.
I hated the thought
because I wasn't gay.
And that was the day
I went to get help.
So you're not gay?
They cured me, Nicole.
That's what all
the head trauma is about.
I'm sorry I didn't tell you,
but it's all in the past now.
It doesn't matter anymore.
What is it?
Oh, my head!
He's got severe headaches.
So do I.
Should I call or raise
with a double gutshot draw?
Nope. What about infection?
That's what we're thinking.
Cerebral infection would explain the
headaches, could've caused POTS.
If it's fungal, could've
spread to the heart.
I was talking about you.
Has the little gent
been wearing a tent?
Remind me why that has
anything to do with you.
A distracted person makes
a distracted professional.
And destroying my marriage
will help me focus.
Probably.
Do a spinal tap, run the CSF.
Still talking about you!
But you can do it on the
patient, too, if you want.
What about her?
The bartender?
She's the only one
who's not here for fun.
Trust me, she's not straight.
If your gaydar is so great,
how come you didn't know about the
patient till you met his boyfriend?
Guy walked in with his bride,
it took me awhile
to rotate my dish.
It's unbelievable
what he's doing to her.
You don't think he loves her?
He may love her, but he needs
to have sex with other men.
Taub loves his wife, he needs
to have sex with other women.
Yeah, it sucks what he's doing to
her, too, but it's hardly the same.
To be faithful to his wife,
our patient has to
deny his identity.
Taub just needs to...
Has to resist
the biological imperative.
It is easier to
say no to dessert
than to pretend you don't eat.
Says someone who's obviously
never been on a diet.
My life's a breeze.
You're successful, smart, and you
attract everything that moves.
If you wanna focus on the fact
that you're not gonna see
50, that's your choice.
You know what?
I agree with you.
My self-pity's optional.
What about yours?
Yeah.
CSF was negative for infection,
and his headaches are worse.
We were just talking about you.
Please don't.
It's not POTS,
we're back to square one.
Not quite.
You did a spinal tap and
the headaches got worse.
We're maxing him out
on morphine.
He sprung a leak. He's losing
CSF from the tap site.
We made his headaches worse?
Just you, actually.
That still wouldn't explain why he got
the headaches in the first place.
Low pressure in his brain caused the
POTS, not the other way around.
Patch the leak, top him
up with artificial CSF.
There.
That should stop the leak.
You should be feeling
some relief soon.
I spoke to my parents.
How are they doing?
They're still worried.
Well, tell them not to be.
Everything's going to be okay.
Ted?
What's happening?
He's stroking.
Both eyes are responsive.
Tell me your full name.
Theodore Philip Taylor.
This isn't a stroke.
Then what is it?
What's happening to me?
It's really not POTS, we're
really back to square one.
So what's masquerading
as a stroke?
Voted the worst Halloween
costume, by the way.
MRI showed no problems with
blood flow to the brain,
rules out TIA.
Sarcoidosis?
Chest X-rays showed
no hilar masses.
Any luck with the pottery?
Wasn't easy.
Bought a suitably cruddy set of
fife and drum napkin rings online.
Scleroderma?
Skin's fine, ANA was negative.
So what'd that set you back?
Too much.
I got into a bidding war
with some lunatic.
Histoplasmosis.
EIA was clear.
But, hey, could've gone
a lot higher than $215.
You're KissMyAsthma99?
What about MELAS?
Mitochondrial
encephalomyopathy,
lactic acidosis and
stroke-like episodes.
NILLAS.
No, idiot, lactate levels are stable.
We're missing something.
We've run every test
that makes sense,
asked every question
we can think of,
gone over his history
a dozen times.
We know how much
we can trust his history.
If history's written
by the victor,
how do we find out
what really happened?
Talk to the loser.
Call the boyfriend.
Let's get them all
in the same room.
Or we could question them
separately and not torture them.
Or we could get them all in the
same room and get the truth.
Oh.
Drinks are on me
and Foreman tonight.
Can't. Pap smear.
We don't want to do it either,
but Wilson already paid us.
It's going to suck.
I know.
Where and when?
Any incidents of dizziness?
Seizures?
Blackouts?
Other than our wedding day.
Don't you think I would've
told you if there were?
My sister's birthday.
I was drunk.
You had one martini.
On an empty stomach.
Look, he was just
sitting on the couch,
and then he fell over
and that was it.
Once I slept it off,
I was fine.
Well, I stayed up that night,
checking on him
every 15 minutes.
What about sex?
Yes, I have sex with my
girlfriend because I'm not gay.
We have sex.
Thank you.
No problems?
Well, there have
been some issues.
Nic...
Erectile dysfunction?
Every guy has it sometimes.
We never had that problem.
Gee, that must be because
Ted doesn't like girls.
Or because it's vascular.
I know we did an MRA, but arterial
disease causing acute ischemia
could explain the heart, neuro
symptoms, maybe even POTS.
Might I suggest
a diagnostic test?
A penile plethysmograph measures
changes in blood flow in your penis,
tells us if there's
a circulatory problem.
You just need to be
in the right state.
What's your pleasure?
I feel terrible, I don't
think anything's gonna work.
Then we'll have
to give you a shot.
Where you don't
want to get one.
Shot it is.
He kept dreaming.
Dreaming.
That someday he'd be a star.
Superstar,
but he didn't get far.
But he sure found
out the hard way.
That dreams don't
always come true.
Dreams don't always come true.
Oh, no.
No No.
He's leaving.
Leaving.
On that midnight
train to Georgia.
Leaving on a midnight train.
Yeah, said he's
going back to find.
Going back to find.
A simpler place and time.
Whenever he takes that ride.
Guess who's gonna
be right by his side
I'm gonna be with him
I know you will.
On a midnight train to Georgia.
Leaving on a midnight
train to Georgia
I'd rather live in his world.
Live in his world.
Than live without him in mine.
World His world.
His tears My world.
His and hers alone
I've got to go, I've got
to go, I've got to go.
His and hers alone.
Nobody wants to follow that.
The night just keeps
getting better.
To Wilson.
Wilson. Wilson.
Everything looks fine.
You sure?
Medically, that's good news.
You feeling feverish
or sweating?
No, I feel lousy, but I don't
know why I'm sweating.
What is it?
You're not sweating.
You're lactating.
If he can't tell
his fiancée he's gay,
how's he going to
tell her he's pregnant?
His therapists loaded
him with hormones.
Male hormones don't
make you lactate.
Except they can
screw up your thyroid.
That was over three months ago,
we just started
milking him last night.
So something else screwed up his thyroid.
Graves', Hashimoto's...
No. TSH was normal.
Pituitary tumor. Could also explain
his libido and heart issues.
And if the tumor's big enough,
his headaches and syncope.
Except we cleared him
for cancer.
Didn't say "cancer,"
prolactinomas can be benign.
Check his prolactin level
and MRI his pituitary.
Sounds like you
had fun last night.
You believe Chase?
I believe Foreman.
And they had fun with you.
What happened?
I realized that they
could be my friends.
You're serious.
And then I sobered up.
You weren't that drunk.
You managed to find your way into
your own little bed last night.
I think I sleep better
in rocket-ship sheets.
No. You want to
blame this on the booze,
but that's easy.
Change is hard.
And wisdom is knowing
the difference
between what you can change...
And what you were born with.
And cowardice is labeling what you
don't wanna change as innate.
I was winning this argument.
Pituitary MRI...
Was normal.
How are the headaches?
Terrible.
Give me your head.
What the hell?
I know, it's the
first time you heard
that sentence with
a possessive pronoun.
Oh, wow, that's better.
Okay. Enough.
How cool is that?
You have a Chiari Malformation,
a narrowing in the base of your
skull that can cut off CSF flow.
But it wasn't a problem until
the ECT at Breeder Boot Camp
caused your brain to swell just
enough to plug the opening.
And when your brain pressed
up against your pituitary,
it signed you up
for La Leche League.
You still won't be pitching
a tent for your lady,
but that's just because,
you know, she's a lady.
Its orthostatic effect
was mimicking POTS.
It also does an uncanny
Christopher Walken.
Unfortunately, if you treat
it like POTS, it gets worse.
So, as far as that goes, oops.
Proper treatment is surgery.
We'll get you in right away.
So, how did I get this thing?
Overbearing mother.
Kidding, CM's congenital.
Like so many other things,
you were born that way.
Thought you might
be running low, so...
Thanks.
I'm not coming back.
Ted, this is a mistake.
I know you're hurting,
and I'm sorry...
I'm talking about hurting her.
I love her.
Ted...
Thank you for your support.
We both really appreciate it.
Good luck.
Hey.
You know what
I've been thinking?
It's your birthday
in three weeks.
What do you say we re-book the
church and make it a doubleheader?
I don't know, Ted.
Less than a week ago, we were standing
at the altar perfectly happy.
Nothing's changed.
Really?
I still love you.
Do you still love me?
Yes, but...
Then that's all that matters.
But I think that
you still love him.
I'm not gay, Nicole.
I promise you.
How can you promise me that?
Because I believe that we get to
choose how we live our lives.
And I've made my choice.
So now, I have to make mine.
I'm so sorry.
Nic...
I'm sorry.
Nic!
No. No.
I'm not saying goodbye.
Yeah.
I want to marry you!
I have to marry you!
Nic.
It's Friday night.
I called it off.
For real this time.
Frees you up for the next one.
One day at a time.
Napkin rings.
My way of saying thanks.
For trying to
wreck your marriage?
For trying to save it.
And I get napkin rings.
Expensive ones.
I hired a replacement
for my PA.
She seems great.
Good work.
You, too.
Your patient's
going home tomorrow.
He doesn't have a home.
You want to grab a bite to eat?
So Wilson got to you, too.
No, this is just me.
Lucas?
Working late.
I'm buying.
Not that hungry.
Okay.
I just want us to be friends.
Funny.
That's the last thing
I want us to be.