- I read this
piece in "The Times"
about this little girl
who needs a new windpipe.
Name's Hannah Warren.
Her family's working
with this doctor in Europe.
- Dr. Paolo Macchiarini.
- The focus of my research
is tracheal transplants
with the help of stem cells
by developing
biosynthetic tracheas.
- So you're basically
tricking the body
into thinking the implant's
already a part of you.
- Will you be interested
in assisting?
- Yes. Yes.
- I was wondering
if you would be interested
in collaborating on rat trials
to test our tracheas.
- Absolutely.
- Welcome to the team.
- So this is the first
artificial-trachea transplant
in the U.S.,
and I want Hannah's journey
to be the focus of the piece.
- Surgery went well.
- I have watched you
for a while now.
What you did, it was a miracle.
Paolo, I shouldn't.
- The science
doesn't seem sound.
- It's not exactly
your kind of science.
- I will admit I don't get it.
- Knife.
After the operation,
she's healthy and happy
with her donor trachea.
* *
- Hannah Warren
will be the youngest patient
ever to receive a biosynthetic
tracheal transplant.
- Okay, stop right there.
Let's swap this out to play
over Dr. Macchiarini talking
about the initial diagnosis.
I think we still need a
little more B-roll
with the parents,
but we are close to locking.
Ow.
- You okay?
- Yeah, I'm okay.
Hi.
I was just talking about you.
- Uh, Benita.
- Daryl?
- I called to, um--
I called to tell you she, uh--
she's gone.
What?
- Hannah's gone.
- What--what do
you mean she's gone?
- It was--
There were complications.
Her--her lungs, after all
the time in the hospital,
she just--
her body couldn't, um...
Hannah's gone.
We were with her, and she
just kept getting worse.
We thought maybe
she was gonna--
that it would pass, but, uh--
* *
- Mom, your phone.
Is it work?
- No, it's not work.
What's up with
the braids, kiddo?
I haven't seen you repeat
a hairstyle twice,
let alone three times,
in a week.
- Dad liked my hair this way.
- I miss him, too.
But I think you look great.
You ready for school?
What are you doing here?
- I wanted to make sure
that you're okay.
You're not answering
my phone calls, my texts.
- You shouldn't be here.
- I know you heard
about Hannah.
I just wanted to make sure
that you're okay, Benita.
- I thought
she was getting better.
- There were complications.
- "Complications.
"Fragile native tissue.
Weakening of the lungs."
I-I read the reports, Paolo.
I know the medicine.
But you told me she
was getting better.
- She was very sick.
And she was going to die.
I tried.
You think that I'm not upset?
But I won't give up.
I don't have
the right to give up.
- No, Paolo, don't.
I-I can't do this.
Let's just call it
what it is, okay?
- What is it?
- A mistake.
- Colleagues, board members,
we are so glad
to have you here
for this momentous occasion.
Tomorrow we will perform the
first-ever human transplant
using a bioartificial scaffold.
Our patient is
Andemariam Beyene,
a 36-year-old Eritrean
PhD student
living in Iceland.
Two years ago, he developed
a malignant tumor
in his windpipe.
They have tried radiation
and surgical intervention.
All failed.
So his doctors
referred him to us.
As you all know,
we only have approval
to perform this procedure
as compassionate use,
a last resort.
We have designed
a biosynthetic trachea
tailor-made
to Mr. Beyene's anatomy,
down to the last micrometer.
- And this truly
is the breakthrough
that will launch us
as a global destination
for this kind of medicine.
- Ladies and gentlemen,
I present to you the future
of regenerative medicine.
Within weeks,
it will grow tissue,
transforming into an actual,
living trachea.
* *
Dr. Macchiarini, I am sorry.
I no longer wish
to have the surgery.
We feel it is too risky.
- It is completely natural
to have concerns, Mr. Beyene.
- The trachea, it's plastic.
How can you be sure
it will work inside my body?
- There you misunderstand.
It is not plastic.
The trachea is medical-grade
polymeric
nano-composite material.
- If I may.
- Yeah, of course.
- Mr. Beyene, you're studying
lava tubes in Iceland.
Is that right?
- Yes.
- I believe
the recellularization process
is just like that.
When a volcano erupts,
underground lava rivers
create tubes.
When the lava drains,
the tubes remain,
but now they're rock solid.
They become a part
of the Earth.
And that means
they last forever.
That's what your
stem cells will do
to the synthetic trachea
to make it last forever
as a part of you.
- You're asking my husband
to be the first
but offer no guarantee
the procedure will work.
- No, we cannot offer
guarantees
because it would be
irresponsible to do so.
Nothing is guaranteed
in medicine.
Even just a year ago,
your options would have been
much more limited.
You are very lucky
to be the first.
Your doctors referred you to us
because the other treatments
failed you.
You could have as little
as six months to live.
This is your best chance
to see your son grow up.
* *
- Okay.
I think it's very difficult
to keep an emotional distance,
especially if it is a child.
Hey.
How you holding up?
- I wish I felt numb.
I just feel...
everything.
- Give yourself a break, B.
You're not on a schedule here.
- It's gonna take
what it takes.
- You know, with
Hannah Warren and John...
it's just a whole lot of death.
- How's Lizzi?
- She's really quiet.
I think she's pretending to be
okay for me,
which makes me feel guilty,
which makes me feel worse.
She's just such a daddy's girl.
And that breaks my heart.
- At least you still have
a heart to break.
- Yeah, the pain reminds us
we're alive.
It's awesome.
- Work is good?
- Work is good.
Work is good.
- Hey, how's that piece
coming along?
- Hey, it's not.
It's...
a special about the future
of medicine.
It's supposed to be hopeful.
And now I don't have
a story at all.
- What about him?
- Shift the focus
to him, you know?
"Dr. Macchiarini,
Miracle Man"--
a look at the pioneer
of generational medicine.
- Regenerative.
- Exactly.
- But then what about Hannah?
- She'd still be part
of the main story.
Medical breakthroughs
are always paved with setbacks.
It doesn't mean
that Macchiarini's work
isn't worth believing in.
* *
- Hold on to the hopeful.
- If anybody can make
it happen, it's you.
* *
When did the pain start?
- Um, off and on
for the last few weeks.
I just thought it was stress
or something.
- Would you describe the pain
as sharp, dull, or burning?
- Sharp, like--
- Aah!
Like someone's
stabbing me. Ow.
- Let's get a CBC,
liver enzymes,
urine test, and a CT
of the abdomen and pelvis,
plus 30 milligrams
of Toradol for the pain.
- So it's my appendix?
- It's not your appendix.
- What?
No, no, no, no, no.
I have a daughter.
She's nine years old.
She just lost her father.
I can't have something wrong
with me.
- We just need to run some
tests to see what's going on.
- Doctor, they're waiting.
- Is there anyone
you want to call?
- Hi, excuse me.
Hi.
- Hi.
Thank you for coming.
I'm sorry.
- No, no, I'm glad you called.
Has the pain subsided?
- No.
I think it's worse, actually.
- What did the doctor say?
- Nothing.
They just ran a bunch of tests,
and no one's told me anything.
I've just been sitting here
by myself.
- You CT scan
shows uterine fibroids.
- What? What is that?
Is that cancer?
- Not at all.
They're very common.
Is it okay if I take a look?
- Yeah.
- Yeah?
- Okay.
- This might hurt a little bit.
- Okay. All right.
Okay.
Yeah, I can feel two.
They're about the size
of grapefruits.
- What?
- It sounds much worse
than what it is.
Don't worry.
They will have them removed.
- So I have to have surgery?
- Yeah, but it's
a very common procedure.
I'm sure your doctor will walk
you through everything.
You're gonna be fine.
Trust me.
* *
- He's got you
working late already?
- I'm preparing.
It's something doctors do.
You should try it.
- Noted.
- I'll sleep
when I'm published.
- Why don't you like him?
- I don't really like anybody.
- That's true.
Still, so few surgeons want to
operate on the throat at all,
and he throws in
stem-cell regeneration.
Aren't you interested
in his work?
- Yes, yes,
I find it all very...
interesting.
- You're an ass.
Look at this.
He has to identify the surgical
planes bordering the trachea,
avoid tumor dissemination,
all without exposing
the larynx,
the thyroid, the esophagus.
Say what you want.
Dr. Macchiarini's
got some balls.
- I guess that's what it takes,
huh--some nice big balls?
- Sorry, I didn't mean
to offend you.
- Yes, I have tiny balls.
You know, a good surgeon
knows when not to cut.
- Fuck that. I'm tired of being
on the verge of something.
Too afraid to make the cut--
this is groundbreaking work.
I'm getting in.
- Just watch your back.
- I always do.
* *
- Dr. Svensson.
- Dr. Macchiarini?
Uh...
- Oh, the trials seem
to be proceeding nicely.
- Uh, yes.
Um, we're on schedule.
- Good.
Any exciting conclusions
so far?
- Well, nothing--
you know, nothing
really determinable yet.
Of course, I won't be able
to truly discern
any results until--
- Yeah, until you completed
the trials, of course.
As you can imagine,
I'm--I'm very anxious
to see any results--
positive or otherwise.
- Well, on the test rats
that have received
synthetic tracheas,
so far none
have responded negatively.
- Well, that--
that is excellent.
- But as you said,
we're still gathering data.
Uh...
the purpose of this trial
is to witness
objective results, of course.
- Of course, of course.
- May I ask, is there
anything in particular
that is concerning you?
- Oh, no, not at all.
I have complete faith
in your research, Doctor,
as well as my own.
I'll just leave you
to your work.
- Okay.
Yeah.
* *
- Thank you.
- Yeah, no problem.
Oh, thank you, thank you,
thank you.
Oh, my God, please.
- Wow, I wish I had
that effect on you.
- 48 hours without caffeine?
Who am I today?
- I spelled your name for them.
You're feeling better?
- Mm-hmm.
I am.
Like two grapefruits lighter.
Thank you, really.
- Pleasure.
- Paolo...
we've both been through a lot
of loss the past few months.
And I know I wasn't dying
in there, but I--
I was really scared, and it...
It just--
it put things
in perspective for me.
Us together, it could cost me
my job, my reputation,
but I think this thing we have,
it's worth the risk.
- For me, too.
* *
- You've heard the criticism--
that you're really taking
a chance with these patients.
What do you say to that?
- I was raised to believe
that if you...
if have even one chance,
you need to take it,
because either that
patient will die,
or we try to do something,
even if it's new.
As a doctor and--
and as a human being, I...
I ask myself, are we
allowed to say no?
I don't think we are.
- And when you got
that call later
that--that she had passed...
- Mm.
- It had to be devastating
for you.
- I couldn't stop thinking...
did I make the right decision?
Did I do everything
to save her?
There are so many patients
all around the world
who need this procedure.
We should really try
to achieve this
for all of them,
because even
in the face of failure,
we should keep hope alive.
* *
- Great job today, guys.
Dr. Macchiarini,
do you mind staying behind
for a few minutes
to go over the schedule?
- Good night.
* *
- Of course.
So?
- So...
Well, I have some
follow-up questions for you
that are gonna happen...
- Really?
- Behind closed doors, yeah.
- I'm so sorry you had
to go through this.
- It's okay.
It's just gonna be a scar.
- One day we will live
in a world
where we won't have to cut
people open to fix them.
You'll see.
- Do you ever have any doubts?
- Of course I do.
- Really?
- Mm-hmm.
- 'Cause you seem so sure
of all of it.
Even the things
that could go wrong,
that have gone wrong...
you just keep moving forward.
- I think a lot about the ones
who came before me.
Like Thomas Starzl--
he started
the first liver transplants.
His first patients died.
- Hmm.
- Or Christiaan Barnard...
he performed
the first heart transplant.
People threw rocks at him.
Everybody thought he was crazy.
- I'm sure people
looked at him the same way
that you're looking
at me right now.
* *
When Hannah died,
I did lose faith.
But these doctors, they--
they believed, they worked,
they persevered
until they found their way.
Being the one
to try something new,
no matter the personal cost,
is vital
to move medicine forward.
It's vital.
And I believe that the work
that we're doing
is going to save many lives.
- I believe it will, too.
* *
- Hi, my love. I'm here,
missing you in Barcelona.
The lemon trees
are ready for you.
- Oh, there is a sushi roll
with my name on it.
Benita?
- Hmm? Oh, yeah, lunch.
- You ready?
- Sorry. Yeah.
- Good.
* *
- Mm.
- Come on, come on...
* *
No, I hear you.
The information is great.
But I'm going to need
another source on it
to confirm her account.
Sure.
Could you email that to me?
Wow, that sounds good.
Yeah.
- It's Lizzi. Okay.
- I'll miss you.
- Yeah.
Sure.
It's okay with me.
If it's okay with Aubrey's mom,
you can sleep over.
Okay. I love you, too.
Bye.
- Did you say "sleep over"?
- Yeah.
- Maybe I could change
my flight.
- Oh, I didn't know
that was an option.
- Mm-hmm.
* *
- What?
- The Stones are sexier.
- No, no, no.
- That's it.
- How can you
even compare them?
- I've always thought this,
and I'm not going to apologize.
- "Blackbird," um...
"Martha My Dear,"
"While My Guitar Gently Weeps,"
"Rocky Raccoon."
- Okay, now we're listing
songs?
- Yeah.
- "Satisfaction"...
- Oh.
- "Gimme Shelter,"
"Sympathy for the Devil."
- No.
No, we can't have
this conversation.
This is terrible.
Now I have to leave you.
- Are you gonna leave me?
- I'm gonna leave you.
- Are you gonna leave me
for The Beatles?
- This is a very, very...
- They're almost--
All of them are dead, almost.
- Important distinction.
- Italian "Vogue,"
nice touch.
- For Lizzi.
- Ah.
Hey, Lizzi?
My friend Paolo is here.
- Your "friend"?
- My friend.
* *
- "Cacio" means "cheese,"
and "pepe" means "pepper."
So it's like Italian
mac and cheese.
And pepper, you know, "pepe."
- It's delicious, right?
What do you think, kiddo?
- I don't like it.
* *
- Your mom tells me
that you play the violin.
- She does, yeah.
- Yeah?
- She practices every day.
Sometimes I don't even have
to ask her to practice.
- Oh, wow.
That's impressive.
It's impressive,
'cause I used to play
the piano when I was your age,
but I hated to practice.
Well, maybe we
can play together.
You--you play the violin,
and I play the piano.
We make a concert for your mom.
* *
Mm.
Did you hear what happened
when Johann Sebastian Bach
dropped his violin?
It Baroque.
It Ba-roque.
- Ba-roque, that's funny.
- Can I go to my room?
- Lizzi, come on, please.
No, it's okay.
But, Lizzi...
I know that you're feeling
a thousand things right now,
all at once.
And I'm ready to wait
for as long as it takes
for you to figure out
how you feel about me.
But I'll make you a deal.
If you let me show you
how much I care about your mom,
I promise you
I will never make you eat
my cacio e pepe again.
Accordo?
* *
- Accordo.
- Good night.
She'll get there.
It takes time.
* *
It's really good.
- But you got it, right,
Baroque?
- I got Baroque.
- Okay.
- Yeah, it's a cute joke.
* *
Hey, three more pages, then
jammies and lights out, okay?
- Okay.
* *
- I love you.
- I love you, too.
- Good night.
- Hey, Mom?
* *
I like his accent.
- What? Are you kidding me?
You cooked.
Get out of here.
- What?
- I have bad news.
Our trip to Barcelona--
- No!
- I have to cancel.
- Oh.
- Uh, there's--
there's a new patient
I need to meet in Moscow.
- I was so looking forward
to finally seeing your place.
- I know, my love,
and I'm so sorry,
but if she agrees to surgery,
this could launch funding
for the entire lab.
- No, I-I get it, I get it.
I just, um...
have to figure out what to tell
Kim and everybody else,
'cause I already took time off.
And I have Laura coming
to stay with Lizzi and--
- Why don't you come with me?
- To Russia?
- To Moscow.
I can show you off in Moscow.
I don't know.
- Oh, come on, Benita,
I want to spend time with you
without having to hide--please.
- We have to wait
until the special airs
before we tell
anybody anything.
- I'm sure our secret
will be safe in Russia.
Please come with me.
Please, come with me.
- Okay.
I mean, who--
who am I to say no
to the great Dr. Macchiarini.
* *
- Accessing the cricoid ring.
I see severe infection,
most likely caused
by the excessive radiation
treatments on the patient.
The cartilage is necrotic.
If the tumor hadn't killed him,
it would have been only
a matter of time
before he succumbed
to infection.
* *
Knife.
Starting resection.
The biosynthetic trachea
will fit perfectly
in the resected area.
* *
Metzenbaum.
Okay.
* *
Okay, switch the oxygen input.
Saline.
Any leaks in the trachea will
produce bubbles in the saline.
* *
Pulse ox?
- Holding steady.
* *
- No signs of leaking.
- Oxygen holding, 98%.
- It's working.
- Congratulations, Doctor.
- Okay, let's close him up.
Doctor?
- BP's dropping.
- He's bleeding.
- Vitals are weakening.
- No, it can't be.
The implant is working.
Where is this blood
coming from?
Doctor?
The left carotid's
most likely ruptured.
- No, I didn't touch it.
I wasn't even near it.
- You said there was
radiation damage.
- Losing OX.
- It must have weakened
the vascular wall.
- Doctor.
- Blood pressure is dropping.
- Doctor, we need to do
something.
- Doctor?
- Losing oxygen.
Paolo!
I can fix this.
- He needs to be stabilized.
- Suction?
- Blood pressure is dropping.
* *
- Found it.
Cautery.
* *
BP is on the rise.
- He's stable.
Sutures for Dr. Macchiarini.
- You should close him.
* *
All right, my love, this way.
- I was texting with Lizzi
about setting up
our Skype call.
- Mm-hmm?
- And she specifically asked
for you to jump on.
- Oh, she did?
- Yeah.
You charmed her,
you big charmer.
- Pardon me.
Uh, compliments
of the gentleman at the bar.
* *
- Thank you.
- To you, to me,
and to ice buckets, always.
Cheers.
So who is our benefactor
this evening?
- I shouldn't say.
- Paolo, come on.
I protect sources for a living.
- He's a Russian oligarch,
very connected.
No, don't look.
There is a network
of high-profile patients,
celebrities, clergy, presidents
that are treated in secret,
that I treat in secret.
Because of who they are,
I have to keep
our arrangement quiet.
- Presidents,
like U.S. presidents?
- Paolo Macchiarini,
surgeon to the stars?
Okay.
I--Somebody's got
to do it, right?
- Shh, they're coming.
- Oh.
- Yulia,
this is Benita Alexander.
- Paolo, good to see you.
- It's nice to meet you.
If you're trying
to impress me, Doctor,
it's--it's working.
- Yulia, my dear,
for you, only the best.
- Uh, Paolo tells me
you're a dancer.
The best in Russia.
- I met Andrej not long
after I joined the Bolshoi.
- I saw her perform
in "Swan Lake."
She was magnificent.
- I was only part of the corps
de ballet, not the soloist.
- Still, I could not
take my eyes off of her.
- While I was on tour
in London a few years ago,
I was involved
in a horrible car accident.
- It's a miracle
she's even alive.
- My windpipe was broken.
My...
Everything was broken.
And it left me
with this hole in my neck.
- I'm so sorry.
- The past is a lighthouse,
not a port.
I found Dr. Macchiarini.
- Up until now,
we have implanted
only patients
for compassionate use,
those who otherwise would die.
But you have shown me
that quality of life
is nearly as important
as life itself.
- So this is
an elective surgery?
- Yeah.
- Mm.
A part of me
hopes it will allow me
to dance again, but, mostly...
we have
a two-year-old son, Sasha.
I want to play with him...
Sing him a lullaby.
- And you're
the perfect candidate.
You're young, healthy,
no other medical issues
that would complicate matters.
You-- you're ready.
- Mm. I really don't
want to go to Sweden.
I wish you were set up
to operate in Russia.
- Then I have great news
for you.
Our colleague, Dr. Lasbrey,
is setting up facilities
in Krasnodar as we speak.
Your procedure will launch
our work here in Russia, Yulia.
You will have
your operation here.
- To Dr. Paolo Macchiarini...
- Ah.
- Our rock-star surgeon.
- Mm.
- You okay?
- Mm-hmm.
- Yeah?
- Yeah, I'm okay.
* *
- This ballet
was first performed in 1871.
You know--
Are you okay?
Hey. Hey, hey, hey, my love.
Hey, are you okay?
- I'm sorry.
I don't think I can--
- No, no, no, we'll go home.
No, we'll go. I text you.
No, she's--
I'll text you, okay?
Let's go.
- Are you sure? Should I--
- Yes.
Yeah, yeah.
* *
- You're getting worse.
You should have let me take you
to the hospital.
- No, I just want to lie down.
- You're burning up.
- Mm. I feel sick.
- Let me check something.
The surgical site is infected.
- What? There's no way.
That was months ago.
It's got to be healed by now.
- No, it's not.
* *
- So--so what,
antibiotics or something?
- No, it's too late for that.
You're in sepsis.
I need to debride your wound.
Otherwise,
you will go into shock.
- "Debride"?
What does that mean?
You're gonna be okay.
Do you trust me?
* *
- Mm-hmm.
- "Two months
after transplantation,
"the patient is asymptomatic,
"breathes normally,
and is tumor free.
"These results are evidence
"that a successful
organ-regeneration strategy
has been accomplished."
"And the procedure's
success provides proof
of the viability
of this approach."
To Dr. Macchiarini,
who dared to make the cut.
Cheers.
- To Andemariam Beyene,
who bravely risked his life
for science.
Cheers.
And last but not least,
to The motherfucking "Lancet"
for publishing
our research article.
Cheers!
- Skol,Anders.
- Nathan, tack.
- So published
in "The Lancet"--
you're halfway to a Nobel.
This is shit.
You'd think they would have
sprung for better bubbly.
- Then feel free
to steal someone else's.
- Fantastic.
- Cheers.
- I'm surprised
to see you here,
knowing how you feel
about Dr. Macchiarini.
- Well, free champagne
is free champagne--
or whatever this is.
- Of course.
- You must all be
on cloud nine.
- I'm excited, of course,
though I also have
the feeling of--
What do you call it?
Impostor's syndrome.
- Why?
You're running
Macchiarini's rat trials.
- Which are still in progress.
Macchiarini included
my name in the byline,
but I have yet to submit
my results.
- Welcome to the world
of scientific publishing.
As I recall someone
once saying,
"Competition fuels progress."
* *
- Okay.
- Here we go.
Watch out for the chair.
Yeah, but I can't
watch anything.
Okay.
- Okay, you can open your eyes.
- No.
- You said you wanted
to start playing again.
- We can do a duet.
- Wow.
Yeah, we can do a duet.
This is incredible.
Thank you.
Careful with your stitches.
- Aw.
- Love, come here.
Thank you so much.
Wow, this is so cool.
But first, I have to
remember how to play.
- Oh, let me get my phone.
- This is so cool.
Thank you.
* *
- * Knowing I'll be missing *
* Christmas Eve
in my hometown *
- Thank you.
- Mm.
- Are you okay?
- Yeah.
Christmas, family...
holidays, you know?
- It makes you sad?
- Not really, not this year.
We feel like a family.
- You read my mind.
Lizzi.
- Wait.
Hold on.
What--what is going on?
This feels like collusion.
* *
* Through dreams
and just pretending *
* I'm there,
and I'll be spending *
* Christmas Eve
in my hometown *
- What do you say, Mom?
- What do you say?
- * In my hometown *
* *
- Hey, come in.
- Hello.
- Hi.
Please come in.
Look...
Mr. Beyene sent it.
- Oh.
- It's nice, isn't it?
- Yeah.
- I wish our work
always ended like that.
- Yes.
Thank you
for sharing that with me.
- Sometimes it's nice
to be reminded why we--
- Sacrifice.
- So you, too?
- Oh, you know, nothing big--
just girlfriends, children,
probably a few years
off my life.
- Well, maybe we can build
something together
that will make it
all worthwhile.
- I think we can.
- The funding
for our transplant research
is about to run out.
- I'm sure "The Lancet" article
garnered some attention.
- Yes, we can capitalize
on that momentum
to secure a new grant,
which will lead
to more surgeries
and to more money.
- Around and around.
- Until we can expand...
globally.
The goal is six operations
within the next three months.
- You can produce that many
custom tracheas in that time?
- Yes, it can be done.
But we need more patients.
- Then let's find
more patients.
* *