- Crowds have gathered today
to hear the verdict
of the Swedish
police investigation
into celebrity surgeon
Paolo Macchiarini,
who has been accused
of medical misconduct.
Officials are hoping
for an indictment
to be issued today in the case
that has taken the global
medical community by storm.
* *
- Do you trust me?
- Oh!
- Oh, my goodness!
* *
- Hello, Keziah.
- The recellularization
is complete, Doctor.
- Wonderful.
* *
Now I need you
to count back from 100.
* *
Knife.
- * She was the one,
she was the one *
* She was the one.
- * She was the one,
she was the one *
* *
- I'm not here
to talk about politics.
- Benita?
- Yeah?
- Have you seen our girl?
- Shoot!
Mm.
- Happy birthday!
Oh. You're ringing.
- Oh.
Hello?
* *
- Always making
such a racket, B.
- Says the guy dragging me
to the hospital at 1:00 a.m.
What happened?
- Ask him.
- Hi.
Is he okay?
- Yes.
Uh, is this your wife?
both: Ex.
- Okay, well, John was admitted
after he was found unconscious
in his apartment.
I've left word
for your oncologist,
but this is likely caused
by the brain tumor.
- So does that mean
the treatment is not working?
- It doesn't mean
anything for sure.
But your doctor has discussed
your prognosis?
- Yeah, we know.
My chances are slim.
- 6%. 6%.
That's the number they love
to throw around all the time,
but someone's got
to be the 6%, right?
Right.
Well, I'll go check
your bloodwork.
Just, uh, sit tight.
- Yeah, I'll be right here.
- You look good, B.
- It was
Kimmy's birthday tonight.
- Well, I saved you
from a wicked hangover.
- Yeah.
- You're welcome.
So what do we tell Lizzi?
- We wait.
You just started
this round of treatment.
We don't have
any of the answers yet,
so I think we wait.
- Okay.
Okay. Yeah.
But, Benita...
I'm sick.
- Someone's got to be
the 6%, John.
* *
- Morning, Benita.
- Morning, Larry.
This is for me, right?
- Yep.
- Thank you.
- Morning, Benita.
- Good morning.
Oh, I have pitches for you.
- Great.
- Lunch?
- Sure.
Meet you in the commissary?
- Yuck. See you then.
Oh, you have my fugitive story?
- Uh...
- Tomorrow. I mean it.
Ah, good morning to you.
- I did shots.
Yeah, you did.
- Sorry I had to take off.
- Oh, God, please.
You don't need--
I'm sorry.
How is he?
- The same.
We can skip the condolences.
- Sure, whatever you need.
Aw, that's pretty.
- Those are John's.
He asked me to look after
them while he's, you know...
Those are his favorite.
Work is good.
Work is good. Work is good.
- Copy that.
Work is good.
- I've been trying
to get an angle
on this medical piece
for a TV special I'm producing.
- Generational medicine?
- Regenerative medicine.
- Sure.
- I read this piece
in "The Times"
about this little girl
who needs a new windpipe,
and her family's working
with this doctor in Europe
who's developing
artificial organs.
- Medical miracles?
- Ooh, I hate that word--
"miracle."
- I don't hate this guy.
- That's the doctor.
He's actually got
a pretty impressive CV.
He's worked
all around the world,
published in "The Lancet,"
research grants
out of Karolinska.
It's where they give out
the Nobel Prize.
- Hmm.
- And he's Italian.
- Mm.
Roma or Olive Garden?
- I don't know.
- So...
who are we today?
Oh.
Bina.
That's cute.
- So this little girl--
she lives in this tiny town,
Yongsan-gu.
- Korea?
- Yeah.
But she's coming to the States
for her surgery--that's her.
That's Hannah Warren.
- This is
a really good story, B.
- It is, right?
- Mm-hmm.
- I like it. It's...
it's really hopeful.
* *
- Yeah, this is worth
missing lunch for.
- Fuck off.
This guy's brilliant.
Did you read the material?
- I'm getting there.
- It's really interesting.
- You having trouble there?
- A little bit.
- I think it's this one here.
- Ah, this one, yeah.
Okay.
- There you go.
All good?
- Yeah, all good, yeah.
- It works.
- Awesome. Thank you.
- Okay, great.
uh, colleagues, good afternoon.
It's great to see
such a wide spectrum of fields
represented here today.
I only wish some
of my own lectures
could get crowds like this.
Now, I'm sure
you're all eager to hear
from Karolinska's
newest addition.
He is a professor, researcher,
and thoracic surgeon--
Dr. Paolo Macchiarini.
- Thank you, Provost Hedley.
I'm simply happy
that you will have me here
working in this
incredible institution.
"God breathed into Adam
the breath of life,
and he became man"--
Genesis 2:7.
Breath is the essence of life,
the one thing
that comes naturally
to all of us from birth--
to breathe.
When a patient has
a damaged trachea,
our options, unfortunately,
have been very limited.
Tracheostomies allow patients
to live, yes,
but with what quality of life?
The focus of my research
is tracheal transplants
with the help of stem cells--
"the God cells" as they
have been called recently.
We harvest the donor trachea
from a cadaver
and strip it
of the donor cells.
Then we reseed the organ
with the patient's stem cells,
preparing it for implantation.
I have successfully applied
this technique
to multiple patients
around the world--
most recently
to a 19-year-old patient
named Keziah Shorten in London.
She was diagnosed
with adenoid cystic carcinoma
and only had months to live.
Now, two months
after the operation,
she's healthy and happy
with her donor trachea.
* *
This is an exciting step,
but it is still
a very flawed process.
Why?
Because of the donors.
We always have to wait
for the perfect-size trachea.
So I thought,
what if we skip that step?
And so we did.
We were able to eliminate
the donors altogether
by developing
biosynthetic tracheas--
custom-designed
to fit the individual patient.
Using the same process,
we seed the trachea
with the patient's stem cells,
transforming it
into a living organ.
We have conducted swine trials
with just incredible results.
Look at those happy pigs.
And that brings us here today,
where I'm happy to announce
the final phase of our work--
the very first human
biosynthetic transplant
to take place
right here at Karolinska.
Once we conquer the trachea,
we'll be able to expand
our work to heart valves,
blood vessels,
even entire organs.
The potential
for this technology is endless.
Imagine for a moment
buying a 3D-printed organ
off the shelf,
like groceries
from a supermarket.
Imagine a world where
no human being will ever die
while waiting
for an organ donor.
Imagine this...
the future of medicine...
the future
that we will build together.
* *
Thank you.
- Ah, Dr. Lasbrey,
let me introduce you.
- Dr. Macchiarini.
- Oh, please call me Paolo.
- Paolo, wonderful to meet you.
- Thank you.
- I've been following
your research closely,
since your first bronchus
transplants in Barcelona.
- Oh, thank you.
That's very flattering.
- Uh, Dr. Lasbrey's
a cardiothoracic surgeon.
Uh, she's been working
on some stem-cell-regeneration
research of her own.
- Oh.
- My focus is vascular repair--
blood vessel regeneration.
I've had some progress,
but I never thought
to recellularize
a bioartificial graft.
Do you build the scaffolds
to replicate the porousness
of real tracheal cartilage?
- Exactly.
- So you're basically tricking
the body
into thinking the implant's
already a part of you.
Well, I haven't really thought
about it that way, but, yes,
that's exactly it, yeah.
- It's brilliant.
- Oh.
- The broad applications
for technology like this--
- How?
H-h-how do you trick them?
More specifically,
h-how does a synthetic cell
create blood vessels,
uh, basal layers,
and fend off bacteria?
- And this is Dr. Gamelli,
also one
of our cardiothoracic surgeons.
He'll be in charge
of post-operative care
for any patients you bring
to Karolinska.
- What's up?
- Very nice to meet you.
Dr. Gamelli, I could walk you
through the research again,
if you like.
- That's very thoughtful
of you.
- Yes, well, we are hopeful
that Dr. Macchiarini's research
will establish Karolinska
as the world leader
in regenerative medicine.
Perhaps he'll even bring
the Nobel home.
- Oh, well, we're just
at the beginning of our work.
- But the implications
for future transplants
are historic.
- Dr. Lasbrey, would you--
would you be interested
in assisting on
the first transplant patient?
- "Interested" isn't exactly
how I'd put it.
- Then it's done.
- Oh, thank you, really.
I-I'm honored.
Welcome to the team.
- I do wonder,
as it relates to my research,
how are the grafts transformed
into living cells?
How do they come alive?
It's, uh...
it's like magic.
* *
- Benita.
- You were supposed to be here
at 3:00, Dr. Macchiarini.
- I'm so sorry. I was riding,
and I went over a bridge
that was supposed
to take me to Brooklyn,
when, in fact, I was already
in Brooklyn.
So that bridge took me
to Staten Island,
which was very interesting
but very far away.
So I'm deeply, deeply sorry
to keep you waiting.
- I guess picturing you
on that bike
crossing the Verrazzano Bridge
might be punishment enough.
Verrazzano Bridge is the name?
- Can I get you something, sir?
- Um, an espresso with sugar.
- Regular sugar or, um...
Uh, sorry.
Ah, oui.
Okay.
I mean, sugar is sugar,
as long as it's sweet, okay?
Merci beaucoup.
- How many languages
do you speak, Dr. Macchiarini?
- Um, one I speak okay,
six very poorly.
- Which one is okay?
- No one will tell me.
Do you bring that
everywhere you go?
- That is rented--
guilty pleasure.
- Why guilty?
- Do you ride?
- Uh, I did,
a long time ago.
- Well, maybe you
will ride again.
- As I said on the phone,
I'm producing a special
on regenerative medicine,
and I'm very interested
in your upcoming operation
on Hannah Warren.
Is this okay?
- Yeah.
- Tell me about it.
- She was born
with a congenital anomaly
called tracheal agenesis.
Very rare.
- Mm.
- Her windpipe
never fully developed,
so she's never been able
to breathe on her own.
She's never been able
to even leave the hospital.
It's a tragedy.
She's stuck in a bed,
not being able to--
to go outside, to play,
to--to run, to eat lollipops...
to be a kid.
Do you have children?
- I have a 9-year-old daughter.
- Can you imagine
if your daughter
never tasted a lollipop?
- No. No, I can't.
- Yeah, that's--that's Hannah.
Do you mind if we--
Should we take a walk outside?
- Sure.
- Yeah.
I think it's better, yeah.
- Okay.
So this is the first artificial
trachea transplant in the U.S.,
and you chose Chicago because
of Hannah's pediatrician?
- Yes. He works
at a Catholic hospital,
and they're funding
the operation.
- The Catholic Church
doesn't mind supporting
stem cell research?
- Well, actually there is, uh--
there is a high commission
at the Vatican involved
in stem cell research.
- Really?
- Yeah.
It's not only that.
They really want
to help Hannah.
They--they believe
she's been sent to us by God.
- Sent to you for a miracle?
Is that what you want to be
known for--performing miracles?
Well...
That sounds a little--
a little too--
What's the word you use here?
Um, h-hokey?
- Hokey, yeah.
- Hokey, yeah, sounds--
- Just a little hokey,
Dr. Macchiarini.
- Too much.
- So, even though
you've performed
this operation before,
Hannah will be the youngest
patient of yours
to ever receive
a biosynthetic transplant.
- That's correct.
- Does that give you pause?
- I've been thinking lately
that my entire career,
maybe even my entire life
has led me here...
to this little girl,
who definitely needs this
more than anyone.
- It's still an extremely
experimental procedure.
- Yeah, it is.
It's new. It's complicated.
It's a little controversial.
We have to fight really hard
to get permission
to operate here in the U.S.
But without it,
Hannah will certainly die.
So, if there's one chance
to save one person,
I think it's worth the risk.
- So I'm doing a story,
and I want Hannah's journey
to be the focus of the piece.
Actually, I was hoping that you
might be able to put me
in touch
with the Warrens directly.
- Okay, I'll see what I can do.
- Great.
All right, Doctor, it's
officially after work hours.
I have to go pick up
my daughter.
- What's her name?
- Her name is Lizzi.
- Lizzi.
- Mm.
- Well, I hope I get to hear
more about her
next time we meet.
- I hope you're on time
Okay.
* *
- Huh.
Okay, driving car,
honking, beep, beep.
- Cars, uh, traffic?
Traffic! Traffic.
Okay, traffic.
- Okay, okay.
- Wait, where'd we go?
- Butter bread?
Toast?
- Peanut butter?
- Traffic--
traffic peanut butter!
- Okay, time's up.
- Traffic jam!
all: Oh!
I love traffic
peanut butter, though.
But she was like, yes.
- All right, it's bedtime
for one of us.
- Mom.
- No, I gave you
an extra half hour, kiddo.
Come here.
Mom, I can't breathe.
- I know, but I'm gonna be
at the airport
when you wake up
in the morning,
and Laura's gonna
take you to school.
- Why can't Daddy just take me?
- 'Cause he's still
not feeling well.
But we're gonna go visit him
as soon as I get back.
I promise you, okay?
All right, brush, jammies,
wash, bed, please.
I'll be right in.
- Night.
- I'm a monster.
- Stop it.
How long are you gonna be
in Chicago?
- Too long.
You would think that leaving
would get easier,
but it does not.
- Well, maybe you can distract
yourself by playing doctor.
Oh, stop it.
Is he single?
- Divorced.
- Ah, see?
Look at you checking his stats.
- Don't be ridiculous.
He's a source.
- Not even a sexy,
charming doctor source
is worth getting fired over.
- Uh, if I can handle myself
around sexy, charming Obama,
I can handle myself
around sexy, charming doctor.
- I know, I know.
I'm just kidding.
both:
You don't fuck your sources.
- Thank you.
- Well, he's not my source.
So, if you need
an Italian translator,
just put in a good word for me.
- Oh.
- If it comes up naturally.
- I'm just saying.
Yeah.
- Hey, that doesn't sound
like brushing to me.
- Okay, okay.
- How's John?
- You know.
- Getting worse?
- I don't know
what I'm gonna do, Kim.
- You're a great mother, B.
Just...
follow your instincts.
- I don't think
I have instincts
when it comes
to something like this.
* *
Svensson--scientist.
Macchiarini--genius.
Well, that is an interesting
way to say hello.
Hi, I'm Paolo.
Not so much a genius.
- Anders Svensson,
not so much scientist.
He's a little shit.
Oh, I'm delighted to meet you,
Dr. Macchiarini.
- Thank you.
- The whole building is--zzz--
buzzing about your arrival.
I'm sorry to have missed
your lecture.
I've been busy with my friends
here, I'm afraid--
a heart study.
- Yeah, yeah, not at all.
I'm actually very glad
to meet you.
I read your research
on progenitor cell functions
in skin regeneration--
very interesting.
- Thank you.
- So these are your friends.
- Yes.
- Eric, Gunnar.
So you give them names.
- Ah, busted!
Well, I...
I know maybe I shouldn't,
but sitting
in these labs all day,
it all quickly become numbers,
gene strains in your head.
It's easy to forget we deal
with real life and death.
So I name the rats.
So here's Mikael 7.
He's a bit of a rascal.
Lost his appetite.
- So, Doctor, um,
I'm very sorry
to come to you right away
with a favor, but here I am.
- No, uh, please.
- I was wondering
if you would be interested
in collaborating on rat trials
to test our tracheas.
Wow. I--
Ooh, I'd be honored. I--
But if I've heard correctly,
you've already completed
swine trials.
- Yeah,
and they went very well,
but, you know, the more trials,
the better.
- I couldn't agree more.
Ah, methodology is a lost art.
- So you will be interested
in conducting the trials?
Ooh-cha-cha!
- Absolutely.
I'd be honored.
- Yeah, fantastic.
Welcome to the team.
- Ah.
* *
- Hey.
- Hi.
My key card's not working.
- Mine neither.
- Well, the woman said
she'd be right back.
I don't know--I thought I'd try
to get a little work done
in the meantime.
- Gambling?
- What?
- Are you a gambler?
- Oh, no. No.
These are--these are
conversation cards.
- What is that?
- They're kind of like
conversation starters.
- May I?
- Yeah, yeah.
I...I found them
when I was young.
They were my grandmother's,
I think.
My family's a little...
But, uh, they're kind of my
secret weapon for interviews.
- Mm, they are?
both: Mm-hmm.
Yeah, people get nervous when
they have to answer questions.
- Ah, of course.
- And this kind of makes it
like a little game.
I just say, pick a card.
- I don't know.
I think it works.
- Ah, I'm sure they do.
Your subjects are so relaxed,
it's like they're
not even on camera.
- Thank you.
- Yeah.
- You are very good
on camera, you know.
- No, no, not at first.
I could use your cards.
- Actually, I-I did.
I did use one of them
on you already.
- You did?
- Mm-hmm.
Mm, yeah.
"If you could be famous for
one thing, what would it be"?
- And you never answered
the question.
- And I'm never going to.
- Okay.
Well, then go ahead
and pick another card.
Go for it.
"Tell me a story
about your childhood fear."
Okay.
Well, life was difficult
when I was a boy.
My mom is Italian,
but I never really felt
Italian myself.
It was just the two of us.
We moved very often.
Spain, of course, but before
that, it was Switzerland.
And that was lonely.
That feeling,
that was my fear--
being an immigrant,
underestimated, isolated.
I held on to that feeling
for a very long time,
and--and I never wanted
to feel that way ever again.
- Miss, I'm so sorry
for the delay.
- Oh, thank you.
- You're welcome.
- Uh, miss, sorry,
could you help me, too, please?
- Oh, yes, of course.
- Thank you.
- I thought you were gonna
say spiders or something.
- Mm.
- Yeah, here's the pink one.
Or should we do that?
She was, um--she was blue
when she came out.
And, uh, we, uh--we just--
we begged her.
We said, cry, baby girl, cry.
And, um, they were able to find
a, uh--a tiny hole
leading to her lungs there,
but they said she would never
leave the hospital, you know,
that she wouldn't survive.
So I, um--I did a, uh, uh--
I did--I did a Google search
on--on trachea surgeries,
and I just started
seeing more and more
about Dr. Macchiarini's
groundbreaking transplants--
you know, the Miracle Man.
So she just needs
one thing, right?
Yeah.
And that's a windpipe
right there.
And then everything's
going to be fine, okay?
- We will monitor her
for a few more days
while we prepare the trachea.
We have discussed
the details...
at length, the risks.
It is a very difficult surgery.
- We have tried everything.
You were the only one willing.
You were the only one
who gave us hope.
You are the one who will give
her a chance to live.
Yeah.
I will try my best.
- Believe me.
- Okay.
- Hmm.
- Yeah, thanks.
- Hmm?
Hello, Hannah.
Right?
Hmm, Hannah?
Hmm?
* *
I have sort of a tradition
when I travel.
I like to eat paella.
It's kind of like
a good-luck thing.
It reminds me of home.
Anyway, there's a restaurant,
a good one, close by.
Maybe you want to join me?
- Yeah.
- Yeah?
- That--that sounds great.
Hey, guys?
- Hmm?
- You want to join the doc
for dinner tonight?
- Sure, sounds good.
- Let's do it.
- Okay, yeah, just text me
the address.
- Okay.
- Yeah.
All right, let's go.
* *
- You didn't eat tonight.
- You were watching me eat?
- No, I was watching you
not eat.
- Is there anything I can do
about what is making you
so sad?
- How do you know I'm so sad?
- Anyone who's really looking
could see.
- It's my ex-husband, John.
It started with the headaches
and then the fainting
and forgetting, and...
and then they started throwing
around the word "terminal."
- Glioblastoma?
- Yeah.
- Is it operable?
- No, the--the tumor is
too deeply embedded in the--
No, it's not.
- I'm sorry.
- And, you know,
with our daughter...
- Lizzi.
- Lizzi, yeah.
You know, even though
we're not together,
it's always been
the three of us.
- Mm, I understand.
I have two children.
They're grown now, but when
their mother and I divorced,
it was difficult.
But, you know, children are
much stronger than we think.
Look at Hannah.
- I just keep
second-guessing myself--
what to tell her,
if I should tell her.
And then I get pissed
because I don't want to have
to tell her anything, you know?
And then I think,
maybe I shouldn't,
because I've been
doing all of this research.
And, you know, 6%--
that's what they
keep telling us, 6%.
Someone's got to be
the 6%, right?
- Benita...
I have seen
far too much death...
sudden, expected, certain.
You know your daughter,
so you know what's best.
But to be able
to say goodbye...
that is a gift.
* *
- Hi.
- Hey, welcome back.
She's in her room.
Mom, you're home early!
- Yeah. Just for the day.
I have to go back tomorrow.
- Oh, my God,
so I have to tell you this,
'cause I was going to tell you
this last night
whenever we talked.
But I wanted to see
what happened today
so I can tell you
the whole story.
I can't wait to hear
all about it.
But first, I wanted to talk
to you about your dad.
- Okay.
* *
It's that first door up here.
Knock, knock.
- Hi, sweetheart.
- Vasilyev to Orlov,
to Orlov again.
- You losing?
- Hey, there you are.
No, no, no, we're ahead.
Those Russian bastards,
they can't stop Zlatan.
- Skol.
- Cheers.
- Happy Hump Day happy hour!
- You're embarrassing.
Mm.
Marja?
You want me to ask
her out for you?
- No, don't--
- Hey, hey, hey.
It would be nice
for Wilma and I to have couples
for dinner.
- Well, I'm washing
my hair that night, so...
Oh.
- I heard you joined
Macchiarini's research team.
- Yes, new rat trials.
Uh, he, uh--uh...
- What?
- Well, I thought the point
of our...
Hump Day happy hour...
Is that you
don't have to talk about work.
- I'm a complicated man,
Anders.
Sorry. Apologize for that,
my language.
- Macchiarini.
- Yeah, his work
is exciting, no?
- Meh.
- "Meh"?
Your lack of interest
is decidedly uninteresting.
You think everyone is "meh."
- The science
doesn't seem sound.
- Well, you know,
it's not exactly
your kind of science--
no offense.
I said, no offense.
- I will admit I don't get it.
I don't understand
how a-a plastic trachea
can produce
its own blood supply.
- Well, stem cells.
- That's just it.
Stem cell research,
regenerative medicine--
it's--it's like an arms race.
Everybody's scrambling
for the most patents,
the most grants,
who can make the most money.
That's not how medicine works.
It's not how it should work.
If I wanted that world, I could
have stayed in New Jersey.
That's a penalty
every day in the week.
Oh, sorry, you were--
you--you were talking to me?
- Mm.
- Hey, I agree with you
on the science.
But this is the way it works.
Competition fuels progress.
- Now a lovely play,
through across...
- I-I...
Hey, oh, oh, hey!
All right.
I'm cool.
- I'm going--I'm going to make
it warm because it's cold.
See, it's cold.
Okay, Hannah, breathe.
Breathe in with me.
* *
You want me to check her, too?
Yes?
* *
Mm.
You want me to take that out?
Hmm? Yeah?
Hmm?
* *
We will tomorrow, yeah?
- Hi.
Uh, could I get
a glass of Malbec
to take up to my room, please?
Thanks.
- Sure.
- Hi.
- Is that Hannah's file?
- Yeah.
Just going through
the details again.
- You seem to have
a lot of rituals.
I didn't realize surgeons
were so superstitious.
- It's more like a prayer.
It doesn't matter
how many times
I perform these operations,
I always get nervous.
You think you're prepared,
but there can always be
something that you miss
that can cost a life.
- I...
cannot imagine the stress.
Someone's life in your hands...
But I have watched you
for a while now,
and the people around you,
your patients--
you really give them hope.
They trust you.
Maybe you should trust you.
* *
Good night, Doc.
- Knife.
* *
- Hey.
- She's okay?
* *
- The surgery went well.
Oh.
- There were no complications,
but she'll be asleep
for a while longer.
- What do we do now?
- Now we wait.
- Okay, Hannah, you're going
to give us a deep breath.
Another one.
* *
So how
are you feeling, then, huh?
Good!
She's feeling good.
We have a little present
for you.
Look, look.
Ah, what's that?
Oh, wow.
- Go ahead, honey.
Yeah.
* *
Good.
It tastes good, yeah?
- Oh.
She loves it.
- It tastes good.
* *
- Hey.
- Hi.
- Got some ice, huh?
- Uh-huh, yeah.
- Today was...
Unlike anything
I've ever seen.
I...
- So you're happy
with the ending of your story?
- It's hopeful, which is
what I was hoping for, yeah.
What you did...
It was a miracle.
- I wanted to say thank you...
For what you said to me
the night before the operation.
Those words...
they were more important
than you could possibly know.
* *
Paolo, I shouldn't.