(TRAIN HORN BLOWING)
(CLICKING TONGUE)
♪ What is man ♪
♪ That you are mindful of him, Lord ♪
♪ You made the stars ♪
♪ You made the sun ♪
♪ And all the worlds ♪
♪ That came to be at your command ♪
♪ What is man? ♪
♪ What has he done? ♪
♪ Then you crown him with glory ♪
♪ And with honor ♪
♪ Give him dominion ♪
♪ Over land and sea ♪
♪ And air ♪
♪ And store up an inheritance ♪
♪ In heaven ♪
♪ Oh, what is man ♪
♪ That you would care? ♪
Come here.
♪ What is man ♪
♪ That you would let him live at all ♪
♪ To shed the blood ♪
♪ Of his own kind ♪
♪ And ever fail ♪
♪ To even follow ♪
♪ Where you call ♪
♪ What is man? ♪
♪ Why do you mind? ♪
♪ Yet you crown me with glory ♪
♪ And with honor ♪
♪ Give me dominion ♪
♪ Over land... ♪
Impressive.
(CHUCKLES) Yes, she is.
♪ And store up my inheritance ♪
♪ In heaven ♪
♪ Oh, what is man ♪
♪ That you care? ♪
♪ What is man, Lord ♪
♪ That you would care? ♪
HARVARD: Can you believe it?
A murderess, right here
under our very own roof.
I'm loath to admit that this
wolf in sheep's clothing
had me bamboozled.
(LAUGHING): Presenting herself
as some kind of
paragon of virtue.
Hey, Dr. Fucko.
You remember me?
(GRUNTING) God...
Who the hell are you?
OFFICER: Mayflower, you made bail.
ORAETTA: Just so I'm in the know,
who was it, exactly,
paid for my release?
I have no idea.
Thank you for your hospitality.
Thank you.
(RAPID GUNFIRE)
You want this war over?
Get your house in order and we can talk.
I'll get back to you.
You do that.
(ENGINE STARTS)
Synced & corrected by QueenMaddie
www.addic7ed.com
(LAUGHTER)
Shit. We've driven every back road
from here to Canada trying
to avoid them bulls.
And just when we thinking we home free,
Pee Wee drives us
right up into the asshole
- of the Sioux Nation.
- (LAUGHTER)
Now, see, on they land,
they still the law.
Man, they took everything.
Booze, guns...
even the damn truck.
I tried to trade them
Pee Wee for the truck,
but it turns out they ain't got
no use for no retarded Negro.
(LAUGHTER)
JOE: Boss.
Boss.
What... What?
We got him.
- What?
- Cannon.
We got Cannon.
It's over.
We won.
- (LAUGHTER)
- (DOOR BELLS TINKLE)
He's dead.
You did it.
Come on.
Bang.
ORAETTA: Got very straight backs.
Oh, yeah.
Oh.
What's she doing here?
(SCOFFS) Very funny,
you Mr. Bail Poster.
What's going on?
Oh, shit!
(GUNFIRE)
What's going on?
I thought...
He said we got the guy.
Why aren't we celebrating?
_
He... he didn't make it.
What is this?
Josto Fadda...
_
What family? Whose family?
You have conspired with this woman
to kill your own father.
- What?
- Your papa...
when he was weak in the hospital.
When he was barely alive,
you asked this woman...
his nurse... to kill him.
That... that never happened.
- Uh...
- Sh... Shut up.
_
Tell him.
ORAETTA: Well, they asked so nice,
and, uh... (SHORT CHUCKLE)
I didn't think,
what with all the peashooters,
that I should lie.
I'm sorry, what is happening right now?
He was dying.
They shot him... those children?
Tell him!
ORAETTA: Yeah, like I said,
as an honest person who
likes to cross her T's
and heart her I's, I'd be remiss
if I didn't afford myself truthfully
in front of the Lord my savior
and, uh, and these fine gentlemen.
But, yeah. Y-Ya... Well, you kinda did.
Did what?
"He's in a lot of pain..."
you said, "and I don't like
to see him like that."
And-and-and you also said,
"Will you take care of him?"
(ORAETTA CHUCKLES BRIEFLY)
We...
We got high.
And then...
She's just a skirt I met the one time.
She was at the funeral.
- Two times!
- ORAETTA: Yeah, and, well,
let's not forget about all
those nights in my apartment.
She's a crazy person!
And I'm the boss!
_
Hmm?
So let's stop this make-believe.
I order you... I order you
to stop now.
_
It's shit, no?
The old way for the old world.
Brothers, uncles, cousins.
We live in the new world now.
We need a new way.
I'm gonna piss.
Are you kidding me?
Mm.
Can I at least get a fucking chair then?
The police say
you kill most of your patients.
I'm sure I don't know
what you mean. (SNIFFLES)
You were arrested for
the killing of your boss.
Well, I mean, but to be clear,
he got better.
This is the woman you choose?
- Un'assassina?
- I didn't ch...
She's a roll-around!
She liked it rough!
Oh, you like it rough.
If you're saying that I...
You thi...
_
How dare you.
You kill your father...
so you can wear the crown.
Then you kill your brother
so you don't have to share.
No, no, no, no, no.
EBAL: And this is why
the family business doesn't work.
Because families are crazy.
You're crazy.
Oh... (SCOFFS)
You can't do this.
Wait till I tell New York about this.
Fucking mutiny?
They'll chop your eyeballs out.
New York knows.
Yeah. (LAUGHS)
- Oh, geez, my heart.
- (FEET STOMPING)
I'm gonna kill you!
You-you... you full-blooded
Italian piece of shit!
You piece of shit!
- No! No, you... I pay you! You...
- Oh!
Now, you just hold your horses, sir!
My-my g... my neck, I've got a bad neck!
Josto!
(STOMPING CONTINUES)
They made me tell them.
I'm not talking to you.
You don't have to be mean.
I've had, and I don't mind saying...
as hard a 24 hours
as has ever been had
on God's green earth.
What do you think's happening right now?
- You killed us.
- I told the truth.
Now you tell the truth? Now?
How about when I said help with my dad,
why didn't you tell me
you were a demented hag?
Don't say that.
Hag.
- (GRUNTING)
- (SCREAMING)
- JOSTO: Hag! Hag!
- You... I said don't say that!
- Hey!
- Hag!
Cut it out.
♪ He is trampling out ♪
♪ The vintage ♪
♪ Where the grapes of wrath ♪
♪ Are stored ♪
♪ He hath loosed ♪
♪ The fateful lightning ♪
♪ Of His terrible ♪
♪ Swift sword ♪
♪ His truth ♪
♪ Is marching on... ♪
♪ Glory, glory ♪
♪ Hallelujah ♪
♪ His truth is... ♪
Get the fuck...
♪ Marching on ♪
Hey, I made some mistakes, okay?
But I didn't know about...
You don't have to do this.
Hasn't there been enough killing?
(LAUGHING)
(ORAETTA LAUGHING)
JOE: Wait.
That a serious question?
Listen to me.
This is it... What they make us do.
We're paisan.
Come on.
We-we change our names.
We eat each other. We forget.
For what?
Don't you get it, Joe?
This is a ladder,
but there's nowhere to go.
Nah.
Any last requests?
Yeah, uh, c-can you shoot
him first so I can watch?
What?
♪ I heard about a man one day ♪
♪ Who wasted not his time away ♪
♪ He prayed to God ♪
♪ He prayed to God every morning ♪
♪ Noon and night ♪
♪ He cared not for the king's decree ♪
♪ But trusted God to set him free ♪
♪ Oh, Daniel prayed ♪
♪ Oh, Daniel prayed every morning ♪
♪ Noon and night ♪
♪ He cared not for the king's decree ♪
♪ But trusted God to set him free ♪
♪ Oh, Daniel prayed ♪
♪ Oh, Daniel prayed every morning ♪
♪ Noon and night ♪
♪ Oh, Daniel served the living God ♪
♪ While here upon this earth he trod ♪
♪ He prayed to God ♪
♪ He prayed to God every morning ♪
♪ Noon and night ♪
♪ He cared not for the things of Baal ♪
♪ But trusted God who never fails ♪
♪ So Daniel prayed ♪
♪ Oh, Daniel prayed every morning ♪
♪ Noon and night ♪
BUEL: Come on, girls.
(CAR DOOR CLOSES)
(DOG BARKING IN DISTANCE)
Wait here.
Satchel.
Dad?
(LAUGHING)
Babe! Babe!
(IN DISTANCE): Babe!
(IN DISTANCE):
(DISTORTED, ECHOING STEPS)
(MAN WHISTLES "AMERICA THE BEAUTIFUL")
(SONG ENDS)
So, all is forgiven?
Back to business.
Oh.
I have a few small
adjustments to the deal.
Adjustments?
It's nothing.
A few details.
_
Are you kidding?
This is half our business.
You want to take half our business?
We had a deal.
In the park.
- We made a deal!
- Please, be calm.
This is just part of the new plan.
Our national plan.
For the nation.
New York, Chicago,
Kansas City, Miami,
Texas, California.
You, too, are a national outfit, yes?
Mm.
Wait, no.
You are one man in one city.
What do they say?
Big fish, small pond.
But we are the sea.
Mm.
I can tell you are thinking,
you can just kill me the way
you kill the men before.
But this is a mistake.
Because when you look at me,
you don't see the man behind me.
And the man behind him.
And all the men that follow.
Forever.
Mm-hmm?
You see them now.
The wave that never ends.
We understand each other.
Cheer up.
Look at it this way:
we are not taking half,
we are leaving half.
You work for us now.
You do what we say or we kill you
and find someone who will.
_
(GLASS THUMPS)
(BRAKES SQUEAK SOFTLY)
OPAL: Boss?
Go home.
War's over.
You sure?
It's over.
(CAR DOOR CLOSES)
(HORN PLAYING)
(CHILDREN CHATTERING)
(HORN CONTINUES PLAYING)
For Swanee.
Shh...
(GASPING)
(HORN CONTINUES PLAYING FAINTLY)
ETHELRIDA: History is a form of memory.
But what does it mean to remember?
We think, naturally, of our own past,
our lives day by day,
and through them we see
the events of our times.
(MEN STOMPING RHYTHMICALLY)
We are Black and white,
rich and poor,
foreign-born and domestic.
And yet, if our pasts are separate,
then aren't our histories separate, too?
Segregated?
Ask yourself:
who writes the books?
Who chooses what we remember
and what gets forgotten?
My name is Ethelrida Pearl Smutny.
This is my history report.
Synced & corrected by QueenMaddie
www.addic7ed.com