America is still going
to the polls at 4:00.
With some precincts opening
as early as 12 this morning,
voters across the country are deciding
who will hold the most important
office in the fr...
Herman Phillips, Bert Cooper.
Actually, "Herman" goes on my checks.
People call me Duck.
My research says I was not to call you Duck.
You should have told me that.
I don't know. I like when you say Herman.
Herman was in London with Y&R.
Isn't this a step down?
I don't know.
Moving back to the power center
of the universe, New York,
and the chance to put on some weight.
English food. I actually ate a kidney.
He landed American Airlines.
You could make something
like that happen here.
Well, you have to
spend money to make money.
So you're not promising anything.
Why would I do that?
My goodness, he does want this job.
I hope you play your cards
close to the vest with clients.
I will keep that in mind.
Here's a test. Who'd you vote for?
If I say Nixon, you'll think
I'm buttering you.
If I say Kennedy,
you'll want to reform me.
So, uh, I'll say Nixon.
That's nice to see.
Cooper has a smoker
at The Waldorf at 6:00.
Marge told me.
23 skidoo.
At 6:15, we turn on the returns
and send for some ice.
Party at the in-laws'.
Another ending to a perfect day.
Well, Jennifer and I were going
to get tickets to Can-Can.
It's empty, you know.
She says apparently the phone company
is a war zone on election night.
That's what I'm
hoping for around here.
Although, You better hope that
she's sitting at her switchboard
and not doing what we're doing.
It's my wife.
Besides, what if Nixon loses?
Won't that put a damper
on things around here?
Who cares? They didn't want our help.
You should care.
I do. It matters for the nation
and for Sterling Coop.
But tonight, either way.
If Nixon wins, we win.
If Nixon loses...
let me console you.
That's him.
Duck Phillips.
I know his name.
Because it's Duck?
I grew up with a Tuck.
At least that has an air of dignity.
Don took him to Cooper. That's a first.
I heard he disintegrated in London.
Got involved with some woman
he met at the British Museum.
Her name was Rosetta.
Rosetta Stone.
He's divorced. Lives in a hotel.
So what's this? His last stop?
No. He's a killer, but he's...
he's damaged goods.
They're bargain hunting.
He's the best one
Draper's paraded around.
Let's see if Cooper's
smart enough to know that.
Can I help you?
What?
Mr. Campbell would like to see you.
Send him in.
Thank you, sweetheart.
So that Duck fellow,
I heard he fell apart in London.
American Airlines.
$7 million in billings.
He's not going to bring that with him.
Listen, Don, I don't feel you've taken me
seriously as a candidate.
Candidate for what?
For the head of account services.
We may have had our differences,
but Roger knows I've done everything
I could to emulate him.
Roger's not involved in this.
Anything else?
I have the loyalty
of our most important clients:
Calvin Highland, Lee Garner.
These men trust me.
They invite me
to their grandchildren's christenings.
When Walter Veidt needed a urologist,
he called me
for a recommendation.
Look, you're good at your job.
Cooper loves you.
What's the hurry?
It's been two and a half years.
I could have jumped
ship a hundred times.
Is that supposed to persuade me?
I have tremendous value
to this company.
I'm aware of that.
But I don't think you are.
I am. I just hope you realize
that, the way things stand,
there will continue to be
someone senior to you.
Why?
What can they offer?
All I'm asking is that you think about it.
There are men younger than me
with this job at bigger firms.
Cooper sign off on what's-his-name?
Duck?
I'll keep you posted.
He's got a big lead.
See you at the victory
party in the morning.
Absolutely.
Well, good night, Don.
He's gone!
Olly olly oxen free!
- Do it.
- All rightie.
- Who's got the cups?
- Oh. Sorry.
With early returns just coming in,
our NBC computer is putting
Senator Kennedy's odds for victory
at a grim-sounding 22-1.
This is not good.
And liquor stores are closed tonight.
Draper has plenty of booze.
We could ask her to join us.
That might soften her up a bit.
I have a bottle of absinthe in my office.
Isn't that illegal?
It's marvelous.
I become incantatory.
And what does that mean?
It means he starts making up words.
Can someone freshen this?
We're not going to make it.
Really?
If I let you into that supply closet,
it is not going to be the sack of Rome.
What do we have too much of?
Rum, creme de menthe,
dog biscuits.
May the best man win.
In matters national and... local.
...majority decision of the American...
I made my judgment long ago.
Stop that. You're going to break it.
Look. They're doing math.
What do the numbers say?
Who the president is going to be.
Hello.
Daddy! Hi!
I wasn't expecting you.
I thought you were going to be
watching returns at the office.
What are you doing up?
Mommy said it was okay.
I'm watching the news.
Nixon definitely won our precinct.
You should have seen the line.
Mommy said to ask you. What's the...
Electoral College.
I don't think that's a conversation
appropriate for children.
Come here.
Do you want something to eat?
I'm going to fix a drink. You?
I'm set.
Senator Kennedy seems
to be closing the gap
on the vice president's early lead.
State-by-state, Ohio, Illinois...
Come here.
What?
You better run.
Go, Allison!
White!
Pink!
You can tell me, or I can find out.
What color panties are you wearing?
What? Oh, my G...
Blue!
Who had blue?
Can I walk you home?
I used to think I'd find a husband here.
I think I'm going to go home.
No, don't go. It's going to be fun.
What are you doing?
Why aren't you asleep?
What is that?
Nothing.
Myrna found it on the top of the closet,
and I didn't want to look at it.
My father has a box like that,
and I looked at it when I was a little girl,
and it was a mistake.
So you didn't open it?
Peter, I don't want secrets.
I can't sleep.
I know.
I've seen it the last few weeks.
You're not very quiet,
and every time I see
the closet door is open
and that box is gone,
I know you're out here.
And you never looked in the box?
It's not yours.
What are you doing with it?
I got it by mistake.
So give it back.
It's peculiar.
It's not yours.
Come to bed.
Vice President Nixon
seems to have carried
predominantly Catholic
Hudson County, New Jersey.
Kinsey, you're a liar.
I couldn't find any absinthe.
Who said you could go in my office?
We were exploring.
But all we found was
a large collection of Mad magazines
and this fascinating dramatic piece.
Death is My Client... Whoa.
A play in one act by Paul Kinsey.
Give it to me.
"Peter Tollifson"...
"An animal in the board room
and the bedroom. "
- Kenny!
- Whoa!
Now, remember, he's angry.
Why do I have to play Tollifson?
I wanted to be Galt.
Tollifson is the hero. He thinks.
Galt's a thug born on the wrong
side of the tracks.
You don't want to be Galt.
Go ahead.
I'm sorry. I don't have the pages.
Oh. Sorry.
Um, "I worked with Tollifson for four years.
I shared everything,
but I never knew him. "
"I thought I knew him.
He used to talk to me. "
"I can't control my genius.
I'm not some boorish natural
like that hack Cosgrove. "
That's crackerjack, Kinsey.
"Your genius be damned. "
"Perhaps. "
"You can make anyone buy anything.
Anyone but me. "
Turn the music down.
We now have confirmation
that the State of Ohio has indeed gone
to Vice President Richard Nixon.
Its 25 electoral votes
will go in Mr. Nixon's purse.
I'm...
I'm really tipsy.
I feel awful.
No, no. Uh... it was me.
I'm... I'm drunk.
I'm happy... but not myself.
I've never really
seen your eyes before.
There they are.
Just the two of them.
As Vice President Nixon's
home state of California
continues to count ballots,
both candidates bid
their supporters a good night.
Vice presidential hopeful
Senator Lyndon Johnson
had these words:
I'm very proud of the manner
in which the Democratic
campaign has been conducted
and which the people have reacted,
particularly in my state,
the entire South,
and in many states...
What's going on?
- I don't know.
... feel, uh, very confident...
It'll be all right in the morning.
He'll win California.
...the counting that...
Turn it off.
All Americans will be proud,
and I think we have
much to be proud of.
I think this is one
of America's finest hours.
Sit down.
No.
You can't sit down in that dress.
You look so different
when you're drunk.
You're not going to call me
Orson Welles again.
You loved that.
Who wouldn't like that?
What did I do wrong?
You have a big mouth.
Joan, I never said...
I do.
I'm not proud of it.
Did you like the play?
No.
The meaner you are, the more I like you.
I know.
Just like that?
I thought we could dance.
1, 2, cha-cha-cha.
Hildy, wake up.
Mm, it's cold in here.
It is. You have to get dressed.
I can't find my glasses.
That's too bad.
Tremendous.
Harry?
Yes?
I hope I didn't step on them.
Damn it.
There's an optometrist on Lexington.
Great. Of course.
I don't want you to be worried.
It didn't mean anything, okay?
You're not drinking for taste.
Don't be such babies.
Oh, God.
It's definitely not helping.
I'm sorry. Does it offend you?
My shirt. And my mad money.
Who did this?
I stole your blouse.
I'm not joking. I had $3.00 in here.
If I give you $3.00,
will you keep your voice down?
You're animals.
I'm reporting it to building security.
Striking resemblance
to Broderick Crawford.
Peggy Olsen, Highway Patrol.
I've read three different newspapers
with three different results.
I'm sure you know something I don't.
Well, I just spent the night literally
in a smoke-filled room at The Waldorf
with every Republican luminary
save MacArthur and Jesus.
There's been widespread fraud.
Daley gave Joe Kennedy
every corpse in Cook County.
Otherwise, Nixon wins.
It shouldn't have been that close.
But it is. It always is.
Those jingles.
When they got Frank Sinatra,
I knew they would close the gap.
So what does he do now?
Walk away? Concede?
A recount in Illinois alone
means 30 days without a president.
You don't want to win like that.
But you want to win.
He got 50% of the vote, maybe more.
This way he lives to see another day.
So... what happens?
Neil from P&G said if Kennedy
is willing to buy an election,
he's probably willing to play ball with us.
Ah, the optimism
of the American corporation.
It's a football game to them.
Doesn't seem fair.
Fair?
Very good.
Where do you think you're going?
If I were you,
I would be very,
very careful from now on
about the way you speak to me.
Can I help you?
What's that?
It's yours.
It came to me by mistake.
Well, thanks.
Have you reconsidered
my qualifications
for the head of account services?
Would it disappoint you
if I told you it hadn't crossed my mind?
I feel strange having
to talk to you in this way.
Spit it out, Campbell.
I know that your name
is not Donald Draper.
It's Dick Whitman.
I don't know who Donald Draper is,
but according to my friend Russ
at the Department of Defense,
Dick Whitman died in Korea in 1950,
and Donald Draper dropped off the map.
Although he's 43 years old,
in which case
you look remarkably good.
That's kind of elaborate.
Really?
I wish I knew more.
I bet a lot of people do.
Pete...
get out.
You're making a fool of yourself.
You can deny it.
But I know it's true.
I can see from your face.
You should leave.
Don...
you should think about
how Bert Cooper will react
when he hears this information.
What information?
You're not who you say you are,
and there's obviously a reason.
Come on.
I would like you
to reconsider my qualifications.
You said everything except "or else. "
Assuming this information
is true, which it isn't,
it sounds to me like
you're blackmailing me.
I'm not.
I'm hoping you'll realize
that this all can be forgotten.
It's not like you're a deserter, is it?
When you threaten someone
in this manner,
you should be aware of the fact
that if your information
is powerful enough
to make them do what you want...
what else can it make them do?
It's very simple.
And it's not a threat. It's just a job.
Think about it.
Whitman.
Yes, Sergeant.
What is this?
This is it.
One? I'm supposed to have 20.
This is going to take a month,
and it should take 48 hours.
Well, you're whining to the wrong guy, sir.
At ease.
Uh, this is for officers.
You can bunk next door.
I- I'd introduce you to the men,
but you're looking
at the complete company.
Where is everybody, sir?
They were gone when I got here.
I'm an engineer.
They're in some action
5 miles over that mountain.
You want to go?
The answer is no.
The locals stopped
showing up three days ago,
which, by the way, is not good.
You're going to be doing all the digging.
Digging what?
Well, this unit... that's you...
will be establishing a field hospital,
but first we're going to be digging
fighting positions on four sides.
What are you doing here?
Are you poor?
I volunteered.
You're kidding me.
Well, they got me with college.
But I'm three years,
six months nearly a civilian.
I'm supposed to be building
swimming pools, not latrines.
You any good with that rifle?
I wouldn't want you
to mistake me for Chinese.
As much practice as I've had, yes.
What misconception
traveled down the road
and made you want to be here?
A movie?
No. I just wanted to leave.
I'll bet you're reconsidering
if this was a step up.
Miss Menken,
Mr. Draper is here to see you.
Please hold my calls.
Did you run over? You're flushed.
Let's go away.
Really? Where?
Anywhere.
Warmer weather?
Sure.
How about Los Angeles?
Mexico? I have money.
I have money, but I have a store to run.
Don, are you well?
No, I'm not.
Did something else happen to Roger?
No.
Something happened, and...
I want to go, and I want you
to come with me,
and I don't want to come back.
What happened?
What does it matter?
Isn't this what you want?
Of course. I've thought about it.
My God, we've talked about it.
I just...
I just didn't think it would happen...
I mean, especially this way.
I just... don't want to be without you,
and I don't want to be here.
I can't just leave.
Maybe this weekend...
Rachel.
No. This isn't how
I thought it would be.
What is the difference?
We'll go somewhere else.
We'll start over like Adam and Eve.
What, are you 15 years old?
My father...
Can't we be together here?
There's nothing here.
What about your children?
I'll provide for them.
And live in Los Angeles?
My God, you haven't
thought this through.
I feel sick.
You're wrong. I know exactly what I want.
You want your children
to go on without a father?
You know how that felt.
Are you having an attack
of conscience after all this?
No. I'm watching you talk
because I feel I don't know you.
You know more about me
than anyone.
You won't even tell me what happened.
Why are you doing this to me?
What kind of man are you?
Go away, drop everything, leave your life?
People do it every day.
- This was a dalliance, a cheap affair.
- Rachel, don't.
You don't want to run away with me.
You just want to run away.
You're a coward.
Please go now.
Get out.
Peggy, this is my office.
Does this door mean nothing to you?
I'm sorry, Mr. Draper.
I didn't know you were coming back. I just...
I just...
Calm down.
Stop it.
I didn't mean to yell at you.
Got to be some semblance
of privacy left here.
I had to get away from them all
for a minute.
Drink this.
Sonny from the elevator
and some janitor... I don't know his name...
they got fired.
That's why you're crying?
It was my fault.
I called security.
They weren't even here last night.
Peggy, I need to be alone right now.
I know.
I don't understand.
I try to do my job.
I follow the rules,
and people hate me.
Innocent people get hurt, and...
and other people...
people who are not good...
get to walk around
doing whatever they want.
It's not fair.
Finish it.
I've thought about what you said.
Glad to hear it.
And then I thought about you
and what a deep lack
of character you have.
I can understand your frustration, Don.
Believe me, I'm not enjoying this
any more than you are.
I'm hiring Duck Phillips.
Don...
don't make me go to Cooper.
I'm not making you do anything.
You haven't thought this through.
- I have.
- Really?
You're just going to go up to the office
and tell Bert Cooper.
If I have to. I don't want to.
Let me ask you.
How do you think he'll react
when you tell him this story of yours?
You expect him to promote you
after the way you've behaved?
I think he'll appreciate the loyalty.
You haven't thought this through.
I don't know.
But I'm pretty sure
you won't be working here anymore.
What are you doing?
Where are you going?
I'm going to take care of this right now.
Is this like in the movies
where I have a gun
and you don't think
I'm going to shoot you?
I will shoot you.
I won't let you hold this over my head.
So you'd rather blow yourself up
than make me head of accounts.
Why can't you give me what I want?
I've earned this job. I deserve it.
Why? Because your parents are rich?
Because you went to prep school
and have a $5.00 haircut?
You've been given everything.
You've never worked
for anything in your life.
For gosh sakes, don't you realize
you're going to lose everything?
I'm giving you a way out.
Would it be so bad?
Why is this so hard for you?
You're really going to do this?
More bad news?
If you came here
to drown your sorrows,
I'm not really much of a drinker.
No. I just wanted to say...
I'm pulling the trigger
on Duck Phillips
as new head of account services.
Oh, good. Well done.
What?
I have to bring this up to you.
Only because I believe
if I kept it from you
in the end it would be
damaging to Sterling Cooper.
It has come to my attention,
completely by accident,
that Donald Draper here
is not who he says he is.
His real name is Dick Whitman,
but... Dick Whitman
died in Korea ten years ago.
It stands to reason
that he is a deserter at the very least
and who knows what else.
Mr. Campbell, who cares?
What?
Who cares?
Mr. Cooper, he's a fraud and a liar.
A criminal, even.
Even if this were true, who cares?
This country was built and run
by men with worse stories
than whatever you've imagined here.
I'm not imagining anything.
The Japanese have a saying:
A man is whatever room he is in,
and right now Donald Draper
is in this room.
I assure you,
there's more profit in forgetting this.
I'd put your energy
into bringing in accounts.
Don,
fire him if you want.
But I'd keep an eye on him.
One never knows how loyalty is born.
Shit!
Sir, what do we do?
Keep your head.
Don't shoot at anything
unless it shoots at you first.
What? What? What?
Shut up! Just stay down!
Shit!
Don't they know this is a hospital?
We're nuts if they know that.
Is it over?
I don't know.
- You think they'll be back?
- I don't know.
We didn't shoot back. That helps.
You pissed yourself.
What?
Did I?
Crap.
How are we doing, Lieutenant Draper?
On behalf of the President
of the United States
and the citizens
of the United States of America...
I present you with
this Purple Heart medal.
The concussion was minor.
You'll feel like yourself in a week.
The colonel here
has some good news for you.
We're releasing you to the Reserves
for your last 80 days.
You're going home.
That's good news.
You're going to be okay.
Lieutenant Draper,
Private Whitman.
You were the last person who knew him
in his chain of command.
We'd like you to take him home.
I think it would mean something.
Lieutenant Nelson, how you doing?
On behalf of the President
of the United States
and the citizens of
the United States of America...
Bunbury.
This is us, Lieutenant.
Lieutenant Draper?
Just go.
I can't.
Okay.
There he is! I see him!
Who?
Dick. He's on the train.
I see him.
No, he's right here.
But I saw him.
I saw him in the window over there.
Stop it. No more of that.
It must be hard for you.
Did you know him?
A little.
You got your whole life ahead of you.
Forget that boy in the box.
Look at you.
Let me buy a soldier a drink.
Dick!
With that, I want to say again
my deep thanks
to all of you who are here
and those who have listened
on television and radio,
and again my congratulations
to Senator Kennedy
for his fine race in this campaign,
and to all of you...
I am sure...
I am sure his supporters
are just as enthusiastic
as you are for me,
and I thank you for that.