Previously on Prison Break:
L.J. and Sara will be traded for Whistler.
Are we clear?
- This can't be done in a week.
- You have a week, that's it.
No one's broken out of this place,
let alone with a week to plan it.
So tell these people, I'm gonna break
this guy out or I'm gonna die trying.
You're gonna stay on as my ears.
Report back to me everything you hear
when I'm not around.
You've got a brother
helping on the outside.
He ran into my girlfriend
and took a book that belongs to me.
This is what they took from me,
so let's be clear.
This is what matters to me.
Not you and not your book.
How's L.J.? How's Sara?
- They told me they're fine.
- What are you not telling me?
- Not the only one affected--
- Killed Sara and put her head in a box.
They've got my son.
J.P. Getty had a formula for success.
Rise early, work hard, strike oil.
I'm just trying
to get a drink of water, Alex.
As a devoted student
of your work and skills...
...I really look forward
to the progress on your plan, Michael.
I'm looking forward to you
getting off my back.
Buenos, welcome to Sona.
Is that your wallet?
You know what I said.
No.
That's the wrong answer.
I'm so ready to get out of here
anytime you are.
Scofield, you have a visitor.
- Looks like you had a long night.
- Yeah.
Spent most of it
feeding chocolate to a rat.
I don't have a whole lot to work with
these days.
She's got the book, man. The bird guide.
She worked it out.
- So we have no leverage.
- No.
Tell me,
when you were handing over the book...
...did you ask for a recent photo
of L.J. and Sara?
- Yeah.
- Well, where is it?
She showed me,
but she wouldn't let me keep them.
I'm not in a position to bargain
with these people, they're pissed.
You break out tomorrow.
Let's just focus on that.
Let's keep on track.
All right.
While I'm working from the inside,
you take care of what happens outside.
We're gonna need a getaway vehicle,
something inconspicuous.
What you find has to be parked half
a mile from here by 3 p.m. tomorrow.
- You mean a.m.
- No, I mean p.m.
We don't have a choice, Linc.
I ran some tests last night.
Jeeps patrol the perimeter at night.
No way of telling
where they're gonna be in the dark.
They were out there all night.
- We need the dark, we can't--
- Just-- Please.
Because we're doing this tomorrow,
in the middle of the day.
Who you looking at?
That guy.
I know him.
McGrady, my friend,
I'm gonna need a watch, maybe two.
I'm not even gonna ask why.
Uh... I'm also gonna need
some binoculars.
Old Guillermo has a pair.
There's no way he'll sell them to you
but they shouldn't be hard to get.
Where can I find this guy?
We're leaving tomorrow.
This...
This is how we get out of Sona.
Getting out of the cellblock
shouldn't be a problem.
The grate and the bars are weak.
But we need some rope, some ladder,
to let us down on the other side.
Figured out the safest line
from here to the hole in the fence.
We do it in the day, we'll only be visible
to the two guard towers.
Perimeter guards are less predictable,
but they're only on at night.
Scurrying across field
in middle of the day?
It's the only way to avoid
the jeep patrol.
In the yard tomorrow,
there's a soccer game at 2.
That should provide
some distraction inside.
Yesterday, when we're digging...
...I saw the glare from the sun
hit this guy in the late afternoon.
Like he had to turn away.
Like maybe his vision was blocked.
- It's not much of a break.
- No.
But it is one way to do
what we need to do.
As far as this other guard,
his weakness is yet to be determined.
If we're gonna get around these guys,
we gotta get to know them.
It's not gonna be easy.
- There's one real road that--
- We don't want a real road.
That's not an option.
- What?
- Your brother's cutting it close.
- You said a week.
- Tomorrow's Wednesday.
- Didn't leave room for error.
- There's no error.
- Listen, I got stuff to do, and I just--
- Which is why I won't waste your time.
When Whistler's free,
I need to get to him.
Still trying to work out
what's gonna happen past the fence.
- Once I know all the details, I'll let you--
- Lincoln, calm down.
Sounds to me like you and your brother
are in over your heads.
There's a bad joke
about Sara somewhere in there.
Listen, I'll let you know all the details
once I know them, and then I'll call you.
I want this to work out
just as badly as you do.
More, I'm sure.
L.J.?
L.J.'s fine. You have 34 hours.
- What did she say?
- Nothing we don't already know.
Let's get out of here.
We got a lot of stuff to do.
No, no.
Wouldn't let them see you do that.
- Who?
- Anyone.
It's a drinking fountain.
They put their lips there.
You'd think it spit straight
Jack Daniels.
You understand what happened?
You're a whatchamacallit, pariah.
Made same mistake when I walked in,
tried to hang on to my wallet.
Next thing I knew, I spent two days
kneecap-deep in human feces.
In Sona, it's every man for himself.
Here, cheese.
- I'm not hungry.
- Yeah, you will be.
I saw the other Americans.
So none of you have called the embassy?
Us gringos ain't all butt buddies.
You want it? Because I'll keep it.
Let's get this done.
We're gonna have to watch
both guards simultaneously.
Your cell should provide a good view
of the guard I saw yesterday.
Track everything he does
and when he does it.
Look for that glare.
See if it shows up again.
- What will you be doing?
- Watching the other tower from here.
With our backs turned,
need a lookout.
- Well, find Mahone.
- I thought we were stringing him along.
Looks like we're out of string.
Teodoro.
What do they say
about all work and no play?
- A boy need his rest.
- Your clientele keeps a tight schedule.
Gotta make sure I see to their needs.
I gave you a more important task.
- But I haven't heard a thing.
- Then listen harder.
Come into my office.
Sit down. Watch the game.
Excuse me.
- Anything yet?
- No, not yet.
So, what's your story, Mahone?
I mean, the next chapter,
when we get out of here.
Suppose you were married to the job.
Drank too much, rabid insomniac,
typical lawman.
Yeah, just like you reek of live bait
and have a girl in every port.
Tell fish stories, or so I've heard.
Prior to this experience,
I had the utmost respect for the law.
This guy hasn't so much
as scratched his jock in an hour.
It's not gonna be easy
to get around that guy.
Maybe not.
You know,
we might just have a break.
I'm gonna go check on Scofield.
Sorry.
- Did you see the glare?
- Hit him hard at 3:13.
Turned to his right and ignored the west
for next six minutes.
As far as I could tell.
This guy thinks he's auditioning
for Buckingham Palace.
But he's also a sports fan.
He's got a TV.
Twice in the last four hours,
the signal got fuzzy.
He had to turn to adjust the antenna.
- That's nothing we can count on.
- True.
But there is a device we can build
out of some pretty common materials.
It's almost like a radio,
except it transmits signals.
Hey, watch it, man.
Oof.
- Pardon me.
- You're the new guy.
- Yeah, and who are you?
- Not the new guy.
So, what's your deal? Public intoxication,
tourist in trouble, what is it?
I don't like people asking questions
when I've done nothing.
- You're an innocent man?
- As a matter of fact, yes.
- Is this your first time in prison?
- Uh-huh. Why?
Because it's obvious. Rule number one:
Mind your own business.
You know,
you might wanna do the same.
You know what I'm talking about.
You got it?
- Yeah.
- I got it.
- Then take a walk.
When did you meet
your boyfriend? Whistler?
My last year of school.
I worked in this place in San lsabel.
He used to come around by himself
and sit down at the bar.
Hitting on the waitress.
That's romantic.
He is.
Every time he goes away,
he brings me back a present.
Like this. Those are from Scottsdale.
His mother lives there
in a retirement home.
What's going on?
- Out of the car.
- What's going on?
- This is a private road.
- I can explain--
- What'd we do?
- Shut your mouth, Americano.
This is state property.
No vehicles allowed.
All roads within two miles of Sona
are closed.
- We didn't see any signs.
- Where you going?
- San lsabel.
- San lsabel?
- Yeah.
- This your car?
This road is not for tourists.
If I ever catch you out here again,
I'll remember you.
- It ain't gonna happen again.
- Get going.
- You okay?
- Yeah.
- This is not gonna work.
- Where's the coast from here?
- I don't know, maybe three miles.
- All right, time for Plan B. Come on.
Found some more of these.
We can make a rope out of this.
Come on,
you don't wanna go in there.
If we wanna get out of here, I do.
Stay here.
Hey, hey, hey. Move it.
Come on.
What, is it chained down?
- It's hanging by a thread.
- It'll have to wait.
It's 4:30.
- We got less than 24 hours.
- We'll make it.
- Tell me why.
- What?
Why can't we get you out
day after tomorrow?
I don't know.
I don't have all the answers.
You don't know me,
I don't know you...
...but it's your job
to get me out of here.
We'll come back later.
- I'll take this.
- Down here for the summer?
- Yep.
- That's what I thought.
Back in 1985, two wives, 20 years later.
You want everything in here?
Yeah, thanks.
International waters, how far out?
- It's 12 nautical miles.
- Twelve nautical miles, huh?
- Is that gonna do it here?
- Yeah.
Ninety-nine twenty-five.
- Here.
- All right.
Thank you.
- What did you get?
- Supplies.
- Could you pop the trunk?
- Who am I gonna tell?
Could be a Russian spy, for all I know.
- You live out of this thing?
- Be prepared in case of an emergency.
Well, we got an emergency.
I'm not going
till you tell me where we're going.
- Solana Beach.
- Why?
They killed Sara, and I'm trying
to make sure they don't kill my son.
If you don't think your boy's
not on that list, stay here.
Couldn't care less.
- What is it?
- It's Augusto.
He won't pay
the payment for you anymore.
I went to him for payment,
like every Monday...
...and he said it's not his responsibility
and that I should ask you.
No, no, no.
You tell Augusto I don't pay for sex.
I know. I did.
But what do I do?
I don't see anyone else.
Yeah? Well, neither do I.
On the other side, when we
get out of here, what's gonna happen?
- Meet someone from this Company?
- Apparently.
And then they're gonna kill me.
You know that.
If they wanted to kill you,
you'd already be dead.
I don't see why they keep me alive.
It's like you said:
You've got something they want.
Once I give it to them,
I'll be no use to them, right?
I don't have all the answers. All I know
is it's my job to get you out of here.
Food's here!
Let's go.
It's "Two-for Tuesday."
My one-time special, just for you.
But there's a price.
Lechero's getting pretty sensitive
about the cash flow.
- Well, I'm a little short right now.
- No worries, Alex.
I am not gonna leave you
hanging, all right?
We can just start you a tab.
- How is a microwave gonna help us?
- I guess we'll find out.
Our third year in school...
...we studied electrical engineering
with a focus on EMPs.
That's electromagnetic pulses.
You hook up a power source
to a transmitter and it generates a pulse.
That pulse crashes anything
electronic.
What's that,
like an intro into anti-terrorist tactics?
Basically.
These days, they have to teach students
how to defend their structures.
Fortunately for us, that guard tower
was engineered a long time ago.
I'm guessing you always won
the elementary science fair.
Plug this in.
Did it crash the telly?
We're too far away.
But it is doing exactly what
we need it to--
Shh, shh.
Okay.
- Get out.
- Why?
They're coming in.
Colonel's coming. Just stay here.
Do not let him see her. Do not.
- Come on.
- Huh?
Go! Go!
Everybody get down.
Everyone on your knees.
Colonel.
We received no word of this.
A rifle scope
was seen from the tower.
Capitán Hurtado
saw it with his own eyes.
That's impossible.
There is a gun in your prison,
and it was pointing at one of my men.
We are going to find it.
- This looks good.
- For what?
Have a seat.
- What am I supposed to be doing here?
- Look like you're having fun.
When was the last time
you saw your son?
Lincoln, I don't automatically
trust people either...
...but I can tell
when they have good intentions.
Good for you.
You know, I'm not gonna try
to prove myself anymore.
You do your job and I do mine.
- You need something?
- What?
You need something?
- No.
- Good.
- Don't you worry, it's all gonna be okay.
- No, it's not.
I promise,
I will not let anyone find you in here.
- No, Lechero hate me.
- Lechero does not hate you.
You hold a very special place
in his heart.
So many girls can take my place.
He's smart, he knows you're better.
You're a real woman.
A woman with her own will,
her own desire.
You know what I am.
In this world, sister,
we are all prostitutes.
You are a queen.
Shh, shh...
Whose cell is that? In the corner?
Is that your cell?
- You, is that your cell?
- It's mine. It's mine.
It's mine.
I found this.
It's not a weapon.
I know what it is.
Why were you watching me?
I'm going to ask you one more time.
- I wasn't watching you.
- I saw you.
- Answer.
- Don't know what you saw...
...but I wasn't watching you.
I wasn't watching--
It's mine.
Why were you watching him?
I wasn't. I was, uh, watching birds.
Yes. Yes.
You see?
Why did you not speak up before?
I, uh...
I was scared.
Come on.
Come on. Please, please, please.
He's coming back up here.
Now, don't worry.
It's all gonna be okay.
You have a little mascara right there.
You need to look pretty for Lechero.
Thank you.
Wait right here.
The patrol passed, but didn't stay.
Knocked things over, then walked away.
I hid your woman in a safe place...
...but I'd be lying
if I didn't say it was a close call.
- She alone?
- Yeah.
Hey, look...
Don't be afraid.
Not now, my dear. They're gone.
- I should go too.
- Oh, no, no, what's your rush?
- Come.
- No, I should get home.
Patrón, I gave her the money.
I was gonna replace it
at the end of the day when I get my cut.
I just didn't get to tell you.
She had no money to get home.
- Is this true?
- Yes.
With all due respect, you don't want
your mistress traveling broke.
She'd end up in a taxi
with no way to pay the cab fare.
Oh, you did this for me?
Teodoro.
The one who does
all the useful things for me. Huh?
And now you do the thinking for me.
No, no. It's not like that, patrón.
Get a bucket. Wash my feet.
So, what do we do now?
- I don't know.
- I'm afraid that's not good enough.
Just give me a moment to think.
Wasting time is not an option.
I need to be out of here.
I know, in time for your fishing trip.
Or is it a bird-watching trip?
That's my trip log, I've told you.
I need to retrace my steps. I'm doing
everything. The same thing you are.
Just leave me alone, please.
Before I was arrested, a man
came to my flat and took my addresses.
They know the name of everyone
I care about and how to find them.
They already found everyone
I care about, okay?
If you can't get me out of here,
tell me now.
Because time's running out.
Huh?
Look, it's hot today.
Yeah.
Prefer the heat to the cold any day.
My brother and I wanted
to come down here to Panama...
...and start a dive shop,
like the one we were at today.
My boy was gonna leave school
and help start the family business.
When this is all over,
why don't you do it?
Too much bad stuff's happened.
Still, you can make it work.
It's only gonna work
if Whistler cooperates.
He plays games, people get hurt.
- You understand that, right?
- He doesn't want anyone to get hurt.
Hope you're right.
I wanna show you something.
Our getaway vehicle.
Now, the next time
you see Whistler...
...I want you to tell him
what you saw.
Tell him we're all in this together.
That we're part of a team, understand?
- Okay, yeah.
- All right. Get up.
We're coming back. This way.
- What?
- This way, come on.
Okay.
If all goes well,
you'll see him tomorrow.
No, no, no.
Hmm?
If we're gonna do this today,
we gotta replace everything we lost.
- Like what?
- For starters, new exit point.
It's gotta be
on the south side of the building.
- Hey, this guy again.
- Hey, hey. I know you.
- Afraid not.
- Yeah, yeah.
You're McFadden, right?
Nice, 1997.
Sorry, you've confused me
with someone else.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, I swear.
You were with the ambassador.
You've mistaken me for someone else.
That chap's insane.
The heat must be getting to him.
Come on, guys.
I got something to show you.
I didn't observe the guards' behavior
in as much detail as you guys...
...but I did notice something
yesterday.
Right around this time.
- It's the day shift. They start up at 6.
- Just keep looking. Keep looking.
There.
Where'd you get your cup, Alex?
In the courtyard,
but apparently it's from him.
He has one in the morning
and one after lunch.
The man's gotta have his fix.
- If we get to that cup--
- We get to the man.
We gotta move.