Previously on Prison Break:
The bracing's gonna be tricky.
Unless the tunnel gets proper support,
it's all gonna come down on our heads.
I want you to call her up.
Tell her you got some information.
Make sure she picks you up.
And get in the car, all right?
- He even bought a gun.
- Hmm.
Just thought you'd wanna know.
If you're really leaving,
take me with you. Please.
I don't wanna be here anymore.
You don't want any part of this.
A part of me doesn't wanna
believe he works for them...
...because he's the man I love.
The man who was gonna take me
to Paris.
If he doesn't take you, I will.
Impressive, blanco.
Too bad you won't be around
to enjoy it.
How long is this gonna set us back?
All right, we got 24 hours
to dig out that tunnel.
The one it took you guys
three days to dig?
Let's just say by some miracle
we are able to part the dirt sea, Moses.
Then what?
How you plan on getting around
the guard's tower?
Michael, Mr. Whistler here says that
you got stopped last time by a cloud--
I'm still working on that.
Wanna know if this girl's
gonna put out...
- ...before I buy her more drinks.
- I agree, Michael.
- You know as I do what's riding on this.
- I'd say I know better.
I don't care who knows what.
As long as somebody knows how
we're getting out of here by tomorrow.
- You coming?
- Not today.
James and I have a lot of things
to clear up.
But I'm done trying to do it
through a fence.
You ever wish
you could go back in time...
...just to remember how it was like
when things made sense?
Every day for the last three years.
Is that Whistler's girlfriend?
- Why is she in the car?
- She thinks she'll see him tomorrow.
- Spending a lot of time together.
- And?
You sure that's wise?
- Where are we?
- Behind schedule.
We should be on the same side
of the fence by tomorrow.
What do you mean "should"?
The tunnel gets us into no man's land.
But to get to the fence...
...we're gonna need a new diversion
for the tower guards.
- What time?
- Daytime's still our best option.
- They double the guards at night.
- The Jeep patrols?
Yeah.
And, uh, there's something else.
- What?
- T-Bag's coming.
And Mahone and Bellick.
Oh, yeah, there's a drug lord too.
It's not about them.
It's about Whistler--
- We don't know who Whistler is.
- What about what he's worth?
My son's life.
I just wish there was another way
to do this.
To save L.J.
without handing Whistler over.
Look, man, that's it. There isn't.
I know.
Listen, you worry about the tunnel.
I worry about the guards.
- I'll see you tomorrow.
- Tomorrow.
Don't skimp on the braces up there.
In fact, if you wanna add a little extra--
You know, we can work on this rail road
all the livelong day.
But it don't matter
if Scofield doesn't know...
...what happens
once we get off the train.
Once we get out,
it's every man for himself.
- Scofield's not responsible for any of us.
- Is that so?
You obviously don't know him
very well, Shakespeare.
When we broke out of Fox River,
he tried to screw every one of us.
Half the men ended up either dead,
captured or worse.
The guys who are easiest to catch...
...are the ones who spend more time
pissing and moaning than running.
My only advice to you:
Ecclesiastes 6:13.
Separate thyself from thy enemies
and take heed of thy friends.
How we doing, Alex?
Well, if those braces hold...
...we could be to the surface
some time tomorrow.
Let's rotate. Keep everybody fresh.
Welcome to the coal mine, canary.
We're gonna be here all day.
Yo, man.
Don't drip your body water
upon me like that.
Hey, it ain't coming from me, I swear.
Engineer, come.
Look at this.
- Hit a pipe or something?
- Oh, no.
That's right above our tunnel.
The ground's not gonna hold
till tomorrow.
So, what do we do?
We leave tonight.
Tonight? I thought you said
a nighttime escape was impossible.
If the rain keeps up, the tunnel will
collapse again and that'll be the end.
That'll be the end for you.
You're the one on a deadline.
What if it gives out
while we're inside--?
You want out, get out!
Look, you're not pulling this off without
all of us working around the clock.
None of us are making it out
of here without his plan.
So if you tell me that you can figure out
a way how to do this at night...
...then I, we, can figure out a way
how to get that tunnel dug in time.
Let's start digging.
I think you dropped something.
I've read in old newspapers
that make it to Sona...
...how Americans hold others
to standards they ignore.
How they think no one
should have power but them.
I tell everyone it's a lie,
but I see it's true.
I know you're leaving.
And to think that after everything
I've done to help...
...I think it sucks
you're not taking me with you.
It doesn't seem like it,
but I'm doing you a favor.
I'm giving you a gift.
Huh. Wow, life in prison? Thank you,
I've always wanted one of those.
It's better than a life on the run.
I don't belong here.
- All I did was give a guy--
- You're not going.
I'm sorry. It's for the best.
How do you know
what's best for me?
Okay.
It's good to go.
You know where and when to be?
- If you're not there, we're screwed.
- Yeah.
- You all right?
- Yeah, I'm fine.
- I'm just gonna grab my stuff.
- Yeah.
It's probably best
if you and James disappear.
I know. I know.
You know where to meet us, right?
Playa Blanca. You will be on the...?
- Three-twelve.
Well, I'll see you tomorrow, then.
- Good luck.
- You too.
Hey, it's that Susan chick.
She wants to meet again.
Good. Let her know
everything's on track.
We wanna make her feel
as comfortable as possible.
Why shouldn't she be?
She's gonna get her guy tomorrow.
Well, if Michael's conscience
doesn't get in the way.
What do you mean?
He's having doubts.
- About if he can pull it off?
- About if he should.
But he's gonna
go through with it, right?
What are you looking for?
Where the power lines connect
to Sona's exterior lights.
If cutting the power was an option,
why didn't we do that?
One, the power out there
isn't controlled from in here.
And two, there's that.
Every prison has a backup generator.
If we cut the lights...
...they'll just come back on
again, immediately.
Well, that's a big, bloody problem.
Tell Lechero I need his phone.
Change of plans,
Linc. We're doing this tonight.
Tonight? What happened, Michael?
Rain, dirt, tunnel problem.
- How long can it hold?
- That depends.
Depends on what?
When the rain stops.
You said breaking out at night
was impossible.
Yeah, well...
Wanna tell me
how you're gonna pull this off?
For starters,
I need to get ahold of Sucre.
Sucre, do you know
what I do for a living?
I have a pretty good idea.
I read people.
And you, my friend,
are a coloring book.
I think you left this in my car.
- Look, that was just-- I mean, we--
- No.
No, no, no. My fault.
I guess I just didn't
make myself clear...
...when I laid out the terms
of our arrangement.
So I'm gonna try again
as simply as I know how.
Anything happens...
...anything at all
that I wasn't expecting...
...and there will be one less pregnant girl
in Chicago.
Look, Michael and Lincoln
don't tell me everything.
Fernando, this is your last chance.
I want a yes or a no.
Are the brothers going to break Whistler
out of Sona?
Yes.
Are they planning on handing him
over to me?
Yes.
Where do you want me
to shoot Maricruz first?
In the bun or in the oven?
Okay.
There's one thing I heard.
It's Michael. He's having
some concerns about Whistler.
What kind of concerns?
About handing him over.
You got to understand, he broke out
some pretty bad guys last time.
I think he's never forgiven himself
for that.
- He's planning on leaving him behind?
- Maybe. I don't know.
Shh.
Hello, Lincoln.
It's going down tonight.
Tonight?
Should I be worried?
I called you first thing.
I'm being straight up with you.
Oh, that's refreshing.
So I'll see you tonight.
Hmm. You show me yours
and I'll show you mine.
It's going down tonight.
Do you know about that?
I didn't know, I swear.
Get out of here.
- How'd it go?
- She found the bomb, Linc.
The one we put in her car.
How did she find the bomb, Sucre?
I don't know, bro. I'm sorry.
- It's not your fault.
- Look, I'll make it up to you, I swear.
You can start now.
Michael's in a bit of trouble at Sona.
What kind of trouble?
The rain stopped.
- Does that mean that--?
- No, the damage is done.
We can't risk waiting.
Anything interesting?
Like some coordinates...
...the Company might wanna get
their hands on?
If they didn't want me out of here...
...and your nephew was safe,
would you still be doing this?
Breaking out?
No.
Why would you choose to stay
if there was a chance at freedom?
Well, I guess that's the difference
between us.
I'm willing to pay for my sins.
And I'm not?
That's a good question.
Water's coming down pretty fast
up in here, patrón.
Then we have to dig faster.
You know, I've been thinking.
It doesn't have to be every man
for himself.
You and I can help each other.
If I need a hand,
I'll find someone with a spare.
Heh-heh-heh. It's true, I may be
lacking something in the west...
...but I more than make up for it
in the north.
Think about it. Scofield's got us
down here doing manual labor.
Slave labor.
I ain't no slave.
I'm doing this for me.
Why do you think Scofield's up
and we're down here?
He's planning something.
Who among us isn't?
What the hell is that?
- We're good.
- Yeah.
- We're all right.
- Yeah?
- Hello, Lincoln.
Long time no see.
Not long enough.
I was thinking that we could have
a little chat in person.
Make sure we're all on the same page
about tonight.
- All right.
- Thirty minutes. This location.
Jorge.
Hey, uh...
Ah.
- Hello?
- Hey, papi, it's me.
Hey.
Lincoln said you needed some help.
How much do you know
about electricity?
Hey, you're back.
I'm not real comfortable
being alone down here with those--
What's that, syrup?
Honey. Make a little pile of dirt,
gather some dirt.
Scofield said we gotta make something
to cover the hole, once we get out.
So when the lights
come back on, uh...
...it's gonna look like nobody
ever left.
All right, spread it around.
I was thinking, uh,
we should be a team.
Not just during the escape, but after.
Like Butch and Sundance.
Butch and Sundance died.
I mean in the other parts.
Now, here's an idea.
We go along with Scofield's plan.
When everyone stops to take a breath,
we grab them:
Burrows, Scofield, Bagwell.
Take them back home, face charges.
We'd be heroes.
We might get a book deal. We could
write it together. How would that be?
- A book deal?
- Yeah.
- That'll make you happy, Brad?
- You got a better idea?
Yeah, I do.
- Something to do with the wife and kid?
- Yeah, something like that.
You...
You got room for one more?
I mean, come on, Alex.
What's a guy like me gonna do?
Let's just let Scofield get us out of here.
Then we'll worry about everything else.
- All right.
- Come on, a little more dirt.
Listen very carefully
and do exactly as I tell you.
You sure you don't want Linc
to do this?
He knows more about this
than I do.
It's not what you know,
it's where you work.
And as a Sona employee, my friend...
...you have the unique ability
of not getting shot for being here.
You see the admin building?
- I see it.
- Go to it and make a left.
To it and left. Got it.
On the other side is a berm.
There should be a metal cage.
That's the backup generator.
Okay, I see it.
But don't let the tower guard
see you get too close. Just act casual.
When I say "now,"
you run and duck behind it.
Almost.
Hold on.
Now.
Okay. Okay.
There should be
some writing near the bottom.
I need the name of the manufacturer.
Make, model number, anything.
Yeah, yeah, yeah. I got it.
It's, uh--
It's, uh, Prana industrial.
Model number 3210.
Three-two-one-zero?
Is there a customer service number?
It's 1-800-555-0196.
All right, thanks. That's all I need.
- You think you can pull this off tonight?
- You wanna know the truth?
No, I just want all of it
to go down smooth.
For everyone to get what they want.
Yeah, I do.
Listen, even if you get this worked out
with the lights...
...what will you do
about the Jeep patrols?
- We're gonna have to take our chances.
- Maybe you don't.
You all right?
Yeah, I'm fine.
- Where's L.J.?
- Somewhere safe.
Take a load off.
Can I offer you a drink?
What's going on, Susan?
I wanted to get everyone together
so we can discuss tonight's agenda.
Maybe nail down a few guidelines.
It's the same. Nothing's changed.
Actually, I was thinking we should
probably include all the players.
Don't you?
What are you doing in here?
Just keeping watch.
Make sure nobody tries
to get down to the tunnel.
Who are you calling?
Yeah, hi,
is this, uh, Customer Service?
Yeah, I'm, uh-- I'm a sub working
a building down here in Panama.
And, um,
we've got a client on site.
They're asking questions about
the 3210 generator we're installing.
Yeah, exactly.
Um, they wanna know
if the main power shuts down...
...how long are they
gonna be in the dark...
...um, before the generator
kicks in?
Yeah, thanks. I'll hold.
You're a very good liar.
That's the timing?
No, that's, uh...
That's it. Appreciate it.
Well? We gonna make it?
We should have just enough dark
to make it out.
With everyone?
- Hey.
- You with Whistler?
Yes.
Susan's with me.
She wants to get a message to him.
- Why?
- Put him on.
It's for you.
- Yes?
- All right, I got him. What now?
Tell him I want him to listen
very carefully...
...to the following instructions.
- She wants you to listen--
- I can hear. Instructions about what?
James?
Was that Sofia? Is she there?
- Yeah.
- What's going on?
- He wants to know what this is about.
- All right, I'll tell him.
- Aah!
- No!
Was--? Was that Sof--?
Is that Sofia?
Have you figured out
the coordinates yet, James?
Please.
- Almost.
- Wrong answer.
- No!
I'll get them for you
when we get out of here, I swear.
All your promises, your guarantees...
...they mean nothing.
I'm pretty sick of waiting around
for you boys to screw me over.
I'm gonna need those coordinates
by the end of the day.
No. Aah!
I've gotta figure this out.
I've gotta do something.
We both know that you can't
just hand over that information.
Why? Why can't I?
Once they get what they want,
they'll have no reason to keep you...
...or your girlfriend
or my nephew alive.
So, what do I do?
I just let them torture Sofia?
We'll work something out.
We'll think it through.
I already have.
Whistler.
Whistler. What is so special
about him, anyway, huh?
Huh?
Do you think he has anything to do
with why they want Scofield down here?
It's really none of my business.
- What exactly is your business?
- Something on your mind?
I'm just saying,
if we needed a bargaining chip...
...you think a sharp stick
in that dull limey would help us out?
There is no "us."
You and me are a lot more alike
than you think, Alex.
We both know how it feels
to lose a great love.
How it feels to kill a man.
We both ended up in here
because of Michael Scofield.
Wouldn't it be poetic justice
if we could just return the favor?
Justice?
If there was an ounce of it
left in this world...
...you'd be lying face down
in the same unmarked grave...
...as the rest of your inbred family.
The only difference between me
and you, Alex, is a badge.
Last time I checked,
you didn't have that.
So you can just keep on hoping
for your happy endings.
You just keep on plowing ahead
with them blinders on.
But the thing about them blinders is...
...it makes it really hard
to watch your back.
It's gonna be better soon, I promise.
He's right, you know.
If James loves you,
he'll give us what we want.
And then you and your white knight
can ride off into the sunset.
Unless you're already with him.
You scared, Susan?
Do I look scared, Lincoln?
Pull something like this...
- You desperate?
- You need to stop fighting with me.
If you really understood,
you'd know we're not the bad guys.
Could've fooled me.
Ever done
the wrong things for the right reason?
What are the right reasons?
What is it about Whistler
that's so important?
I could tell you,
but then I'd have to kill you.
You're gonna do that anyway.
Whistler gives us what we want,
maybe I won't have to.
Linc called.
They're on their way.
I figured them out.
The coordinates.
I'm gonna hand them over.
I thought you should know, so you can
take whatever precautions you can.
What if, uh-- What if you give them
the wrong coordinates?
It might buy us some more time.
- Maybe Linc can get Sofia to safety.
- Like he did with Sara?
I'm sorry, I...
I didn't mean to. I, uh...
I just don't know what else to do.
I'm damned if I do, damned if I don't.
There's no way to win.
It's not about winning anymore,
it's about surviving.
- Which is not the same as giving up.
- But you can go gracefully.
There's honor,
protecting the ones you love.
Honor's a luxury
men like us can't afford.
Can you promise me
we'll make it out of here tonight?
No games.
Can you honestly promise me?
I can promise you
I'll do everything in my power.
I wish that were good enough.
If you do this,
if you give them what they want...
...everything that's been lost
will have been for nothing.
Monjares.
Jorge.
Whistler, you have a visitor.
Linc, he's gonna give it to them.
Relax. I'll see you in a minute.
What are you talking about?
Scofield, you have a visitor.
I suppose introductions
are unnecessary at this point.
What are we doing here, Gretchen?
We're here to say goodbye.
I promise you,
they're not gonna hurt you anymore.
Do you have the coordinates, James?
- Yes.
- I'm sorry.
- I tried to run away--
- This isn't your fault.
It's mine.
When I took this job,
I knew they weren't good people.
I just didn't know how bad they were.
And everything that's happened...
...it's all because of me.
For that, I'm truly sorry.
The coordinates.
Just pass them through.
What the hell are you doing?
I'm buying some goodwill.
You're buying her funeral.
You know I have what you need.
And I'll give you the rest.
But only after I know that Sofia,
that L.J...
...and that these men here...
...they're all safe.
Do you understand me?
James.
Everything's gonna be all right.
I'm impressed.
Seems our fisherman grew himself
a set of oysters.
Can you really trust these men
with her life?
Yeah. Yeah, I believe I can.
All right, James.
But there's been some confusion
about the timing of things.
Last-minute changes, et cetera.
Gonna make this clear
for everyone involved.
If time runs out...
...and I don't have the second half
of those coordinates...
...L.J. and the señorita stop breathing.
- Say goodbye, sweetheart.
- Lincoln.
- Linc--
- Don't be stupid, Lincoln.
I've helped you.
Now you help me.
Please.
Just get us out of here.
You sure about the backup generator?
Yeah. All we gotta do now
is cut the power to the exterior lights.
- How you gonna do that?
- I'm not.
They can't be accessed
from the inside.
- How much time have I got?
- Let's say, uh, 5:15 tomorrow morning.
That should give us time to dig out
before the sun comes up.
- What about Whistler?
- What about him?
He could've handed over
the information, but he didn't.
- Still concerned about handing him over?
- I've got concerns about everybody.
- You know what I mean?
- Yeah.
Mostly I'm just tired.
Tired of choices...
...and consequences.
I just want this to be over. Tonight.
Let's do it.
When you're on the run, you're always
looking over your shoulder...
...listening for the sirens.
Wondering if that pretty girl
across the street is staring at you...
...because she wants you
or because you're wanted.
You change your name,
the way you look.
Leave everything
you ever knew behind.
And the ones you love,
they're the ones who have to pay.
That's what's waiting for you
on the outside.
That's why I couldn't bring you on.
Because nothing good
can come of this.
Can anything good come
from staying in?
It has to be your decision.
I cannot be responsible for you.
You won't have to be.
Does your father still have
that phone number I gave you?
I think so.
Well, tell him to call my brother...
...if he wants to find out
where to pick you up tomorrow.
Does that mean...?
It means if a million things
fall in place...
I'm gonna see my father tomorrow.
Don't let anyone see you
with that phone.
I think we did it, Michael.
I believe we're ready.
She's a little wet, but she's ready.
Makes me think of the first thing I'd do
when we gonna get out.
It's just-- Does anybody know
what's Spanish for "Don't shoot"?
No dispare.
- No dis what?
- Just relax.
Nobody's gonna get shot.
Just don't panic.
As soon as Linc cuts the power,
we go.
- What about the Jeep patrol?
- Taken care of.
What about the backup generator?
- Backup generator?
- Nobody said anything--
There's a lag when the power cuts
to when the generator kicks in.
Well, how long a lag
we talking about here?
Thirty seconds.
And you expect us to run
in 30 seconds?
As soon as the lights go out,
I'm gone.
With or without you.
Jorge Rivera.
Now.
Let's go.
Off the bus, now. Get off the bus!
As soon as the lights go out,
we gotta be ready to move.
- What's the taquito doing down here?
- He's coming with us.
- I don't think so.
- That's not up to you.
Huh.
Actually, I think...
- Oh, you gotta be kidding me.
- See, we made a little, uh...
...decision here.
What with the time frame
being so short and all...
...we'd feel better
if we could go first.
- What are you gonna do, kill me?
- No, no.
- If we ain't first, he's not going.
- All right, all right. Just...
All right.
All right, go. Just go.
Just go.
Every man for himself, right?
You wanna move up in line too?
No, I think I'm gonna stay back here.
I just don't wanna turn my back
on anybody.
Thirty seconds. Go.