Previously on Prison Break:
I just wanna go.
It's okay.
What special talents do you have
that you are worth more alive than dead?
Be careful, Alex.
- Were you able to find my book?
- Yeah.
But there was this guy. He took it.
He said to tell you
that Scofield's brother has it now.
- You'll have to bring them out.
- L.J.! Sara!
Never try anything like that again.
But just to make sure,
I left you something in the garage.
Yo, yo, yo,
check them out over there, dawg.
What's so interesting out there,
other than our freedom?
The vine's alive, so the fence is dead.
No current.
Everyone in here knows that fence
doesn't work. It doesn't mean a thing.
Soldiers will shoot you
before you get within 30 yards.
Well, I guess I got a lot of work to do,
don't I?
I get what you're doing with my book.
They hold your friend, you hold what
they want. Counter needs, Churchill 101.
They're gonna ask my progress
in figuring out what they want.
I'm gonna say,
"Nil. Lincoln Burrows has the book."
You know what? Threatening the brother
of who's supposed to get you out...
- ...might not be the smartest move.
- I'm not threatening.
We play games with that book...
...the people who want me out
will take action against us all.
"I never worry about action,
only inaction."
Churchill 101.
Now, like I said,
I got a lot of work to do.
- Linc, you all right?
- I'm sorry, man.
It's just all this stuff,
it's starting to get to me, you know?
Listen, our situation could change
very, very soon.
The gravedigger for the prison,
I need you to reach out to him.
- Tell him what?
- It's all written down.
But we gotta get started now.
What are you not telling me?
All these people that have been hurt
because of me...
...you know, it's...
- I'm so sorry, Michael.
- They did this, not you.
Okay? It's not your fault.
Just get to the gravedigger.
I feel like we're running out of time.
Sara.
I am just a soldier in this war,
Lincoln...
...just like you.
I did not want to do that.
Can you even comprehend
the intimacy of the mechanics...
...of what I had to do to that woman?
It's horrible.
Now, if you and your brother
are done playing games, L.J. will be fine.
If not, the last thing I wanna do
is start mailing pieces of him to you.
But if you push me...
...and not even that far, I will.
I'll do anything you want.
Just don't hurt my son.
It's really up to you.
I know the past few days
have been hard, for me as well.
If you wanna talk about it,
I know what this pain feels like.
I just wanna get your boy out of Sona
and get my son back.
- Michael's got a plan.
- I need details.
We need to bring someone
who works at the prison onto the team.
- Who?
- The gravedigger.
Get it done.
Lincoln, I'm gonna need that book.
The Company did handwriting analysis
on the one you gave me...
...and yours hasn't changed
since high school.
Just soldiers, Linc. Different armies,
but soldiers just the same.
Nice.
- I was best in my school.
- All girls?
Kiss my ass, bro.
Twenty bucks says
you can't do that again.
- Bet.
- Wait.
- Adjust for wind.
- Shut up.
It's just a bit outside.
Hey, bro, you know I don't have
that kind of verde lying around.
- It's gonna take a while.
- The thing is I don't have a while.
- So unless you want--
- No more favors.
All right. Then I'll borrow
that cross of yours.
- I'll take it in trade.
- My dad gave me this.
- Besides, it's not even real gold.
- That's why I need it.
Look, I'll give it back, okay?
It's just a loan.
Come on, I've gotta go.
This time, I wanna know why.
It's light again.
Somebody getting fat off
everything I built, while I rot in here.
Don't get upset, patrón. I only have
a few more hours. Let's be nice.
This motherless bitch.
Alex.
- You just get here?
- Yes.
Listen, I've been thinking about
our little talk...
...and you're in.
I'm in. Okay.
- Just like that?
- I really--
I really don't have a choice, do I?
- What's the plan?
- I'm working on it.
Meanwhile, I could use your help.
- What do you need?
- A black felt-tipped pen.
- A pen?
- Yeah.
- Why?
- Some documents that need altering.
I'll explain it to you later.
Right now, I need that pen, okay?
Yeah.
I'll tell you what else I need.
I need you to get your act together.
Bring yourself under control,
because you're attracting attention.
And that we don't need.
- I'm under control.
- Of course you are.
This is what happens
when the system is overloaded.
See? Look.
- Son of a--
- Power is out.
- Fix it.
- I'm a truck driver.
Hey, Alex.
Glad I found you.
Wanted to see how you're holding up.
Just dandy.
I've been having a tough time of it.
It shouldn't be that way for us...
...seeing as how we're the only lawmen
here in Taco Hell.
Hey, whoa.
Wait on a second there, Alex.
You and me, we were a team
on the outside. I was your dawg.
- I still got a lot of bark left--
- I'm busy, Brad.
- What do you want?
- You and Scofield.
You're up to something.
You can tell me, one badge to another.
- I can help.
- Do you have a black felt-tipped pen?
- Not on me.
- Then you can't help me.
- I know.
- You know what?
I know you're trying to escape from here
with that man Scofield.
- Sweetheart--
- Please, don't lie to me.
Lincoln Burrows,
he told me everything.
There are some very powerful people
that want me out of here.
- They want the brothers to get me out.
- Why?
I'm not sure. It has something to do
with a charter I did in Seattle.
What I do know is, their endgame
is the same as ours.
And that's me out of this hellhole.
Once that happens,
you and I will disappear forever.
- I don't wanna involve you in this mess.
- I want to help.
- It's too dangerous.
- I'm not asking permission.
I'm telling you.
I can't do this on my own.
If you can tell me what you know,
we can work it through together.
I don't understand everything
that's going on.
They're trying to find out
what they can about me.
Let's see what we can discover
about them.
- Find what their plan is.
- They're trying to get you out...
- ...and you don't trust them?
- I don't trust any of these guys.
And you shouldn't either.
If you insist on getting into this,
promise you'll be careful.
Because God knows,
I will die if anything happens to you.
Hey.
Michael.
Here.
I said I needed a black felt-tipped pen.
- It's black.
- It's not what I need.
Keep looking.
He's playing me.
He's playing you.
Do not trust him.
Your amigo, the American...
...he's a builder, an engineer, no?
No amigo of mine, boss.
Trust me, you do not wanna get
under the covers--
Is he or is he not an engineer?
Well, yeah, but--
Scofield.
- What do you know about electricity?
- Only that we don't have any right now.
Let me tell you something.
This phone keeps all the food
coming to the gate...
...keeps my business running,
Sona running.
Electricity die, phone die.
Phone die, we die.
We die or you die?
Boy, you have enough education
but you're not being smart.
Now, I come to you,
that is an opportunity.
Be wise and take advantage.
Now, can you fix the electricity
just like you fixed the water?
It's not that simple.
The water pipes are inside the prison.
The electrical lines are probably running
underground along an exterior wall.
Which means they're out there
somewhere in no man's land.
- So you can fix the power?
- Last I checked...
...they shoot prisoners who go out there,
so I'm thinking the answer is no.
Now, you listen to me.
And you listen closely, water boy.
Like it or not, soldiers or not...
...you're going out into no man's land.
- It's a suicide mission.
- I'll make some calls.
- You're gonna keep me safe?
- As best I can.
- I don't think I can do this.
- No, no, no.
You will help me with this.
Look, I will do something for you.
I get you a new pillow.
Goose feather, like mine.
Or a small TV.
All right.
Get me that.
- Why?
- It's the first to get sun in the morning.
You get me that cell,
I'll get you electricity.
Hey, Linc.
Look, bro, I'm gonna be out of your way
real soon.
I saw these fliers for migrant workers
in Colombia.
Coffee bean season.
They're letting Panamanians in.
So I figure with a good ID,
I could pass.
- Bus leaves today, okay?
- All right.
Before you get out of here, man...
...I'm meeting someone
and I need a translator.
Linc, I appreciate everything
you've done--
Just be a couple of hours.
Just be a couple of hours, that's it.
When I was 15, my cousin told me about
a job that only lasts a few hours.
- And I got three months.
- I can't do this without you.
- I'm in Panama, I don't speak--
- I can't miss that bus.
I'm gonna make money
and send it home.
On the run or not, I'm gonna be a dad.
You, of all people, should understand--
I spoke to James.
He confirmed what you told me
about the escape.
You and I, we both have people in there
we care about.
Please, let me help you.
Your Spanish as good as your English?
Yes, colonel.
I just have one favor to ask.
Just outside of the gate.
Well, you can bring your men.
The phone is dying.
Make him one.
This is it?
Not everyone has it yet. We let credit
go a week and there is still time.
- It's in your veins, adicto.
- No, patrón.
No, patrón. I don't use anymore,
I swear to you. I swear to you.
Chin up, pal of mine, chin up.
Sí, colonel.
Yes, thank you, colonel.
We'll be right there.
Come with me.
Excuse me, do you...?
Do you have a pen?
Pen, pen. Not the brush.
- With the pen. Pen, pen.
- No, no, pintura.
The pintura, yeah.
He's leaving you.
He's leaving you. He'll be gone...
...and you'll be stuck
in this maze forever.
Thank you for arranging this
for us, colonel.
I am getting something out of this,
I assure you.
You know you can fix
this electric problem?
I won't know for sure until we can start
digging, but, yes, I think so.
My men will shoot you in the head...
...if you so much as look
at the fence, huh?
And you, patrón...
...if anything goes wrong,
it will not only be his life that is lost.
- You have my word on that.
- It's no worries, colonel.
I'll keep this boy in line.
- I'll dig.
- I don't need your help.
Hey, come on, man, don't be proud.
I heard you talking just yesterday,
talking to Mahone.
You know, about how us Americans
should stick together.
So I help you now and I'm sure
you'll help me down the road.
Right, Mikey?
What is it, a '66 or a '67?
The car.
- Sixty-six.
- What is it, 325 horses?
Three-seven-five.
- What's he saying?
- He recognizes me.
- He doesn't realize it was at prison.
- Does he want cash...
...to get this car cherry
by next week?
He knows we're not talking
about cars.
That's right.
I know you're getting out of here.
I heard about you and the limey.
- I'm just fixing the electricity.
- And I'm just single because I'm choosy.
- Don't make me tell what I know.
- What is it you think you know?
Something called the Company wanted
you in here with Whistler. Am I warm?
What's the Company?
What do they want with Whistler?
I don't know, but you do.
Doesn't sound like you know much.
I don't need to know how to change
a diaper to know when it stinks.
- You're doing something here, Scofield.
- You're right, I am.
I'm fixing the electricity.
You wanted to help dig? Dig.
Hey. This is it.
We're doing more
than playing electrician.
Don't worry.
We're exactly where we need to be.
Heat's getting to me, Scofield.
It's quitting time.
You mind telling me
why he's even out here with us?
He knows something's up.
- How the hell does he know that?
- Let's just say I have a bit of a rep.
From Fox River?
I know who you are, mate.
Figured it out just lately.
Finally made sense why they'd pick you,
of all people, to send here.
No worries.
It's in my interest
to keep your little secret.
But Bellick? He can't be trusted.
I can handle Bellick.
He's not in on this.
- Okay, good.
- But Mahone is.
Mahone? He's looking about as stable
as a three-legged chair...
- ...and he's escaping with us?
- No, he just thinks he is.
He needs his meds. Without them,
he'll self-destruct.
It's just a matter of time.
And if he doesn't?
I'll string him along,
tell him what he wants to hear.
Then I'll cut him loose.
How do I know you're not gonna do
the same thing to me?
You don't.
You need a hookup, my friend?
- No.
- Take your time.
I don't hard sell.
My product speaks for itself.
Outside, I took something.
This prescription drug
called Veratril.
And I was wondering if you...
This ain't no farmacia.
But what I got right here...
...is better than anything your doctor
gave you back in the States.
- That's tar.
- Just take a taste.
You know, keep it in check.
I don't have any money right now.
Then I don't have any drugs.
But there are a few ways for a man...
...to make a few dollars,
servicing the needs of others.
- Not something I'm into but--
- You think I'm a punk?
I'm just helping you get well, my friend.
Just helping you get well.
Señor Luchero.
- What do you want?
- I know you're busy...
...but I wanted to tell you,
Michael Scofield's taking you for a ride.
No, cerdo, I don't think so.
I heard him talking about escape
yesterday, about breaking out of here.
If he's talking about escape, why are you
here and you're not going with him, eh?
I would if he'd let me
but he's cut me out.
He says he's square,
but I know he's up to something.
So I figured, I might as well tell you,
and make my time in here a bit easier.
Every man fantasizes
about escaping from Sona.
Yeah, but they aren't all
in no man's land with shovels.
I gave him the shovels. Get him out.
I gave him shovels too,
and guys to work with.
I worked in the prison he broke out of.
He said he was doing me a favor,
fixing damage from a fire he started.
And you know what I got? Hogtied
and left in a pipe under my own prison.
There's nothing he can do.
The soldiers are watching him.
That's what I thought, until he tunneled
out of my guard's room.
He's buried something
in the junction box and covered it.
I saw him. Go see for yourself.
If I'm lying, I'm dying.
Trouble keeps finding you here
in Sona, doesn't it?
Take a walk, eh?
There are rumors
that you're trying to trick me.
I'm just doing what I'm told.
Well, let's hope for your sake
that's true.
But just to make sure...
...let's go on out to no man's land
and see what you buried there.
I just wanna make sure my men
are doing a good job for the colonel.
Get in there.
Open it.
Move the dirt. Now.
It's duct tape to fix the frayed wires.
It's why the power was so inconsistent.
I didn't want the tape to come loose,
so I packed it down with dirt.
Beautiful.
Where you going?
I gotta turn the main power switch
back on.
I had to turn it off
so we could work on the wires safely.
- I'll come with you.
- It's just a switch.
- I can handle it myself.
- Yeah, you can, but you won't.
Water boy, it's back here.
Don't need the chain, just the cross.
It's the perfect size. It's not gold...
...so it won't conduct current.
Keep the circuit open, no power,
even when the main switch is turned on.
Take the cross out,
Sona lights up again.
Lechero find out you mess
with his electric, you're dead.
That's why he can't ever find out.
Now, don't make me come get you.
Nobody back there can help you.
It's some kind of mistake.
- It should be working.
- Only mistake I made was trusting you.
Sammy.
Transformer delay. It's an old prison.
Now, if you don't mind,
I'd like to move into my new cell.
Thank you for your words before,
blanco.
Working for Lechero...
...not an easy field to plow,
comprende?
Oh, yeah, yeah, I comprende.
But you and me,
we're amigos, Nieves.
When Lechero's in a better mood,
I put in a good word.
Help you-- How you say?
--move up the ladder.
Oh, I appreciate it, compadre,
but I was always taught...
...that God helps those
that help themselves.
- Fifteen thousand.
- Why?
Because that's what he wanted.
Relax, I'll get you the money.
- And I will meet you there.
- Okay.
How you holding up?
- I just wanna get this done.
- Good.
Stay here.
- I'm coming with you.
- Stay here.
- Do you expect me to stay and wait?
- I don't care.
You don't care? Who the hell
are you to say you don't care?
- You're not the only one affected.
- I know, that's the problem.
And you will run and do what you want?
What kind of a man are you that just--?
They killed Sara and put her head
in a box. And they've got my son.
Oh, Linc, I'm sorry.
You still here?
- Hey, Lechero wants to talk to you.
- I was just about to get a little trim.
- Lechero said I was looking all bootoo.
- It'll wait.
Did you know about this?
- Did you know anything about this?
- Me? No, no.
Nieves...
Nieves, we was friends, man.
That's right.
Now, if you knew that he was using
and didn't tell me...
...his death is on your head.
Patrón, patrón, patrón.
I don't know nothing about drugs.
I don't.
I mean, I tried me some reefer
when I was 12.
I almost coughed up a lung.
Good.
That's good, Teodoro.
There appears to be an opening
on my crew.
McGrady, here's your cross back
and thank you.
You're a real smart guy.
What the hell are you doing in prison?
Here.
That's perfect. How'd you get it?
- It's what you wanted, right?
- Yeah.
- Good work.
- So, what's the next step?
We wait and I'll keep you posted.
You know what you need to do.
What do you think?
I know you fixed the electricity
for a reason.
But it can't have been
to make that fence sizzle.
Unless you wanna
make the colonel happy.
It's in both of our best interests to make
that fence as deadly as possible.
All we gotta do is wait for my brother
to come through with the gravedigger.
He wants more.
You said 15,000.
- You said 15,000! You said 15,000!
- Lincoln, I got it.
No, no, no.
What the hell are you doing?
We need him.
He will sell us out to the cops after
he takes as much as he can from us.
- No.
- No!
He's packing up to go.
Kill him.
He's gonna betray you. Kill him.
Good news, Agent Mahone.
Due to the untimely demise
of Señor Juan Nieves...
...I have now been promoted
manager in charge...
...of retail distribution
and customer liaison.
- Get away from me.
- All in due time.
Now, I'm not you mama,
and I ain't one to wipe others' noses...
...but let's just say
you've looked better.
I want nothing from you.
But sure seems you need something.
On the arm, no strings attached.
Get your head straight, Alex.
Come on in, now.
Come watch the match, come.
Oh, yeah, you guys call this football
down here, right?
Very good, very good. It's World Cup.
Football without the silly hats
you wear in America.
They all jump on top of each other
like a bunch of batty boys.
Have a seat. Come.
Teodoro...
Café
The only thing I hate more than a rat
is a rat with bad information.
Yeah, look, I'm sorry about all that,
but my information was good.
It's just that Scofield's
a tricky bastard.
He'll try something again, you'll see.
Why--? Wait a minute.
Come on, what are you doing to me?
Come on, I gave you good information.
Scofield's planning to escape.
I'm telling you.
He's a sly bastard. Come on, guys.
Come on, what are you doing?
Don't do this to me.
What are you doing?
- Don't-- Look...
- Shh, shh, shh.
I gave you good information.
You say something this morning about,
"If I'm lying, I'm dying."
Be thankful I don't hold you to that.
Come on, Bagwell, help me here, man.
Come on, Bagwell.
You left this in your old cell.
- Thanks, Alex.
- You're welcome.
It's funny that you could forget
something as important as this is.
Well, I'm glad you found it for me.
Yeah.
Oh, oh, look.
You are breathing
only by my grace, Michael.
Now, you remember the next time
that you're gonna send me...
- ...on a goose chase, okay?
- I didn't mean to--
No, no, you did.
You think you can manipulate me...
...just like you did Sucre
and Tweener...
...and Haywire.
I'm not your errand boy.
I'm gonna go with you when you escape.
And if you think, in any way...
...that you'll leave me,
I will put this piece of metal...
...right in that very small space...
...right between your eyes.
I will.
How's L.J.? How's Sara?
They told me they're fine.
- Listen, the gravedigger, he's gone.
- What do you mean, he's gone?
Linc, we can't do this without him.
I know, I know.
We went to his supervisor.
The guy who approves and hires
for that job.
Turns out he could use some cash.
Mail call.
- This is how we're getting out.
- Yes.
With a little help from an old friend.
- What is that?
- Kesslivol.
It's a chemical that kills the odors
caused by decomposing bodies.
And, when heated
to a certain degree...
...it eats through steel.