Previously on Prison Break:
We're losing the light. Go back.
You, is that your cell?
You are breaking out of this prison,
Mr. Scofield.
You're taking me with you.
So with this deal, what specifically
are they expecting from me?
They need to know everything.
They wanna confirm that you
have viable incriminating information.
You can be a cooperative witness.
Show me the pictures.
I can't show you the pictures, man.
She's dead, Michael.
I thought we agreed
it was best for you to not come.
I need to know
how this is gonna affect things.
Four more days.
If I'm out of here by then,
I can still do it.
I'll let the brothers know.
Michael.
- You like this?
- Yeah, yeah.
It's a special occasion.
My dad's coming today, so I'm just
gonna wait here till he shows up.
- You look sharp.
- Thanks.
Scofield, you have a visitor.
- L.J., is he--?
- Alive.
- They've given us four more days.
- Okay, good.
Back at the exchange point,
I saw three body bags.
You, me and L.J.,
we weren't getting out of there alive.
That's the last time
I get caught flatfooted.
Then do what you gotta do, Linc.
As long as I take care of my end,
right?
Michael, I know you're angry at me
about Sara, but--
- You lied.
- I had to lie.
Your son is my nephew.
And there's nothing
I wouldn't do for him.
But apparently...
Apparently, you think I only care
about myself.
I know you don't care about yourself,
but you cared about Sara.
You loved her, and I'm sorry.
But L.J. is my son.
I couldn't let anything happen to him.
You know that.
You used me, Linc.
So I guess you and the Company
have something in common.
I don't know where he is.
I have tried every number I have.
Well, listen,
I'll check back with headquarters...
...and see what they say.
Never mind. I found him.
Carter Blue Label.
You always had such high-end taste
for a girl from Wheeling.
Since I paid for it.
You know how much
I hate to travel, Gretchen?
But considering the mess down here,
I made an exception.
- It was a mess before I got here.
- And it's time to clean it up.
We're ending this today.
Ah.
Bang and burn.
General, that was analyzed.
What you're asking for is too dangerous.
Not to mention next to impossible
with the given time frame.
I remember a substantial wire transfer
to an offshore account...
...that took the word "impossible"
out of the equation.
Or tell me,
did I hire the wrong person?
I am doing my job
when I tell you to seriously reconsider.
And now I have to do my job.
I don't pay you to be my advisor.
You're my operative.
You have your instructions.
Now, get it done.
Because if you don't, I'll make
what happened to you in Mosul...
...feel like a massage.
This was a big mistake, Gretchen.
Can't make a habit
of coming to Sona.
I won't.
Because we're going with
the bang and burn.
That's suicide.
We have more time.
My boss wants things to move
a bit faster.
Well, tell him you can't pull it off.
- I might get killed if we do this.
- And I might get killed if we don't.
Between you and me,
who do you think I care about more?
Look at me, James.
See if you can tell how serious I am.
If you don't play ball,
I will leave you in Sona to rot.
I promise.
Be ready by 5.
That's when it happens.
Everybody goes.
What about Scofield?
Kill him.
You know the consequences
if I'm seen talking to you?
The military's reinforcing the bars
on all the windows.
Can you talk to the colonel?
Get him to postpone that?
After your performance yesterday,
I have no sway with the colonel.
I'm afraid you've brokered your way
into an escape plan that no longer exists.
I have an idea.
Lechero.
Wait here for me.
What?
Some of the men don't feel the need
to pay their debts anymore.
It's been one week, man,
and we lost three men.
Now, if we gonna keep Sona,
we're gonna need numbers.
I don't trust nobody here, Norino.
Especially now.
I'll work with the men I have.
Really, brother?
You, me and the gimp over there,
we gonna run this place?
I wanna bring on Cristobal.
He's solid, man.
One of them Darrien ghetto boys.
Bring him over.
But I promise you nothing.
Find me anything that can sustain
heavy RPGs and small arms.
A Cougar, a Stryker.
Not gonna happen. We do have a call
into a Sergeant York--
Yeah, that's not gonna cut it.
Call Suezamel, put him on standby.
Tell him we might need him.
Is there a problem?
- We're doing this at 5:00?
- We can wait until tonight...
...when our guys are moving too fast for
night vision to work. You can tag along.
Get it done.
Hello?
Yes, I'm trying to
locate the family of Mr. James Whistler.
I am his--
I'm his wife. Who's calling?
My name's Tommy Day. I own
the apartment Mr. Whistler rents from.
There's a busted pipe in his unit
that's caused damage...
...to the apartment next door.
I'm sorry, I think you have confused
James with someone else.
He's not renting another apartment.
Oh, I assure you,
Mr. Whistler's my tenant.
I couldn't find anyone
after his conviction.
But I checked his phone bill. There
were numerous calls to this number.
If you could come to the apartment...
...the address is 40 Abel Bravo
in Obarrio, Unit 4.
Tell your men the lntel says...
...the Panamanians have no access
to SAM.
- Yeah?
- There's been a development.
Hey. The Company's giving us
four more days.
- Okay.
- Problem is, I...
I don't know
how we're getting out of here.
Lechero might have some ideas,
but I'm still waiting to hear from him.
- I'm sorry, is this a bad time for you?
- It's been an intense 24 hours.
- I have things on my mind.
- Yeah?
Like your last trip to visitation,
maybe?
What, you're a spy now?
Forgive me if I'm wrong, but she didn't
strike me as the girlfriend type.
She was Company.
After your failed escape, she came
to remind me I have a stake in this too.
Which you seem to have forgotten.
So forgive me if I don't jump for joy...
...when you say you're working
on a plan that may very well fail again.
I gotta get out of here and it's getting
to the point where I don't care how.
Got what we talked about?
You never met me.
Enough.
Shales. Shales.
Oh, my God.
What the hell is going on?
- Shales.
- What about Oscar Shales?
He raped, killed and tortured.
I couldn't turn him over
to some scumbag lawyer...
...who was just gonna get him off or--
Couldn't. No. No, I just--
So I killed him.
And I felt good.
I felt-- I felt really good.
But then, there came the visions
of Shales begging for his life.
And I couldn't get rid of them.
So I got these drugs
that kept me on an even keel.
And then when I got to Sona,
I couldn't get my pills.
So I had to...
...improvise.
Did you want me
to get drugs for you?
I assume that whoever set this up
must think that I might have some value.
That's why you came back for me.
I came here to help a man that
I respect and care about.
I appreciate that.
But I can't testify like this.
Please?
One-inch reinforced steel
on every window.
I don't think
we're getting through those.
I'll figure something out.
I know you will.
Listen, man, I'm sorry about before.
Like I said, things have been intense.
So much depends on this working out.
My nephew's life
depends on this working.
I know it does.
I never asked, how old is he?
- Sixteen.
- Oh, hell.
Knock, knock.
What do you want?
Me? I just came by
to slip something in your mail slot.
It's from EI Patron himself,
but it was meant for your eyes only.
Grabby.
It don't look like no invitation
to the Sona-Hawkins Dance.
- What do you got cooking with Lechero?
- It's none of your business, Theodore.
You wanna keep secrets? You wanna
treat me like a pesky insect? Fine.
Just remember, information,
like crumbs...
...always trickles down
to the vermin on the floor.
Four o'clock?
It's a sketch of Lechero's quarters.
To be honest, when a tenant pays
a year's rent in advance...
...and then gets locked up...
...I normally rent the place out
and double my money.
But James was a good man.
I was hoping things
will turn out well for him.
Look, uh, miss.
A lot of guys
have a little something on the side.
This apartment,
whoever he brought here...
...doesn't mean he didn't love you.
You said you have
James' insurance papers?
Right on, right on. I'll go get them.
There's another door in here.
Forty-four thirteen.
Forty-four thirteen, huh?
- What about Scofield?
- Kill him.
You know,
if Lechero didn't send this...
...T-Bag might be setting me up
for someone.
What do you say we get out of here?
I'm truly sorry you got caught up
in my troubles, Michael.
Scofield?
- I take it there's another code.
- And I'm the only one who knows it.
For a man who likes secrets, using T-Bag
might not be the smartest move.
By the time he figures it out,
we'll be long gone.
Sammy's on his way back, let's go.
What the hell is this?
Underground tunnel.
The old administration used it
to travel between Cell Blocks A and B.
After the riots,
they moved us all to B.
And then the soldiers came in,
blew this tunnel up.
Looks like someone already
tried to get through the debris.
Well, I never planned to spend
my whole life in Sona.
Just didn't expect it to end so soon.
You're the engineer, though, right?
You can dig our way out of this?
Yeah, we need a couple of Payloaders.
No, now, you listen.
You're gonna dig out of this place.
We're not digging out.
But we might be digging up.
Hello, Sofia.
Hello. Who are you?
A friend of James. Old friend.
Well, he isn't here.
I know where he is.
I can see why James loves you.
You are beautiful.
But if you keep sticking your nose
where it doesn't belong...
...I'm gonna make him miss you
very, very much.
Do you understand what I'm saying
to you?
Good.
You don't need to worry about this.
Now, listen very carefully to me, Sofia,
and you won't get hurt.
I want you to go home, do your hair,
and paint your nails and get all ready...
...for when James comes home.
- You two will live happily ever after.
- What do you want from him?
See, you're not listening already.
Don't get in the way or I promise you,
things will get very bad for you.
You are truly beautiful.
I hope you can stay that way.
Get the hell out of here.
All right. If we get through the ceiling,
foundation and earth on top of that...
...we can make it to middle
of no-man's-land.
We maybe hit the fence
before we get shot.
Yeah. Well, we wouldn't want that.
Yes, but you can dig out though,
right?
Based on gravity and the sand
that Sona's built on...
...we're gonna need some kind of
support brace for the tunnel, or...
Or what?
Or the whole thing collapses
and we're buried alive.
Go ahead and relax, huh?
I'll get some rum.
- How long will it take?
- Maybe two days.
I gotta get upstairs
and estimate where in no-man's-land...
...that tunnel's gonna let out.
Where you going? I'm meditating.
I was just getting rum
for Cristobal and his boys.
Rum? His boys?
No, I said I'd meet with Cristobal.
Not every half-breed in Sona.
- All right, well, they're up there now.
- Let's go.
- Let me just get some rum, man.
- No.
They drink beer like everyone else.
Look, man.
I offered them something good.
Don't make me look the fool.
The rum is for me, Sammy.
Now, you have a problem with that?
- No, sir.
- Good. Let's go.
Let's get back to work.
Hey, only Lechero has the code.
We don't need a code.
Get inside before Sammy comes back.
Alex.
Where's Agent Lang?
Agent-- I don't know.
What--? What the hell's wrong with you?
What's going on?
I think I have a right to be nervous.
My life is on the line, you know.
What are you talking about?
You have given live press conferences
your entire life.
I've seen you many times, you're an old
pro. Now splash water on your face.
- The panel wants us there right now.
- What?
Get dressed. Or would you rather
have me drag your ass back to Sona?
Water on the face. Get your suit on.
We're going.
Yeah, it's Sullins.
We're almost ready to move here.
Where the hell is Lang? No.
Where we at?
- Everything's in place.
- Good.
We've done our part. Now it's time
for Whistler to step up and do his.
Come 5:00, he better be ready.
Three feet of concrete and rebar,
plus 10 feet of dirt and sand...
...before we see sky.
Are you all right?
To be completely honest, no.
Not really.
- I have this thing for confined spaces.
- You're telling me you're claustrophobic?
Ever since I was a boy. Um...
- I need to be upstairs.
- That's not really an option right now.
Staying here is not really an option
for me either.
- I suggest you get yourself together.
- I just need some air.
- What the hell's the matter with you?
- I need to get out of here, I need air.
You walk through that door,
you'll never need air again.
You don't understand.
I need to get out of here now.
What's really going on here?
Why do you keep looking at your watch?
What are you really up to?
Scofield, the men are gone,
let's move.
- I need your phone.
- Sammy's on his way.
- I have to call my brother.
- The phone stays with me. Get out.
Oh, just so that we're clear, she's got
no electricity and no running water.
Septic's out too,
but there's an outhouse in the woods.
It's perfect.
A hundred bucks a month.
- Two hundred.
- A hundred bucks a month.
Deal.
But I don't want growing no drugs
on the land.
No marijuana.
You got that?
- Welcome home, my friend.
- Thanks.
Listen, if you wanna get out of here,
I get it and Michael would too.
You've done more than enough.
If I had a kid
in the same situation as your son...
...would you and your brother
walk out on me?
Yeah.
Here, this is good. Put it down there.
Okay, hold on.
- You ready?
- Yeah.
I hope this works, papi.
All right, let's go.
McGrady.
I need your help.
Not now, bro. My father got here,
I'm gonna see him.
Actually, I need his help too.
- What you want from my old man?
- Someone to deliver a message outside.
- Someone I can trust.
- Hell, no.
My papa don't get into trouble
like you do.
- It's not trouble, just a phone call.
- No.
- I love my father.
- And I love my brother.
If he doesn't get this message,
something's gonna happen to him.
Look, something really bad is going on.
Please.
- Hello, son.
- Papa.
You look very handsome.
Like your school picture.
I cleaned a guy's cell for this shirt.
- You should be in school now.
- It's okay, Papa.
With your friends.
Papa, please don't get upset.
I have friends in here.
- The American?
- Yes. He's nice.
He keeps his word.
It's very rare in Sona.
And, uh, he needs my help.
Thank God you're here.
I thought you might have come earlier
just to make sure I was okay.
I read the newspaper.
I knew you were safe.
I am, for now. But you might not be.
Now, listen to me carefully.
Promise me you won't go near
Lincoln Burrows today.
- Lincoln?
- Too dangerous to be around him.
To be with him, to be near him.
Just go home and stay there.
And I will call you tonight.
That's all I can say.
Do you understand?
- Call me? From where?
- Do you understand me?
- Yeah.
- Promise me.
Say it out loud.
I promise.
Why are you so scared?
Because I can't have you get hurt.
Because I love you
more than anything in the world.
Do you?
Yeah.
James, I got a call today from a man
who says he's your landlord.
Talking about another apartment.
Should I call him back?
- Must have been a wrong number.
- He asked for you by name.
The man is clearly confused.
I don't know anything
about another apartment.
Sofia, all I know is that
you've gotta stay away from Lincoln.
Please.
Okay, James.
I'll wait for your call.
Here.
I have this.
I don't wanna see it.
I'll put it with the others.
I'm not coming home. Accept that.
You should go.
Make that call for my friend.
Happy birthday, son.
Maybe we should pick up some locks,
secure the house.
We can't have anything new on it.
The place needs to look abandoned.
Yeah?
I have a message for you.
Don't come home for dinner.
Who is this?
I'm supposed to tell you,
don't come home for dinner.
What?
When me and Mikey were kids,
we had a code...
...when Social Services
were trying to get me into juvie.
He's telling me to watch my back.
- What are you doing here?
- Why haven't you returned my calls?
- You have him?
- Yeah, he just arrived back at his hotel.
But Whistler's girl tracked him down.
And she's talking to Lincoln
and the Mexican.
After what she saw today,
she could be complicating things.
- You have a directive?
- I warned her.
- Take them all out.
- What will Whistler say?
I said take them all out.
I don't care about your
boyfriend's apartment. I just don't care.
No, I went there
and a woman showed up.
She threatened me.
She knows James.
- Susan.
- What, you know her?
She's the one who has L.J.
She took something I found.
A passport.
It had James' picture and birthday.
But his name said Gary Miller.
- I don't know what's going on.
- I'll tell you.
Your boyfriend's a liar.
I told you that from the start.
James told me to stay away from you
today. That it was dangerous.
Let's go.
I need to speak to Michael Scofield.
I'm his brother.
How you get this number?
He called me two days back.
I didn't answer.
But listen,
I need to speak to him now.
Where we going?
Let's go.
You never guess who that was.
Michael Scofield's brother.
Who calls me and who I call
is my business.
- Where's your friends?
- I don't know.
- I don't know, please don't shoot.
Please.
Drop it.
Why you coming after us?
Different day, same problem, huh?
You know how this turned out...
...when L.J. was in this position
and today is no different.
So be a good boy
and put down the gun.
Come on, Linc.
I know you learned your lesson.
You're right. I have.
For the record,
this is an international hearing...
...requested by
the United States government...
...for the purpose of hearing testimony
from one Mr. Alexander Mahone.
- You gotta be kidding me.
- So, Mr. Mahone...
...when were you first contacted
by anyone...
...from the group
referred to as the Company?
Now, they told me that if I didn't kill
every one of the Fox River Eight...
...they would come after me.
They had all worked
with Scofield on the escape...
...so the Company wasn't sure
what they knew--
Mr. Mahone, I'm gonna ask
you to please keep your answer...
...related to the question.
Related? It's all connected--
It's just-- It's-- It's a web.
And it's a web that I got caught in,
and Lincoln Burrows got caught in...
...and Michael Scofield got caught in.
- If I may, I think what Agent Mahone--
- We're all just like flies.
- Is trying to say--
- Thank you...
...but we're here
to hear from Mr. Mahone.
Now, we're gonna try this again.
When were you first contacted
by the Company?
I cannot say.
You know,
they could be in contact with you...
...or you could be in contact with
them, and you'd never know, it's--
They could be in contact with us
right now.
I mean, it's-- It sounds crazy, right?
It's cra--
And-- And it would be, except
for the simple fact that it's true.
The government
that I had dedicated my life to...
...manipulated and extorted me
and blackmailed me...
...so that I would kill for them.
And I did the things
that they made me do...
...so I could protect my family.
And so...
I would like to go home.
So can I do that, please?
Hey.
Where have you been?
I came looking for scrap metal
for the support brace for the tunnel.
Really?
Looks like a tight squeeze up there.
You sure there's enough air
or does the claustrophobia come and go?
What's it like going through life
always distrustful?
You tell me, James.
Hate to break up the brouhaha,
gentlemen...
...but Lechero would like to see you.
Says it has something to do
with your big brother.
Give us moment, will you, Teodoro?
If your brother should ever call
my cell phone again...
...you tell him
you're the one that's gonna pay.
- Yeah?
- You got the message?
You were right.
They tried to take us out.
I know. Whistler got
a visitor from the Company.
He's been acting strange ever since.
I'm telling you, something's up.
More than acting strange. He told Sofia
not to be near me, it was dangerous.
The Company's coming after us.
They don't need us anymore.
Here we go.
They're breaking him out
on their own.
We're 100 yards from the target.
Keep your eyes open.
Let's get in and out fast.
Come on.
Damn.
Come on! Come on, keep it coming!
- Come on.
- Hey.
Come on.
Fly it. Go, go, go.
I have two on the line.
Repeat, two men on the line.
Move it, move it, move it.
Chopper 1, depart with both inmates.
We can't. We're taking too much fire.
Can 't get a clean shot.
I'm getting lower. Take them out.
Stay on them. Stay on them.
Give us some covering fire.
Fire, go, fire, fire, fire.
Man down. Man down.
Let go, you son of a bitch.
We're losing him.
We lost Whistler. Abort, abort.
Mission failed.
Return to Base 1 immediately.
Alex, I'm so sorry.
I'm gonna have to take you back
to Sona.
You, get up.
Mr. Scofield.
There have been two escape attempts
in the past two days.
Somehow, I don't think
it's a coincidence...
...that you arrived
shortly before they happened.
I had nothing to do with that.
You've caused too many problems
here in Sona.
So maybe you shouldn't be here
in Sona.
Say goodbye to Sona, Mr. Scofield.