Merry Christmas.
And a happy go to hell.
What's he doing here?
Is he with you?
Detective Tritter and I...
We worked out a deal.
Already got a lawyer.
Get out of my office.
I told him I didn't write
those prescriptions.
I spoke with the DA.
He agreed to two months in a rehab
facility in exchange for a guilty plea.
Get out of my office.
No jail time.
Right. So I should get
locked up in some place I don't belong
in order to avoid getting locked up
in some other place I don't belong.
I got you on forgery,
fraud, enough drugs to...
No sanctions
to the medical board.
And you get your car back
and your bank accounts
and your precious tumor-ridden patients.
I did this to help you.
Next Christmas,
buy me a sweater.
You punched out an employee!
You nearly cut a little girl in half
because you were too strung out...
I was in pain!
You need to believe
that I've got a problem
so that your betrayal
has the illusion of nobility.
- But you just selfishly...
- Knock it off.
Look, I don't care why
Dr. Wilson is doing this.
And right now,
it makes no difference to you, either,
'cause you need to deal with
the reality of your current situation.
You want to stand on principle,
you end up in a cell.
And you end up
never practicing medicine again.
So you got two choices,
your principles or your life.
Get out of my office.
The DA put a clock on the deal.
You got three days to decide.
House! Just give me a minute.
You're afraid of the pain.
You're not?
You can still have
pain meds in rehab.
- Tramadol, gabapentin.
- Those don't work.
They will once you're
weaned off the Vicodin.
Look, there's Jesus.
Better go tell the Romans.
Fine, run to Cuddy.
You don't think
she's going to support me on this?
Well, the stitches are healing nicely,
there's no sign of infection.
Whoa.
Sorry.
Just need her
for a tiny moment.
Small favor.
Pills.
Who's the wit?
Doctor. Don't worry,
I'll be firing him soon.
Wait in my office.
Incision looks just big enough
for a chest tube.
Collapsed lung?
Someone mistake you for a piñata?
Delightful. Usually we just get
the elf jokes this time of year.
No on trauma.
Negative PPD.
What flavor dwarfs
are you guys?
My daughter and I both have
cartilage-hair hypoplasia.
Think you can make
a pun out of that?
Yes. But I don't
want to be insensitive.
She's got a bit
of a short fuse, doesn't she?
It's a bleb. Wait in my office.
Bleb's not a diagnosis, it's an evasion.
We'll schedule
an MRI to make sure,
but a certain number of these cases
are idiopathic.
Let me translate that
into Tolkien for you guys.
It means Dr. Cuddy's
got no idea
why your daughter's lung
suddenly popped like a balloon.
You think you do?
Gimme her chart. And my pills.
Santa needs us.
Did you get that looked at?
I'm fine.
Great. I just admitted
a cartilage-hair hypoplasia dwarf.
- Fifteen years old...
- What are you going to do?
I thought I'd get your theories, mock
them, then embrace my own. The usual.
Wilson told us he ratted.
Your choice of verb, I take it?
It's appropriate. He betrayed you.
And you should take the deal.
Unexplained lung collapse and anemia.
Cuddy thinks it's idiopathic.
"Cuddy" and "idiop" being
the relevant parts of that sentence.
Well, I'd say TB,
but Cuddy's already ruled it out.
Then you'd be just as big
an idiop as her.
Don't you people know
your dwarfs?
There are over 200 varieties
of dwarfism,
each with different
medical complications.
You can't expect us to be intimately
familiar with all of them?
The sick dwarfs
sure expect you to.
Cartilage-hair hypoplasia.
They have compromised immune systems.
Gold star for Cameron.
For extra credit, explain to
the special needs section of the class
why our patient's negative
TB test is irrelevant.
A PPD involves planting a fragment of TB
under the skin
to see if the immune system
recognizes it.
Because of
a compromised immune system,
our patient could have TB
but not recognize it.
The little people love you.
Let's go see a dwarf
about a gallium scan.
Gallium
is a radioactive isotope.
It travels through your veins,
allowing us to see any bright spots
that might indicate infection.
I'm 4'1".
That's 1.5 canes in metric.
You don't look
a day over four feet.
I saw in the file that her dad
was normal-sized.
It's average-sized.
Compared to you,
I'm sure it was huge.
So did he have a fetish,
or did he just fall in love
with your long-legged soul?
He grew up in the circus.
Said I reminded him of home.
Seems like you're the one
with the fetish.
I'm certainly curious
about the logistics.
Did you stand on a table?
House!
Pretty much,
he'd lay flat and spin me.
Mom.
So, Abigail, you want to
hop up on the table for me?
That's going to be tough.
Oh, I'm sorry.
Let me give you a boost.
Stop treating her
like she's five.
Just bring over a stool
and let her climb up herself.
Mom, it's okay.
I was just trying
to be helpful.
She also hates Jews.
I've dealt with worse.
Being different,
you get used to people's idiocy.
Still beats the hell out of
actually being an idiot.
What?
Care to go for a spin?
What the hell
were you thinking?
You didn't think ratting out
this hospital's best doctor
merited checking
with your boss first?
I didn't rat him out.
I got him a deal.
Which he'll never take.
- He will if we...
- How long have you known House?
Did you think
he'd suddenly become reasonable?
I made the deal. It's done.
You can either keep yelling at me,
or you can help me avoid
a complete disaster.
It already is going to be
a complete disaster!
He's not going to take the deal.
He's going to go to jail.
Because he's a child,
he's too stubborn.
When a child misbehaves,
what do you do?
You take away something
he loves.
We can't take away his Vicodin.
Not only will he be in pain,
he'll start to detox.
And we tell him the only way to get
the pills back is to take the deal.
He won't be able to function.
That's the point.
You going to explain that
to his patient?
What choice do we have?
Gallium scan shows
no bright spots of any kind.
Means it's not TB
or any other infection.
There are no bright spots
'cause the whole thing's too bright.
Except for the liver.
The tech over-exposed
the image a bit, but it's nothing.
The liver looks fine.
Could be lung cancer.
Tumor causes structural damage.
The lung caves in on itself.
Also explains the anemia.
Doesn't explain
the liver problem, though.
Her lung collapsed.
There is no liver problem.
Did you guys look at the liver
on this thing?
There's no liver problem.
Seriously, look at the liver.
There's nothing there.
Why not?
Because there's nothing wrong?
Every organ in this scan
is lit up like a hundred-watt bulb.
Except for her liver,
which is hovering around 60 watts.
And not one of them good 60-watters,
but an energy saving...
You're saying her liver's shutting down
because the lighting is off?
You just don't want
a cancer diagnosis,
because then you'd have
to deal with Wilson.
Lung cancer
is a lame diagnosis.
Avoiding Wilson
is an added bonus.
House, we need to talk.
Not taking the deal.
Glad we talked.
Ultrasound her liver.
Sit down.
Stand up.
Your turn.
House, you're off the case.
Your treatment privileges
are suspended
until you accept
Tritter's deal.
Well, I'm obviously
not going to take the deal
just so I can have the fun
of treating a dwarf.
So, I assume
there's more to this threat.
- I'm also cutting off your Vicodin.
- That could work.
I'm taking over as attending.
Get an MRI of her lungs.
This is not lung cancer.
We'll find out as soon as
we MRI her lungs.
You're going to come begging me
to save this girl
long before I come
begging you for pills.
I hope not.
For everyone's sake.
This is wrong.
Cutting House off?
It might not work, but it's not wrong.
Bone windows look clean.
Abigail, we need you
to hold still, okay?
Can I come out?
Just hang in there two more minutes,
and we'll be done.
Okay.
Because it's effective
doesn't make it right.
Cuddy's bending the rules
to get a patient to do the right thing.
- Who would work for a doctor like that?
- And the ends justify the means?
If the ends involve
us keeping our jobs, sure.
Lung parenchyma's clean.
No masses, it's not lung cancer.
Abigail, you okay?
House was right.
Her liver's failing.
Endoscopy confirmed the vomiting
was caused by variceal bleeding.
Blood work also confirms
House's hypothesis.
I get it. House was right,
it's the liver. Let's move on.
What causes liver disease
and a collapsed lung?
Schistosomiasis,
the parasite could have...
There's no eosinophilia.
- Cirrhosis could explain...
- Could be a hepatoma.
She's 15.
It's not liver cancer.
It's not unheard of.
Cirrhosis fits better.
The question is, what caused it?
- Could be hepatitis, Budd-Chiari...
- Or drugs and alcohol.
If anyone has reason to dull the pain,
it's a teenage dwarf.
I'll do a liver biopsy
to confirm.
And I'll search the patient's home
for drugs and alcohol.
Cameron, got a moment?
What exactly
is your problem with me?
Hepatoma is a weak diagnosis.
So this is all about the case?
What else would it be about?
I made this deal to help him.
And helped yourself
at the same time.
This is not about my practice.
This is not about my car.
I gave both of them up to help House
and I would have gone on without them,
if he hadn't almost maimed that little
girl and if he hadn't punched out Chase.
Was it an easy choice?
Of course not. But it's right.
Then why wasn't it easy?
Because he's my friend.
- It's obviously complicated...
- It's complicated?
When you decided to talk to Tritter,
your life got a million times better.
How do you separate that out?
How do you pretend your windfall
isn't relevant to this decision?
It was the right thing to do.
You pretending your motives are pure
is why I have a problem.
Where's Cuddy?
In this drawer. It's a rescue mission.
I've got it under control,
you can leave.
You were right
about the liver failure,
the patient had variceal bleeding,
which suggested cirrhosis, but...
Off the clock.
You predicted this.
You obviously saw something.
Obviously.
Liver biopsy was negative for cirrhosis
but it showed sclerosing cholangitis.
Even weirder, there's no increase
in alkaline phosphatase.
Medical mystery. Sounds like
the kind of thing I'd be good at.
Breaking and entering sounds like
the kind of thing you'd be good at.
I take it that's where
Cuddy's been keeping your pills.
One theory, one drawer.
Really?
I thought you'd be all for
this "torture House" plan.
It works, therefore it's good.
On the other hand, I don't want
to talk you out of this deal
by pointing out your hypocrisy.
So, patient's life at stake,
blah, blah, blah, blah, blah.
Forget about the specific nature of
the liver dysfunction, it's irrelevant.
The dwarf's problem is global,
that's why the gallium scan was bright.
And it's going to spread throughout
her entire body unless you stop it.
If that were true, more than
her lungs and liver would be affected.
It will be.
It'll spread through the biliary tree
and hit her pancreas next.
Stop retracing your steps,
get ahead of it.
Forget the liver and focus
on the pancreas because after that...
Actually, after that
it doesn't really matter what it hits
because, pretty much,
all roads lead to a dead dwarf.
I get why you
don't want to go to rehab.
But only an idiot goes to prison
for being stubborn.
Only an idiot stands between
Ahab and his whale. Move.
Sorry.
Santa's got gifts.
Olive oil wasn't in the kitchen,
it was in the medicine cabinet.
Home remedy for ear infections.
Ear infections are fairly typical
among CHH dwarfs.
Or, it's a symptom.
Certainly wouldn't indicate
a pancreatic problem.
Or House is wrong
and it's a symptom.
Laxatives. I don't think they were used
to maintain her girlish figure.
Again, intestinal problems
are common.
Again, it might be a symptom.
Glucosamine
suggests chronic joint pain.
Who ordered
an alpha-1 antitrypsin deficiency test?
I did.
You think the problem's
in her pancreas?
I think it will be. I think we need
to forget about the liver.
We just forgot about the lungs,
now we need to forget about the liver?
We need to stop retracing
our steps and get ahead of this thing.
House, you've tanned.
You don't think
I could have come up with this?
Did you?
You suspended House because
it'd be dangerous having him in charge,
but getting his opinion?
I'm sure he gave you that opinion
simply because he was worried
about the patient?
Just because House wants his pills,
doesn't mean his theory is wrong.
No, the test results mean that.
Your test was negative.
And the biopsy indicated
severe duct inflammation.
Do an ERCP to check the liver
for bile duct cancer.
Just because it wasn't alpha-1
doesn't mean the pancreas isn't next.
You needed an organ,
he needed a fix.
He'd have made up any story for a pill.
You didn't give him anything, did you?
No.
There's no bruise or nothing,
but it really hurts.
Unfortunately, that pain
and lack of bruising
is typical of a zygomatic break.
Sounds bad.
Bones are aligned properly.
Which ER did you go to
after the car accident?
Princeton Plainsboro.
Here's my discharge slip.
Okay.
I'm going to get you some
acetaminophen with codeine.
I tried that,
it makes me nauseous.
There's a drug
called gabapentin
which is good
for certain kinds of pain.
Great!
'Cause I haven't slept in days.
Gabapentin's not really
going to help with the sleep.
Oh.
Is there something else
you can give me?
Vicodin's your best bet
with sleep issues.
Well, thanks so much.
Unfortunately, our policy forbids
prescribing opiates to new patients.
Well, how could a clinic have a rule
against relieving pain?
Just with opiates. We find that it helps
weed out drug-seekers.
- You think I'm a drug-seeker?
- I'm not saying that.
- Well, then give me the Vicodin.
- I can't.
Because you think
I'm a drug-seeker.
I just said I didn't.
No, you said that the policy
was to stop drug-seeking.
Then you said I'm not a drug-seeker.
Policy doesn't apply.
I'm sorry, that's the policy.
Gabapentin works on
nerve damage.
You're prescribing it
for a broken face.
Might as well hand out Band-Aids
for a severed carotid.
You're a doctor.
Not by this clinic's definition,
since I'm neither a moron,
nor a mindless drone!
- Security.
- Forget it.
I'll throw myself out.
That tube is going
all the way down to my liver?
Don't worry, you'll be sedated.
Sometimes doctors
have to do things
that make people uncomfortable
to help them.
But we always want to respect
the patient's wishes
and not shove things down
their throats.
Foreman.
You haven't given
her the sedative.
No.
Abigail.
Abigail. She's unconscious.
Check her airway.
Airway's clear.
Her breath smells fruity.
Diabetic ketoacidosis.
Hang an insulin drip
at.1 mgs per kg per hour!
Her pancreas is failing.
You ready to call House yet?
You were right.
The patient's pancreas is failing.
Told you you'd come
begging me for help.
Her insulin production
is almost non-existent.
Give me my pills
or lose an arm.
- The girl is dying!
- So give me my pills.
Take the deal and I will.
You'd rather kill this girl
than give me my pills?
I would rather lose
one patient now
than the dozens we will lose
while you're in prison.
Well, have fun explaining that
to her itsy-bitsy grieving mother.
What if we sacrifice this girl
and House still goes to jail?
I'd feel bad.
Can we get on with this?
House correctly predicted
the spread,
means we've got
a global systemic illness
affecting lungs, liver and pancreas.
So far. Ideas?
Langerhans cell histiocytosis
attacks multiple organ systems.
Histiocytosis usually
starts in the brain,
then moves to the internal organs.
Abigail's brain is fine.
Cystic fibrosis.
Exocrine function's normal.
Hodgkin's lymphoma.
It's a systemic cancer,
which her dwarfism predisposes her to.
- You have any ideas that aren't cancer?
- Cancer fits.
Autoimmune fits better.
We should treat her
with prednisone for lupus.
That'll spike her blood sugar
and put her back in a coma.
It's much safer just to run
a double-stranded DNA test.
Not if she dies before
we get the results.
One of you is probably right.
Why don't we hold the sniping
until we find out which?
Wilson, do an LP for lymphoma,
you guys run an antibody test for lupus.
Because of your daughter's dwarfism,
we've had to pick a higher entry point
for the lumbar puncture,
which increases the risk.
So, why not do
the lupus test first?
In the interest of time, we think
it's best to proceed on both fronts.
You have no idea
what's wrong with my daughter.
- We have several theories.
- What does Dr. House think?
He's... He had to go home sick.
My daughter may be dying
- and he's gone home with the sniffles?
- Well, he's not...
He was the only one who seemed to have
any idea what was wrong with her.
He better be really damn sick.
He is.
Unless you've got Vicodin,
go away.
House, it's me, I...
Oh, God.
- I don't have...
- No pills?
No eggnog.
What happened to your arm?
Cut myself.
Wilson was wrong
about lymphoma.
Kid's not losing any weight,
no night sweats.
- Cuddy sent you?
- No.
She doesn't trust me
not to give you pills.
Is she right?
House, these cuts
are straight, in a row.
You did this on purpose.
Cutting releases endorphins,
endorphins relieve pain.
You going to get me some pills?
No.
Well, then you can leave.
No constitutional
symptoms means...
As soon as the kid gets cured,
Cuddy's got no pressure to fold.
You really think
she's going to fold?
Autoimmune fits better
than cancer.
But lupus loves kidneys.
Usually attacks them first.
Kidneys are fine, right?
Yeah.
House,
take the deal.
You can survive
without Vicodin.
After you were shot,
you stayed clean for months.
Yeah.
I wonder if it had something
to do with the absence of pain.
Leave that. I want to be able to pour
alcohol on it so I can distract myself.
Then you can rip off
the bandage.
Kid been sick lately?
There's a history
of ear infections.
See, Abigail's immune system
is like a shy guy in a bar.
The ear infections, they come in
and they try to coax him to...
To hell with the metaphor.
You get the point, right?
Nerd gets drunk,
trashes the bar.
One of the autoimmunes
triggered by a minor infection?
Factor in her age,
elevated sed rate, anemia...
It's Still's disease.
We start her on prednisone,
methotrexate, cyclosporin.
House.
Stop this.
Please.
- What'd he say?
- Still's disease.
It's chronic, but manageable...
A diagnosis
that's virtually unconfirmable
and with a treatment
that's more dangerous
than what we were considering for lupus.
How bad is he?
Are you asking because you care
or because you're wondering
whether to trust his opinion?
Both.
He's detoxing. In agony.
He's started cutting himself.
But he's still House.
I'll order the treatment.
Your plan isn't working.
Two days down, one to go.
Figured I'd show you
how much it isn't working.
Yeah. Clearly, the drugs
have no hold on you.
We both know that my pride
far surpasses my instinct
for self-preservation.
You want to redeem yourself?
Give up now.
And you'll go to jail.
I've done nothing wrong.
Which makes this your last chance
to do me a kindness
before ruining my life forever.
Nausea's bad this time.
You can write me a scrip
for metoclopramide so I can stop puking.
They'd give me that in rehab.
Then you should go to rehab.
I have a patient.
I'm so sorry, I know it's little
solace, but he went without pain...
House?
Well, look on the bright side.
At least you don't have to go
by Mrs. Zebalusky anymore.
That's got to be a relief.
- You know this man?
- I'm sorry, he's sick...
You hear my diagnosis on the dwarf?
Still's disease.
Did you even consider
those ear infections,
or you just wrote it off
as a dwarf thing?
Are you sure he's dead?
Because Dr. Wilson
sometimes misses things.
Trying to embarrass me
in front of a grieving widow
- crosses lines that even...
- Right. I'm pathetic.
I'm strung out, I haven't slept,
puking every hour,
and I still out-diagnosed you.
But I'm supposed to let you
decide what's best...
Please.
Please leave.
Sorry.
I'm done.
House!
You didn't come in here
just to embarrass me,
you can do that any time.
Stealing Oxy from a dead man.
Yeah. You don't have a problem.
How's the girl?
Much better.
House was right.
It happens.
I thought we could handle this.
Still's disease
never crossed my mind.
Don't beat yourself up,
I didn't get it, either.
I feel like a mob informant.
You want to go inside?
Got a cafeteria in there, right?
I can't testify.
Drug addicts hurt the people
around them with their habit.
House has hurt plenty of people.
You included.
He saves lives.
People that no one else can save.
And, no matter how much
of an ass he is,
statistically, House
is a positive force in the universe.
Pills let him do that.
Vicodin does not make House
a genius.
Whatever he does on the pills,
he can do off.
He is just not willing to try.
I won't testify against him.
Then we'll subpoena you.
Your previous statement
will be read into evidence
and you'll be charged with
interfering with an investigation.
And you will go to jail.
Again, statistically,
better me than him.
Statistically, the two of you
will be in jail.
Dr. Cameron?
Come quick,
there's something wrong with Abby.
It can't be too severe,
her cardiac alarm didn't go off.
It's not her heart.
She's bleeding.
Picking up a scrip
under Zebalusky.
This is Dr. Wilson's patient.
Yeah. Wilson's busy right now.
What with Mr. Zebalusky dying in agony
on account of his metastatic lung cancer
and not having the pills
to relieve that agony
because of some
moron pharmacist.
Sign the book.
The bleeding wasn't a ruptured eardrum,
ear infection or bleeding disorder.
Her heart rate's climbing,
blood pressure's dropping,
she's on the verge
of a multi-system failure.
Head CT was clean, means it's not
a neurological problem.
Basically we have nothing.
The cancer's
still on the table.
Spinal fluid
was negative for lymphoma.
- What other...
- Leukemia.
We need to do
a bone marrow biopsy.
None of the blood tests
suggest leukemia.
Cancer doesn't explain
the collapsed lung.
Unless a small clot
led to a pulmonary infarct.
It's a long shot.
Autoimmune is way more likely.
Autoimmune diseases respond to steroids,
which we've given her.
And she got better for a while,
we stopped the treatment too soon.
Because she crashed.
All we're doing is bouncing back
and forth between cancer and autoimmune.
We're going in circles.
Give me half an hour.
Can I have a French fry?
Get your own.
You took the last ones.
What's wrong with you?
I've got spinal
muscular atrophy.
I guess it's not contagious.
Nice bear.
It's a dog.
House, it's not Still's.
Steroids helped
until the patient started bleeding
from the ears and mouth.
It's a bear.
His name is Bill. He's a dog.
You win, you can have Vicodin.
Words have set meanings
for a reason.
If you see an animal like Bill
and you try to play fetch,
Bill's going to eat you.
Because Bill's a bear.
Are you on something?
You got your hands
on pain meds.
Bill has fur,
four legs, and a collar.
He's a dog.
It's between cancer
and autoimmune.
See, that's what we call
a faulty syllogism.
Just because you call Bill
a dog, doesn't mean that he is
a dog.
We got to x-ray
our patient's leg.
Her leg looks fine.
Weird, huh?
Why aren't you detoxing?
Willpower.
What... What...
Normal's not normal
if you're not normal.
Did you just take a pill?
No.
So how does a dwarf have
completely normal growth plates?
It's impossible.
We must be missing something.
How many pills have you taken?
Not nearly as many
as I'm going to take.
I'd forgotten how delicious
they were.
I didn't give them to him.
Can we forget my vices,
get back to my virtues?
We were missing the fact that
just because we called her
a dwarf doesn't mean she is a dwarf.
Everyone assumed she was,
because of her mother.
There's no test
for CHH dwarfism,
so she lost an identity,
but we gained a symptom.
If she doesn't have
skeletal dwarfism,
then her short stature must be
caused by a growth hormone deficiency.
And something's wrong
with her pituitary gland
and based on her size,
it's been wrong for a while.
So what connects
a long-term pituitary issue
with problems in the lungs,
liver and pancreas?
You guys and your bickering.
Cancer versus autoimmune.
Obviously, you think
it's something else.
Nope. I think it's both.
Langerhans cell histiocytosis.
Also known as,
"You got your cancer
in my autoimmune" disease.
The immune component responded
to the Still's treatment,
led to the short-term improvement.
The cancer portion didn't.
We dismissed this earlier, because
there were no neurological symptoms.
Yeah. It's not your fault.
The only neurological symptom
was her height.
Who could have noticed?
This is your pituitary gland.
This is the granuloma
that's been crushing it.
No pituitary equals no growth hormone,
equals about that much.
She's not a dwarf?
Just hormonally challenged.
What about my mom?
Your mom's the real deal.
But you're just a tiny little poseur.
Your recent ear infections
caused your body to release
a cascade of the same cells
that made the granuloma.
They attacked your lungs,
moved on to your liver,
then hitched a ride over
to your pancreas.
We can nuke them
with a mild course of chemo
and then remove the granuloma.
And then what?
What will happen to her then?
Well, let me see
if I can make this clear.
This pill represents
a pill.
And my mouth represents
your daughter's mouth.
We deposit the pill
in the mouth.
You may never be tall enough
to play in the WNBA,
but you should be able to
post up your mom, no problem.
What if I don't take the pills?
What if you remove the thing in my head
and give me the chemo,
but not the pills?
Would I still get better?
Your body needs growth hormone
for lots of things.
Like
to grow.
I like who I am now.
Nobody your age
likes who they are now.
I do.
You like needing help when
you want something off a high shelf?
Not being able to press an
elevator button above the eighth floor?
Having to smell ass
every time you stand in line?
You don't need growth hormone.
It's just your ticket
out of the freak show.
Can't you deliver a diagnosis
without making her feel
that her life isn't worth living?
I'm trying to help her.
You're trying
to make her taller.
Not too tall.
Just tall enough
to wipe her own butt.
Are you high?
Higher than you.
If my daughter doesn't want
to choose the easy path,
I won't force her to.
Then you're a lousy mom.
You want your daughter
to be a freak.
We're not freaks.
You want her to overcome
adversity.
- Yes.
- Then why stop at height?
Poke a stick in her eye.
Imagine how interesting she'll be then.
Being little
is not the same as...
You and I have found out
that being normal sucks.
Because we're freaks.
The advantage of being a freak
is it makes you stronger.
Now, how strong
do you really want her to have to be?
You told her
what you had to tell her.
Now you tell her you lied.
Even if you didn't.
This is who
you were supposed to be.
You hate normal.
It's not that simple.
If I grow,
I'll fade into the background.
I'll be boring.
We'll get you a funny hat.
You could never be boring.
You want me
to be like everybody else?
I want you to have
what I can't.
Abigail agreed...
Abigail agreed
to take growth hormone.
Who's Abigail?
Your non-dwarf dwarf patient.
Good.
Then the growth hormone
makes sense.
Christmas Eve.
Yeah, I know.
Deal expires tomorrow.
You have plans for tonight?
You worried I'm going to be
popping more pills?
Thought you might prefer
people over pills.
Hey, Mom.
I guess you guys are already up
at Aunt Sarah's.
I'm sure Dad's in the eggnog
and you're probably suffering
through another dried-out turkey.
I just wanted to say,
"Merry Christmas."
House?
Are you okay?
I called three times.
I'm ready to take the deal.
Well, that's off the table.
- The clock doesn't expire until...
- Got new evidence.
We don't need Wilson anymore.
Thing about addicts is,
no matter how smart they are,
they are dumb
when it comes to drugs.
So, I've been keeping an eye
on the pharmacy log.
Seems some patient of Wilson's
named Zebalusky,
managed to pick up his Oxy prescription
after he died.
Jesus walks, huh?
Merry Christmas.