Grace.
Grace, are you okay, honey?
Has something happened?
Where's Ian?
Grace, are you coming out?
What do I do?
Just leave her a bit. Should we call Ian?
I'll call Bibi.
I'll put the kettle on.
You're very ripe.
Have a wash after your toast.
Hey!
Will you put mine in the oven?
I'm gonna just go for a run.
- What?
- Don't end up in Navan.
Jesus, you do one run to Navan.
Yeah, well, it's hard to
forget an accidental 34 miles, Bibi.
I had a lot on my mind that day.
Well, we've to be at the clinic for 12:00.
I've booked the day off for it.
Don't run away.
- What?
- Could you get over here?
Something's wrong with Grace.
Ian's gone.
Grace?
Grace!
- Hey.
- She won't come out.
She can stay in there then.
Bla.
Hey, listen,
can you use your phones in school?
We're allowed to check them at lunch.
Okay, well, look, I'll just--
I'll text you as soon as Ian's back, okay?
Why were the Guards here yesterday?
I didn't know they were, honey.
She was hysterical last night,
like, it was insane.
- She's mental.
- Oh, come on, Bla. Don't--
What? She is.
Enjoy school.
What's going on? I'm missing breakfast.
- Nora made shakshuka.
- Yum.
Jesus. I didn't even have time
to brush my teeth.
If you had time to put mascara on,
you had time to brush your teeth.
Well, I disagree with that.
Listen, come here.
The Guards were here last night.
- The Guards? Why?
- Yeah.
Hi, hon, you okay?
Do you want a cup of tea or--
- Yeah.
- Here. Here. It's hot.
Did Bla take her iPad? It was charging.
Yeah, she has it.
Listen, are you-- What's happened, hon?
Where's Ian?
We had an argument is all.
- He left.
- Why?
What were the police doing here?
Don't bark at her.
Give her a chance to answer.
They found a dead body in a suitcase.
They what the fucking what?
John Paul's father. George.
They said he was murdered.
- Did you not hear what I said?
- Yeah, no, we did. It's--
I'm just computing.
- Shit. I can't believe that.
- Oh, my God.
- Oh, yeah, that's insane.
Well, look-- Well, whatever happens,
whatever that leads to,
I mean, it's not gonna--
it's not your problem, is it?
It is my problem.
The detective asked me about John Paul's
life insurance claim as they were leaving.
As they were leaving, such a cop move.
Well, why did he ask you that?
Because he was the one who
exhumed John Paul's body.
Shit. Fuck.
Wait. What?
Wait, is that why you were
fighting with Ian?
I think...
Roger is going to talk to the police.
Roger?
Shellfish Roger?
Roger's gonna talk to
the police about what?
You have two new messages.
Fergal, it's Nadine.
Don't forget Sean is picking up
Jessie from school today.
And can you sign the consent forms?
We're supposed to be
on a plane to Sydney in a few weeks
and you're cutting it bloody fine.
Could you just get it done?
- Oh, shit.
- Ew, Dad, lock the door!
It's broke!
I had a flannel over me--
No, Dad!
- Next message.
- Sorry.
I forgot to say.
Can you just do something for someone else
for once in your fucking life?
I don't think they're there.
They teach you those
observational skills at Templemore?
Mrs. Claffin and Sons
have clearly packed up.
Wonder where that
doofus of a brother went to.
Do you want me to look into it?
No, don't worry about it. I'll do that.
Geez. Of course
I want you to look into it.
Who picks your wardrobe?
Rupert the Bear?
No, my mum-- It--
Yeah, I'll just-- I'll rethink it, sir.
Yeah, do. Rethink the whole thing.
You've been parachuted in here, yeah?
The least you can do is dress for the job.
Yep. Absolutely, sir, on it.
I was looking into the
John Paul Williams inquest file again.
There's no way that was suicide.
Agreed.
Unless he created some sort of, like,
self-collapsing, like, pulley system.
But I mean, who would
bother killing themselves like that?
I thought that we could go and see--
No, we are not digging up
the same body twice, okay?
You can forget about that.
- No, I meant--
- Just get in.
Oh, Christ.
Sorry, sir.
I can't believe Roger helped her.
That's a big secret to keep.
I mean, that's a big thing
to keep from us, don't you think?
Why'd he do it? Why take the risk?
He'd do anything for her.
Maybe she should just give him a leg-over.
- That'll keep him quiet.
- You are such a dick.
It is a good idea though.
I don't know if en masse
is the right approach.
He might think we're
trying to intimidate him.
We are trying to intimidate him.
I'm starving. Do you have any food?
Can we just go in, please?
I can't do this all day.
Joe keeps asking where I am.
What's-her-trots might be in there.
Still can't believe
the prick chopped up his own da.
Yeah, I thought he was
the kinda guy who just froze dads.
That is hardcore though.
These are so stale they're soft.
Well, don't eat them if they're soft,
you mank.
Geez, you'd swear
you were the one pregnant.
Nora's not pregnant yet.
She's on the hormone tablets.
Her uterus will be
getting nice and fluffy now.
- Disgusting.
- Cute.
Oh, shit, there he is.
Roger!
What are you doing? Come back.
Don't follow him. That's weird.
- Do you think he's going to the cops?
- Go after him in the car.
You can't tail someone on a bike, can you?
Oh, God.
Jesus Christ,
what are you sneaking up on me for?
I'm not. This is my local.
Whatever Roger's having, four lemonades
and a packet of cheese and onion.
Sure.
Shall I find us a table?
We already have one.
You can't go to the Guards, Roger.
Why youse talking to me?
Where's Grace?
She's at home.
She's in a state.
Did she know about the...
body in the pond?
Of course not.
Grace is the best person
any of us will ever know.
And John Paul was a monster.
He was a turd of a man.
What happened to him--
What Grace had to do--
The world's better off without him.
Even the Pope would say that.
But if Grace goes to jail, if you go
to jail who would that help?
Don't throw your life away for him.
But I've done a terrible thing.
Roger, we all did.
Roger, we are all involved in this.
We all tried to kill that fucker.
No. We mean--
We're involved because we knew.
You know, we covered it up.
Oh, yeah.
- Yeah.
- We're accessories, Roger.
After the fact.
Whatever you're feeling,
you know, guilt, anger, regret.
You have to be strong now, Roger,
for Grace and Blanaid.
We weren't able to help last time.
We wanna help now, you and Grace.
We can all be quiet together.
Shit!
Fuck! I'm supposed to be at the clinic.
Nora's gonna skin me.
Please don't talk to anyone, Roger.
I thought I'd find you here.
- Do you mind if I join you?
- Yeah, of course.
Father Furey will be in a little later
if you'd like to clear your thoughts.
Really, I have to go.
I know why you pulled away, Grace.
I know what you did.
What I've...
Roger told me.
He told me everything.
I know you killed
your first husband, Grace.
What did he say to you?
I'm not here to chastise.
I'm here to understand.
Help to bring you some peace
or some penance maybe.
I'm sorry, I just--
I will call you.
Is that okay? And we can talk, I promise.
I know I let things slide before
and I'm sorry.
But I will--
I will call you.
I know you will.
No.
Now are we all good to go?
Work away.
This one here's seen
it all coming up in the flats.
Isn't that right, Houli-hoop?
Tough as Chinese.
Sorry?
No, the language Chinese.
It's a saying.
To learn the Chinese language, it's tough.
It's fine, sir.
Given the length of time dead,
he's in good shape.
Hate to see your idea of bad shape.
You dug up his son, John Paul Williams,
two years ago.
Your point is?
There were traces of his DNA on
a hacksaw they located in the house
matches the blade
used on our friend George here.
Serrated edge matches the cut marks.
So he chopped up his own da?
Looks like it.
So, you gonna dig him up and arrest him?
Ha-ha-fucking-ha-ha.
Is that the end of the road then, sir?
For George, maybe.
Oh, no. Sorry.
Oh, God. God.
It's all right. No, you go.
I want you to check any untoward action
in Grace Reilly's account for me.
And the older Williams's account
as well, yeah?
- God's sake. Fuck's sake.
- Sorry, sir.
Fuck.
So do you think it could be like a
family silver kind of a thing?
What? Just call my man in the bank, yeah?
Tell them Adolf sent you.
Adolf?
Yeah, and that's not racist either,
by the way, it's a nickname.
It's my golf nickname.
Two shots in a bunker?
It's just-- You don't
have to write it down, just drive.
Okay.
I couldn't sleep last night. Can you talk?
I'm just heading back into work.
Is no one else worried?
Hey. About what? Roger?
I think we got through to him.
No, not about Roger, about Grace.
About her not telling us she involved an
innocent man in the disposing of a body.
- Hey, look.
- Gorgeous.
What do you mean? Bibi?
- Here, take the ball.
- Bibi, what do you mean?
I'm starting to have thoughts I
don't wanna have about my own sister.
- Have you spoken to her?
- Hey.
Not this morning, no.
Eva called Blanaid
on the way to school earlier.
Still no Ian.
What are you saying?
Something's happened to him? An accident?
I don't know what to think.
Can we meet at Grace's after work?
Fine, but you're really stressing me out.
Coffee.
How you feeling, love?
Okay.
Okay, just another ten minutes.
We'll get you sorted, okay? Hang in there.
- Hi.
Sorry, sister.
Yeah.
And this one comes in cupcake?
Well, I might wanna mix it up
for my party.
Half-and-half.
It was in your calendar.
Cakes.
- Could you give us a minute?
- For what?
- Is this for your retirement party?
- What do you want?
Adolf called. Not Adolf, you're Adolf.
Your man at the bank rang.
John Paul was siphoning off his
dead dad's pension for nearly ten years.
Yeah. Predictable, if nothing else. And?
The Williams' property,
Grace Reilly inherited
all of that after her husband died.
No wonder she walked away
from the insurance claim.
Right. Let's go.
Thank you for the spork.
- What are you doing?
- Sorry, sir.
- I'm holding the door.
- Sorry.
I should've prepped this bed weeks ago.
Don't know what I was thinking.
Have you heard any more from Roger, Grace?
No, and I don't wanna talk about that.
Anything from Ian?
Wait, you haven't heard
from Ian in two days?
Sorry I'm late.
There was an outbreak of cholera.
Okay. Anyone want tea? I'm gasping.
Oh, yeah. Yes, please.
Look, I don't want Blanaid hearing us
talking about any of this. Okay?
Okay.
Can someone grab me
some toilet paper, please?
Toilet paper, please!
Don't worry about making tea for me.
I need to get away from her
for my own sanity.
What are you doing?
- What?
- Is this blood?
It was in the little cupboard thingy,
in the toilet.
Whose phone is that?
I found it in the bathroom.
I wasn't snooping.
I was just looking
for something to wipe my fanny.
Is that Ian's?
Why hasn't he his phone with him, Grace?
- Is Ian taking me to the match?
- He's not back yet, love.
- Why?
- I don't know, Blanaid.
- Did you frighten him off?
- Don't talk to me like that.
If you hadn't been fighting with my dad,
maybe he wouldn't have
gone off angry and got killed.
I wasn't really fighting with your dad.
I just said that 'cause I was upset,
and I was looking for
reasons for what happened.
Maybe the reason is just you.
Blanaid!
Of course this is
the age they become monsters.
Why are you looking at me?
Blanaid okay, love?
What? Yeah.
Do you want me to go with you, Grace?
To take the heat off?
Ruben's got football.
What?
It's fine, they'll be here about George.
Just let them in.
Just get over.
- Hello again.
- Mrs. Reilly,
we'd like to ask you
a few follow-up questions.
- Close it.
- Shouldn't take long.
Come on through.
- Thanking you.
- What?
Sorry to intrude.
No problem.
Oh, God.
So, what can we do for ya?
Well, as you know, the body of
George Williams has been identified
and this ring was found on his person.
Do you recognize it?
John Paul had a signet ring
with a very similar crest.
It's a family coat of arms.
Yeah. Classy.
Are you any closer
to finding out what happened?
Someone chopped up a body
and put it in a suitcase.
Sorry, yeah, no, I mean, are you
any closer to finding out who did it?
Someone who panicked.
Idiotic to conceal a body
so close to the house.
So someone was clearly planning
on returning at some point to retrieve it,
but then didn't or couldn't.
- Because they were dead.
- Just--
So we'd like to ask you
a few more questions
about your husband's accident.
You said he committed suicide.
We've looked at the inquest files and
I have to say that seems very unlikely.
What makes you think he killed himself?
Whose business is that?
We spoke to your insurers,
Claffin and Sons.
Yeah, unfortunately, they were--
And they've confirmed
that you've dropped the claim
and, obviously,
that's exactly what they wanted,
- which is very interesting.
- Please.
Hey, love.
The Guards were
just asking some questions.
- Are you off to play a match?
- Uh-huh.
- Yeah? Who you playing?
- Balcarrick.
Those Balcarrick girls,
they are built like brick shithouses.
Use plenty of elbow, yeah?
I'm gonna wait in the car.
I may have to follow up
with this if that's okay.
Is Mr. Reilly back later?
No, he's away at a golf tournament.
He's gone golfing without his clubs?
No, he's a spectator.
Oh, well, good for him.
- Good evening to you all.
- Good evening.
We'll see ourselves out.
Friendly bunch.
Here-- Are you-- The short one, sir?
Watch your mouth.
Look.
There's a tortoise. There's two of them.
Yeah, I don't care.
For Christ's sake, Grace.
Why did you say JP killed himself?
Well, they asked about the claim.
I panicked. I just panicked.
But why'd you lie to the cops?
I mean, who lies to the cops?
Well, I mean, we do.
We lie to the cops.
I need to go. Come on.
We'll stay.
Yeah, in case Ian comes home.
It's fine, right? Donal's got the kids.
Okay, well, there's some bolognese
in the freezer
if you want to do
some spaghetti with that.
What?
Well, I mean,
you didn't even ask if I had plans or...
Do you?
No, don't be a bitch.
I'll go after her. Keep an eye on her.
She's gonna land us all in jail.
Let's go!
- How's it going? How are you?
- How are you, Bibi?
Hey. Sorry.
Why would he leave without his phone?
What the hell is going on?
I mean, do we even know it's Ian's phone?
Well, it's definitely not Grace's.
Blanaid wouldn't be caught dead
with a phone like that.
Did you see the look on her face?
She looked like she was gonna faint.
- Ian's missing.
- He's not missing.
They had a fight.
They had a fight clearly.
What am I looking at?
It's blood.
Are you sure it's not pasta sauce?
I've seen plenty of pasta sauce
and plenty of blood,
and I can tell the difference.
Men like Ian don't just vanish.
Am I the one who's gonna have to say it?
- Shut up, Urs.
- Bibi's thinking the same.
- I don't like this.
- It's the Guards this time,
and if they're sniffing around,
which they are
because there's a body
in a bloody suitcase,
then we need to make sure
there's nothing they're gonna find.
Look, I know this is mad,
but maybe we just check the house.
Clean up a bit just in case
the police come back, yeah?
Yeah.
Oh, my God.
Mind yourselves now.
Caroline!
Could you ever bank this for me?
Because Tina Cullen's cancer
has moved to her lymphs
and that pig husband of hers
is nowhere to be seen,
so I just thought I'd drop up tomorrow
and see if she fancied a game of poker.
Sure.
Yeah. Blanaid.
I have a match about to start.
Are you all right, pet?
You look a bit pale. Is your mammy here?
She's by the pitch.
Is Ian not waving you on tonight?
Ian's gone.
Come on, girls!
Yes, Blanaid! Go on, Blanaid!
There you are.
Ghoul.
She's all right.
She does a lot for the community,
which is more than I can say for some.
Anyone who has to tell you
what a good person they are all the time
I fundamentally do not trust.
You look cold.
It's bitter out, all right.
Come on, Cailin!
God help us.
- They're tanks those Balcarrick girls.
- Come on, girls!
- Your favorite.
- Yes, Blanaid! Lovely!
I think we ought to have that chat, Grace.
I know you've been absorbed
with other things,
but it's key that we're
on the same page, I think.
I don't wanna
talk right now, Angelica. Sorry.
I mean, I do feel
I've been led astray a wee bit.
How do you mean?
Well, if you're gonna trust me
with this serious a matter,
I need to know everything.
You mustn't protect your sisters
at the expense of yourself and Blanaid.
I'm not. That's not what happened.
But if your sisters are invol--
My sisters are none of your business!
Why are you shouting?
I'm only trying to help you.
You're not helping me.
You are suffocating me.
I can't breathe. It's too much.
Grace, are you okay?
Grace.
What the hell did you say
to upset her like that?
That is hysterical behavior.
And it is going to be
all around the town, you know?
What are you talking about?
And it's not gonna do any of you
any favors at all.
Are you okay?
Something's going on with the family.
Bibi's not herself either.
But I'm sure that was, well, not pleasant.
So, I'm sorry.
You shouldn't worry about me, my goodness.
You have to be thinking about yourself.
I hear you may have
another wee one on the way.
Well, news travels fast,
but not quite yet.
Fingers crossed
it's smooth sailing from here.
Well, I'm sure that that UV--
IV-- Egg donor route
is never straightforward.
I know herself was concerned about...
connecting with a baby that wasn't hers.
You know,
having had such trouble with Ruben.
Well, she was great with Ruben.
Well, not in
the first two years apparently.
Apologies if I misunderstood.
You tell me to just mind my own business,
but I often feel that we do things
for those we love
at the expense of ourselves,
and it usually ends badly.
God bless.
Where the hell is Becka?
Grace is going to be back soon.
She's going through the cupboards
in the bedrooms.
Did you know that cop earlier?
'Cause he knew you.
Speed dating event.
- Are you serious?
- I don't wanna talk about it.
- Yeah, but did you--
- No.
- What you didn't even--
- Yeah.
You didn't even--
All of his stuff is still here.
What are we doing?
Seriously, this is ridiculous.
It's ri-- Shit.
- God, you nearly gave me a heart attack.
- The key was in the lock, sorry.
Something really weird just happened.
Grace lost it with Angelica by the pitch.
What? Why? Did Roger talk?
She's right behind me.
I think we need to ask her
what's going on.
You ask her.
Hey! Did you win at the mud wrestling?
I'm gonna have a shower.
Give me that.
- Is there hot water?
- Should be.
- Look, you cleaned up. Thanks.
- Yeah, nearly.
I'm sorry about before.
- Are you okay?
- Oh, yeah.
Just a bit jumpy is all.
Something smells delicious.
It's the bolognese you made.
- Complimenting myself.
- Sit her down.
Grace, will you sit down a minute?
Why?
We're just worried.
Why? I'm fine.
Well, you're not acting fine.
Where's Ian, Gracie?
Is that Ian's phone that Becka found?
Why doesn't he have it with him?
- Why was it hidden?
- Is there something you haven't told us?
What are you saying?
- We're not saying anything--
- We are.
No, we're just-- we just
need to know what's going on.
- We're nervous.
- We're worried is all.
Why did you say that Ian
was golfing to the Guards?
Grace, there's blood on some clothes
in the washing machine.
There's a cut on your hand.
- I smashed a cup.
- Did something happen with Ian?
All his stuff is still here.
I think you should go now.
No, we just need you to listen, okay?
We won't judge you, Gracie. We love you.
But if something happened with Ian...
- I think you should leave. Now, please.
- ...please just tell us.
- Look, will you just listen?
- Just get away from me!
Oh, God.
Grace, love,
- I hate seeing you like this--
- Please. Don't.
Oh, my God.
Take them. They'll calm you down.
I'll call you later.
Oh, God.
You winded me, you monster.
- Where's Mam?
- She's in the sitting room.
She's a bit sad.
Hey.
Go on up to bed, Rubes.
I'll be straight up.
Is everything okay?
What's going on?
Nora?
It's okay. We're not doing it.
No new baby for you
to get all existential about.
- So the pressure's off.
- Has--
Has something happened?
You can't just say we're not doing it.
It's what was my decision too.
Just be honest, Bibi.
I don't even mean with me, for God's sake.
Just be honest with yourself.
I'm telling the clinic
that we're pulling out.
So do you feel better now?
- Are you gonna see the boss?
- Yeah, you're not needed.
Dick.
Turns out John Paul Williams's
been siphoning off
his father's pension for years.
That Grace Reilly, his widow,
was the beneficiary
of his entire family's estate.
What's she doing?
Fuck off.
- Thank you, sir. I just wanted to s--
- Quiet.
So what are you saying?
I'm saying I think Grace Reilly
was involved in John Paul's death.
Well, he was clearly a violent man
so she could have retaliated.
What?
Those two insurance brothers say
there was foul play in Williams's death
involving the widow
and you said there wasn't.
Yeah, but we may as well
leave all that behind now.
May we as well?
We think there's something
much bigger at play here.
We have reason to believe that
the fella she remarried not long after
has now gone walkabout himself, sir.
Black widow?
Nice church-going lady like that?
What does she have to say about it?
Well, when we questioned Grace Reilly
about John Paul Williams's death,
she said that he killed himself.
- Is that a possibility?
- No way. She's lying.
Grace Reilly hasn't stopped lying
since our first visit.
Well, fuck it. Get on with it then.
Get a warrant, bring her in,
and see what we get.
Don't interrupt me like that again.
Sorry, sir, I just thought
you needed a bit of help.
Did you now?
Well, I'll be the one
to determine that, Houlihan.
Nice new jacket.
Okay.
Come on, Blanaid. You're gonna be late.
There's some toast or some cereal.
I'm not hungry.
Look, I'm wearing the lovely earrings
you got me for the wedding.
I might be home a bit late tonight, Bla,
but I'll leave some money
for some fish and chips
or there's some spag bol leftovers.
I can drop you at the bus on my way to--
- I'd rather walk.
- Fine! Fucking walk then!
I'm sorry.
I love you so much.
Hi, Eva Garvey's phone,
please leave a message.
Oh, shit.
Hey, Eva.
Eva, it's me.
I'm-- I really need your help.
I'm so sorry.
Please call me back.
Oh, no.
No, where is it? Blanaid.
Oh, f--
- What's happened?
- Miss Garvey? I'm really sorry.
Oh, no. No.
No.