In the beginning, God was nothing.
So he started making stuff.
He made the dirt, he made the sky,
he made the water,
he made things that swim,
things that slither, things with legs.
I mean, God turned himself
into a big shot.
Then, in a couple of days,
or a couple of million years,
he breathed life into man.
And he's been sucking the life
out of us ever since.
I am the resurrection and the life.
He that believeth in me,
though he were dead,
yet shall he live.
MAN:
♪ It's me, it's me, it's me, O Lord ♪
♪ Standing in the need of prayer ♪
ALL:
♪ It's me, it's me, it's me, O Lord- ♪
People, we've got three murders
in two weeks.
I got the commissioner yelling in my ear
and the press shoved up my ass.
The governor's threatening
to send in the feds.
And my daughter wants to move
into an apartment with her boyfriend.
Somebody help me out here.
♪ It's me, O Lord ♪
♪ Standing in the need of prayer- ♪
Post burned Ortolani, so obviously
the Wiseguys wasted Post.
-The next move is Jefferson Keane's.
-And he's gonna make it.
McMANUS: No, not necessarily.
I've noticed a change in the guy.
A slight change.
Maybe it's because he got married.
Or maybe he's just tired
of the gangster way of life.
♪ It's me, O Lord ♪
♪ Standing in the need- ♪
We hit this guy hard right now,
all his street instincts
are gonna pop back up.
This is one case where we can't meet
violence with violence.
♪ Need of prayer ♪
When are we gonna kill those wops?
You know Glynn is gonna lock
this place down any minute.
You sure the wops killed Johnny?
Kill him.
And start with his dick.
Just give me the word,
those wops are dead.
KEANE:
Everything's all right. Just chill.
What? You don't give a shit?
You know I give a shit.
I had much love for Johnny.
-Well, you ain't showing it.
-Yeah, man. Last few days
you seemed like a million years away.
What's up with that?
We also gotta find out who ratted
on Johnny and kill those fuckers too.
Mr. Schibetta, I know who killed Dino.
I know who ratted on Johnny.
I just ain't saying.
How's the white race?
KEANE:
I'll kill that motherfucker myself.
Okay, you're the boss.
[WHISPERS] Yo. Now, the Wiseguys
know that Johnny killed Ortolani,
but do they know who ordered the hit?
Watch your back, brother.
You could be next.
-Let the fuckers come. Please.
-All right.
HILL: Being in a gang is a lot
like being in a religion.
You got rules to follow,
a leader to obey,
and at the heart, it's about love.
"Love thy fellow man"
becomes "Love thy brother gangster."
But what if you stop believing
the religion you've been preaching?
You come to see that the hole
is still in your soul,
that the God/love you thought you had
is nothing but a hologram.
Hey, Mavis. Yeah, it's me baby.
How you doing?
What you doing?
Really? What you wearing?
Oh, yeah.
Ooh. Say that again.
Say that again, like that. Yeah.
I like that. Oh, baby, yeah.
Yeah, now I'm feeling you baby.
You go ahead.
Now I'm feeling you, definitely.
Oh, yeah.
What did you say? You say you want
me to spank that ass?
Oh, damn.
I gotta be interrogated by Burrano again.
Like I know anything about Johnny Post.
They cut off his dick
and stuck it in his mouth.
-Where'd you hear that?
-God told me.
Yo, yo, Italian ice, what's up?
SIMON: You ever hear how
the word "doo-wop" came to pass?
No, man, tell me about it.
Well, over in Harlem town,
back in the old days,
a couple of Italians were giving muscle
to a cat running a speakeasy.
He was doing a set,
I think maybe of Billie Holiday.
These Italians come into the club
thinking they can push a brother around.
But instead, the brother finds a blunt.
And outside in the alley, while
Miss Billie Holiday is singing the blues,
the brother do the wops.
And that's how doo-wop was born.
[MARKSTROM LAUGHING]
How'd you like Johnny Post's dick
up your ass?
How would you like to put it there?
Aah! Shit!
[GRUNTING]
[ALARM BLARING]
[CHOKING]
Break it up now! Break it up!
[GASPING]
MAN 1: Fuck this! Yeah, that's right.
MAN 2: That's right!
I want the SORT team put on alert.
And leave word for the commissioner
to call me ASAP.
[KNOCKING]
Yeah.
-Gentlemen, we have a problem.
-They know why they're here.
I want the violence to stop
before anyone else dies,
before this place is flooded with feds,
before we have a full-blown riot.
Nobody wants a riot, right?
-Schibetta?
-No.
-Keane?
Said?
Violence for its own sake
accomplishes nothing.
Then spread the word
that if one more fight breaks out,
I'm gonna shut this prison down
so hard, so fast,
you won't see daylight
till the third millennium.
Everybody got that?
What'd you find out?
Said, Schibetta and Keane
agreed to keep the peace.
Yo, so Glynn said he ain't
gonna lock us down yet.
It's madness. It's madness.
HILL:
To belong, you gotta be able to deal.
You gotta share power.
You gotta share pain.
MARKSTROM: What's that?
KEANE: Probably some cannolis and shit.
-Cannolis?
-Oh, goddamn!
-What?
-Motherfucker, Johnny's dick!
-Shit! Goddamn!
-Oh, fuck!
Motherfuckers!
There's some pain that you don't share,
some pain like your fingerprints,
that's all yours,
all alone.
Fire! Fire! Fire!
There's a fucking-! Get the fuck up!
Fire! Fire!
[ALARM RINGING]
Pyro fuck, huh?
You're a little pyro fucker, are we?
You wanna tell me
what the fuck you did that for?
-I was bored.
-Bullshit.
I've watched you since the day
you checked into Em City.
I've seen you make cold,
calculated decisions.
I've seen you restrain loose cannons.
Now, all of a sudden,
you torch your fucking mattress
knowing it's gonna
end you up in the hole.
You wanna go to lockup so bad,
because why?
Someone's after you?
I never ran away from a fight in my life.
McMANUS: Then what?
I just wanna spend some time alone.
Well, you're gonna do that.
Officer.
You know, your brother Billie's
coming back from the hospital.
KEANE: So I hear.
Yeah, but he's not gonna be in Em City.
He's gonna be in Cell block 3.
Fucking fag unit.
Take him to ADSEG.
Keane.
I wish you'd learn to trust me.
Hello, Keane.
[GRUNTS]
-What the fuck is that about?
-A little warning.
Nothing better happen to Ryan O'Reily.
[YELLS]
[SIRENS WAILING]
[TIRES SCREECHING]
Patrick, you're-Fuck!
Freeze! Stop! Get down! Don't you move!
Check the car. Stay still.
HILL: Prisoner number 97P904,
Ryan O'Reily.
[LAUGHING] Convicted July 12th, '97.
Two counts of vehicular manslaughter,
five counts of reckless endangerment,
possession of controlled substance,
criminal possession of a weapon,
parole violation.
Sentence: life imprisonment.
Up for parole in 12 years.
So this dude,
he's fiending for a cigarette.
I mean, he's about to smoke
the stuffing in his mattress
he's dying so bad.
So he comes to me
and he asks me for a cig.
Just one to get him through the night.
He begs me on his knees,
weeping like a little girl:
"Please? Please? Please?"
So pathetic. I said no.
-You said no.
-Well, actually I lied.
I told him that I was out,
I didn't have any.
I don't think he believed me.
And you said no because...?
For his own good.
He's gotta kick the habit, right?
-So you were being altruistic?
-Whatever.
So you weren't actually committing a sin.
No, Father.
Then why did you come to confession?
-The truth?
-Sure.
I figured when I was done
I could sneak a smoke.
HILL: They say confession
is good for the soul.
You go into a confessional
and you can tell a priest anything.
Anything!
And he can't repeat it.
You go into an interview room with
your local PD and say what you done-
Well, the cops are telling the DA
and the papers and everybody else.
So you do some deed
and you want to clean your conscience
and still get away with it?
Well, tell your mama or tell a priest.
Psst.
-Hey, how you doing, man?
-Okay.
Can you believe that shit
that's going down around here?
Three guys capped in three weeks?
That's fucked up.
BEECHER: Yep.
You're a lawyer, right?
I was disbarred automatically
after I was convicted of a felony.
Even so, how come you ain't
appealing your case
and shit like that?
I did. My appeal was rejected.
How come?
I was drunk driving.
I killed a little girl.
They decided to make an example of me,
so they sent me here
instead of some cushy Club Med.
Maybe you can help me out.
My attorney was a raging dickbrain.
He just fucking rolled over in court.
Could you take a look at my case
and see if there's any way I can appeal?
I didn't do criminal law.
I was in litigation.
I'm telling you, man,
I gotta get out of this place.
[SIGHS]
Okay.
Ryan O'Reily.
Tobias Beecher.
HILL: When you pray,
do you go into a zone?
Does the rest of the world drop away?
I never been there. God and coma.
I can say an Our Father and think
about lunch at the same time.
ALL: Our Father, who art in heaven,
hallowed be thy name-
HILL: Some people say
that if you don't accept Jesus Christ
as the son of God,
as your personal savior,
you won't go to heaven.
But is there a guarantee
that if you do believe in Jesus,
you will be saved?
Or will God, the great practical joker,
leave you hanging?
SCHILLINGER: Hey, sweet pea.
How was church, huh?
You feeling all sanctified and pure?
Get undressed. We're taking a shower.
I already took a shower.
Oh, that's okay.
When I'm done with you,
you'll need another one.
So my assistant got paroled.
See, that's what's wrong with this place.
You finally break in an assistant,
he learns your rhythms,
he's good at the job, and then boom.
The parole board decides
that he's ready to rejoin society.
Meanwhile, I am left with a stack
of untyped psychiatric reports.
Sister, I'm glad you thought
of me for this job.
I really wasn't suited for factory work.
Listen, when I heard
you knew Word and Lotus,
I knelt down and praised Jesus.
I'm lucky he heard you.
He hasn't been listening to me.
-Oh, yes, he does. He listens.
-No, he doesn't.
Since I got to Oz, I've prayed more
than the night before my bar exam,
more than the day my son fell off
his skateboard.
Either God's hearing has gotten bad
or he's ignoring me.
No, listen. First of all, quantity
of prayer doesn't mean anything.
And secondly, maybe he has answered you,
only it's not what you expect.
God almighty, creator of all things,
including the loophole.
Come on.
There's your desk, such as it is.
Tobias,
what do you ask for when you pray?
To get out of here.
Ah. You don't need God for that.
You just need a good lawyer.
I spent my life dealing with the law,
finding ways over, under, around it.
And then when I needed it
to be there for me,
the system snapped back into my face.
I was a good lawyer. I was.
I was a lot of things:
A husband, father, son, brother, friend.
And then I made a mistake.
One huge, huge mistake, but one mistake.
And as a result,
God took everything.
Listen, maybe he stripped you
of the superficial sense of yourself-
You know, doctor, lawyer, Indian chief.
So that you could find the real you
through him.
That's what I'm saying.
That's what I've been trying to do.
But God isn't in Oz.
Oh, yeah, he is. He is everywhere.
He is in you right now, Tobias.
Genevieve is divorcing me.
I think she decided when she saw
the swastika on my butt.
She's gonna take the kids
and go live with her parents.
If God is in me, he's a tumor.
Wow?
It's "Mom."
One of these Muslim monkeys
was trying to tell me
that Jesus was a nigger.
He even quoted from the Bible
trying to back his shit up.
Well, Jesus was from Judea,
so he was probably
of an olive-colored skin.
Look at that picture there.
Does that look like a nigger to you?
No.
You're getting awful mouthy,
aren't you, prag?
No, sir. I am not, sir.
Yeah, I think I'm gonna have
to teach you a lesson.
Polish my boots.
Yes, sir.
With your tongue.
[ALL CHUCKLING]
Son of a bitch.
-Hey, lawboy.
-Yeah?
How's my appeal coming?
-You been crying?
-No.
Sure you have.
That's okay, man. I cry, too, sometimes.
Look, you'd have to be brain-dead not to.
But I got a cure for the blues, homey.
Come on.
What's going on?
Hug the wall.
[SNIFFING]
Let's get high.
Count time, gentlemen!
In front of your cells!
Count!
92M758, 93C472.
May the road rise up to meet you.
May the wind be always at your back.
May the sun shine warm upon your face
and rain fall soft upon your fields.
And until we meet again, may God
hold you in the hollow of his hand.
-Where you been, prag?
-Nowhere, sir.
You're fucked up.
Yes, sir.
I don't want you doing drugs,
sharing needles. Understand?
Yes, sir.
Listen to me, bitch.
I catch you so much
as snorting fucking lint,
I'm gonna beat the shit out of you.
Yes, sir. But you can do whatever
you want to me. I don't care.
Yeah, because you're high.
Because God is everywhere
and God is holding me
in the hollow of his hand.
Praise the Lord and pass the ammunition.
-What?
-I don't know what to do.
I've never done confession before.
I didn't think that you were Catholic.
What are you doing here?
I got caught sneaking
into the morgue again.
You ever seen a guy
with his prick cut off?
-No, I can't say that I have.
-It's not pretty.
I got put in the hole.
The hack comes around and says
that he'll let me out for ten minutes
-if I need to see you, so I say yes.
-You have to go back.
Wait, Father, maybe I'm a convert.
You can't become a Catholic
just to get out of the hole.
-Come on.
-No, no, wait.
I've been reading a lot since I got here
about different faiths
-and yours is pretty nifty.
-Catholicism is nifty?
You have that whole mystical
transubstantiation bit going.
That's right. The Eucharist
becomes the body of Christ.
So you're actually eating his flesh
and drinking his blood.
-That's right.
-Now, how can I not get
behind a religion like that?
HILL: And God said, "Let there be light."
And there was light.
Well, that's easy for God to say.
He's God.
But for the rest of us,
finding the light takes time.
A lifetime.
[INMATES CHATTERING AND WHISTLING]
Jefferson, meet your new roommate,
Kenny Wangler.
Fuck you!
Prisoner number 97W566,
Kenneth Wangler. Yeah, boy.
Sixteen years old tried as an adult.
Convicted July 6th, '97.
Murder in the first degree.
Sentence: 200 years.
Up for parole in six. Ha-Ha! Yeah.
[HILL LAUGHING]
My man here told me
that y'all was the crew to get with.
I wanna be G.
I'll think about it.
What the hell is there to think about?
I said I'll fucking think about it,
all right?
We're gonna need every man we can get
if we're gonna shackle
with those Wiseguys.
Keep thinking.
In Oz, sometimes the things
you can't touch
are more real than the things you can.
For instance, fear, hatred, loneliness,
are more real to me than a shank.
And a soul, every day, can grow
into something you can almost hold.
How fucked up is that?
In a shithole like this,
to first and finally see the face of God.
KENNY: Minister Said.
How you doing? I just wanted
to shake your hand. Shake the hand.
It's like, I saw you talk on TV
the other day and the things you said-
Like, the things you said-
I just want to shake the hand of
the man who said the things you said.
-What is your name, little brother?
-Kenny. Kenny Wangler.
SAID: Kenny. Well, Kenny,
the things that I say out loud,
you already know.
These are words
that are buried deep in your heart.
Do you understand me, little brother?
Let's welcome the little brother.
[SPEAKS IN ARABIC]
What's up? How you doing?
What's going on?
You have been robbed, Kenny.
And you have been robbed
of a very special gift.
It's a gift that can never be replaced.
KENNY: What's that?
Your childhood, Kenny. Your youth.
But the thief was tricky,
because he fooled you
by leaving something in its place.
Fear.
-I ain't afraid of nothing.
-We're all afraid of something, Kenny.
See, me, I was afraid of being poor.
But, see, you've got no fear now, right?
Yes, I do.
I fear God, Kenny.
And I love God.
It's what we call taqwa.
-What's taqwa?
-Never mind. It doesn't matter.
You want to be in a gang, right?
I want you to be in my gang.
I want you to follow us.
Follow our style,
and you can learn to be a real man.
[MEN CHANTING IN ARABIC]
[INAUDIBLE DIALOGUE]
Mr. Woodson. Hey.
Yeah. ls Mavis there?
She's out? Where'd she go?
What you mean you can't tell me?
Don't tell me you don't know!
You track every move that girl makes!
Yeah, I'm calling you a liar,
motherfucker,
because you ain't telling me the truth!
Tell me where the fuck Mavis is now!
[COUGHS AND SNIFFLES]
Bitches. All women is bitches.
Yeah, man, we don't know
Mavis is cheating, man.
I know.
That boy is 16 years old
and he's in for 200,
which means he can be out in six.
He could be back on the street
by the time he's 22.
He can still have a life.
-Get the fuck out of here, Kenny.
-What?
You heard me. I said get the fuck going.
Come on, Kenny,
let's give them some privacy.
Later.
You wanna rage at the faith?
You feel the fire, my brother.
Feel the fire.
I am done with you.
Reverend.
[ALL YELLING]
I do.
I do feel the fire.
Save me.
[CRYING]
Oh, no.
You save me.
Some say finding God is a glorious thing.
They're wrong. It's dangerous.
You spend your whole life
in a world of men.
But when you finally see his power,
his greatness,
other men fall out of view.
Because you're so focused on him,
you can barely see them
from the corners of your eyes.
You lose sight of them.
-Hey.
-I'm out of the hospital.
-I see.
You gonna give me a hug or what?
Thanks for taking care of Ortolani.
What's the matter?
You ain't glad to see me?
Things have changed, Billie.
I've changed.
Now you gonna have to change too.
Change? How?
You have to stop being a fag, that's how.
Stop? I can't stop. I don't wanna.
If you don't stop,
I can't protect you no more.
Fine.
If you don't stop,
you can't be my brother no more.
Fine.
I'll beat the black off you
-if you don't stop being a faggot.
SAID: No, brother, no.
[CRYING]
No, no, no.
But I thought you said that
we're not down with faggots.
Islam rejects homosexuality, yes.
But you are never gonna reach
Billie's heart through intimidation.
You have to learn to open up yours
and show him the way by example,
as I did to you.
Through love.
Reverend, I hear what
you're saying to me, but it's hard.
I mean, I been using these
my whole life to settle things.
And that's okay, brother.
Ain't nobody expecting you
to change overnight.
We all have to struggle
with the devil and his temptations.
But you see, it's like this.
Right now you have Allah on your side.
And you can call him,
and he will come, my brother,
and he will give you strength.
It's just that I feel so bad
and so ashamed of everything
I did before.
It's like I feel as though
I should be going around
to all the people that I hurt
and telling them I'm sorry.
Then that's what you must do.
You go out there and you make
your enemies your friends.
They're my friends?
Well, now, you're gonna have
to prepare yourself, brother.
You see, your faith
is gonna be a threat to them.
You're gonna have
to love them all the more.
Yo, Kenny, I see that drug counselor
doing you a whole hell of a lot of good.
Yo, man, fuck that drug counselor, man.
Fuck him.
What are you doing here?
Yo, Jefferson, what's up, man?
Brothers, my name is now Tizi Ouzou.
T what?
Step up, Brother Tizi. Step up.
I'm done with that.
What the fuck's the matter with you?
Simon, we've been doing it
all wrong, brother.
The whole package. This is not the way.
I told you,
Said's been fucking with his head.
We gotta cut out all this hatred.
We need to learn to love one another,
embrace one another.
The only person
we need to be fearing is God.
Motherfucker,
shut the fuck up with that shit.
Are you still with us?
Are you still a brother?
I am your brother.
-We all God's-
-I said cut that shit, nigga.
What I mean is, you still a brother?
Like this? Doing this? No.
[WHISPERS] Get the fuck away from me.
[KEANE SPEAKS IN ARABIC]
Homeboy getting soft, man.
He come here and ask for love and shit.
Give me that shit.
Fucking faggot, just like his brother.
[BELL RINGING]
Hey, I just mopped there, asswipes.
-What's up, cuz?
-Follow me. Be cool.
We must repent
for what we did to Ortolani
and for getting Johnny killed.
Repent? Are you kidding or are you high?
I ain't gonna rat on you.
And I ain't gonna tell no one
that you set it up with the hacks
to get Johnny in the hole.
Why you being so good to me?
What's the catch?
I tell, you die.
And I would much rather
you see the sins you've committed
and, like myself,
try to change your ways.
You are high.
[SPEAKS IN ARABIC]
Mr. Schibetta?
Jefferson Keane ordered the hit on Dino.
Let me arrange for Keane to die.
Why would you wanna do that?
As a sign of good faith between us.
-Good faith?
-Yeah.
All right.
Why are you letting him
take care of this?
He wants to get his hands dirty,
what do I care?
Besides, this way
the niggers will kill him.
What do you need?
[WHISPERING]
Okay, Keane, you're coming with us.
Why? What'd I do? HEALY: Move your ass!
The man asked a question. What'd he do?
I don't have to explain anything to you,
your holiness.
KEANE: Where the hell are you taking me?
HEALY: Shut the fuck up!
What's this about?
I ain't got no beef with y'all.
I don't wanna fight nobody.
Huh?
[GRUNTING]
Let the games begin.
[SPEAKING IN SPANISH]
[CHOKING]
[YELLS]
OFFICER: Hey, look at that.
The motherfucker killed Martinez.
No! No!
No! No! No!
Lock it down.
[ALARM BLARING]
WOMAN:
It's a lock-down! Get to your cells!
[CHATTERING]
I am deeply concerned
by the rash of murders
that have occurred in Oswald
over the past few weeks.
And though I have every confidence
in Warden Glynn here and his fine staff,
I felt it was necessary
to make an on-site inspection.
And we are always happy
to see the governor
and engage in
a free-flowing exchange of ideas.
Now, if you'll excuse us. Governor?
What the fuck are you people doing?
Do any of you have a fucking clue
as to how to run this prison?
Governor, all these deaths
are interrelated.
We got a race war in the making and
we're trying to contain the situation.
Well, you're not doing a very good job.
McMANUS: And you're not helping much.
What? Who are you?
Tim McManus. I run Cell block 5.
Oh, yeah. Emerald City.
The wave of the future.
You are creating a lot of the tension
that we're dealing with around here.
And how am I doing that?
Well, you ban smoking, you ban conjugals.
Bit by bit you're stripping these men
of their basic human needs.
This is a prison.
These men are criminals.
The whole point is to strip them
of their basic human needs.
If a knee-jerk, liberal prissy
like you would see that,
we wouldn't be having the problems
we're having today.
The campaign's over, governor.
Get off your soapbox.
McManus, when you look at me,
what do you see?
A man.
Eh...
You've heard of Olympus, right?
Mount Olympus in ancient Greece,
where the gods lived?
-Yeah.
-Well, there was a hierarchy,
even among the gods.
Mercury was lesser than Apollo,
Apollo lesser than Zeus.
Now, you run your cell block
and you think you're a god.
Glynn runs the whole prison,
he thinks he's a greater god.
Well, guys,
I am Zeus.
I am omnipotent.
I must be obeyed
or my thunderbolts will strike.
You're not Zeus. You're a politician.
McManus, take a walk, you're not helping.
Fine.
-Thank you, warden.
-Devlin, tell me what you want.
One, I want the murders to stop.
Two, I want this Jefferson Keane
to go on trial.
I want him convicted
and I want him to die.
He's gonna be the first executed
now that I've brought
the death penalty back.
Three, end the lock-down.
What?
The public hears the whole prison
is locked down, they get tense.
They think we've lost control.
The fact that we're in lock-down
proves we're in control.
I'm not talking about what's real,
I'm talking about John Q.'s perception.
And what if we have a riot?
What will John Q. think then?
What will that do
for your political career?
I wouldn't worry about me, warden.
I'm the one with
the thunderbolts, remember?
I just got a call from the governor,
who got a call
from your friend Senator Shriner
complaining about his interference in Oz.
Well, Leo, somebody's gotta stop
this fucking little Napoleon.
Ken Shriner's got the balls to do it.
Devlin is bringing the FBI
to investigate the murders.
Maybe they'll do a better job
than Burrano has.
Hey, this is my prison. Look.
I don't want the feds running around,
waking my inmates,
faxing me memorandums.
And the last thing I want,
the last thing I need, is for you
taking shit like this on yourself.
This is your fault, McManus,
and I won't forget that.
Welcome to Oswald.
Johnny Post got into Ortolani's cell
somehow and burned him alive.
You think the guards were involved?
GLYNN: Ortolani was strapped down
here when we found him torched.
You cut his dick off
because you're the big don.
You can do anything.
GLYNN: We found Post tied up here.
His penis had been cut off
and stuffed in his mouth.
GOLDSTEIN: I don't understand.
How'd it work out that you and Martinez
were in the gym with no guards?
GLYNN: The fight took place here.
Keane snapped Martinez's neck.
GOLDSTEIN: Come in.
-Hi. Jeremy Goldstein.
-Tim McManus.
Thanks for taking time
out of your busy day.
Well, I want these murders solved
as much as anyone.
I'm sure you do.
Interesting place, Oz.
I haven't been called "kike" this much
since prep school.
You don't have a problem with me
being Jewish, do you?
No, not at all.
You don't think of me
as a Christ killer or anything?
Well, I'm not even really sure
that Christ died, so...
Good. Fair enough.
But Dino Ortolani sure as hell did.
Roasted by Johnny Post.
You think he did that
of his own volition?
Probably not.
Post wasn't exactly a brain trust.
So someone told him to off Ortolani,
but we don't know who.
-My guess is Jefferson Keane.
-Keane, yeah.
He snaps the neck of a Latino,
one Julio Martinez.
-Why?
-I don't know.
Jefferson hasn't said a word
except to pray ever since.
I tried to talk to him earlier, I know.
Doesn't it seem odd to you
that Keane and Martinez
were left in the gym unsupervised?
Yes, in the same way it seems odd
that Post was let into the hole
to burn Ortolani.
So I wouldn't be too far off to think
that the guards were involved?
It's possible. It's probable.
-How about you?
-How about me, what?
Would I be too far off to think
that you were involved?
Are you saying I'm a suspect?
I'm FBI. Until I got a reason
not to believe it, you're a suspect.
[CHUCKLES]
Here's a pop quiz.
Name the seven deadly sins.
Come on, you saw that Brad Pitt movie.
Lust. Yeah, well,
everybody gets that one, huh?
Gluttony, sure. Greed, yeah.
Envy, sloth, anger-
Or to be a little more technical, wrath.
What else? What else?
Let me put it this way:
if you think you know the answer
and because of that, you think
you're better than everybody else,
then you're guilty of it. Ha-ha!
[METAL SCRAPING]
Prisoner number 97A413, Miguel Alvarez.
Convicted February 3rd, '97.
Assault with a deadly weapon,
criminal mischief in the second degree.
Sentence: 15 years. Up for parole in two.
According to this file,
you're about to be a father.
You've got a girlfriend, Maritza.
She's an inmate of Parker Women's.
Yeah, we got arrested together.
Ain't that sweet?
MUKADA: I can arrange for you
to be there for the birth.
[SPEAKING IN SPANISH]
Carlos, he is a handsome fuck.
Hey, Miguel, when you fucked Maritza,
did you, like, stare at yourself
in the mirror the whole time and shit?
Fuck you, motherfuckers.
-What's up with Keane?
-What about him?
Yo, come on, man.
That pendejo broke Julio's neck.
-All right? Yo, he gotta get done.
-He's in the fucking hole.
So? Yo, Post got to Ortolani
in the hole, right?
Yeah. Wonder how the hell
he did that shit.
Carlos, you wanted something?
Yeah, man.
-Can we do a little business?
-Always.
All right.
We need to get into Keane's cell.
-So? Why you coming to me?
-I hear things, papa.
-The wrong things, papa.
-You're not in tight with the hacks?
I don't know what you're talking about.
But even if I did,
I would tell you
things are too crazy right now.
Nobody's gonna help nobody do nothing.
Miguel, the hospital just called.
Maritza just went into labor.
Oh, shit! Oh, shit!
[CHOIR SINGING]
All right, go on in.
[NO AUDIBLE DIALOGUE]
-There he is. That's my boy.
McMANUS: Congratulations.
-Thanks.
-Look at that.
-He's beautiful, right?
-Yeah, he must take after his mother.
[ALL LAUGHING]
I'd do anything for him, you know.
I'd die for him.
Well, you try and stay alive instead.
Look, I got a message here.
You gotta call Maritza right away.
Father, ever since the baby was born,
you know, I been bragging
to all the other guys
about how beautiful he is
and shit like that.
I mean, you really gotta admit, I mean,
he's the most beautiful baby
in the world.
So now I'm thinking that, like,
maybe I went a little overboard
because Maritza called me
this morning talking about
how the baby got a bad liver
and he's still in the hospital
and they think that he's gonna die.
So now I'm thinking that maybe God
heard me bragging so much
and he decided,
to, you know, punish me.
Oh, Miguel, God doesn't work that way.
I mean, growing up, I knew
I was the best-looking in my hood.
You know, I told everybody.
You know, I was the best athlete,
I was the best lover, you know,
even my fucking car.
So now I'm thinking that,
you know, God's pissed off.
I'm wondering
if you could talk to God for me
and tell him that if he saves my baby,
you know,
I'll stop being such a bigmouth.
Could you do that for me, Father?
I will, but you gotta pray to God, too,
you know?
Don't negotiate. You gotta stop
bragging for your own good.
I know that.
But if my baby dies, you know,
I don't know what I'm gonna do.
I mean, it's like I'll die.
Miguel, you should pray to God
for your son's health,
but you should also ask God
to give you and Maritza the strength
to face whatever happens.
Maritza says that the doctor says
that all this is going on
because of the drugs that we did
before she was pregnant, you know.
And after she was pregnant, you know,
People were fucking telling us,
you know, not to, you know-
And Maritza didn't want to, you know,
and I thought nothing bad
was gonna fucking happen to me.
Me.
Pray for me. Pray for my baby.
[WHISPERS] I will.
Repeat after me:
O my God, I am heartily sorry
for having offended thee,
and I detest all my sins-
No, that ain't enough. That ain't enough.
I mean, God wants a piece
of my fucking ass.
HILL: We try to figure out what God
wants from us, why he put us here.
We try to make deals with him.
But God is one tough motherfucker.
And we know to get what we need,
we got to give up what matters most.
Anything less, he's not interested.
[BELLS CHIMING]
Lamb of God,
you take away the sins of the world.
Have mercy on us.
The body of Christ.
-The body of Christ.
-Amen.
The body of Christ.
God knows he's perfect and we're not.
And we can never be.
But he expects us to be.
And he punishes us if we're not,
you know what I'm saying?
God is the ultimate gangster.
The supreme mob boss,
you know what I mean?
Making us live by his code.
Deaden us if we don't.
Yo, he never has to talk to us
face to face
and he never has to explain exactly
why he does what he does.
Know what I'm saying? Nigger sits up
there in heaven somewhere,
drinking a cappuccino, chilling.
[SINGS] Got the whole world in his hands
He got the whole world by the balls.
In excelsis Deo and all that shit.
[HUMMING]
[SPEAKING IN ARABIC]