Ah.
All right!
So, tell us what brings you
here today, Christopher?
What brings me here today? Erm...
Well...
Um...anyone, really.
Er...
Er, I... I like to read,
which I suppose makes sense.
I'm a librarian.
So, anyone interested in books,
erm, I suppose.
Er, I like films.
'I love going to the cinema.
I like old films especially.
I like, er, romantic films,
um... French films.
Oh, I love old Westerns.
I used to watch those
with my grandfather.'
'The older ones.
Er, Some Like It Hot.
Er, The Golden Age.
Oh, though, I do like...
Oh, what's he called?
Gerard Depardieu.
Erm, yeah, there's something
about him I find quite...'
interesting.
'John Wayne films er...'
I love that film High Noon.
Anything with Gary Cooper in it.
'If you could just tell us
a bit more about who you are...
as a person.'
'Who I am?'
'Yeah, just what sort of person
do you think you are deep down?'
Deep down.
That's quite tricky, isn't it?
'Uh...
Sorry.
Um...
I sup... I'm...'
'Take your time.'
I...um...
Sorry. I didn't expect you
to ask me that.
That's OK.
'He was often
very proud, very stubborn.
Smart boy in many ways.
Could've gone to university.'
But he just wasn't motivated
in that way.
Hard working
but not always productive,
if you know what I mean.
And he didn't want to leave
his mother was the other thing.
Or his brother.
So, he was close to his mum?
And his brother - was it "David"?
Yes.
Yes, it was David.
What about his erm...
relationship with the victims,
the er... Wycherleys?
I only met the Wycherleys once,
at the wedding.
Well, the mother, anyway.
The father
I don't remember that much.
But Chris never really spoke to me
about that kind of thing.
And the truth is he and I
never spoke much about anything.
After he and Susan got married...
..they both just disappeared
into their own world.
How do you mean?
Well, neither of them
are built for THIS one, are they?
If you told me that they'd beamed
their way in on little spaceships,
I'd have half a mind to believe you.
Oh, don't tell me
I'm onto something.
Are they aliens?
So, this erm...
this might seem like
a stupid question,
but can I ask you
about the word "fragile"?
Chris, he often refers to Susan
as "fragile" in his...
in his emails, in...
in conversation.
Yes.
Yes, he does.
Just wondering what that's about,
I guess.
If you want to understand
my step-son, you should know
that he has always found himself
someone like that.
Someone "fragile", if you like.
Whether it be his mother
or his brother.
It's not my story to tell,
I'm afraid.
But they both died
before their time...
..put it that way.
And Chris took it very, very hard.
Especially when David went.
I'd never seen a man
weep like that before.
Quite harrowing, actually.
It's one of the only times
I ever held him.
He's a lot bigger than me
but, my goodness, did he feel small.
But that's Chris, you see.
He's always trying
to save someone...
..and he never manages to do it.
Would you like me
to make you a cup of tea?
No, thanks.
I'll be all right in a minute.
OK.
Let me know if you change your mind.
Yes, please, actually.
Two sugars, please.
Need a bit of a pick-me-up.
Coming right up!
'Dear Gerard Depardieu,
my husband and I are huge fans
of your work,
particularly the dramas,
though we also think
you're an excellent comedic actor.
I am writing to ask you most humbly
for a signed photograph.
I would love to give this
to my husband, Chris,
to lift his spirits,
as he has recently been bereaved.
He tragically lost his dear brother
David several months ago
and has been inconsolable
ever since.
I know that a message and a gift
from you would give him strength.
We live in England
but we love France.
We think you live in the most
romantic country in the world.
Un grand merci in advance,
Mr Depardieu.
Yours faithfully, Susan Edwards.
Susan's at her parents' house
in Mansfield - without Chris.
He's back in London.
Her mother, Patricia Wycherley -
possible drink problem.
Her father, William,
was sexually abusive towards Susan.
Allegedly.
Let's assume it's true.
Patricia shoots her husband.
She's pissed. Some kind of row.
Bang, bang. First question -
why has Patricia got a gun?
Patricia drops the gun.
Susan picks it up.
Patricia says horrible things
to Susan, winds her up -
Bang, bang again.
Whoops, Mum's dead too.
She cannelloni's her parents
in a blanket and leaves them
under the bed for a week.
Correct, sir. Then she gets
the coach back down to London,
tells her husband
her parents are off to Blackpool,
so they need to house-sit.
They head back up to Mansfield.
Fish supper.
Susan can't take it any more.
Spills the beans.
Husband digs a massive hole,
buries both bodies in the garden.
And we think
that's a load of old...?
Bullshit!
Good.
So, first task
is to prove that it's rubbish.
Second task is to work out
what actually happened.
Was it premeditated?
Are we looking at joint enterprise?
If so, how do we convince the CPS?
'For the record,
I'm placing evidence
from Catalogue A on the table.'
Gary Cooper.
President Eisenhower.
John Wayne.
Kirk Douglas.
Sir Winston Churchill.
Charles de Gaulle.
Personal correspondence
with the actor Gerard Depardieu.
Oh, yes, Gerard.
Be very careful with those, please.
Are you friends with him,
Mr Edwards?
Not exactly.
Susan wrote to him once
and we just stayed in touch.
All right.
These are all glamorous men,
aren't they?
Heroic men.
How do YOU fit into that?
This is all you brought back
with you from France.
It's all you've got left, in't it?
No money in the bank.
No other assets to speak of.
Half of it bought behind your back
with credit cards
you had to work to pay off.
She was using money you had earned
to buy tat.
Look...
..this may not be to your taste,
but it is not tat.
Some of these are highly
sought-after and very rare.
Actually, Susan has immaculate taste
when it comes to things like this.
700 quid.
Don't know what you paid for it,
but we've had it appraised at 700.
It is, I'm afraid,
what we call in the business...
a big old pile of useless tat.
You're lying.
I can do that?
It's all right, love.
We've, er...
We've got some, have we?
In the spice drawer.
Oh! Dang it.
The top's come off!
They've gone everywhere.
No, no, no, you finish your eggs
in peace.
It's my mess.
Dustpan's under the sink!
You all right?
No, er... They've scurried into
all the nooks and corners.
I need the hoover.
Oh, no. I can do that.
It's a bit of a jumble.
I'm not a baby, Susan.
And it's hardly a jumble.
What are these?
This is a lot of money, Susan.
It's an investment. We can sell it.
Picture Show Magazine, £400.
It's signed by Gary Cooper!
That's not the point!
We don't have this money!
We've never had this money.
I don't earn enough.
I was gonna tell you about that one.
"Dear Mr Wycherley..."
This is to your father.
Look, I can explain.
"As you are about to turn 100,
we at the Department
for Work and Pensions
would like to visit you
at the above address
to conduct an in-person interview"!
But it...it's OK.
How is it OK? We've told 'em he's
living with us. He isn't, is he?
No, but I wrote to them
and asked them to delay.
It doesn't matter how long we wait.
Your father's never gonna
attend this interview, is he?
I know that.
What did you think would happen?
Hey? Why did you hide
this letter from me?
'It's a compulsion.
It's her way of dealing
with things that er...
It's like she's trying
to buy back the happiness
that her parents
stole away from her.'
But that was when she was a child -
three decades earlier.
She's a grown woman now.
I assume you're trying
to goad me into something
by deliberately oversimplifying,
but it's clear that these
experiences are not...
You can't just shake them off.
And besides, William and Patricia
never stopped being horrible to her.
They never stopped trying to take
every chance of happiness
away from her.
You must have hated them.
No, I tried not to.
This was very difficult.
I tried not to get involved -
So, what did they do
to "steal her happiness"?
Well, they were
abusive to her verbally,
they constantly
undermined her confidence
and on one occasion,
they literally stole from her.
What I mean is, they were -
They stole from her?
In a way, yes,
that's just a small example,
but what I mean is they were...
in general, they...
they were not at all nice to her.
What did they steal from her, Chris?
Oh, look, "steal"...
"stole", that's an exaggeration.
What I mean is Susan...
This is the power they had over her.
She gave it to them
quite willingly as a gift.
Because she wanted them to like her.
Which I never understood -
A gift of what?
Well, money, essentially.
Well, when was this?
Oh, I can't remember.
It was that long ago.
Maybe the late...'80s.
And it wasn't money as such,
it was that,
look, they had
shared ownership in a house.
Susan and I were married now
so we moved into my flat,
and they -
the...the Wycherleys - they...
..well, they thought
it'd be better if...
If Susan just handed over
her share to them?
Oh...
'Susan had helped them
buy it some years previously,
so her name was on the deeds.'
'She helped them buy it?'
'Yes, they...'
Hi.
'She'd received an inheritance
from her grandfather...
on her mother's side.
He was the one who got her into
all the old Western movies.
He was a... He was a war hero,
and somewhat confusingly about
the same age as William, her dad.
William hated him, of course, but
William seemed to hate everyone.'
William.
Good to see you.
Ah, likewise. Likewise, yeah.
Go on through.
Oh.
'And so, did her mum not inherit
anything herself, then?'
'No. That was the tricky thing.
I suppose, because of
the animosity with William,
her father didn't want William
to get his hands on it,
so he just left it all to Susan.'
Chris, perhaps you could
take William off for a port.
We don't have any port.
Or something.
You know...leave us girls
to have a little catch-up.
What's your poison, William?
My wife.
You have no idea how awful it is.
My life shouldn't have been
like this, Susan.
I used to have friends.
Used to laugh.
Oh, Mum. It's not so bad.
You've still got me.
You've no fucking idea, Susan.
You've escaped.
I'm stuck with him.
I'm sorry.
No, I'm sorry, Susan.
I'm not myself.
How's your organ?
Broken.
Patricia hammering away on it
with her fat fingers.
I'm going for a pee.
Do you want anything while I'm up?
Again?
You've got the bladder of a mouse.
A lady mouse.
That was MY money.
He was my father, Susan!
Oh, you can be a thoughtless
little bitch sometimes.
I'm sorry, Susan.
I never mean to hurt you.
You know that, don't you?
Will you consider it?
Give your poor old mother
a bit of peace?
Just consider it a loan.
That's all it is.
A simple loan.
'So, she signs it over?'
'Yes.'
'And what happens to the house?'
It's all too predictable,
I'm afraid.
Before the ink is dry
on the transfer deed,
they sell the house - for a very
healthy profit I might add -
and they sod off up to Mansfield.
To Mansfield?
Yes.
Gosh, I can see how that
might have exercised you.
Well, no, I'm not...
I... I wasn't exercised.
I was more regretful, I suppose.
But one tries to rise above it.
Please don't be angry with me -
How can you be so stupid?!
'It's your money! It's our money!'
And you just let 'em take it
like they've taken every other
bloody thing from you!
They promised they wouldn't sell it.
Their promises are worth nothing!
Of course, they're gonna sell it.
They're liars.
The whole lot of you are liars!
Why can't you ever learn, Susan?
I tell you what. Why don't
we do something else for a bit?
We could play I Spy. Erm...
There's about five things
in this room.
Or we could play cards.
I don't have any cards.
Or we could chat, you know.
I guess, the point is to keep
your mind off things for a bit
so it's not gonna...
What about YOUR life?
Er... Er, yeah.
Yeah, er...
Or we could play that game
where it's like erm...
the first letter is the last
letter of the word before -
What's your father like?
Er... Hmm.
My dad erm...
My dad wasn't around much.
Which is kind of a cliche,
I guess, but it's true.
What about your mum?
I love my mum. She's amazing.
And a wife?
I've...got a girlfriend.
And you know what, actually, erm...
..last night, on my way home,
I was...
I was thinking about
the way you talk about Chris.
I hope she talks about me that way.
Like how you stick up for him
and stuff.
See, I don't know, erm...
I don't know.
That's real, isn't it?
You really love him.
Sorry.
'She didn't step up
to the plate like you'd hoped.
You wanted her
to stand up for herself
but she's refused to change.'
No. She wanted to.
She tried to. But she couldn't.
So, it should have been YOU
stepping up to the plate?
I couldn't know
what the Wycherleys were up to -
You were watching telly with the man
who'd sexually abused your wife
while her mother
stole her inheritance.
That is unfairly reductive.
And on that night,
when the Wycherleys
were shot and killed,
you did exactly the same thing,
didn't you?
You abandoned Susan to her parents.
No, I did not.
You let her go alone
up to Mansfield
to visit the two people
she hated most in the world.
And look what happened to her.
Unless that is when you see it.
That Susan is never gonna change.
That she can't suddenly
start standing up for herself.
And that's when you realise
that you have to.
I was not in Mansfield the weekend
the Wycherleys were killed.
I wish I was. I might have been able
to prevent this from happening.
But I was in Dagenham.
Here we go.
For the record,
I'm showing the suspect item PW-56.
Paid another visit
to your step-mother today, Chris.
And, erm...she lent us
this box of photos.
Is that your mother-in-law -
Patricia?
Yes.
Where's William?
He... He didn't come.
He didn't approve of me marrying
his daughter...for some reason.
And, er, did that... Did that hurt?
Not really.
Is that your mum - Ange?
Yes.
And is that your brother - David?
Mm, yes.
So um...
Emma and I had a chat and we don't
wanna put you through something
which is obviously...very painful,
but the feeling is,
is that this erm...
history, if you like,
it may be relevant to the case.
So do you mind if we ask you
a couple more questions?
Look, Chris, my dad's a drinker,
so I've got "fragile"
in the family as well.
And...don't get me wrong,
I love my dad.
But, by God, is he exhausting.
Every time the phone rings,
I know it's gonna be
some kind of drama.
But do you know what makes me
angrier than anything else?
Watching my mum pour all her energy
into worrying.
They're not even together any more
and yet still
every decision she makes
revolves around him
and his drinking.
And I've told her a million times...
..let it go.
It's not worth it.
Because some people are beyond help,
aren't they, really?
Let's face it.
Stop trying to help people
who can't be helped.
Look where it's got you both.
I don't agree with you.
I don't agree that
anyone's beyond help.
Nobody's beyond help in this world.
That's the whole point
of this world.
Not my mother...
not David and certainly not Susan.
I wasn't trying to save my mother
or save my brother.
I was trying to love them.
And that's all I've ever done
with Susan, is love her.
But how will she explain to a jury
that she cleared out
her parents' bank account
the day after they were shot dead?
No-one's gonna buy she was provoked.
She's going down
for double murder, Chris,
and the fact that you love her
is not gonna change anything.
She didn't shoot them both.
She couldn't have -
Yes, she could.
No, she couldn't.
The nature of the bullet wounds
indicate that whoever shot William
also shot -
She couldn't have done it.
She's terrified of guns.
What do you mean
she's terrified of guns?
Oh, Susan.
I know what this
is going to look like.
But I have to stand up for my wife.
I know she couldn't have
killed them both.
I know she was terrified of guns
because I used to belong
to a gun club.
I used to own guns myself, in fact.
I owned two pistols.
'Both of which I got rid of
long before the Wycherleys died,
before the Dunblane law even,
when I would've had
to turn them in, anyway.'
But I dragged Susan along
to the range once or twice,
and she couldn't even
bring herself to touch a gun,
much less shoot one. So I know...
that she could never have killed
two people with a gun.
She could never have contemplated
killing two people with a gun.
That is impossible.
'So, that awful weekend in May
when you were alone -
you say - your parents are dead,
you're up all night wondering
how to dispose of the bodies...
what to do with the gun,
sleeping in that house
and then going
and opening that bank account.
That's a lot for anyone
to go through, Susan.
And for someone "fragile" like you.'
'Can you get to the point, please?
My client is pretty exhausted
already from waiting all day,
so I think the least you could do
is to be concise.'
'The point is, Susan,
we can't imagine you
going through it on your own.
We think Chris helped you.
Which means we're not
asking for manslaughter.'
We're recommending murder.
For both of you.
No.
We think Chris was with you
that first weekend -
probably the only weekend -
and you murdered them together
and then he buried them.
No!
What are you basing this on?
You both felt you were owed money
from that house.
No...er... The house?
In Edgware.
The one they "stole" from you -
to quote your husband.
Let me tell you
what our report's gonna say.
See if it makes sense to you.
Come on, Susan.
I'm sorry, but I have to object.
You, too. This way.
Where are you going?
What's happening?
Shall I bring the camera, Emma?
Nah.
You don't have to follow them.
Where are you going!
Susan!
Chop, chop.
You don't have to go with them.
You can come back! Susan.
No -
Grant, come on.
Excuse me. Sorry. No!
Where are you going? No!
Susan!
Good evening, you two.
You're looking fresher
than when I last saw you.
Oh, stop it. Isn't she funny?
Where shall I stand?
Or... Or... Or shall I sit?
Shall... Shall I plug in?
Nah, you're all right.
Ah. Come through.
No, because this is silly.
Oh, hello, darlings!
Don't you look lovely.
Come in, come in.
Hello, my girl!
Fuck you, Dad!
No. I wouldn't say that
because I don't swear.
William. Good to see you.
Yeah, good to see you, too.
Ow, why are you squeezing my hand
so hard?
Because of what you did to my wife.
That's a bit much, don't you think?
This is not how it happened.
No, it didn't.
It didn't happen like this!
I keep telling you,
Chris wasn't there!
Hello, darling.
What you doing?
Mr Wycherley, excuse me, sir.
Would you mind getting up?
Delighted.
Unless one of you tells us, Susan,
we're never gonna know
exactly what happened -
whether you're all having
a nice time,
or you're all having a row,
or what -
but sooner or later you had them
both up here in the bedroom.
Right, can you give me the...
Now? OK?
Actually, William and Patricia...
Yes, ma'am?
This is ridiculous.
Could you get into bed and go
to sleep? That makes more sense.
That's a good note.
Thank you, Officer.
Patricia would probably be
sleeping quite lightly, I think,
because of her back pain.
Yeah, OK.
Right, all yours, Chris.
Woah...sorry.
No, just don't worry about that.
Right, yes. Ah...
We think Chris was with you
that first weekend -
probably the only weekend -
and you murdered them together.
Then, over the next couple of days,
he buried the bodies -
No, that was the following weekend.
The weekend
of the Eurovision Song Contest.
Because we stayed up
to watch it on television
while our neighbours went to bed,
so we could bury the bodies.
I remember it was the year
that Dana International won -
Dana Inter...
You never give up, do you?
Chris informed us that he used
to have a couple of revolvers.
.38s, as it happens.
Susan...you're within your rights
to take five to discuss this.
That was a long time ago.
He got rid of them.
He says you couldn't stand guns.
That's right.
I was terrified -
Terrified of them. Yeah, he said.
Couldn't even bring yourself
to touch one.
You don't think
that's his way of telling us
- that HE did the shooting?
- No!
Kind of like when he called
his step-mother... No, no!
He's not confessing to anything!
Susan.
- What?!
- Are you sure
you don't wanna discuss this?
What difference would that make?!
I can advise you on how best to -
How to what?
There's a lot being discussed -
We are not murderers!
She's calling me a murderer!
I don't know what he was thinking,
telling you about his guns.
That's not clever.
But doesn't it just show you, like
when he called his step-mother -
which he was very hurt by,
by the way she betrayed him -
doesn't that just show you
he has nothing to hide?
If you want to know
where the gun came from,
it was my father's, actually.
And you're gonna think
this is a lie but...
but he actually was fascinated
by fascist iconography and Nazis.
Susan -
This is the truth! Believe me.
He had a collection in a cabinet
and we got rid of them
because we didn't like
having them in the house.
So we got rid of everything.
You have to believe me. Please.
Are you done?
In truth, it no longer matters
what I believe.
We're gonna stop there, Susan.
Thank you.
We're going to prison.
My Chris is going to prison
and I'll never see him again.
You can get through this, Susan.
Um, you have to stay calm.
It... It's...
There's a whole trial yet, OK?
You have to trust me.
When will I see Chris again?
I... I...
Maybe not for a while but...
I mean, if...
if the trial does happen,
I'll make sure he finds
a really good lawyer and...
If you do get charged
and prison does happen,
for either one of you,
once you get your head around it,
it's not so bad.
OK? It's actually a lot more
comfortable than being in here.
You just have to trust me -
I don't trust you!
I don't trust anyone except Chris.
Fair enough. I get it, I get it.
And I know you're upset. I just...
I'm very sorry, but you
have to keep it together, OK.
I get it. Honestly, I do -
You don't get it!
You don't. You don't get it!
Susan, I...I...
Why didn't you stop them?!
You didn't do anything!
I'm sorry if you're not happy
with how I represented you,
but it's a big case for me, Susan,
and I just...
I... I didn't know...
I didn't know about the house.
I didn't know
about the bank account.
I didn't know about Chris
and his guns.
You didn't tell me -
I wasn't supposed to tell you,
so why would I tell you?!
Yeah, OK.
Stupid Chris. What is he doing?
He's been in questioning for
two days straight without support.
It's tough, Susan. People break.
It's so tough.
Erm, OK, OK, listen.
I don't normally tell anybody
about this -
at least not my clients - because
I'm not really proud of it, but...
..if it makes you feel any better,
I have... I've been to prison.
Yeah, I know, but it's true.
And, OK, it was when I was younger,
er, silly stuff.
Getting into fights and so on,
but...but, look, I had my mum.
And I had my girl,
the same way you have Chris.
And now here I am.
That's not the same thing.
What's not the same thing?
It's not the same thing!
Chris is the only thing I love
and I can't lose...
I can't lose him. I can't.
All right!
All right, calm down.
You're not getting a table dance.
Obviously, a lot of hard graft
has gone into this -
including all you lot
behind the scenes.
But I think we can all agree
that DC Lancing and DC Wilkie
have done us proud.
Howdy, Sheriff.
Fair fucks to you, Emma -
balls of steel.
We can be pretty confident now
that the story that pair
of vampires came in with
is as fairy-tale
as Father Fucking Christmas.
Except Santa never killed anyone,
as far as we know.
We ain't caught him yet, anyway.
But, on a serious note,
the hope is
that because of our work,
a double murder has been solved
and two cold-hearted criminals
will be brought to justice.
And that's what it's all about.
That's what gets me up
in the morning....
..and that's why I love this job.
If the lawyers don't fuck it up.
That's right, Paul.
It's all down to them
wiggy bloody penguins now.
That's why they get paid
the big bucks, is it?
So, anyway, good work.
Let's have a few drinks,
big case but onto the next one.
Come on!
To justice.
Right, who's got the bottle opener?
Right, good work.
'"Dear Chris,
thank you for the kind letter
requesting a signed photograph,
which I include in this envelope.
I cannot imagine the pain that
you are suffering at the moment
and I wish
that I could take it away."'
'Hello?'
Hiya, Dad.
'Is that you, ducky?'
Yeah. You all right?
'Yeah, I'm all right. Are you?'
Yeah.
'This is a nice surprise.'
'"In life,
there are moments of darkness.
I have experienced many
in my life, too.
But I know there will always be
some hope to come around the corner.
My dear Chris, at times of darkness
it is natural to grieve,
but you must not despair.
Your beautiful brother David
is in heaven amongst the angels
where there is only light,
and you will see him once more
in this place.
Please write to me again.
I would be very happy
to be your friend.
Yours sincerely, Gerard Depardieu."'
I can't believe it.
I can't believe that someone like
that would write to people like us.
Can you?
Yeah, it's definitely surprising.
What an extraordinary gesture.
What an extraordinary man.
Yeah. Has it made you feel better?
I think it has.
It's made me feel like
there's some good in the world
and it's important
to be reminded of that, isn't it?
Yeah, definitely.
Gerard Depardieu
friends with the likes of us.
Can I tell you a secret?
A secret?
When I was a little girl...
and I used to go for walks
sometimes on my own
just to get away from Mum and Dad
when they were fighting
or, you know, there was this horse
I used to go and look at
every now and then.
And I never knew whose it was...
but he'd just stand around
in his bit of field by the road,
eating the grass
and getting on with his day.
And...
And I'd talk to him sometimes.
Did you?
Yeah.
Out loud?
Yeah. I called it Susan.
You didn't.
I did.
And I'd say,
"Hello, Susan, how are you today?
I hope you're enjoying
your lovely grass.
Oh, it's windy today,
isn't it, Susan?"
And stuff like that.
And then when I'd get home,
I'd sit on the sofa like this...
..and I'd look at the back...
and, you see where the...
the line meets the wall?
Can you see? Like a horizon?
Oh. Oh, yeah.
And I used to imagine
that the wall was the sky
and that this was the great big
dusty plain like in the films.
And then I'd picture
a tiny little Susan
galloping and galloping for hours...
..and I used to sit and imagine it.
Can you see?
Yes, I can.
Yeah.
That's my life, isn't it, Chris?
That horse.
I suppose it is, yes.
And now since I've met you,
I imagine you on the horse.
Me?
Yeah. And I'm with you.
And we're riding and riding
across the plain,
the wind in our hair...
and I'm holding onto you
as tight as I can.
And then what happens?
Nothing.
Just ride, Chris. Just ride.
Well...
I'm afraid I don't know
how to ride a horse...
..but I can learn.
'In 2005, the Edwards
faked signatures on documents.'
'And around the same time, the
couple's bank account was drained.'
'In later years,
the house was sold...
and benefits were
claimed in their names.'
'They had taken something
in the region of £300,000
and they appear to have spent
every single penny of it.'
'But the deceit didn't end there.
To cover up what they'd done,
the couple also tricked
friends and family
into thinking the Wycherleys
were still alive.
At this point,
William and Patricia Wycherley
had been dead for 13 years.
But the Edwards
eventually ran out of luck.
On what would have been
William Wycherley's 100th birthday,
the Department of Work and Pensions
wrote him a letter,
asking to see him.'
'This was a double murder
motivated by money.'
'Motivated by greed.'
'The Edwards have insisted
they've told the truth.
But police say that from the moment
they were arrested,
the couple have displayed
a heartless attitude.'
'Christopher and Susan Edwards
will appear before
a Crown Court judge on Monday.'
AccessibleCustomerService@sky.uk