Keyworth Pictures
invites you to Hotel Reverie.
Renowned Dr. Alex Palmer
encounters tragic
heiress Clara Ryce.
Waiter, another scotch, please.
- And for yourself?
- Thank you. A Black Rose.
A rose for a rose.
A piano standing silent
always makes me so melancholy.
It's silly, I know.
If it's "Clair de Lune" you want,
it's "Clair de Lune" you shall have.
Yet, even as
their affection grows,
the pair are unaware
Clara's fiendish husband,
Claude, is plotting her death.
My accursed wife has more
lives than a damn cat.
She dies tonight.
Don't move.
Oh my goodness!
Your studio, Keyworth Pictures,
has the most incredible back catalog.
Noir thrillers,
wartime romances,
caper comedies.
An unrivaled collection
of heritage media.
By "heritage," you mean old.
I mean, uh, vintage.
You have a great reputation.
Fifty years ago, yes.
Look, I know you're trying
to blow smoke up my arse,
but let's be real.
My stages are empty. We're
up to our knockers in debt.
I was in Cannes last week
trying to sell our library to
some streamers, and they were NFI.
NFI? That's a non-fungible...
Not fucking interested.
The Keyworth brand
is not what it was.
We're going under, and
everybody knows it.
Well, I believe with
your prestige content...
Please don't call it
content. Makes me heave.
Okay. Okay.
I'm... I'm sorry.
Prestige movies.
Dreams. Classics.
Like Hotel Reverie.
"I'll be yours forevermore."
My father's favorite.
And mine.
But try telling
that to the public.
- I think you'll find them...
- NFI.
Well, you know,
what's the point of watching an
old movie starring Ralph Redwell
when you could watch a new movie
starring Ryan Gosling or Ryan...
Reynolds?
Yeah. But they're way
out of my price league.
Well, what if I told you
my company has an affordable way
to take a shuttered
classic, like Hotel Reverie,
and almost instantly recast the lead
with a contemporary Hollywood star?
- We can't...
- Whoa, whoa, whoa!
Who you will be able to afford
because you'll only need
96 minutes of their time.
You're gonna use one
of those AI paint boxes
and deepfake Ryan over Ralph...
What we're proposing isn't fake.
It's real.
Oh, you've intrigued me.
So which Ryan are
we calling first?
Hey, Brandy.
Listen, the studio are chasing.
I'm telling you, I just love
this project for you right now.
We all do.
And, hey, the money
is off the chart.
Call me when you get a
chance. Bye now. Bye-bye.
No.
Whoa now. Did you read the material?
Lola's in almost every scene.
- It's a big role.
- It's a big supporting role.
Backing up Mr. "Lead
Dude" again.
Hey.
You get lead roles.
Yeah, for Sundance misery porn.
You don't want those
roles anymore either?
I'm saying I'm tired of
my only available options
being noble victim
or fuckable sidekick.
I can't control which box
the world wants to put you in.
It's the same box,
and I'm sick of it.
You know I got into
this to be other things.
To express other things.
Like what?
Like something romantic.
This is romantic.
For the lead guy. I
don't wanna be pursued.
Why can't I pursue?
Huh?
I just want
something... magical.
Timeless. Something
I can escape into.
Are you talking career
or personal life?
Both.
Where's my Casablanca?
Where's... where's...
where's my Brief Encounter?
Come on! British
romance. 1940s. Classic.
Like Hotel Reverie?
Yes! Hotel Reverie.
"I'll be yours forevermore."
Is that where that
line comes from?
The iconic final line? Yeah.
Hey, I knew the
line, not the movie.
Weird thing is, this is the second
time this has come up this morning.
- What do you mean?
- The studio. Uh, Keyworth... something.
- They're doing some kind of reboot.
- They're remaking Hotel Reverie?
Yeah, with a high-tech shooting style.
They want an A-lister for the male lead.
- To play Alex? Dr. Palmer? I wanna do it.
- Yeah.
It's a male lead.
So they... they can't flip it?
Have a woman play the lead?
They want a Ryan.
One of the Ryans.
Tell them I wanna do this.
- So I'm afraid Ryan's a "no."
- Which one?
Both of them.
Sorry, did you say that they don't have to
talk British? They... they can be American?
Didn't get that far.
Also, Timothée
Chalamet is unavail.
Chris Hemsworth didn't
connect with the material.
Donald Glover says thanks
for thinking of him,
but he has a family commitment.
- So they're all NFI?
- Sorry?
Is there really not one
A-lister who's curious?
Well, you won't believe this,
but Brandy Friday's team
says she's interested.
Holy shit! Brandy Friday?
She big?
She's... she's huge.
She... she's available?
I tried to explain it's
not the Clara role, but...
Well, could we make
it the Clara role?
That's the thing.
They said she's only interested
if she plays the lead.
- Well, that's just...
- Brilliant.
Ready.
Should I just pretend
it's a normal call?
- Yes.
- Right.
Here we go.
I realize I'm... I'm waiting for it to
ring, but it's not connected, is it?
No.
God, I'm such a fool.
Right, I'll imagine
it's ringing.
Hello, Ryce-Lechere residence.
To whom am I speaking?
I...
Oh, God damn it.
Well, it's just so hard when
there's no one on the other end.
Uh, from the top.
Take two.
Hello, Ryce-Lechere residence.
To whom am I...
Buckinghamshire, England.
And an outpouring of grief
as actress Dorothy Chambers
is found dead at home.
The cause of death, an
overdose of sleeping pills.
The reclusive
beauty never married
and was well known to be
troubled by pernicious gossip
surrounding her personal life.
- Oh, hi.
- Hey.
- This is for you.
- Thank you.
- It needs a signature just here.
- Oh, sure.
Sorry, I shouldn't, but
I really loved that movie you were
in about the secret CIA agent.
- Thank you.
- He was so good.
- Are you still with that actor...
Uh, no, we're not
together anymore.
Oh, he was so good in that movie
about the pilot that saves the...
- I've got to take this.
- Okay.
Don't let the gate hit you.
Hey.
Great news. You got it.
Got what?
The lead in Hotel Reverie. I
guess they're gonna flip it.
- Yes!
- Okay, so look.
It's a straight offer, so they're
sending the materials to you.
Oh, yeah, I think
I just got those.
They say they're gonna need
you in the studio next Monday.
- That's in England.
- Wait. They start filming next Monday?
Uh, no, they say no.
It's some kind of test.
Who's playing Clara?
Seems confidential.
It's all laid out
in that info pack.
Pepe from Streamberry is here.
- Thank you.
- Wait.
Laid out where?
Yeah, oh, congratulations again.
Okay, look, I gotta go. Bye, bye, bye.
Okay, thanks.
Drop your weapon.
Shoot him. He's
trying to kill me.
Wait. I know that man.
He diagnosed my allergy.
Arrest the other man.
Non!
Non! Laissez-moi.
Mais laissez-moi.
Stay with me.
Promise me you'll stay.
I'll be yours... forevermore.
I'll be
yours forevermore.
I'll be yours forevermore.
What is
up with the printer?
I just need to
get this up and running.
There we go.
- Powering up in a few minutes.
- Jack.
Give me
two seconds. Um...
- Jack.
- Yeah?
No liquids near the tech.
Isn't that your mantra?
Oh...
Sorry.
- She's late.
- Her driver said she's stuck in traffic.
You've only got this
stage for two more hours.
It's leased to some Swedes who are
shooting a loo roll commercial.
You said we had three hours. No?
I said I'd ask for three.
Hey.
- Hi.
- Uh... Ms. Friday.
Judith Keyworth.
Goodness, can I tell you
how thrilled we are
that you're doing this?
Oh, it's my pleasure.
I love old movies.
I'm sure.
Meet the young lady who I've
entrusted with my studio's life.
Uh, Kimmy. Project leader.
Um, and can I just say I've been
a fan of you since Zodiac Suite?
You saw Zodiac Suite?
I did. Off-Broadway
when I was back in NYU.
- Oh wow.
- And I loved...
- Yes.
- Anyway.
Anyway. Yes.
We, uh... Let's... let's,
uh... Let's dive on in.
Okay.
So you know the
ReDream, how it works?
Re-what?
Uh, ReDream. The system
that we're using.
You got the info pack, right?
The info pack? I...
- You got the script and the movie?
- Read the script. Watched the movie.
There was a USB stick in there,
too, with the info pack on it.
You... you didn't see that?
Uh, no.
- Uh...
- Talk me through it.
What exactly am I looking at?
Do... You know
your lines, right?
Sure.
Come with me.
We're making the movie
right now, in real time,
like theater.
ReDream is the
system we're using.
It ingests a movie and all
of its surrounding material.
Screenplay, casting
reels, dailies, all of it.
It creates an entirely self-sufficient
fictive dimension in which we immerse you.
- Can you slow down a little bit, please?
- Yeah.
I bet this is very overwhelming.
Why don't you lie down? Lie down
and make yourself comfortable.
So, if you hold still, I'm just
gonna attach this mesmerizer.
"Mesmerizer"?
Yeah, it's a nickname
for a synaptic fictive interface.
It's... whatever.
- I don't know what you're saying.
- Yeah.
Um, when you're in there,
everyone and everything except you
will be in stasis until the titles,
which should give you a minute to adjust.
Adjust to what?
You're a pro.
Just say your lines,
hit the story beats.
If we get too far off
arc, we'll pull you out.
That won't happen,
though, you know?
Okay.
Executing runtime.
And... syncing realms.
Oh my God.
Okay, how we doing in there?
I'll be giving you direction. Brandy?
This is insane!
I mean, is this the
original movie set?
Yeah, it's a little
intense in there at first.
Oh, you think?
I'm in black and white! Uh...
Look, we've got about 90 seconds
until we roll the credits.
So... head for the table,
the one with the newspaper,
behind the piano.
- Like in the opening scene?
- Exactly.
- There's, like, frozen people?
- Yeah.
They'll unpause when
the titles start.
And when they do, just remember
that, to them, this is real.
They think that they're real
people living in a real world.
- So who are they gonna think I am?
- Alex Palmer, Doctor of Tropical Medicine.
Who's a middle-aged
British white guy?
Right, that's not
who they'll see.
They will see and
hear you as you are,
and they'll just accept
that you're Alex Palmer,
the character in the story.
Okay, so to them,
Dr. Palmer is a Black woman
just rolling up in 1940-whatever,
and it's just fine?
That's fine.
It's fine?
Yes, that's fine.
It's fine.
They're AIs.
They're... they're constructs.
They only know the parameters of
the story and the character names.
I know it sounds crazy. It
won't even cross their minds.
Okay.
Just, uh,
keep the story going.
If you say your
lines, we're all good.
Good luck.
Get the newspaper.
Okay.
Arc ready.
Feedback ready.
Supervision ready.
Forecasting ready.
- Prep titles.
- Prepped. Simulation running.
Five, four,
three, two, one.
And action.
Titles rolling.
Exterior, hotel, night.
Clara, inbound.
Yes, it's Dorothy
Chambers. Stop staring.
Clara speaks
in three, two, one...
Excuse me.
Oui. What do you want?
May I have a seat at your table?
It's awfully crowded in
here. I was hoping...
I do not understand.
- Which seat do you wish to take?
- Keep the paper up, Brandy.
Perhaps that one.
That one is for
mon petit Bonbon.
Oh.
Bonbon does not sit on the
ground. Do you, Bonbon?
Okay, Brandy. You're up.
Live dialogue
in three, two...
Ma'am?
I have a spare seat.
And I can assure you, no Bonbon.
I couldn't impose.
I could use the company.
It's a very different
flavor than dear old Ralphy.
- Alex Palmer.
- Oh. Clara Ryce-Lechere.
Ryce-Lechere? That's
half the alphabet.
All in sync.
She's word-perfect.
Lechere comes courtesy of
my husband, who's French.
Story on track.
Pierre Lechere?
Claude. Sorry
to disappoint you.
Will Claude be joining us?
No, no. Claude has
work commitments.
He holds an important
role in the business.
- The business?
- Oh, my father's business, Ryce Holdings.
Oh my. I didn't realize
you were the Clara Ryce.
Oh yes, the Clara Ryce,
heir to the Ryce empire.
- Exposition delivered.
- What brings you to Cairo?
I'm giving a talk at
the School of Medicine.
- You're a surgeon?
- Just a doctor.
Albeit one who knows an absurd
amount about tropical diseases.
Backstory deployed.
Hitting all her beats.
Dreadful, yes. Accomplished,
I'm not so sure.
Oh, waiter. Another scotch,
please. And for yourself?
Thank you. A Black Rose.
Ah. A rose for a rose.
- Attraction building.
- It's a tradition for me.
One scotch and one Black Rose.
For the heiress?
- Murder attempt number one imminent.
- Yes.
Black Rose created. I repeat,
Black Rose has been created.
- Oh dear.
- What's wrong?
Oh, nothing really.
Just the piano.
A piano standing silent always
makes me melancholy. Silly, I know.
Say a pianist walked in right
now. What would you have him play?
"Clair de Lune."
Oh, that's easy.
- My dad's favorite.
- Debussy?
Do you know it? Oh,
it's the most wonderful piece.
It transports me to
the gayest of places.
And at the same time, it's
so sad, so full of yearning.
Well, Clara, if it's
"Clair de Lune" you want,
it's "Clair de Lune"
you shall have.
What... What's she doing?
- Uh...
- Brandy?
What the hell?
You didn't say it
was a real piano.
I thought you could
play the real piano.
No!
- But you played the piano in Zodiac Suite.
- That was a backing track.
She can't stop.
The piano playing sets
up the inciting incident.
Uh, Brandy, you gotta keep playing.
That's the point of the scene.
My God, she's doing "Chopsticks."
Narrative
integrity failing.
We're heading for yellow here.
I take it that
means something bad.
If that one
hits red, it collapses.
Oh, great.
Mika, how
far off base are we?
So, in the original,
the beautiful music makes
Clara choke up with emotion.
She steps outside. Alex
follows. They talk.
It's the encounter that
sets the story rolling.
Can we hit that plot
point some other way?
Maybe, but we've got
an even bigger problem.
Bigger than that?
The poisoned cocktail.
The Black Rose.
Shit.
Clara's supposed to have left before
it makes it to the table, but now...
She's just sitting there.
And if she drinks it, she dies.
- Correct.
- And the whole thing's bollocksed.
Narrative
stress is rising, guys.
Brandy, don't speak. I need you to follow
some instructions to get us back on track.
Stop playing the piano.
Go sit next to
Clara. Now. Go. Now.
Apologize for your poor piano.
I'm afraid I'm a little
out of practice.
It certainly sounded that way.
On the bright side, you seem to have
given Madam "Doglover" a headache.
What a shame.
One scotch.
And a Black Rose.
Just in time. I
could use a tipple.
Do not let her
drink that. Improvise!
- Oh my God. Look.
- What?
- Uh, the big... goose.
- No.
Get rid of the drink.
- But I don't see anything.
- Right there. See? Look.
- Was there really a goose?
- Yes.
No. There wasn't.
No, there wasn't.
- Mm-mm. I was kidding.
- I see.
Another joke, I presume.
Gotcha.
I don't appreciate
mockery, Dr. Palmer.
I had quite enough of
that in my school days.
- Good luck with your talk.
- Attraction falling, guys.
Don't let her go.
Follow her.
Uh, wait!
Uh, come back!
Wait! I... I'm s...
Dorothy!
Clara! Her name is Clara.
Divergence rising.
Uh, Clara.
Why did you call me Dorothy?
Oh dear.
Uh, you remind me of someone.
Someone named Dorothy?
Yeah.
Why do I remind you of her?
- They're way off script here.
- Sh, sh!
She was
someone who the
world looked at and
assumed had everything, but
on the inside, she was...
Blue.
I don't know.
But I think so.
Then it's no surprise
I remind you of her.
Follow her
into the garden.
Sit beside her.
I was going to.
Going to what?
Oh, I was going to... to ask
if you wanna talk about it?
Oh, no.
One should never unburden
oneself to a stranger.
Oh, it's no burden.
Trust me, I'm a doctor.
And I've given up on my
dreams of piano playing.
Well, I
think that's wise.
I would talk to my
husband about it, but honestly,
Claude stopped noticing my
temperament some time ago.
He's so consumed
by the business.
Papa used to joke that Claude
was marrying the company
rather than marrying me.
If that's true,
then Claude's crazy.
You're sweet.
Romantic interest rising.
This
Dorothy you mention,
what's true of her
is also true of me.
You know, it's silly, but sometimes a
sense of such wretchedness seizes me
as though I'm connected to some
fathomless sorrow reaching through time.
Perhaps I was a tragic
figure in some other life.
I thought you said they
weren't self-aware.
They're not.
The... the only reality she's
aware of is... is the story.
Actually, I think she might
be sensing some echoes.
Well, our Clara AI
is derived from the original
performance by Dorothy Chambers. Uh...
And Chambers drew
on her own life.
She sunk as much of herself as
possible into the role of Clara.
There's echoes of her running
right through the data set.
But when she heard her name,
connected with that essence,
she's grown a dimension.
And... and it's not really
built to accommodate that.
Scene ending in T-minus
30 seconds, guys.
This Dorothy,
what happened to her?
- We lost touch.
- Oh.
I hope she's happy somewhere.
Me too.
Look at me complaining
about my life.
You must think me so ungrateful.
Oh, no. I've been there.
- "Been there"?
- I mean, I get it.
Oh, you... you "get it."
Yeah. You know, life shit.
- No one says "shit" in the movie.
- Oh my God. I mean, um...
"Life shit"?
She's saying it now.
I... misspoke.
No, I'm not...
I'm not offended.
If anything, it's refreshing.
I've never met someone so
differently alive.
Romantic likelihood increasing.
Good night, Dr. Palmer.
Good night.
Forecast good.
We're back on track.
Narrative
stress falling.
Interior. Lobby.
Continuous.
Gorgeous Claude.
Darling.
Claude.
This is the scene with Claude.
Brandy's not on screen for two
minutes, so you're free to talk.
Me too.
I'm somewhat tired.
Uh, think we're good.
Brandy, thank you.
Um, the camera's not
on you right now,
so catch your breath.
Hey, you
guys saw that, right?
I mean, that was insane.
Are you sure she's a...
computer person or whatever?
Because she... she touched me.
- It was weird. I don't...
- Uh, mm-hmm.
I've just seen my wife,
who is most terribly alive.
You were supposed to serve
that special Black Rose.
Oh no.
I did, boss,
but she never drank it.
Never drank it?
Guys? Oi!
What is it?
Bonbon's
drinking the cocktail.
Oh.
Shit!
Just a moment, Brandy.
Non!
Bonbon!
Il est mort!
Dead dog confirmed.
I repeat, dead dog confirmed.
We have a plot hole forming.
Can... can we plug it?
Okay, so Madam Roban was supposed to
steal the cocktail and drink the poison...
This poor lady is dead.
...which means Inspector
Lavigne gets called to the hotel
and asks Alex to sign
the death certificate.
And Alex sees Inspector
Lavigne sneezing
and diagnoses him with
allergies to his own cologne.
Which sets up the beat for the
final scene when the police burst in.
Lavigne recognizes Alex and
tells his men not to shoot.
He diagnosed my allergy.
- But then they won't have met before.
- So the police will just shoot her.
That's horrid.
Yeah, I've got it here.
Uh, so that's gonna
tank the whole thing.
So it's over, isn't it?
No. We... we can reset.
We can try it again.
From scratch?
No, we can't.
There isn't any time.
They've got to get in and start
building some gargantuan toilet by noon.
I'm sorry.
Jack, pull her out.
Okay, everybody. That's
a wrap, I'm afraid.
- Um, it's still going.
- Jack, just pull her out, please.
Uh, yeah, we may have an
operational issue in that regard.
What?
Uh, well, the expansion
of Clara's character
seems to have triggered a stack overflow,
causing the exit code to, um, misbehave.
"Misbehave"? As in, how?
The extraction routine is
non-responsive at this time.
- What?!
- So you can't pull her out?
Not until she gets to the end
credits. If she gets to the credits.
Well, the story's broken anyway. Why
don't you just turn the machine off?
No! No, no. Interrupting
the simulation
while her consciousness
is marooned in there
could cause a catastrophic
synaptic failure in the subject.
He's saying Brandy's consciousness
would be deleted, and she'd die.
What?
Uh, real Brandy
Friday would die?
Well, I mean, there's a 98%
chance of fatality, yes.
Oh, marvelous.
Keyworth Pictures
reinventing vintage movies,
attracting Hollywood stars,
and killing them.
Hey, she's back on-screen
in T-minus 90 seconds.
Maybe we should get her...
What about the Lavigne plot hole?
They'll shoot Alex in the final scene.
Oh Jesus.
That's the end. We have
90 minutes to fix this.
- Crystal, can we find a workaround?
- Yeah, maybe. Will I get a story credit?
No. We'll discuss that later.
That's fine. Uh, I'll get to work.
Brandy, we need to
talk for a moment.
Yeah, we do. I know I went
off script, but so did she.
I know I wasn't
supposed to say shit.
- But she kind of laughed.
- Brandy.
I just... I wasn't expecting it.
I wasn't expecting her
to feel so... so real.
- I feel like...
- Brandy.
- We're gonna move on to the next scene.
- Right. Uh...
The next scene is, uh,
Lavigne, the cop guy.
- Whoa, whoa, whoa.
- To sign the lady's death certificate.
But he's sneezing. And
then I'm supposed to...
There's been a change of plan.
Change of plan, how?
Um...
Madam Roban did not drink
the cocktail. Her dog did.
Oh, the dog died.
- Wait, the old French lady's still alive?
- Yes.
- Wait. So the cop guy scene can't happen?
- We're working on it.
No, we gotta reset. We gotta start
over. We gotta get the story right.
So the thing about that
is, um... we can't.
Can't, how?
We're experiencing a slight
technical difficulty,
um, which means that we can't extract
you until the narrative arc is complete,
as in, the credits roll.
- I'm stuck here?
- Until you bring the story to a close.
So I have to make it to
the end of the movie?
Yes. You say to Clara your
final line, "Yours forevermore,"
credits roll, we
pull you on out.
- What if I can't make it that far?
- Let's focus on where we are.
Uh, it's day two.
Clock's a-tickin'.
Day two? What does that...
Clara goes sightseeing.
You ask to accompany her.
Okay, yeah. That's...
Scene change in ten...
New story day inbound.
Brandy, you're gonna feel
a time jump at any moment.
- Feel, how?
- It might be a bit of a rug pull.
Time and space change instantly with
the edit. Being, like, teleported.
- What do you mean "teleported"?
- New story day.
Interior. Hotel lobby. Morning.
The scene is on.
It's fully populated.
A lot of eyes on you. Blink
twice if you understand.
Clara's en route.
Bump into her. Make
it look natural.
- Oh! Sorry!
- Oh!
- Hey, Clara!
- Dr. Palmer.
I'm in the habit of
apologizing to you.
Oh, it's quite all
right. No harm done.
You heading out?
Well, I was planning on
doing some sightseeing,
but Claude's been
called away on business,
so it seems it's going to
be rather a solitary affair.
- Invite yourself along.
- Unless you...
I don't suppose... you would want to
accompany me, would you, Dr. Palmer?
- Palmer's supposed to ask her that.
- Shit.
I'm sorry. It's
rather forward of me.
She's gaining agency.
What's wrong with that?
Actors love agency.
Yeah. I think it
adds something to it.
- So why did you say "shit"?
- I said, "Shit, yeah."
No, I'm just happy you asked.
So what sights are we seeing?
All that Cairo has to offer.
Um, you're gonna
experience some dissolves.
Uh, there's a montage coming up. It
might make you a little nauseous.
- So looking forward to seeing Cairo.
- I can't wait.
Hang on in there.
No, because then there's no
time for the... the scene
when, uh, Alex overhears
Claude talking to Otto.
Fuck!
I could do this for hours.
I had the
most magical day.
Yeah, that was a trip.
You do say the funniest things.
I couldn't have asked for
a more agreeable companion.
- Me either.
- You mean "neither."
But I said "either."
Don't debate grammar.
Thanks for asking me along.
There's no need to thank me.
At all.
Here's where
she twists her ankle.
Oh God!
- Oh God.
- God. Are you okay?
Damn my damned heels.
Help her to her room.
I know!
I know you'll need help
getting to your room.
- Oh.
- Here.
Seduction scene next.
Oh, not at all.
Okay, so here's where, uh,
you ask to check her leg,
and things get a
little... heated.
That was quite
the fall you took.
Maybe I should check
if it's swollen?
Um, well, go gently on me.
I'll do my best.
How does this feel?
Oh, that
doesn't feel bad at all.
That's a good sign.
Will I still be able
to join the Bolshoi?
I think so.
Perhaps to make certain, you
might try a little bit higher.
Like... here?
That's good.
How about here?
Is that
tender?
Ever so tender.
A tad fruitier
than the original.
Uh, that'll be the ice I
ordered for the swelling.
Mm.
Second murder attempt imminent.
I swear I just ordered the ice.
Well, it would be a
shame to waste it.
Are you sure?
Champagne in my room with a stranger.
I'd never survive the scandal.
Gosh, how
I yearn to be free.
This is your
scorpion moment.
Don't move.
Hmm?
Oh my
goodness!
Oh, I daren't even think what might
have happened if you hadn't been here.
Oh, Alex.
Romance levels peaking.
Uh, yeah, that...
that is peaking.
She wasn't like
this with Ralphy.
No.
Oh shit!
- Data feed down.
- We've lost picture.
- Time code borked.
- Live feed down.
No! Fuck!
- I'm sorry.
- The coffee, Jack. The fucking...
My heart is pounding
like a drum.
I feel as if the whole world
has somehow stopped turning.
So do I.
What is it?
Do you hear that?
It's silent.
So it is.
- I'm sorry! I spilled my coffee.
- Brandy! Brandy, can you hear me?
Brandy!
God damn it!
- Oh.
- Who is that?
It's Otto.
Your husband's henchman
kind of guy. Oh, wait.
You're not supposed to know
that. Forget I said that.
Claude doesn't have henchmen.
Why isn't he moving?
They must be resetting.
"They"?
- No, no. I...
- Can you fix this?
- Can I have... Towel!
- I told you about the coffee, dude.
I don't understand.
Kimmy?
- Alex?
- Kimmy?
Alex, I...
Wait.
- What's going on?
- We've lost connection.
- But it's still running.
- Sure, but she is stuck in the simulation.
So she could die? Be honest.
- No.
- Maybe.
If you had to put
a percentage on it?
Fifty-fifty?
She said be honest!
Hello?
Guys?
Kimmy, can you hear me?
Kimmy?
Who's Kimmy?
Madam Roban.
She's... she's still alive.
She's supposed to be dead, and
the story's all messed up now.
- You're... you're frightening me.
- Guys?
G-Guys?
Kimmy, it's not cool to
leave me hanging like this.
- Please tell me what's happening.
- Guys?
- Alex?
- I'm not fucking Alex!
I need to speak to Kimmy, okay?
I'd... I'd explain,
but you won't get it.
How do you know
what I won't get?
The world's broken, and
they're gonna have to reset it.
You... probably won't
remember any of this.
The movie is over. I
repeat, the movie is over!
- What movie?
- The...
Oh my God. This whole
world's a movie.
No, it's not.
Look around.
Yeah. It's not even in color.
I don't know what you mean.
See this banana?
Not yellow.
This orange?
Un-orange.
That's a perfectly
normal orange.
So what color is this apple?
The same color an
apple always is.
Red or green?
See? None of this is real.
You're not real.
I... No, I'm... I'm
as real as you are.
Do you remember being a kid?
Do you have any childhood
memories at all?
I...
You mentioned your dad earlier.
Can you describe
what he looks like?
Anything about him?
- You can't.
- I...
You don't even know his face
because he's not in this movie.
I don't... I don't
like this game.
No, that... that's exactly it.
It's a game.
It's... "let's pretend."
It's a performance.
You're a performance!
No.
Stop it. I'm...
When I called you Dorothy earlier,
she wasn't someone I knew.
She was you.
The real you.
She's an actress.
Or... was an actress.
Dorothy Chambers?
You're a role she played.
No.
No, no.
Shit.
Hey.
Uh, I'm sorry I yelled
at you back there.
This... whole thing's just
really hard to explain.
This is all a story
in a computer.
Or, uh...
Or I... I guess think
of it like a play
in the brain of a machine.
For now, the movie's stopped...
for the moment.
I don't know why.
Maybe some technical problem.
I know I said you weren't real.
But I'm kind of not either.
My name's not Alex. It's Brandy.
I'm like you.
I'm an actor.
They... they hired me to...
recast this whole thing.
I don't know if
any of this makes
any sense to you?
But, um...
I'm really sorry.
Wait. So the story's on
hold, but time's still advancing?
Yeah, the chronographic
tempo's way out of whack.
Which means?
It means time in there for her is running
a lot faster than it is for us out here.
Faster, as in?
As in six, seven hours a second.
Does that mean we have
to pay her for more days?
- Clara?
- I thought you said I was Dorothy.
Sleeping in the lobby
makes you look like a hobo.
I tried the doors. None
of them have insides.
They're not part of the
story. Where are you going?
To find a way out.
- I'll come with you.
- No, you won't.
Something just
breached the fringe.
What?
There it is again.
Is it Brandy?
I think it might be Clara.
- Clara?
- Yeah.
She... she would've been
exposed to the full data pool.
I guess.
Do we think that's... bad?
Yeah. Yeah, that's...
Oh no.
- You seriously have to fix this.
- You seriously have to let me.
Stop.
Look, I may not be real, and you
may not be who you say you are,
and this entire existence might
be a meaningless pantomime, but
if you and I are going to
be stuck here together,
then I'm not going to let you
defile that piano one moment longer.
Go on, budge.
Sit over there. Watch and learn.
Come on,
come on, come on!
I think I've got something.
Uh...
- Oh my God.
- Whoa. What's that?
- Clara...
- Okay.
Why is Clara at the piano?
- That's not in the script.
- What is that?
What is she doing?
Oh, uh...
- What?
- What? Oh God.
- Ready?
- I'm ready.
- Morning.
I love you.
Mm-hmm.
"Mm-hmm"?
You know I do too. I...
Phew.
I just...
I wonder...
What do you wonder?
Do you think you love me because
Clara was written
to feel that way?
About this person
she met, this...
this Alex Palmer.
But you're not Alex Palmer.
- We have got a save state!
- Thank God!
Chronographic
tempo restored.
I think we can
reinstate comms too.
- I can talk to her?
- Voice only.
We won't have a
visual until we reset.
Brandy?
- Kimmy?
- Oh, thank God!
Brandy? What is it?
It's them.
- Them?
- As in "them."
You mean the people
on the outside?
Look, we had a hardware issue.
We're just gonna have to pick
it up from where we were.
Where we were? As in...
The... the scene
in Clara's hotel suite.
The kiss after the scorpion.
Bit of time has passed for her.
Wait, we're going back to...
Resetting the
scorpion scene, yes.
Uh, wait, Clara's here, and she
knows who I am, and we've been...
No, don't worry.
Um, she won't remember anything
that occurred after the save point.
Okay. Save state prepped.
She won't remember?
No, just back to the
film like nothing happened.
What won't I remember?
Um, you ready?
Reloading save
state in five. Four.
- Link reestablished.
- Three.
Two.
- One.
- Wait! No, no, no, no!
My heart is pounding
like a drum.
- Yes!
- Great.
Oh, thank God.
She's got dialogue here.
Brandy?
You're supposed to
say, "As is mine."
Brandy?
As is mine.
I feel as though the whole
world has stopped turning.
"So do I."
The line is, "So do I."
So do I.
Oh my word.
I'm a married woman.
I mustn't behave
this way. I can't
feel this way.
"Feel what way?"
Feel what way?
Don't make me say it.
Um, okay, so your
line here is...
You don't have to say
anything you don't want to.
That's not the line.
- What?
- What's going on?
You must go.
You heard her. You gotta go.
I don't want to.
Jesus Christ!
Oh, but you must.
Yes, Brandy.
You really must!
It's part of the story.
I'm so sorry, Dr. Palmer.
So am I.
How we doing in there?
Um, Brandy?
You... you can talk to me.
I'm here.
I need you to focus.
Can you focus?
Look, all you need to
do is keep the arc going
and say your final
line at the right time.
Trigger the end credits.
When the credits roll, we
can extract you. You got it?
What... what if I don't say it?
What?
What happens if I don't
say the final line?
Um, well, you'd
be stuck in there.
For how long?
Forever.
Mm.
And, listen, Brandy,
if that happens,
your actual body out here,
that would die.
But... but my spirit,
consciousness,
whatever, that would...
that would stay here?
With her?
Brandy, what are you asking me?
Nothing.
Good. Don't lose it now.
I won't. What happens next?
Courtyard scene. You
head out for a smoke,
overhear Otto tell Claude
about the scorpion.
- We good?
- Sure.
Uh, head out, light my
cigarette, overhear the bad guys.
What is going on with her?
I... don't know.
Scene 63. Alex
smoking in the garden.
Well, is my
problem taken care of?
No, boss.
The doctor
trapped it in a glass.
Wait. What doctor?
The one attending to her.
Earlier, she fell and
twisted her ankle.
If only she'd snapped her neck.
Look surprised as you overhear them.
This is fresh information to you.
She dies tonight.
Great. Now beat it
back to Clara's suite
before the assholes start
discussing the rooftop plot.
Let's try plan C.
Did you sabotage the
railing as we agreed?
Loosened up nicely, boss.
Excellent.
I'll invite her up there
to take in the view,
then a quick shove,
then my troubles are over.
- Hey.
- Alex.
- Your husband's trying to kill you.
- If this is another of your absurd japes...
My husband may have many faults,
Dr. Palmer, but a murderer he is not.
Darling.
- Who are you?
- Bran...
- Alex Palmer.
- Crystal, how we doing?
- Okay. I have a pitch for the third act.
- Uh-huh.
So, at the end of this scene,
uh, Alex leaves the room,
spots Otto, threatens him.
So then Otto tells Alex
about the loosened railing.
But Alex already knows
they'll be on the roof,
so that beat's actually
sort of redundant.
That's right.
So what if, instead
of chasing Otto,
Alex runs across the street
to the police station,
warns them about Claude,
then she can meet Lavigne?
- And diagnose his allergies there.
- Great.
Do I get a credit?
If it works.
Okay.
- Will it work?
- Don't ask me. You called it "great."
There's no time for notes.
Is there anything I can help
you with, my good doctor?
The doctor was just leaving.
I'll show you out, Dr. Palmer.
- I swear that's the voice I heard.
- That's enough.
- Please, I...
- I want you to leave this room.
And you can leave this
damned hotel for all I care.
I never want to see you again.
My darling.
Okay, so this is where
you'd usually turn left.
Yeah, spot Otto, give chase, get the
info about the rooftop. I've got it.
No, no, no. We have a
rewrite. Uh, new pages.
Okay.
So you have to make a right
and head to the police station.
Across the street?
Demand to speak to the
highest-ranking cop.
- Uh, Lavigne.
- Correct.
All you have to do is tell him
Clara's husband is plotting something.
- He won't believe you, but...
- But he'll sneeze.
I'll diagnose his cologne allergy,
and he'll remember me for the finale.
- Yeah, that works.
- But hurry, okay?
Okay, it's creating a new scene.
Interior. Police station. Night.
Just a dog?
Bonbon was not just a dog.
And he was murdered.
Oh no, Madam Roban!
I forgot she was still in play.
- Oh.
- Damn it!
Brandy, just ignore the
French lady. Jump the line.
I need to speak to
your most senior inspector here.
Please wait your turn.
Madam was here first.
And I am reporting a murder.
Yes, of your poor sweet dog.
- That's right.
- That's why I'm here.
It is?
No, it isn't.
Yes, I know the man responsible
for murdering Bonbon.
- Bonbon?
- Madam's dog.
You do?
Yes. The most dangerous maniac.
And who is this maniac?
I'll only tell your most
senior inspector here.
What's all this?
Explain yourself.
Four minutes.
Brandy, just
summarize and split.
This woman's dog has been
murdered by Claude Ryce-Lechere.
He's about to kill his wife.
He's been trying for days.
What are you talking about?
Also, I'm a doctor. You're
allergic to your cologne.
Change it, and
you'll stop sneezing.
Okay, listen out
for gunshots, okay?
And remember this face.
Final murder attempt imminent.
Oh, Claude.
Oh, it's so romantic.
Is everything all right?
Yes. It's just, um,
you've been so busy.
I thought it was high time
you got what you deserve.
Darling.
Was that enough?
Uh, mm...
- We think so.
- You can't tell?
Three minutes remaining.
Just head to the roof.
How confident are we?
4.5.
Out of...
- I'll tell you later.
- Seven minutes until end credits.
I chose this spot
so you could enjoy the finest
vantage point in all of Cairo.
You do think of everything.
Indeed, I have.
Why,
oh, look at the pretty oil
lamps of the street vendors.
I can't make them out.
Come a little closer.
Lean over the railing.
I...
It looks a bit dirty.
I don't know.
But it... it also
looks quite unsafe.
Nonsense.
Lean against it.
- I re... I really don't want to.
- I said lean!
Claude, what has got into you?
Just do as I say.
- No, please, no!
- Lean over the railing. Lean!
What?
- Get away from her!
- Not one step closer.
The police station
is across the street.
Pull that trigger,
they'll come running.
Well, that's a chance
I'm willing to take.
Alex, no!
Come here.
I knew something
was amiss with you.
Huh? The good doctor.
Well...
The story arc really
doesn't like this.
This is the end for you both.
You?
What did she do that for?
- I don't...
- Claude's not meant to die.
No, he's not.
Police inbound.
Shit, they'll arrest Clara.
What will happen
if they do that?
So they cuff Clara, and they
haul her away on a murder charge.
But Alex can still say the last
line as they drag Clara away.
- That should trigger the credits.
- So it... it becomes a tearjerker?
Young love destroyed when one
of them winds up in the slammer?
I... I don't know. It's
different, but it works.
- A bit ahead of its time.
- It gets her out of there.
I killed him.
- Brandy, new ending.
- I killed him.
- The cops are coming.
- The police are coming.
- They'll arrest her.
- They'll arrest you.
- Let them.
- Yes, let them.
And then what happens?
She goes to jail. So what?
- For how long?
- From her perspective, forever.
But she's not fucking
real, so who cares, Brandy?
I was born in a cage.
I should die in a cage.
I...
No!
- Uh...
- What are you doing?
- We tell the police I shot your husband.
- No.
They'll arrest me.
- Believe me. It is the best way.
I won't let them.
Story arc is critical.
I love you.
And I love you.
Forgive me.
Clara, no!
- What are you doing?
- Stop!
Stop, or I shoot.
Drop your weapon.
Wait. I know this person.
He's a doctor. He...
No!
Oh God.
No. No.
Don't cry for me.
Remember me.
Arc closing?
Her body's
going into shock.
I can't extract till she cues
titles. She's gotta say the line.
Say the line, Brandy.
Say the line.
No!
Brandy.
Brandy, say the line.
Say the line, Brandy.
I'll be yours
forevermore.
- We have an ending.
- Extracting.
Do you think
it worked? The ending?
Did it for me.
Roll credits.
Not a dry eye in the house.
Last century,
Keyworth Pictures invited
guests to Hotel Reverie.
Now, with the help of ReDream
and our friends at Streamberry,
we'd like to welcome you back.
You might notice a few
changes in the old place.
Renowned Dr. Alex Palmer encounters
tragic heiress Clara Ryce.
Waiter, another scotch,
please. And for yourself?
Thank you. A Black Rose.
A rose for a rose.
A piano standing silent
always makes me so melancholy.
It's silly, I know.
If it's "Clair de Lune" you want,
it's "Clair de Lune" you shall have.
Yet, even as
their affection grows,
the pair are unaware of Clara's
fiendish husband, Claude,
plotting her death.
My accursed wife has more
lives than a damn cat.
She dies tonight.
Don't move.
Oh my goodness!
So I... I just pretend it's
a normal telephone call?
Well, yes.
Right
you are, Capt. Keyworth.
I'm... I'm here waiting
for it to ring. It...
but it's not connected, is it?
No.
Hello,
Ryce-Lechere residence.
Hi.
Who's this?
A... friend?
Do I know you?
Yes and no.
What an intriguing answer.
Well, tell me more.
How much time do you have?
Since you've got a kind voice...
I've got all the
time in the world.