My god!
Wow, look at us.
We were so happy then.
What happened to us?
I blame you.
I think it's your fault.
- Happy anniversary.
Happy anniversary.
- Save it for tonight.
- What?!
- Yeah.
- I'll make some coffee.
Okay, that's great.
You can stay here and
look at more pictures of me.
Does anyone know how
autonomous drone insects
help with flowers?
Anyone? Tisha.
Polarization.
Almost. Very close.
Pollination.
So the adis buzz from flower to flower
and spread pollen,
which is the same way
organic bees used to do.
And the technology
around this is amazing.
That's it.
Class is over.
Happy weekend, everybody.
- Bye.
- Bye-bye. Bye-bye, see ya.
Hey, Eva.
Everything okay? What's up?
It's tisha again.
She laughed at my shoes.
We can't afford new ones.
These were my sister's.
Tisha says they're old.
They're not old. They're vintage,
which means they tell their own story.
And that is cool.
Okay, I guess so.
All right. Have a great weekend.
- Bye.
- Bye. Who has the coolest shoes?
I guess me.
- Hey, cool shoes.
- Thanks.
Amanda, are you coming for a drink?
- Yes, you are, is the answer, but…
- well, the problem is I can't.
Come on, I could use the moral support.
I would love to come. Really, I can't.
Why not?
That's why not. Our anniversary.
He's taking me away for the weekend.
- Guten tag, ladies.
- They're back.
They were at the back
of your sock drawer.
I really tried my best to never
see them again, but here we are.
It's tradition, isn't it?
Got the suede shorts, but I didn't think
I should wear them around the school.
Are you taking her somewhere nice?
God, no. No, same old shithole.
- Where we got married.
- All right, have a good time, you guys.
- Thank you. Bye.
- Bye.
Be safe out there.
I'm so excited. Happy anniversary.
The minute your brain
tries to think about it,
it can't think about it.
Still the same sign as ever.
You think Phyllis is still
working the desk? I hope so.
I hope she's not, actually.
Do you remember when Janice
got up and started singing?
Your maid of honor?
Yes. Would she remember?
Do you think she was drunk?
- My god.
- And one Juniper brat burger.
- Jeez Louise.
- One more Juniper brat burger.
Thank you, Polly.
- Wow.
- Yeah, sure. Knock yourselves out.
- Thank you. Thank you?
- It hasn't changed.
They have really outdone themselves.
- Ooh!
- Look at that.
- Ready?
- Yeah.
Three, two, one.
That's dense.
I like when my food fights back.
Wow. He's sweet.
I hope they're an item.
He's more committed than ever before.
Look.
The old piece of gum is still here.
Hello, our little friend.
Who stuck you up there?
We all know how you feel.
What's with the sex yoga?
Apparently, this helps your
little swimmers find their target.
Are you sure you wanna try again?
This isn't an official try.
But I'm okay with a happy accident.
Okay.
Although, arguably, I'm doing a
lot of encouraging right now, so
I'll encourage you.
- You okay?
- Another headache.
Another fucking
headache. You poor thing.
Lucky for you, it's post-coitus.
Coitus. Nice.
- Can you grab my…
- yeah, I got you.
- Medic… thank you.
- Here you go.
Ooh.
That's… wow.
Made you some coffee, babe.
Babes?
Babe?
Hey. You okay?
I got my period.
Hey, we'll get 'em next time, okay?
- We bought this too soon.
- No, don't do that.
Yeah. I mean, you know
I can't resist a bargain,
but maybe it was bad luck.
Come on, Amanda.
Maybe it still is.
Let's put it on eBay and
just get a couple bucks.
Shut up.
We're gonna need it soon.
After last time, we
don't even… know if I can.
You can.
And you will.
Or my dick will die trying.
- I'm late. I love you.
- Love you.
Mike!
- What?
- Come here.
- What's up?
- We need Shane on the rig.
- Where is he?
- Taking too long on his break again.
All right, you weirdos.
Shane!
Don't be resting.
- Nothing.
- Wait one moment.
Come on. You're taking
the piss. Get out there.
I just threw some coin at
this loser on dum dummies.
- On what?
- Dum dummies.
- You don't know about dum dummies?
- No, come on.
It's so fucking funny.
Desperate people go on here,
and then the audience pays
them to do some dark shit.
- When we reach 20 bucks...
- I don't, I
this guy is gonna drink
his own piss. Look at him.
Look, look. Target reached.
- Fucking sick.
- He's drinking piss.
Jesus Christ.
- I'm supporting the gig economy.
- Don't do it on the work computer.
You're so good at your job, I just
wanna see you do it, you know?
Fuck you guys.
Fucking Americans.
Then the sun's rays travel
millions and millions of miles,
all from space,
and come down and hit the solar panels.
And then, once they hit the solar panels,
they, travel
far
travel… long.
Mike! Mike!
Hey, Mike!
Mike!
- What?
- Hospital's trying to call you.
- Something about Amanda.
- Did they say what it was?
- I don't know, but it sounded serious.
There is no simple solution
due to where it's located and
how long it's been growing.
It's essentially fused
to her parietal lobe.
- Mr. Waters?
- Yeah.
- As I was saying, there's no...
- is she gonna be okay?
I'm sorry. Her prognosis isn't good.
How
sorry, what are you
saying to me right now?
She may never regain consciousness.
No.
No. I mean, come on, look at her.
She's breathing in there. There
must be something you can do.
Even just a few months
ago, I'd have said no,
but now there may be an option.
It's… it's a new start-up.
They have an experimental procedure.
- It's very new, so not without risk.
- Okay.
Their rep was in here just last week.
I can't make a personal recommendation,
but you want me to call her?
Yeah, I want you to call her.
Hi.
You must be Mike.
I'm gay nor from river mind.
Come with me.
Rivermind is a revolution
in neurological science.
How it works is both
high-tech and incredibly simple.
So we take an imprint of the
affected part of her neural structure,
and we clone it onto our mainframe.
So basically, we just…
we make a backup
of part of her brain onto our computer.
And then we remove the tumor
and the surrounding tissue and
wait, wait, wait. Isn't that dangerous?
Well, normally, yeah.
But we made a backup, remember?
And then we replace what we
removed with synthetic receiver tissue.
And then the river mind system
transmits cognitive function
from the backup on
the cloud-based server.
- Allowing her to live her life.
- Okay, has anyb
does this work, honestly?
Has this been tested even?
Yes, it has.
I am living proof.
Wait. What are you talking about?
Do you want me to show you?
Okay, you see me right now, right?
- I do.
- Okay.
Eighteen months ago, this was me.
- Shit.
- I had a terrible accident.
I got a knock to the head
that technically killed me.
So I was… I was lucky to be
one of the first river minders.
- Otherwise, I would not be here...
- are you
I'm sorry. I don't... i… I don't
know how else to say this.
- No, go ahead. Bring it on.
- Are you
tell me. Normal?
- Yes.
Physically, mentally, I.
I am fine.
And my kids say that I am still
the same pain in the ass that I was.
It's really sweet.
- Do you have children?
- Not yet.
Been close a couple of times.
Mike.
This will give you time.
- Yeah.
It will.
Yeah.
So a couple things you need to know.
She's gonna sleep more every night.
One or two more hours.
It's one of the ways that we
help the demand on our servers.
And then she has to physically
stay within the coverage range.
It's kind of like cell service. We're
new, but let me just show you.
So we already have
most of the state covered,
and in the next year or so,
we're gonna roll out
nationwide and worldwide.
How much is this gonna cost?
It's less than you think.
Is it less than we have?
Because it's pretty tight.
Honestly, it's less than you think.
We're really trying to drive uptake,
so our pricing is really reasonable.
And
the surgery is free.
Wow, okay.
- Yes.
- Okay.
And then for the streaming,
we run a subscription model.
So it's 300.
It's 300 a month.
Okay.
Mr. Waters?
She did great. You can see her now.
Hey.
- Hi.
- Hey, babe.
Hi.
Is it really you?
Aw, I'm so happy to see you.
Ditto.
They said I was gone for a couple days.
Yeah, you were.
I came back.
- So you did.
- Thanks to you.
The doctor said I could
go home next week.
Yeah. Yeah, we're gonna get you home.
Missed you.
That nurse said I was a miracle.
You are a fucking miracle.
I am a fucking miracle.
Holy shit! I mean,
I'm, like, really happy I'm
alive, but 300 bucks a month?
Mike, it's a lot of money every month.
Yeah, I know. I know.
But I'm taking extra shifts, and
there's stuff that we can cut back on.
Like… maybe we don't
need that trip to galway.
To see your dad? No.
It says river mind won't roll out
in Ireland for a couple of years,
and dad's a bit of a cunt now anyway,
so that's a cutback I can live with.
Come on!
You know you're going,
like, five miles per hour, right?
You just had surgery on
your brain. I'm being cautious.
Yeah, well, there's cautious,
and then there's, like, this.
You're so pretty when you're alive.
Okay, guys, let's take
a look at our little friend,
our little amphibian.
Don't put your fingers in there
'cause he might think it's food.
- Hey.
Go easy on those. Can't
afford more until payday.
- Go grab me another one.
- Sure.
Guy's pulling out his own tooth.
Yeah!
Look, he swallowed it!
Shit.
Babe.
Sorry I'm late.
Shane knocked over a scaffold.
Amanda?
Shit.
It's June 5th this Saturday.
Okay, and?
And?
Ju… June 5th.
Our anniversary?
- Shit.
- God.
I'm sorry.
I didn't plan anything.
I did though.
We're going to the Juniper.
Okay.
A fun little splurge.
You okay, hon?
- I can drive.
- I'm fine, Amanda.
Just a really long day today.
Yeah. You're doing too many shifts.
Yeah, well, we need the money.
It's not like you can get a second job.
You need to sleep.
Yeah, that's not really my fault.
I know. I know.
I'm not... that wasn't...
that's not what I was saying.
You know, we could
just not go to the Juniper
and save some money, you know?
We promised we'd always
go on our anniversary, babe.
I know, I just… I'm saying
we could celebrate at home.
I need a break, Amanda.
I work my fucking arse off.
- We both do. It's not just you.
- I'm not saying you don't. I'm not s.
- I didn't...
- but I sleep all the time.
- And I'm just a teacher.
- "Just a teacher."
- Not manual labor.
- I see where we're going.
- But that...
- you work hard, Amanda.
- I'm not fucking disputing that.
- I'm not making money
we both work hard!
Nobody is disputing that!
I'm just saying, don't you wanna
have fun in our free time, you know?
Babe? Shit.
Babe, babe, babe?
Sweetheart, can you hear me?
Okay, babe? Babe. We're gonna
get you to the hospital, okay?
All right, wait, wait.
Shit.
Fuck, fuck!
What happened? What happened?
- Why are you driving so fast? Don't…
- I'm not.
Slow down.
What's wrong?
My god.
God.
I understand.
Wow, that must have been
so frightening, you guys.
Yeah.
The good news is there's
no malfunction, Amanda.
- There… wh…
- what?
Did you not just… she blacked out.
- Yeah, it was…
- I thought she was dead.
It's because you passed
outside the coverage area.
- But you said that you checked the map.
- I did check the m
- I looked. It said it was within range.
- You were gonna
what happened was we are
upgrading some of our towers,
and the ones in Palmer county
are on the new bandwidth,
which is part of an exciting
change to river mind's service.
What do you mean, change?
From Monday,
we are introducing river mind plus.
Plus?
A new subscription tier that
has extended coverage, okay?
So it makes great use
of those upgraded towers.
- I'm gonna show you. Stand by.
- That could be good.
- Yeah. We have this…
- here we go. All right, look at this.
This is it.
As you can see, we will be extending
our coverage all over North America.
- So we can travel.
- Yeah.
Yes, if you upgrade, then
absolutely you can travel.
And if we don't?
Then you just stay within
your existing coverage range.
So you're saying that we
have to upgrade to plus
if we wanna leave the county?
Right, yeah.
When we signed up, you said it
was just gonna roll out everywhere.
Yes, it is, with river mind plus.
That's what this is. This is the roll out.
How much is the…
how much is the plus?
So it is $500 a month
on top of the existing package.
So $800 in total.
- 800 bucks a month?
- Yeah.
We can't afford that.
That's not... we can't
you don't have to worry about that.
I mean, if you choose not to upgrade,
you'll just stay on river mind common.
"Common"?
And you will continue to
enjoy experiencing the services
that you already have
at the current price point.
You okay? It's nearly eight
o'clock. Won't you be late?
Yeah. I swear I'm sleeping more,
which was a life goal, but
this isn't like normal sleep.
There's like a… …electronic
whistling in my head.
- You want a coffee?
- Yes, please. God, yes, thank you.
Have you tried Espresso grande?
The beans are roasted slow and
long for a richer, smoother taste.
Can't say that I have.
- Can't say that you have what?
- Tried Espresso grande.
Is that what this is?
What? No. That's just our usual shit.
- So why did you bring up Espresso grande?
- I didn't.
- Wait, what?
- Sh... fucking Shane.
Fucking Shane today.
See you later.
So, at the hive,
the bees pass the nectar
between themselves until it's gooey,
and then they push it into the
wax chamber until it becomes
anyone? Bobby.
It becomes honey.
That's right. Honey.
Kids love honey.
That's why parents love honey nugs.
Whole grain chunks covered
in golden tupelo honey,
the sweetest way to start your day.
Honey nugs from ditta.
And can anyone tell me
something with honey in it?
Mickey.
Honey nugs.
Honey what?
What are… what are those?
The sweetest way to start your day.
Okay, if you say so.
Anyone else?
Bye-bye. Bye.
Bye, sweetie. See you tomorrow.
Hey, Oscar, what's up?
You're kind of quiet today.
You okay?
Well, mom says we have to
move out to get away from dad.
Well,
you know, your mom must
have a very good reason
to even think about
saying something like that.
Yeah, dad gets mad all the time.
That must be really scary.
Yeah, but he says it's mom's fault.
I don't wanna go.
I hear you, Oscar.
Listen,
sometimes we have to do
things that we don't wanna do,
but they turn out for the best.
And the truth is,
families that stay together
bask in the glow of Christ's heart.
For more information on
faith-based family counseling,
visit christsheart.Com.
Okay.
Have a good day.
Long day?
Yeah.
Too long for a happy accident?
Fuck no.
Yeah..
Ride smooth with thirst trap lube.
Available in six flavors,
none of them vanilla.
What did you say?
What?
- What did you just say?
- I didn't say anything.
No, I mean when you
were just talking about lube.
I don't need lube.
Wait, wait, wait, wait.
Why did you just say, "ride
smooth with thirst trap lube"?
What? I didn't… I didn't say that.
Yeah, you did. Yeah, you did, just now.
I know the kind of sex stuff
that I say. I would never say that.
No, no. Sorry.
Fuck of a buzzkill, that.
Hoping for a hard time?
Try manville erectile dysfunction gel.
Side effects may include high
blood pressure and suicidal ideation.
What?
Yeah, that's a commercial message.
Jesus Christ.
As in an advertisement?
It's something that we are trialing as
a part of the evolution of our service.
You must be in one of our test
cells. Let me just check and see.
So you're running ads through me?
You're, like, giving me, like,
commercial fucking tourette's?
Okay, not all the customers
appreciate the messages.
Ads! Those are ads!
- Yes.
- Not messages, ads!
But they are designed
to be contextually relevant
to the situation that you're in.
So they will stand out
less in a conversation.
- They'll be less intrusive.
- That makes them worse.
What's your next trick? You gonna
make my asshole whistle jingles?
- That's not part of our development.
- Can we opt out?
Of course you can.
Yeah, all you need to do
is upgrade to river mind plus.
That is right, Amanda.
- Upgrade.
- We can't afford that.
You people are sick.
Hot, new fall nikes.
Just $200. Now at foot locker.
Amanda?
A quick word?
Sorry. Wait, she said I said what?
What I just told you.
She says that you recommended
Christian family counseling to her son.
And, listen, she's pissed, right?
God.
Like, I mean,
I said it doesn't sound like
something that you'd say.
I didn't think that was happening
during school hours. Shit.
You didn't think what would happen?
Feeling over the hill?
Don't panic. There's hope for you.
Find your mature match at silver swans.
Exclusive dating for the over 50.
I'm 49.
- What?
- And… what the fuck are you talking about?
So she said if I can't stop doing it
that they're gonna have to let me go.
What? I mean, she can't fire you.
What choice do they have?
I can't be around kids.
Amanda
you know, if you lose your job,
we're gonna struggle to even
cover our common subscription.
I know.
We'll work it out.
We'll do something.
I'll do something.
Say goodbye to stomach gas
with debloat's gummies,
our unique blend of simethicone and thc.
Hi, it's gay nor from river mind.
- How are you this morning?
- Hello? Yes, yes.
Yes, thank god.
- You got my payment?
- Yeah.
Can you flick a switch or whatever?
We are processing your
river mind plus upgrade now.
- How long does it take to kick in?
- Should be pretty much instant.
Okay, great.
Ketchup, mustard, and
while I have you, would you
like to hear about exciting plans
fuck no. Hey, babe.
- Hey.
Okay, so you're, officially
on river mind plus.
- What?
- Yeah.
I had a bit more left over
from my overtime and stuff,
so I just… made an upgrade.
- Yeah, okay.
- No more ads?
No more ads. No more ads.
And, hey, now, with the
location restrictions off,
next anniversary,
we can go back to the Juniper.
Aw.
- I wish we could afford it.
- I'll make sure we can afford it.
- Okay, thank you.
- Yeah.
- Love you.
- I love you.
Hey, Oscar. Listen, I just
mom said not to speak to you anymore.
Okay, I'm sorry. Can you tell your mom
I'm not supposed to listen to you either.
- Hey, Oscar. Why don't you come with me?
- Yeah.
Okay, guys.
We've just got 20 more
bucks to reach our target.
And I will put my nose in this mousetrap.
I'm not gonna put it on my dick.
Not doing that either.
Mask stays on.
Fuck.
Okay.
How about… how about this, guys?
How about for $90,
I'll put the fucking
mousetrap on my tongue.
It's 10:00 A.M.
How long have I been asleep?
Like… like, 12 hours.
What?
Jesus.
Thank god it's the holidays.
Thank god.
What's wrong with you?
Bit my tongue.
Why am I sleeping longer?
As a part of our last firmware update,
we did extend the sleep time a little bit.
To 12 hours a night?
Well, everyone can use
a little extra rest, right?
It's not, restful though.
Like, I'm not dreaming.
I wake up tired.
It doesn't feel like actual sleep.
Well, that's 'cause it's sleep mode.
- "Sleep mode"?
- Yeah.
While you're in sleep mode,
our servers are harnessing
your spare processing capabilities
to help with the overall workload.
So you're using my brain
to… to power the server?
Shouldn't it be the other way around?
It is, except when you're in sleep
mode. You can kind of think of it like
giving back to the grid.
Why do I have to give back to the grid?
Why? I mean, we pay for fucking plus.
It's supposed to be better than common.
It's better than common.
Seriously, if you were still on common,
my god, you would be looking at
sleeping at, like, up to 16 hours a night,
and with ads?
I mean, Amanda, I'd be happy
to drop you back down a tier.
No.
Or you could move up
to our exciting new tier.
It's actually the reason
that we have extended sleep
mode for our non-premium users.
We're premium users.
Well, plus is actually now standard.
But it is better than common.
And this new tier, it is ultra-premium.
We call it
river mind Lux.
If you could just turn your
attention to the monitor.
Take a look here. Right?
Ever since my fatal
liposuction procedure,
river mind has been a lifesaver.
And now there's something
even better. Rivermind Lux.
Rivermind Lux doesn't
just keep your brain running.
It heightens your senses.
Meaning sights, sounds, flavors,
even the feeling of this breeze.
In fact, all physical
sensations are simply more
sensational than ever.
And you're in charge.
Dial it up or dial it down.
Take control of your mood
with the river mind app.
And with the exclusive
river mind Lux ability browser,
you can use skills and attributes
sourced from other river mind users.
So if you thought you couldn't
do park our… think again.
Whoo!
Rivermind Lux.
It's life, but not as you know it.
So, if I could have you back over here.
That was pretty cool, right?
Great.
How much does it cost?
It's just an additional $1,000 a month.
Sweetheart, you'll
wanna watch your head.
We can't… we can barely
afford what we're paying now.
I know. We understand
that Lux is a real vip package.
So if you don't choose to
subscribe to the full-time package,
we actually have temporary boosters
for, like, a few hours.
Or a few days.
No? So maybe if you have
a special occasion, Amanda?
- We're not interested.
- Okay.
- Thank you.
- I understand.
How much are those booster packs?
What have you got, dum dummies?
No, I'm not putting one of
my bunny ears up my a-hole.
Okay.
Let's make this fucking quick.
All good?
You feeling okay?
Yep. Free to roam.
Okay!
It's better than that.
- What do you mean?
- Check the glove box.
That's 12 hours of river mind Lux.
You're gonna have a very good time.
Mike, come on. We can't afford this.
I know, I know, I know.
It's one weekend.
I want you to enjoy it.
In fact, I order you to.
Thank you.
Yeah, that's it. You just scratch it.
And then you look at the
code, and that activates it.
Okay, well, I put the app on your phone.
And then you just dial up your pleasure.
Like this?
That's it.
Wow.
Feel it?
Hi!
I like your truck.
Your hand feels so nice.
- Yeah, yours feel nice.
- Like extra, extra nice.
Two Juniper brat burgers.
Thank you.
Cheers.
Three, two, one.
You're in.
My god.
It's exactly as I remember it. That is
that's pungent.
That is just
that's fucking amazing.
Look, they're back. Christ.
Babe.
Amanda.
Hey, you don't need to
do all that for me, baby.
It feels so good.
It's just… it sounds like
you're exaggerating a little bit.
I'm not. Your skin feels so fucking good.
Yeah.
All right, maybe we can
just dial it down a little bit.
Just literally on the app.
- No, no, no, not right now.
- No. Okay. All right.
Jesus Christ. Do you mind
if I just take a little breather?
Okay, okay.
Okay, you...
Jesus.
Babe?
Babe, it's 11:00 A.M.
We gotta check out.
I guess Lux is over, then?
Jack, Jack.
- Man.
- Shit.
Jesus.
Morning.
Hey!
Mikey! If you're gonna live by the
sword, you're gonna die by it, man.
- Okay. Whoa, watch out now, big guy.
- Fucking arsehole.
Hey, just chill, man.
Fuck. What the fuck?
What, it's not so funny now?
Is that not funny now?
Come on, funny man.
- Give us a fuckin' giggle!
- Let him go.
- Prick.
- You're a fuckin' psycho!
Don't fuckin' speak!
Piss-drinking motherfucker!
- Come on!
- Hey!
We're coming, man!
What the fuck are you doing? Back up!
You're home early.
What's wrong?
Mike?
Come on, you're scaring me.
I just got fired.
What?
But you've worked there for ten years.
I fucked up so bad, babe.
How? What did you...
they can't just fire you.
I don't wanna talk about it.
You get fired and don't
wanna talk about it?
Yeah, I don't wanna talk about it.
Wait. So how do we.
I don't… what do we… how do we
how will we pay for river mind plus?
- I don't know.
- I… I can't start running ads again.
They won't let me back in school.
Well, we'll… do you know what? We'll
go to river mind and plead our case.
They won't listen.
Because we're… we're loyal customers.
Yeah.
She knows us. She… yeah.
- I mean, it's been a long time.
- Yeah?
We pay on time.
They have to listen, right?
Yeah.
I am afraid not.
You know, given a little time,
I'm sure I will just get another job.
At Uber, post mates, or whatever.
Great. Yes, that's great.
And when you do,
we will reinstate your full subscription.
I… I'll lose my job
if, if I can't get back on plus.
- Sorry, plus is actually now standard.
- Please!
- … okay.
- We are good customers
we're just asking for a little credit
so we can get back on our feet.
I understand your circumstances, I do,
but the system won't even let me input it.
- Come on.
- Not even if I try. My hands are tied.
Don't make us use the baby money.
There's… there's still baby money?
- I mean, not fucking much, but yeah.
- You didn't tell me.
- Let's not use it.
- I didn't know.
Because if we use it, then
that's it. What's the point?
- Yeah, but...
- that's just giving in.
- Are you trying to get pregnant?
- Surely… yes!
You are?
I mean… we haven't been
trying very hard lately, but
we were hoping for a happy accident.
Okay. But you're not pregnant now.
Why are you asking?
Pregnancy costs extra.
When you're pregnant,
it just alters the brain.
There are cortical shifts and
changes to the ventral striatum.
It's a lot for your brain to
process when you're pregnant.
Like, literally.
So it's $90 a month.
Fuck you!
Hey. We're here for the crib.
I'll get it.
Good luck with the baby.
We're not having a baby.
Then why'd you want the crib?
We're setting it on
fire for our music video.
Hey
hey, babe.
Hey.
How are you doing, sleepy head?
Happy anniversary.
You remembered.
Happy anniversary, babe.
Come with me, please.
I could only afford 30 minutes.
Mike.
- How did you even pay for this?
- Don't worry about it.
You told me you weren't
gonna do any more… tooth stuff.
No, no. It's just
it's a private buyer. It's dum
dummies, but it's a specialist thing.
Don't even think about it. Come on.
I'm just gonna slide
your Serenity up to Max.
I think it's time.
- No, I...
- yeah.
- I think we're okay for a little while.
- It's time.
Only if you're sure.
I'm sure.
Okay.
Do it when I'm not here.
There we go.
Are you comfy, babe?
I love you.
I love you too.
- Are you filled with dread?
- Babe!
Wracked with despair?
Babe? Not yet.
Let the sun shine in with
endorphox antidepressant lozenges.
- Sustained release.
- It's okay.
Endorphox is…
God.
I love you.