What?
- I said, "Are you all right?"
- Yeah, I'm fine.
Maybe you should talk to your
sister. It's an important decision.
- My sister?
- Yes.
- Mark?
- Yeah.
Are you sure you're okay?
Yes. I'm sorry, I just... I
got a little woozy and then...
I'm gonna stop by the bathroom.
Uh-uh. I think
it's the other way.
Right.
I don't know if I hate
senators or congressmen more.
How many of those have you had?
Just this one.
Good. We need you nimble. We gotta
get down there. You're on in 20.
I was on with the Board earlier.
They're really grateful for this.
- Gabby.
- Natalie, hello.
Hi.
Gabby, this is Helena Eagan.
My gosh. Helena, so good
to finally meet you.
Likewise.
This better be
working, assholes.
Where am I?
Mark. You okay, milady?
So Rebeck smells weird.
Rebeck smells weird?
Yeah, she was making chewing
noises, but she was not chewing.
Just be prepared 'cause you might
have to share a book with her.
A book, right.
The one you forgot to bring
even though I did remind you.
Right. Yeah, I'm sure... Sorry.
That's okay.
Okay.
How's our baby?
Our... I'm gonna assume you mean that
in the "it takes a village" sense.
And she's good. She's hungry.
I wanna have the life change talk.
I just need to pump before I die.
- I'll be really fast. Okay.
- Okay.
Hey. Hi. Hi.
"Radar."
What's the thesis?
I agree. It's very confused.
Mark, hello.
Hey, guys. What's up?
- Patton, no.
- Mark,
we were just discussing whether
it might have been a wiser move
for your sister to put off introducing
the child until after tonight's event.
Mark, you don't have
to weigh in on that.
- Obviously the child is an absolute angel.
- Wait... That's my sister? With the baby?
Exactly, it's his sister.
- Excuse me.
- Sure.
Well, that was awkward.
Okay, so my sister has the
baby. And Cobel is here?
I've been asked to
share my book with you.
So I've heard. Rebecca?
Rebeck. I have small eyes, so
I have to read pretty close.
Okay. Well, I'm...
I'm sure that'll be fine.
If you'll excuse me?
And I have some sores on the
back of my head from my bird.
- You might see them.
- Okay.
Hey.
Hello, Mark.
I pumped, so it's Miller time. Okay,
so life change. What's happening?
We're, this is
gonna sound weird…
We're close, you and I?
What do you... What's going on?
Can we talk privately?
- I just have to...
- Okay, my dearest ones,
we are nearing that hour,
so if you'd all peacefully
waft in the living room…
Okay. Let's talk at the
first reflection break.
- Okay?
- Okay.
You just don't realize how much
kids are gonna change your life.
But they do.
- How many kids do you have?
- Just gave birth to my third.
I should've stopped at two.
- Hey, there you are.
- Hey.
- Angelo, great to see you.
- You too.
Helena, this is my
husband, Angelo Arteta.
Helena, nice to meet you.
I've gotta hop backstage.
- I'll see you in a second.
- Okay.
Lovely to see you, Natalie.
- You okay?
- She couldn't find the bottle.
Wow. Three kids.
Couldn't have done it
without a little help.
I mean, the idea that people
would want to outlaw severance.
I know.
The photo display
is very moving.
I already knew how I'd
be voting, but I think...
Well, seeing that and seeing you
and hearing what you have to say,
all of this could really
make a difference.
I hope so.
Let's change some minds.
Well, I'm certainly gonna try.
Thank you.
And please thank your
father if you see him.
I will.
Mark. Come here.
Saved us a seat.
I just have to find my glasses.
Mark, can you just hold that
- for a second?
- Yeah.
Oh, my God.
Sorry, you can't unring
the bell-ringing app apparently.
Okay. Thank you
all for being here.
Before we start,
there is one person
that I would like to
thank first and foremost.
Family is both my bedrock
and my inspiration.
So I dedicate the reading
to my firstborn daughter,
who is here tonight.
Eleanor, I love you.
My brother-in-law.
And with that… I begin.
"It's said that as a child,
Wolfgang Mozart killed another boy
by slamming his head in a piano.
Don't worry.
My research for this book
has proven the claim untrue.
As your heart rate
settles though,
- "consider the power an author…"
- Mark.
Can I look at her book too?
I can crane.
- "…can hold over a reader…"
- Sure.
"…heretofore called 'you.'
But what, indeed, is 'you'?"
Good luck tonight.
It was great to
meet you, Helena.
"How can 'you' mean
different things
to millions of readers
around a vast Earth?
"And perhaps, most
importantly, who are you?"
"All creatures,
from the leaping cat
to the cowering shrew,
think of themselves as 'you, ' a
logical center for the universe.
Yet the cat eats the shrew,
and we, like Schrödinger,
"live on to wonder
what it means."
End of chapter.
Let's all take a
seven-minute reflection
break and then come back.
Balf. Prepare the neti pot.
It was transformative.
I'm gonna have to
change my name again.
What a wordsmith. He seemed to have
a little something in his throat.
- Oh, yeah.
- Hey.
I'm gonna see if she'll
have more bottle.
Give me a couple of minutes,
then meet me in the baby room?
- Okay.
Excuse me.
Mr. Hale... Ricken?
I don't know why my
voice shakes like that.
I sound like a sad
old hamburger waiter
prattling on about sauces.
"Hamburger waiter."
What the fuck is that?
Jesus, why do I ever
open my buffoon mouth?
It's going great.
- I mean, the book is brilliant, and...
- Okay, Mark.
Thank you, but you
don't have to say that.
I'm well aware of how
I come across to you.
What? No, I mean it.
The... Your book, it... It
opened up the world for me.
Mark, are you okay?
Yes. This book
changed my whole life.
You actually read it?
Ricken, are we friends?
Look, I know I sometimes
make you feel "less than"
for having had the procedure.
And I regret that.
You had to deal with Gemma's passing
in a way that was best for you.
You know, I was scrolling through
old pictures this morning,
and I found one of the four
of us on the crest hike.
- You remember the funny bees?
- Do you have that on you? The picture?
Yeah, sure. I should.
- Ricken. The neti pot is warm.
- Thank you, Balf.
Mark, I need to
flush my sinuses.
But thank you. You have no idea
how much this has meant to me.
Mark, I was worried about you.
I'm fine. Thanks.
I'm just going to
check on my sister.
When you hugged me before, you
suddenly became tense. What was that?
I didn't know I did.
Well, you did. You're tense now.
Yeah, sorry, it's just parties.
Did you mean what
you said before?
About your plans.
Of course.
Tell me more.
You know, I'm so sorry. I'm just...
I'm on uncle duty for my sister.
So I'll be right back.
- Okay?
- Okay.
Okay. Thanks, Ms. Cobel.
- I know. Hey, there you are.
- Hey, I really need to talk to you.
No, I know. I just have to deal
with her. She's having a meltdown.
But just meet me in there, okay?
- Okay, I'll just... Wait. Okay.
- I promise I'll be back.
Thank God, Mrs. Selvig. Hi.
Can you take her for a
sec while I talk to Mark?
- Of course, love.
- Thank you.
- Is Mark all right?
- Yeah, he's fine.
Thank you, you're an angel.
Okay… I'm all yours.
My name is Helena,
and I'm an Eagan.
So one of the things you
learn growing up as an Eagan
is that the workers
are our family.
And I remember being
confused about that as a kid,
because I thought that meant
I had a few hundred thousand
literal brothers and sisters
scattered around the world.
Oh, my God.
But as I grew older, I learned
that it's about shared ideals.
My dad used to make me recite
the nine core principles
before bed every night,
which I can't say I always
did happily. Sorry, Dad.
But those are now the values that I
share with everyone who works at Lumon,
and that's what
makes them my family.
And I would never ever
ask them to do anything
that I'm not willing or
excited to do myself.
Look, my dad would
love for me to sit here
and say that I'm taking
this job out of loyalty
and that it was the spirit of
pure Eagan calling me to service.
But I took a severed job because
it sounds freaking awesome.
So, no, I don't think
severance divides us.
I think it brings us together.
Greetings.
- I'm not here right now.
- Goddamn it, Milchick!
Helena.
She's in here, sir.
You look so nice.
Like a film.
Thank you.
Are you…
Are you still in pain?
I'm not.
Not anymore.
I cried in my bed when they told
me what she tried to do to you.
What that innie
tried to do. I...
Thank you for going
through with this.
The Grandfather would
cherish what you've done.
And one day you will sit
with me at my revolving.
Are you feeling well?
Yeah.
I think, I think the drink
just hit me a little bit.
You'll be all right
for the speech?
For my speech. Yeah. Of course.
Do you remember when I brought
home the first chip to show you?
The prototype.
It had the blue and
green lights back then.
Yeah.
I remember you said to me,
"It's so pretty, Daddy."
"Everybody in the whole
world should get one."
They will.
Because of you.
They'll all be Kier's children.
Mr. Eagan. Helena. It's
time to head to stage.
Forgive me for the harm
I've caused this world.
None may atone for
my actions… but me.
And only in me shall
their stain live on.
All I can be is sorry.
And that is all I am.
You swear you're
not fucking with me?
I swear.
This is so insane.
They need to send people down to
check every inch of that place.
Like, inspectors or whatever.
Is that a thing? Inspectors?
Yeah. There are inspectors.
Mark has b... I mean, out here,
you have been trying to figure
out what Lumon does. What you do.
Okay.
I just…
I just want to know why.
Why he put me in there.
He lost his wife.
You lost your wife. A little
before you started at Lumon.
Gemma.
It was a car accident, and, at
first, you tried to keep teaching.
I was a teacher?
A professor. Of history.
You tried to go back to teaching
three weeks after she died,
and it was a disaster.
She was just still in
your veins, you know?
Making everything hurt.
Which is why I guess you
thought the severed job would...
He hoped you'd be
spared from the pain.
It's a nice name. Gemma.
Yeah.
We were all really
close. It was great.
She was wonderful.
She made you wonderful.
They told me not to talk to you.
The goddamn OTC's been triggered!
Mark S. Is his fucking innie!
What? That's not possible.
It's Dylan. They've been
plotting this all along.
Helly's at the gala.
I'll take care of Helly. I'll
fix it like I fix everything.
Get to the security office,
and shut it off now!
Shit!
Goddamn it! Dylan!
Dylan!
I know you're in there,
Dylan. Open the door!
Fuck you, Mr. Milchick!
Dylan! Dylan!
Ricken knows a lot of high-end
journalists in New York.
And you think that's
better than the police?
Well, Lumon has their
hands in so many pies.
Sorry, do you
understand metaphor?
Yeah, hands in pies. I get it.
I think we have to be really
careful about who we talk to.
- Okay.
- How much time do you have?
I don't know. Maybe an hour?
Right. Because once
your bosses find out…
Jesus, I totally forgot.
Cobel! Why is Cobel here?
What?
My boss from Lumon. Ms.
Cobel. She's at this party.
What are you talking about?
I mean, she's dressed different.
Kind of a flowy, purple
outfit, silver hair.
Mark, are you talking
about Mrs. Selvig?
Maybe, but her name
is Harmony Cobel.
And she works at Lumon?
Yeah, she's my boss.
Jesus fucking Christ.
Dylan.
Why are you doing this, man?
Come on.
You are the refiner
of the quarter!
"While most cultures
view sex as ugly or foul,
- "I've always seen it..."
- Mrs. Selvig?
- What?
- Is she there? Is Mrs. Selvig there?
- Do you...
- What?
Mrs. Selvig?
- What is going on?
- She has Eleanor!
What? Excuse me a moment, okay.
Honey? What did you say?
Mrs. Selvig has Eleanor.
Did you see her?
- Oh, my God.
- What is going on?
Oh, my God. Her car's gone.
I gave her the
baby, and she left!
- She left? With Eleanor?
- I handed her the baby,
and she left!
- Have we looked everywhere?
- Not yet!
Okay, let's go inside and look.
Oh, my God!
I bet the tempers
were disappointed.
I can still get
you back in there.
I can get you any
perk you want, Dylan.
Hey, there's stuff you
don't even know about.
There's paintball,
there's coffee cozies.
Dylan, come on!
Just say the word, and I'll get you a
coffee cozy literally right now, Dylan.
Come on, man!
I wanna remember my
fucking kid being born!
You have two others.
I can tell you about 'em.
Open the door, and I'll
tell you their names.
Come on, Dylan.
Dylan!
It's rolling.
My name is Helena,
and I'm an Eagan.
So one of the things you learn growing
up as an Eagan is that the workers…
- We start in two minutes.
- Thanks.
Good luck.
I'll tee you up. Just stick
to the talking points.
Use the line about how you
see your innie as your sister.
- They'll love that.
- Got it.
It's gonna be great.
She's not in the baby room.
Have all these
rooms been checked?
Thank God.
Devon! I got her!
Devon, she's here! I found her.
I found your child.
I'm the one who found her!
Dylan!
…Improvements in morale,
a happier workplace.
As with any transformative
technology, there have been setbacks.
Bumps in the road.
But I'm here tonight to tell you that
we are on the verge of a revolution.
A kind and empathetic revolution
that puts the human being…
- Oh, my God!
- Is it you?
What are you talking about?
It is you, isn't it?
I'm gonna kill your company.
Your company!
Who the hell do
you think you are?
No. Your friends
are gonna suffer.
Mark will suffer.
You'll be long gone,
but we will keep
them alive, in pain.
You're on.
…decided that we
could do better.
He may never have seen a
severance chip in his lifetime,
but it represents his gentle and
elegant vision made manifest.
But why don't we hear from someone who
can tell us all about it firsthand?
Ladies and gentlemen,
our guest of honor,
Helena Eagan.
Thank you, Natalie.
Devon!
My name is Helly R.
I'm an innie.
And everything they've told
you about severance is a lie!
Devon!
Burt!
No, no, no. Listen, we're
not happy. We're miserable.
Burt!
They torture us down there!
Devon! Please!
We're prisoners!
She's alive!
Burt!