[theme music playing]
[Billie] One of my professors once told me
a therapist can't depend on her patients
to be reliable narrators
of their own lives.
[moaning]
Not because they intend to be deceitful,
but because the human condition is such...
that we can want things
to be one way so badly,
we aren't honest
about the way they really are.
We can't be honest with others,
because we can't even
be honest with ourselves.
Hey, sleepyhead.
I had fun last night.
It was super unexpected,
but in like the best way possible.
[sighs]
It was definitely unexpected.
So, not to be weird or whatever,
but The National is playing
Pier 27 on Saturday
and some friends from NYU are going.
You want to come?
You go to NYU?
Yeah, I'm a junior.
Okay.
I'm gonna go make some coffee.
[Brett] Sweet mother of Jesus.
I had no idea your brother was here.
Spence, did you know?
No. Who could possibly think
anyone else was here?
It was so quiet all night.
Mm-hm.
All I heard was the sound of silence.
[moaning]
Ah-ah-ah. All right.
Hey, I'm not complaining.
Sounded like you had yourself
a good old time over and over.
I am complaining
because it is not at all disturbing
to hear your baby brother
getting his rocks off.
[door opens]
You have roommates.
Who's your friend, Cooper?
Uh, this is Summer.
Actually, I'm Autumn.
At least he didn't go with Spring, honey.
No big. I didn't remember his name
'til you just said it.
Ooh. I like her.
See you, Coop.
[door opens, then closes]
So, where did you and Autumn meet?
I think she was my Uber driver.
I hope you gave her a five-star rating.
Cooper, what are you doing?
Making up for lost time.
What does it matter to you?
This is the first time you spent the night
at our house since you split from Billie.
- You got a random teenager with you.
- Okay.
She's in college.
Shower's calling. Go easy on him, Spence.
You remember Francesca,
your "alleged" girlfriend?
I've never met her before
but she texted me last night repeatedly
saying she hadn't heard from you in days
and was worried sick.
- Shit.
- I covered for you,
but you introduced her to your kids.
What happened?
I had a run-in with Billie.
A couple, actually.
Cooper, you need to take time
to deal with the emotional fallout
from your split.
- I am.
- No, you're not.
You walked out on Billie
and ran straight to Francesca,
and you jumped in with both feet
on the same night.
Divorce is a huge loss.
- It's like a death.
- A death I wanted.
Everything I'm doing now is what I want.
Maybe for the first time in my life.
I did the whole
"sex is a salve for your problems" thing,
it works great for 15 minutes,
you feel like the hottest guy.
You forget how much
you fucking hate yourself.
No, I hate her. Not me.
Mm-hm. You've never hated anyone.
You've never had a reason to.
Which means you've lived
a pretty charmed life.
It also means now that things
aren't going exactly according to plan,
you don't know how to process.
I always knew some good would come out
of being a miserable, closeted gay kid
in uber-heteronormative '90s Connecticut.
It was fucking traumatizing.
But I dealt with my shit
so I could show up
for the rest of my life, including Brett.
Good for you.
Whatever you're going through,
just go through it.
Come out the other end like I did.
Try to minimize collateral damage.
It's not fair
to drag Francesca down with you.
Okay, honey, I am gonna miss you so much.
But I hope you have fun with Daddy.
Daddy said he's taking us for sledding
and hot chocolate.
He did?
That's great.
Yoo-hoo! Carpool's arrived.
Do you like my tiara?
It is my birthday tiara
and I'm going to wear it all day
even at my Manhattan spa party.
Are you as excited as I am?
Caroline, I am so sorry,
I don't think I'll be able to make it.
It's been a crazy few days.
Well, Hudson, why don't you
go jump in the car with Hannah,
and I will be right there.
Okay.
- Bye.
- Bye, sweetheart.
I know what happened
with Cooper and Trina.
And I think that you and Trina need to
talk it out in a relaxed environment.
Like a spa.
- No.
- You can't avoid each other forever.
Not in Greenwich, anyway.
Besides... it's my birthday
and I want my two besties
there to celebrate me.
Pretty, pretty, pretty, please.
Okay, fine.
Yay!
Oh, P.S., I saw the news this morning
about your sexy ex.
It's so sad what's happening to him.
What are you talking about?
The lawsuit.
What?
Oh.
I mean, at least it's a nice picture.
He is so photogenic.
Sash, what's with the getup?
This is what it's like when you're
top of Twitter's 10 Most Hated.
One second I'm talking
about Kam's magic penis
and the next, I'm anti-feminist?
It's ridiculous but it'll blow over.
- It's a 60-second news cycle these days.
- Yeah.
And, hey, at least
I'm not being sued for $450 million.
Oh, my God. Right?
I still can't believe it.
I mean, I'm sure Brad's totally innocent.
Of course you think that.
Brad loved his artists like family.
He would never steal from them.
Even that article
said it was that guy, Ron Shelby,
who did the actual embezzling.
Do you remember him?
I always had a bad feeling about him.
I even told Brad that when he hired him.
Plus, he shaved his arms.
Never trust a man who shaves his arms.
Brad must be devastated.
I wish there was something I could do.
Uh, yeah, that definitely falls
under the category of...
Not my sink, not my dishes?
I was gonna say,
not your garden, not your weeds,
but same thing.
I know.
Maybe I should reach out to him.
Do you not remember how hard it was
seeing him and his wife at Majid's party?
I really think
I have to put all that stuff to the side.
That business is cutthroat.
People can turn on you in a second.
You know, he probably
needs a friend right now.
You're gonna be his friend?
He'd do it for me.
And he would do it for you too, Sash.
You know that.
Okay, fine.
Are you sure you
aren't wanting to reach out to Brad
'cause you're in a bad place with Majid?
We're not in a bad place.
We're in no place.
He hasn't reached out since the party
and neither have I.
I haven't even had time to think about it.
- This is my first day back in the city.
- I know.
It's gonna be what it's gonna be.
But me reaching out to Brad
has nothing to do with Majid.
I'm gonna text him.
Hey.
Do you want me
to cancel my shoot and stay?
I'm happy to.
I want to support you in any way I can.
It'll all be fine. I'm gonna beat this.
Of course you are.
You're Brad Simon,
you always come out on top.
[cell phone chimes]
What is it?
It's nothing. Just...
It's just one of the lawyers.
Listen...
I'm not just here
for the good times, okay?
I want you to know
you can lean on me all the time.
I'm your wife.
Don't forget to eat.
I won't.
You have a good shoot, okay?
Nothing.
A least someone has good boundaries.
Oh, wait. He's writing back.
He wants to meet.
Oh, for fuck's sake.
I have to be there for him.
It's the right thing to do.
His loft.
You know what?
I have enough of a clusterfuck of my own
to deal with today.
Have fun being Brad's friend.
I'm sure that's gonna be
super easy for you.
[Brad] Thanks for coming.
- For reaching out.
- Of course. Yeah.
Where's, um, Gigi?
She's...
She's on a shoot.
Do you want a coffee?
- Sure.
- Yeah.
Yeah.
[moaning]
You have a new couch.
It's pink.
It's blush.
I was assured of that.
And you're a Buddhist now.
Uh, Gigi got it.
She's made a few changes here.
[Billie] I can see that.
Thank you.
You wanna sit?
- Yeah.
- Yeah, yeah.
You were the first person I wanted to call
when it all happened.
You always warned me about Ron.
I really fucked up. I...
I wasn't overseeing the day-to-day
the way I should have.
I knew Ron was tough...
but I had no idea he was stealing.
I swear.
Of course you didn't.
I should've listened to you.
You've always known what's good for me.
Before I know it myself.
I'm always coming around too late.
I think I'm gonna lose the company.
I don't know who I am without it.
Brad...
You are not your company.
I know how much it means to you
and meant to you for your dad.
But you made all that right
before he passed.
There is so much more to you
than your success.
I'm about to be a father, Billie.
And I'm scared to death.
The money...
was the one thing
I knew I had going for me.
You know?
I knew, if nothing else, I...
I could provide for my son.
But now...
You're gonna be a great father.
I've always known that.
Whether it happened with us or with Gigi.
That little boy is lucky...
to have you as his dad.
You don't want to do this.
Maybe I do.
Well, I don't.
I can't.
You've always been right about me too.
This isn't who I am, who I want to be.
This is not who you are either.
[new age music playing over speakers]
Hello, Mick.
Oh.
I'm sorry.
Your assistant said you wanted to meet.
Sit down.
As I predicted,
your brand is bleeding out.
Got a Dr. Evans problem
you got to fix, stat.
I know, but I'm sure
it's all gonna blow over.
It's a 60-second news cycle
these days, right?
Besides, I have been
preparing some inspired
hashtag "IndependentWoman4Life" posts
that are gonna slay.
[mimics buzzer]
Not gonna cut it.
This is your personal Chernobyl.
You need to put on your hazmat suit
and clean this shit up.
You're writing a book called Unattached.
You gotta be unattached.
[Sasha] Okay, I hear you.
But here's another idea just to chew on.
What if I push back,
make Kam eat a little crow
so that we're reframing the issue to:
"Sasha Snow has got her man in check."
- It's good.
- It's shit.
Independent Woman for Life
rehabs some douchebag who shuts her up
in front of 4 million viewers?
Okay. That hand-over-mouth thing
was taken way out of context.
We were just joking around.
We're done.
[music stops]
Perception... is reality.
I was just on the phone
with Goop Lab's executive producer
pitching you for a regular segment.
She was practically
creaming her panties over the idea.
Oh, my God.
That's amazing.
Yeah, well, it's only a dress rehearsal.
You could be Gwyneth's Dr. Phil...
but you gotta do things my way.
I'm an independent woman.
Isn't it my job to question you?
Sally, get me Amanda Gorman on the phone.
I was just playing.
I really wanna make this work.
Then 86 the boyfriend.
- [Sally] I have Amanda.
- Amanda.
Poet! Renaissance woman of the century!
You ever hear of Goop?
Billie.
I'm so sorry I'm late.
I just... I got held up at, uh, school.
Well, all that matters is you're here now
and I scheduled some
amazing spa treatments for us,
including massages with
my favorite masseur of all time, Sven.
- Oh!
- That's his real name.
Wow. Can't wait.
Caroline, I have your room ready.
- Just how you like it.
- Great.
He knows I love a warm massage table
with a couple drops of eucalyptus oil.
See you later.
Billie...
I'm so sorry.
- I've been trying to reach you.
- I know.
- I just...
- [Helen] Billie and Trina?
Hi. I'm Helen,
and I am taking you for your
restorative couple's seaweed wrap.
Oh, no, no, no, no. We're not a couple.
This is a judgment free space. Follow me.
Hey, Ben.
Sorry, Cooper, but I have instructions
from Francesca not to let you up.
Could you please call her
and let her know I'm here?
Don't you want to call her yourself?
I think it'll be better if you do it.
Now, hand me your robes.
Ladies, we're all women of the earth here
and shedding our cloaks
is part of the cleansing process. Just...
[exhales sharply]
Good. Very good. Thank you.
Now, take the seaweed.
Go ahead. Take it and gently rub it
onto the front of your bodies.
Very good. Yes, Just like that.
And make sure to cover all the areas.
Really feel the curative effects
of that seaweed
as it draws out those toxins
and releases all of that negative energy.
[yelling] Release that energy. Release!
[in normal voice]
I want you to do each other's backs.
That's okay.
I have really long arms, I can reach.
No, no, no. Open yourselves up
to each other's restorative touch.
Hmm? I'll be back in a few minutes.
Is it okay to use
my restorative touch on you?
I hear it works wonders.
Honestly, it'll help
if I don't have to look you in the eye
when I say what I have to say to you.
Have at it.
I am so truly sorry...
and...
ashamed...
of what happened with Cooper
and especially Hudson.
Is he okay?
We convinced him
you two were playing a game.
He's young enough that he bought it.
I'm really glad.
What I did was not to hurt you.
I need you to know that.
I've just been...
so envious of you for having the guts
to go after your own happiness
when I don't even have the foggiest idea
what would make me happy.
What are you talking about?
Turns out the sex parties
were just a distraction
from what was happening in my marriage...
or what wasn't happening.
I tried going back to work. Like you.
Honestly, I'm grasping at straws,
and Cooper was one of those straws.
Trina.
You should not be envious of me.
I don't have anything figured out.
Not by a mile.
You made such bold choices.
You didn't just stay silent,
do what we're all supposed to do,
keep our mouths shut and act grateful.
You can make bold choices too, you know.
And I will be here
to help you in any way that I can.
[Helen] Okay, ladies.
Are we ready to rinse
all that negative energy away?
Yes, Helen. Let's rinse that shit away.
[Francesca] Cooper.
Here's your shit. We're done.
What the hell is he doing here?
The receptionist's not enough for you?
Got big cojones coming at me
given what you did with my wife.
I called Devon after you went MIA.
I called everyone
because I thought you were dead.
But after the earful I got from him,
you may as well be.
- Can we talk in private? Just you and me.
- No, he stays.
I want you to be humiliated
the same way you humiliated me.
Okay.
I'm sorry.
I jumped in with both feet too soon
and I hadn't processed all of
the unresolved baggage with Billie and me.
And I'm sorry
you got caught in the middle.
In the middle?
I thought we were
building a life together.
I lost my job because of you.
Now I'm unhireable because
you made me the whore of Wall Street.
I'm so sorry, Francesca.
The truth is, it wasn't just Trina.
There were others.
There was a woman
at the Chinese restaurant.
Oh, my God.
My Uber driver last night.
Dude.
I'm just... I'm fucked up right now. Okay?
I used to think Billie was the problem
in your marriage,
but maybe I had it wrong.
Maybe the problem is you.
- So, what can I do to make it right?
- You could've talked to me.
You could've told me
any part of what was going on.
But you did nothing. You said nothing.
This is private property.
Take your shit and get out.
Francesca, wait.
[Caroline sighs] I feel like a new woman.
How was your seaweed wrap?
You and Trina make up?
Yeah.
I think we did.
- Yay!
- Mm-hm.
I knew Helen would clear out
all of that bad energy.
She is very insistent about that.
Mm.
So...
have you talked to bad boy Brad
about the lawsuit?
No. Why would I?
- We're not together.
- I know.
But you never said why you're not.
Brad had such a pull on you.
I was so excited for what might happen.
I used to lie in bed thinking about
what your life was like now.
- Let me tell you...
- [Trina] What the hell, Caroline.
Your sick fuck of a masseur, Sven,
just tried to go down on me.
- What?
- Are you serious?
Yeah. I'm about to go report
his ass to management.
- No, no, no, you can't.
- Why not?
Did he try something on you too, Caroline?
Uh...
Okay, um...
Yes, he did.
And I let him.
In fact, I let him about once a month.
- What the fuck are you talking about?
- I'm sorry.
I didn't realize
he was doing that with everyone.
I thought it was our special thing.
He probably thought he was doing
you a favor like he has been for me.
Okay, Caroline, I don't understand.
You always seemed
so happy in your marriage.
I am happy. I love Jeffrey.
But you said
I need to start questioning my life.
Oh, my God. So this is on me now?
No. I was inspired...
to figure out why I don't like sex.
Well, it turns out I do like sex.
I like sex a lot.
Just not with my husband.
Please don't report him.
Don't ruin this for me.
[woman on intercom]
There's a delivery here
that requires your signature.
Send him in.
[pop music playing]
Special delivery for Dr. Evans.
♪ I sit alone in dark places ♪
♪ I speak half-truths to total strangers ♪
♪ I fake smile through conversation ♪
♪ Since I left you... ♪
I was told a signature would be required.
I'm certain you'll leave your signature.
All...
over...
me.
You know these walls are paper thin.
Then you better not scream too loud.
Have fun being a patient, Dr. Evans.
[both moaning]
Well, the scent of eucalyptus
is forever ruined for me.
Oh, he gave you the eucalyptus too?
Listen, um...
I know on some level
I should be... flattered.
I mean, you both are making
some really big decisions
based on... me and my life choices, but...
I'm not so sure that's a good idea.
[Caroline] Why not?
I did go see Brad today.
[gasps]
- Did something happen?
- It almost did.
I wanted it to.
But...
- I have a boyfriend.
- A boyfriend?
That's so exciting.
Well, I mean,
things are a little weird right now.
Because you still love Brad?
Brad is married.
He and his wife are about to have a baby.
No. That's so sad.
I mean, happy for them.
A child is a blessing.
But sad for you...
- and also me.
- [cell phone chimes]
- Oh, shit.
- [Trina] What's wrong?
Who is it?
Brad's wife.
[Kam] I know the last few days
have been rough,
but I'm happy to report
you still got your swagger.
But speaking of which,
Mick called me in to discuss
how to stop the hemorrhaging.
Like a Twitter tourniquet.
Actually, we decided
I should break up with you.
- Publicly.
- You're breaking up with me?
No, of course not.
We can keep seeing each other
just in private.
In secret?
Hey, secrecy... can be really hot.
Oh, my God.
That's why you came and seduced me.
To soften me up before lowering the boom.
That's not what this is.
No, this is you sacrificing
your integrity for your brand.
I have to do whatever it takes
to expand my platform,
to teach women to fight back
against the patriarchy
and live the way they want to.
You know that.
Whatever it takes, huh?
My next book is called Unattached.
Your agent came up with that title,
not you.
It's a good fucking title
because it describes who I am,
who I've been for the last 17 years
before you showed up again.
But it's not who you are now.
Like it or not, you have a partner.
As of last week,
you were telling me how sustained you felt
by that partnership.
- Why don't you tell that to your fans?
- I will.
My next book can be about that.
I can be honest then.
Sasha, look around.
My whole career has been built
on living a life of integrity.
How could you possibly expect me to cosign
on selling some bullshit reality?
Oh, I see.
We're back to that.
Your career,
which always comes before mine.
Mm-mm. Stop.
That is not what this is.
I'm just not gonna live a lie.
I love you, Sasha Snow.
But you've got a decision to make.
["Cheers to Poison" playing]
[man] Elongate your torso.
All right. Chin up.
Yes. A little to the right.
Little to the left.
Beautiful. Okay.
Chin down a tiny bit.
Straight into the lens.
Right. Love that.
All right, legs up. Arch your back.
You're exquisite.
Sorry, Nino, I need ten.
[Nino] Okay.
Gigi, wow. You're gorgeous.
I know you were at the loft earlier.
I get notifications on my phone with
camera footage when someone buzzes up.
What were you doing there?
Oh, I just reached out
when I heard the news.
I wanted to make sure Brad was okay.
And then he asked you
to come over to our home,
that I'm getting ready for our baby.
As a friend.
You are the ghost in our relationship
and I think you always will be.
No, Gigi.
I only recently put it together
but I get it now.
You left your husband.
But by that time,
Brad was already with me.
So the only reason
you two aren't together is this baby.
That's not true.
Brad loves you.
That has never been a question.
I'm not an idiot.
I saw you both at the party.
How affected you were by each other.
I asked Brad not to contact you again.
But he couldn't help himself.
Look...
Brad is going through a lot.
Oh, I'm aware.
And you have no idea how it feels
to know that you're the one
he wants to talk to about this.
[sobbing] Shit. I can't fuck this up,
it's a $10,000 makeup job.
No, no. Okay, hold on.
Here you go.
You've had your chance.
Now it's my turn.
Please, let me have it.
[cell phone buzzing]
[groans]
Hey, Olga.
Hey, I was just calling to see
how much longer you're going to be.
Hudson says you're going sledding
and getting hot chocolate.
Oh... shit.
I got, um...
I got stuck at work
and I lost track of time.
Daddy says he's so sorry.
He loves you
and he'll see you in the morning.
Yeah, that.
Thank you, Olga.
[whistles]
I'll take another one, please.
Sorry, man. I gotta cut you off.
Happy to call you a cab.
I don't need a fucking cab.
I just need another drink.
Not my rules.
Okay.
Your job is to pour.
So, pour.
Do your fucking job.
You want me to come back there
and show you how to do it?
Cooper.
[Cooper] Emily?
What are you doing here?
I was getting drinks with some colleagues
and I saw you.
Oh.
Here, sit down.
Sit down.
Maybe you can get this guy
to get us a drink.
I can only stay a moment.
I heard you're getting divorced.
Oh.
Yep.
That's me.
- Mr. Failed Marriage.
- Don't do that to yourself.
No one ever tells you
how hard this part is.
For months, my standing Postmates order
was an avocado toast
and a fifth of Grey Goose.
Plus a straw.
Classy. I know.
Going through a divorce
can make you doubt yourself,
your choices.
You start to feel like a fraud.
Yeah. Except maybe I am.
The fraud.
I mean, the woman I've been seeing
would definitely agree.
And Billie.
Maybe they're both right.
Maybe...
Maybe I'm not the man
that I always thought I was.
No.
I've known you for a long time, Cooper.
Long before there ever was a Billie,
let alone this other woman.
I know your heart.
I know who you are. And...
I've always loved that man.
No. Not like this.
I know you'll find your way
back to yourself, but I can't.
I can't be here for this part.
[cell phone chimes]
[cell phone ringing]
[Majid] Billie.
How'd you know
I was a sucker for amaryllis?
Did you think these were for you?
I'm just selling these.
Sir, care to buy some flowers?
What are you doing here?
Yeah. So...
It actually took me a few days
to work up the courage to reach out.
Considered just letting the whole thing go
rather than... confessing.
It was like,
if I don't tell her, we're done.
If I do tell her,
we're probably done anyway.
Tell me what, Maj?
You were right.
You have been
unflinchingly honest with me,
so I know I need to just man up
and do the same.
Crystal was one of my original investors.
I'd been scraping pennies together,
raising money for a long time,
finally thought I had enough
to put a down payment on the space.
But then in the 11th hour,
the last piece of financing fell apart.
I didn't want to ask my family.
I couldn't.
So...
A buddy introduced me to Crystal
and she came through,
but there was a string attached.
I have sex with her.
That's... been the arrangement.
I haven't been with her since I met you.
I've been putting her off for months.
But the other night at the restaurant,
I knew I had to talk to her.
I shouldn't have let it
get as far as it did.
But after you left,
I spoke to her and I drew the line.
She is very clear on my boundaries now.
So, I was hoping maybe you
could give me another chance.
It's okay.
I get it.
I never would have forgiven myself
if I hadn't taken the chance. So...
Wait.
I know what it's like...
to want something so much...
you'll go after it,
no matter the consequences.
I saw Brad today.
I reached out under the...
guise of concern about the lawsuit.
But the truth is...
I wanted to see him.
Nothing happened.
But it almost did.
So...
Look, we're both adults.
We both have pasts.
And it would be naive
to pretend that we didn't.
Do you want to come up?
Sure.
As soon as I finish selling these flowers.
Give me.
[cell phone ringing]
What is it? There's lots happening here.
I've been buried.
[woman] This is the labor
and delivery nurse at Mount Sinai.
Your wife's in active labor.
She's been trying to reach you.
You should get here as soon as possible.
Oh, my God.
[laughs]
I love you, Billie.
I want to be everything to you.
Tell me what you want.
What you've never dared to say. Or do.
[Billie moans]
Anything?
["Make It Work" playing]
Sasha, hi.
- Hi.
- Where's Dr. Evans?
Flying solo, Sangita.
Well, there's been a lot
of Internet chatter
about hashtag "TalkToTheHand."
What do you have to say?
What I'll say is sexism and misogyny
are so prevalent in our society,
so internalized,
that even someone like me fell prey.
I should've never
attributed my success to a man.
The only person responsible
for my success is me.
So, are you and Kam still together?
Oh, honey.
I'm an independent woman for life
and always will be.
Yeah, Sasha Snow not melting for anyone!
That's right.
[Sangita] So, what comes next?
[Sasha] Well, next is my new book.
You'll have to check it out.
It's called Unattached.
[Sangita] Thank you so much.
Have a good night.
[Sasha] Thank you.
[TV turns off]
["All The Things Lost" playing]
♪ Oh, no words could ever help
Relieve this pain ♪
[vocalizing]
Hi.
Not everyone has it.
♪ All our silence could not excuse... ♪
[Billie] The desire to wake up.
To stop sleepwalking through our lives.
To stop trying to do the right thing...
while denying our truth.
Francesca. I'm just checking in.
I know today was rough,
and I'm here for you.
So, call me day or night.
[Billie] But those of us who do...
What's happening?
I want a divorce.
...who are ready to stop settling
for what we don't want...
and identify what we do...
♪ Anything other
Than what we already know ♪
[Billie] ...we tread in dangerous waters.
Because once you wake up...
once you get even just a tiny taste...
there's no going back.
And doing the right thing...
Is this Gigi Everett's room?
I'm Brad Simon, the father.
Hang on. You gotta put on a gown.
[Billie] ...will never feel right again.
At least not for you.
So be sure...
when you make that choice...
you're willing to follow through.
[both moaning]
[screaming]
I'm so sorry I'm late.
I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
[sobbing]
I kept trying to reach you.
- Why didn't you pick up?
- I'm so sorry.
I'm sorry, okay?
But I'm here now. Hey, I'm here. I'm here.
[doctor] Okay, here we go.
You're ready.
You can do this. Hey.
You got this.
Push.
[doctor] Push, Gigi.
Oh, my God.
He's coming. He's coming.
He's coming.
♪ Spent your life collecting
So you can never forget ♪
[doctor] Congratulations.
♪ Treasured moments
Become lost treasures ♪
♪ When you can't recollect ♪
♪ Everyone keeps asking are we okay ♪
♪ The truth is we're not
But I don't know what to say ♪
[vocalizing]
[Billie] Because if you choose wrong...
be prepared to live
with the consequences...
forever.
[theme music playing]