How'd you sleep, lieutenant?
- You want me to lie to you?
- Sort of.
Fantastic. Like a baby.
Good morning, detective.
Good morning. Lieutenant slept great.
I didn't ask. And no, she did not.
Mason puts Anthony acosta's
death between three and five p ...M.
Confirmation of shotgun?
It's the murder weapon.
Next of kin?
Primary suspect, the wife,
Lynette a cost a, vanished.
They have one daughter,
letty, studying up in Santa Cruz.
Should be on her way down here now.
You gave her the news?
So, how do we find the wife?
Only other next of kin
is the sister, Sofia bellier.
Who did this?
Hey! Who did this?
Who changed our board?
A man is dead. Our
primary suspect is missing.
This is not a joke.
Daphne, I wanna know who did this.
Mom!
No, we don't need a
magazine about castles.
Put it back.
It's just lip gloss.
You know, I watched a
documentary the other night,
we can make our own
lip gloss out of beeswax.
Like when we made our own
detergent and all got rashes?
- That could have been foot.
- And-mouth, we don't know.
Why can't you be more like your sister?
She just tried to eat deodorant.
And look how happy she is.
All right. Your grand
total is one... 168.47.
$173.81. Good guess though.
Yeah, it's-it's 168.47.
- Sorry, it's one hundred...
- maybe you missed a coupon.
30% off detergent at 7.87,
that's 2.36 for a total of 5.51.
15% off strawberries, that's 84 cents.
And up to two, so you
can scan this one twice.
Okay. 35% off canola
oil at 7.88, 5.13 total.
Okay, I was worried about this
one 'cause I had a little falling-out
with the group on
people, but I apologized.
- We were supposed to be good.
- That one scanned.
3.12 more then.
The ham expires
tomorrow, so we get 40% off.
That is $6.15.
Yeah, the total is 168.47.
4.99 plus tax is 5.34.
173.81 minus 5.34 is 168.47.
Thank you.
Who the hell is this?
When are we getting the car back?
Do you have any idea
how much carburetors cost?
$395.95.
Now, plus tax.
- 420.89.
- Plus labor.
- I don't know how much labor costs.
- Nobody does.
Stop showing off, both of you.
You can pay for groceries
like a normal person.
- You don't have to perform.
- It's not on purpose.
I just see the numbers. I can't help it.
This is our stop.
Driver, can you put
out the disabled ramp?
Ask him to put out the disabled ramp.
- No. Mom!
- Driver!
Whoopsie. Whoops!
Could you grab 'em?
We got a lot of options. I know, buddy.
You hungry? Let's go!
- Ooh. Oops.
- I'll see you inside, Chloe.
Don't even offer to help.
I got it. I got it.
It's okay, Henry. I can manage.
Thank you.
Come on.
Don't break your old body.
I can't afford to lose
a babysitter right now.
Your concern is truly touching.
Have you heard from ludo?
We talk every day, Henry. We co-parent.
We're not enemies, we're
just not together anymore.
Does he ever ask about me?
All the time.
He says losing you was the hardest part.
It's for the best and you know it.
- Ludo can't handle me.
- Few can.
Morgan gillory, I'm detective karadec.
This is detective ozdil. We need
you to come down to the station.
Sometimes the music takes control.
Tampering with a criminal
case is a serious crime.
So is obstruction of justice.
It wasn't tampering. I saw
a problem and I tried to fix it.
- You were trying to help us?
- No.
I don't care about you. I
wanted to be able to sleep.
I have a compulsion to put things right.
If I see a mistake, I need to correct it.
Otherwise, I'm up all night obsessing.
That's all I was doing,
cleaning up your mess.
Wanna arrest me for
that? Fine. Go ahead.
You got it.
What mistakes did you see?
Okay. So you got a dead body.
I'm assuming you think this lady offed
her husband, but that's not possible.
Look at this room.
Look at this couch.
All of these pillows are evenly
spaced with alternating colors.
Check out these shelves.
Those objects are perfectly sized.
Even the choice of metals is consistent.
This house is immaculate.
The owner is a tidiness freak.
Except...
All of these curtains are
fastened with a tieback
except for one for some reason.
That's odd, isn't it?
You're telling me this woman,
who meticulously
arranges her couch pillows,
doesn't care about her curtains?
So the tieback must have
been used for something else.
See, look. You've got
hair stuck to the chair leg.
Somebody put tape
around it, ripped it off,
the glue stayed and trapped the little bits.
The samples are at the lab.
We found no tape at the scene.
That means someone was
tied up with the curtain cord
and taped to the chair
around their ankles.
And since there are no
marks on the victim's wrist,
it wasn't him who was tied up,
which means there was a third person.
We have Lynette tied to the
chair, victim on the ground
and our unknown bondage freak,
who has either kidnapped
or bumped off Lynette.
That's the person you need to find.
So, you guys made
mistakes, I've fixed them.
Let's not make a big deal out of this.
You got a suspect to find.
I have some expired ham
to fry up before tomorrow.
- So, if you will excuse me.
- Sit down.
Let's wait for the lab results.
For now, this is just speculation.
We have the surveillance footage.
A woman was seen entering the
house at the time of the murder.
The third person.
Oz, please escort miss
gillory to the holding cell.
- What?
- We have to check your story out.
If it all checks out, then you
have nothing to worry about.
- Yeah, I know how to stand.
- Ma'am... thanks.
I was just cleaning up your mess.
You're welcome.
Since when do you show
an open case file to a civilian?
A potential suspect?
Can you refute anything she said?
No.
We have to be sure
because if she's right
then we currently have a botched
homicide investigation with no leads.
And even worse...
We have a second victim.
Hello?
Hi.
This is footage from the a cost a house
at the approximate time of the murder.
Who is she?
Lishka zhang.
A few months ago,
she filed a civil lawsuit
against one of Lynette acosta's clients.
Acosta won the case. It
appears zhang didn't take it well.
She started sending
threatening emails to a cost a.
Miss zhang, three months
ago, you sued Brian dimon,
your boss at spatial technologies.
He harassed me for months.
I ran out of ways to tell him no.
So, one night, he locked me
in his office and assaulted me.
I reported it to the police. I'm
sure you have that in your file.
Insufficient evidence.
Couldn't file criminal
charges, so I sued him.
And you lost.
Is that why you've been sending
Lynette a cost a threatening emails?
I was just questioning
why Lynette a cost a
chose to be complicit in the
suffering of women like me.
You were angry at Mrs. Acosta?
Of course.
Even though dimon was
the one who assaulted you.
I am angry with him too,
but the police failed me on that front.
What were you doing at
acosta's house yesterday?
I wasn't at her house yesterday.
We have you on video.
And 30 minutes after you
arrived, Anthony a cost a was dead.
That's impossible.
No. No, I-I wasn't there yesterday.
I was at home all day working.
Can anyone confirm that?
No.
You're cleared. Just need you to sign
your paperwork and you're good to go.
She claims to know nothing
about Lynette's whereabouts,
but zhang has no alibi.
We have her at the
scene, and we have motive.
Once we make the arrest, we'll
lean on her for Lynette's location.
- Start writing it up.
- Yeah.
The video has the wrong
date on the time stamp.
This doesn't concern you anymore.
Great.
Wait, what are you talking about?
That's not from yesterday.
Look at the trees.
The wind is blowing from south to north.
Wind in the la basin blows
from the south in the summer,
specifically mid July to September.
Then in late fall,
winds shift in from the
north, peaking in January.
So that's gotta be from
several months ago.
How do you know which
way the wind is blowing?
Have you even looked at your footage?
You got a church.
Churches face east.
Okay, around the eighth century,
priests started orienting
their churches facing east.
They said it was based off the
designs for the holy temple in Jerusalem.
But it's also possible that they
wanted the sunrise behind them
to make themselves appear
more godlike and impressive.
But that's not something
we need to get into right now.
All churches face east?
And can't the wind change direction?
Catholic churches built
here in the 1800s do, so yes.
And the wind was definitely
blowing from the north yesterday.
She's right on both counts.
Someone doctored the video.
See ya.
Good lord.
Wait.
How do you do that?
Like I told you, I don't sleep
much. Watch a lot of documentaries.
That doesn't remotely explain this.
I also have an IQ of 160, so that
might have something to do with it.
But you can learn a lot
from a good documentary.
You'd be surprised.
It's a high IQ, we get it. Can I go now?
I know a lot of really smart
people and they're not you.
The technical term is
high potential intellectual.
Means you have
advanced cognitive abilities.
Intellectual creativity,
photographic memory, stuff like that.
But I don't know, I've
just always been this way.
So, it's some sort of a gift?
No, not a gift.
I obsess over every little problem I see.
My mind is constantly
spinning out of control,
which makes it impossible
to hold a job, relationship.
A conversation.
Not a gift.
Morgan.
Ludo? What are you doing here?
Elliot called me and told
me you were arrested again.
I was not technically arrested this time.
Well, great. That's a relief.
- Who's watching our children?
- Hey.
Take it somewhere else.
I'd love to, but you're
standing right in the way.
- Why are you looking at him?
- Please don't look at me.
- Take her out of here.
- He's not taking me anywhere.
He is a driver's ed instructor.
That's not really relevant right now.
It is if you show up in your rehearsal car,
- which I will not be caught...
- I don't care.
Put a muzzle on her or I will.
That's not what you should say..
- Did you say... don't touch me, okay?
- Okay. Morgan.
- Morgan, let's not...
- okay. That's fine. I'm not gonna
- she's got a...
- Hey!
Get off me!
- Always fun to see you, Morgan.
- Don't start.
Hey, how much longer
is this gonna take?
Do you have any idea how
expensive childcare is these days?
Wait, you're paying Henry now?
No, she doesn't have to know that.
Henry misses you, by the way.
Aw.
Letty a cost a, I'm detective
karadec. We spoke on the phone.
I'm handling the investigation
of your father's death.
I'm very sorry for your loss.
My mom's dead too, isn't she?
I don't know.
But I believe that she's
out there, and she's alive,
and I will not stop looking until I find her.
But I need your help, letty.
The more you can tell
me, the faster we can move.
Mom's been having a hard time.
She had a colleague at work.
She killed herself.
I think mom felt guilty about it.
- Who was this colleague?
- I don't know.
But she wrote mom a letter a
couple weeks back and after that,
mom started to spiral.
What did the letter say?
She wouldn't tell me.
But it shook her up bad.
And that's really when all this started.
Do you know where your mom
might keep a letter like that, letty?
If it's not at the house,
it would be in her office.
And you don't know who sent it?
Only her first name. It was
Sarah.
Because it's material evidence
into a homicide investigation.
I understand. I understand.
Yes, sir. Thank you.
It's no use.
Lynette a cost a is a defense attorney.
There's no way we're gonna get
a warrant to search her law offices
based on the vague mention of a
letter from someone named Sarah.
I'm gonna go down to their offices
and appeal to their better nature.
I don't like our odds.
Neither do I, but we have
to try everything, right?
A woman is missing,
and we're desperate here.
Take Morgan gillory with you.
If it wasn't for her, we'd be nowhere.
We'd still be treating Lynette
as the primary suspect.
What is she supposed to do?
Same thing she's been doing,
spot the things my detectives miss.
To be fair, I missed them too.
- Look...
- this isn't a debate, Adam.
Looks like I'm gonna be stuck
here a little bit longer than I thought.
Just tell him I love him, and I'll
be home as soon as I can, okay?
Thank you, Henry. I really owe you.
Hey, letty, I'm so sorry about
everything that's happened.
Thanks.
Sorry, who are you?
It's
long story. I saw your file.
- They're gonna find your mom.
- You can't know that.
Sorry, everyone keeps
saying the same thing.
"Don't give up hope."
My dad's dead and
now my mom is gone.
So, what am I supposed to do?
Yeah.
Do you have any pictures of her?
This one, she just sent me two days ago.
Wow. She's beautiful.
It's the last photo I have of her.
You know, what was really helpful for
me was to think of the little moments.
Think of your mom's laugh.
Think about her favorite foods.
You're gonna have to redirect
your brain when you think about her.
Otherwise, you're just gonna
drive yourself crazy while you wait.
You lost someone?
I did, yeah. Long time ago.
Miss a cost a, they're ready for you.
Hey, did you ever find them?
No.
Well, I'm sorry.
Thank you.
So, the way I see it, we're
looking at evidence tampering,
assault on an officer, battery.
Even if we knock it
down to misdemeanors,
you're still looking at six months
minimum and thousands in fines.
Did you really think
this was gonna work?
You're gonna what,
intimidate me into helping you?
If you'd like my help, you
should just ask me nicely.
A woman is missing.
Please, help us find her.
You got it.
Here's what we know. Anthony
a cost a died yesterday afternoon.
Last time anyone saw Lynette, however,
was two days ago at her law office.
Okay. But I'm wondering
who made this case board.
'Cause this is a lot of work.
Also I'm banned from hobby lobby.
Their daughter, letty, believes
that one of Lynette's clients,
identified only as Sarah,
wrote a letter causing significant
tension between her parents.
We're gonna talk to the firm but
only after we interview Lynette's sister
sister. Because she's the last
person who spoke to Lynette,
which I learned from
looking at this case board.
Also, guys, I just figured out this
gentleman in the corner, he's the one.
He makes the case boards.
Why aren't we moving?
Okay, let's be very clear.
You are not gonna say anything,
you are not gonna touch anything,
and you are not going to do anything.
Right, right. I should probably
be strapped in case things pop off.
I'm serious. Do nothing.
You can take my bedroom,
and I'll sleep on the couch.
Sophia, did your sister mention
anyone from her professional circle
who may have died of suicide
recently? Someone named Sarah?
Doesn't sound familiar.
She wrote Lynette a letter. We believe
something in it caused her distress.
Sorry. Could you put
that down? It's breakable.
She said nothing?
May get the Sarah part.
Every third woman's name
is Sarah these days, but
somebody writes my sister a
letter, and then she offs herself.
Like, she's probably
gonna say something.
I don't have a sister, but you get it.
Sorry. Who is she?
She is consulting for us.
When was the last time
you spoke to your sister?
Two days ago, she called to
wish me luck with my presentation.
You're a biologist?
Yeah, I had a phd defense.
In front of my peers. I was
nervous, and she calmed me down.
You can read that from over there?
I only read half of it. Biology is boring.
Is that where you were yesterday,
- at your presentation...
- Morgan.
- From, like, 3:00 to 5:00 P.M.?
- Stop it.
I'm just asking about her alibi.
My goodness. You'd think
he's never done this before.
If you can't keep your mouth shut, please
treat our witnesses with some compassion,
particularly grieving
members of the victim's family.
You don't think the Sarah
thing was a little weird?
You died today, I'm telling people about it,
and I've only known
you for, like, four hours.
We have to get our hands on that letter.
Yes, exactly. Let's do it.
We will ask Emery Walker
to search acosta's office.
You will wait in the car.
If I get in that back seat, he's
gonna lock me in the car, isn't he?
Probably.
What am I even doing here?
Do you want my help or not?
No, I do not.
I thought I made that absolutely
clear. I think this whole idea is moronic,
and I am praying that
you will just quit and...
And walk away.
Okay. Let's confirm the sister's alibi.
You go to the university,
talk to her colleagues,
and I'll deal with Emery Walker.
What about her?
Not our problem anymore.
Detective karadec,
it is my personal desire to assist
your investigation in any way possible,
but as you can understand, I must also
represent the interests of my law firm.
But your partner's life might be in danger.
And if you return with a
warrant, I'll be happy to comply.
- Hello, bathroom friend.
- Jesus.
What are you doing in here?
I figured I'd find you in
here after the meeting.
Did you think that I wouldn't notice
you compulsively washing your hands
like some sort of clean freak?
- You do know that's a cry for help, right?
- You can't be here.
I know.
Imagine what a men's room is like for
somebody who notices every little detail.
Calm down. Found the Sarah letter.
What? How?
I broke into her office and took it.
Read the letter. Sarah Atkinson was
a paralegal on the Brian dimon case.
And guess what? Brian
dimon assaulted her also.
It's all in there. Same pattern as before.
She begs a cost a to take
action against her client.
I figure, Lynette a cost a
had a crisis of conscience,
was going to turn on dimon,
so he did something about it.
We have motive. We
have a serial criminal.
Let's go arrest him.
Stop.
You have no idea what you have done.
We have nothing here.
This letter is inadmissible. I
can't have this in my possession.
What? You're gonna let
him go on a technicality?
No, these are not
technicalities. These are laws.
Principles that I have
devoted my entire life to protect.
Jesus. I thought my life was sad.
Your life is sad.
You've got shopping carts from three
different grocery stores in your yard.
I wouldn't have to go to different stores,
but safe way has
those weird wheel locks.
This is the law. There is
absolutely nothing here
that proves that Brian
dimon murdered anyone.
And even if there was, guess
what, we can't use it in court.
Because despite what you may think,
we can't run around breaking into
offices and arresting people at whim.
That's not how the law works.
Right now, the only clear crime
here has been committed by you.
And by me if I let you get away with it.
- But if...
- stop talking.
Okay. This didn't happen.
You're gonna take this letter,
and you're gonna put it back
exactly where you found it.
And if you get caught, I am
going to arrest you myself.
And then what?
And then we're gonna
go talk to Brian dimon.
Mr. Dimon. A few months ago,
you were sued by lishka zhang.
- And I won.
- Yes.
She wrote to your lawyer in fact, "he
harassed me over the course of six"...
This is my first
interrogation. What do we do?
You don't do anything.
Is it like a good cop, bad cop situation?
You want me to go in
and flip the table over?
No.
She lost her case.
The jury saw the truth. Lishka zhang
is simply an employee with a grudge.
Those seem to follow you around.
Tell me about your
relationship with Sarah Atkinson.
When do we get to hit
him with a phone book?
Never.
Hey, how's it coming?
Let's get ready for his alibi. Give me
a data print on the day of the murder.
I'm on it. Yeah.
Also tell Daphne I took one of
her lollipops, and I feel bad about it.
I'm not telling her that.
I heard her. And thank you.
I thought I was here to help
with my lawyer's disappearance,
not relitigate old claims.
The Atkinson claims are not old.
Well, if there have been new claims
against me, I'm not aware of them.
Yeah? I got bad news.
Dimon wasn't in town the day of
the murder. Wasn't anywhere close.
He was in Fontana.
You certain?
Positive.
Fontana? The Kentucky
of California? "Fontucky"?
What the hell was he doing in Fontana?
Doesn't matter. He wasn't here.
Look at his shoes. Those
are Italian seams handcrafted.
Look at his watch.
That guy is not gonna be
caught dead in Fontana.
There are only two
reasons you go to Fontana.
Number one, you wanna
catch hepatitis at the water park.
Number two, you have to go to
your cousin's bachelorette party,
and she is on a budget.
I can literally think of a hundred
other reasons to go to Fontana.
Okay, ask him.
Tell karadec to ask dimon
what he was doing in Fontana.
My lawyer, my friend, is missing.
Please tell me you didn't bring me
in here to rehash vague grievances
by hysterical employees.
What is happening? I
gotta see him right now.
I understand. I understand.
Let's take care of this right now.
The incompetence!
Tell karadec.
It's not how this works.
Hey!
Ask him about Fontana.
- Hey!
- The hell is this?
Don't say another word.
Mr. Dimon, thank you for your time.
What?
No!
Chester Emery's secretary
noted a woman dressed, quote,
"quite provocatively for the cleaning staff"
entered acosta's office
twice this afternoon.
What happened?
Karadec.
Karadec. Dimon was in Fontana on the
day of the murder. You gotta ask him why.
Stop. We're done. This entire
idiotic experiment is finished.
It doesn't make any sense.
Stop pretending you can do this. It's over.
Be grateful you're not in jail.
Go back to your real life, Morgan.
Leave this to the professionals.
Do you know what direction all
stairs went in medieval castles?
Clockwise. You know why?
To make it easier to chop
people coming up the stairs?
Exactly.
But what if you're left-handed?
Well, the world wasn't exactly
built for people who are different.
Phone away at the table, please.
Eat dinner with your
family like a normal person.
Hey.
You know, Chloe and Elliot are
gonna be with ludo this weekend.
So I was thinking we could go to the
park like we used to. Get some ice cream.
I'm not six.
What's going on?
I'm-I'm not like you and Elliot.
He's got your memory, your... your
brain, your way of noticing everything.
Well, you got some of my qualities too.
You know, you got my
rebelliousness, my distrust of authority,
- my sweet fashion sense.
- I have your worst qualities.
Elliot and Chloe have everything.
To be fair, Chloe is still a baby.
We don't really know her deal yet.
It's not what I'm talking about.
Ludo thinks of you as his daughter.
It's not the same.
No. No, you're right. It's not.
Honey, your father loved you so much.
Sure. That's why he left.
No, it's more complicated than that.
It's fine. Whatever. I don't
even remember him. Who cares?
- If he could be here...
- I'm glad he's not.
I wanna be alone.
Okay.
Wait, Elliot, don't forget
your science project.
Ava, you can't have
doughnuts for breakfast.
Shall we eat? Why are you
being a jerky today? Here you go.
Elliot.
There's a man standing in our yard.
Why did you want me to
ask dimon about Fontana?
Come inside.
This mush needs to go into this kid.
Dimon is not a Fontana guy.
More importantly, I noticed something
in Sofia's apartment yesterday.
All of the little tchotchkes on her
shelves were dusty except for one.
Sofia was in Fontana
recently. So was dimon.
So what? People go to Fontana.
Both of them?
Why does it matter? They both
have alibis for the time of the murder.
Come on.
Pick up the phone, Henry!
You can't borrow my car today.
I don't need to borrow your car today.
I did need to borrow his car
today. But that's beside the point.
Just come over here!
How long does it take for flowers
to die after you deliver them?
Like, wilted and brown die?
It depends on a few factors.
Mainly, the type of flower.
- Ranunculus?
- Four days, at least.
Henry.
You are a good man.
And an even better florist.
Let's go!
What?
I'll explain on the way.
Go, go, go. Grab the car seat.
Grab the car seat.
Dimon and Sofia are having an affair.
He was trying to groom her like
the others, but she was on board.
He's doing it to stay close to Lynette
because he knows he's
guilty and he needs leverage.
Can we run the siren?
- Absolutely not.
- Sure.
No, no. Mom, no, stop.
Not in the drop-off line.
This is the LAPD. We have an
apb out on two extreme cutie-pies.
All right. Everyone, have
a good day. Go, bulldogs.
Bye. Love you.
So, dimon, he learns of
Lynette's change of heart, right?
He knows this is the end
for him. He's desperate now.
He and Sofia go to Lynette's house
to put pressure on her. But, surprise.
Her husband Anthony is there too.
And that is when things
quickly get out of hand.
I... I'm with a student.
Great. You can teach her how
to install a car seat. Thanks, babe.
- Again, the problem is...
- that they both have alibis.
But what if the murder did not
happen when we think it happened?
Okay.
Dimon and Sofia are
trying to threaten Lynette.
Noted second amendment enthusiast
Anthony a cost a gets involved.
Turns out to be not the
best decision for him.
And now we've got a dead body.
Which is a real kick in the nards 'cause
what are we gonna do with Lynette?
But how did they cover it up?
Time of death was
during Sofia's presentation.
All of her colleagues are there.
Letty's last picture of her
mom was taken three days ago.
These flowers were fresh and
new. They should still be pink.
But they were already dead
in the crime scene photos.
What does dimon do for a living?
Security technology.
And what does Sofia do for a living?
She's a botanist.
Do you know what this room is?
A greenhouse.
- Yes. Yes. These are state.
- Of-the-art climate control.
So dimon turns the entire
place into one giant refrigerator.
He freezes acosta's body and leaves.
That night, he doctors the
video, framing lishka zhang.
The next day, he raises
the temperature remotely,
cooking the house and
completely messing up
the coroner's time of death estimate.
And what did they do with Lynette?
If they were gonna kill her,
they would've done that here.
That's the smart move.
Well, maybe Sofia has
a hard time with that.
I mean, it is her sister,
so they kidnap her, right?
To buy themselves some time.
And where did they take her?
Ask dimon what he
was doing in Fontana.
You see, Fontana's not that far
away. It has to be relatively close.
They gotta get there and
back in the same night.
And there's no paper trail, no
charges for either of them in that area.
So they're taking her someplace
secure. Someplace one of them owns.
Someplace they've been
meeting up to have their affair.
Someplace remote...
But familiar.
It's okay.
Lynette a cost a is gonna
be okay thanks to you.
It's a job offer.
Come be a consultant. Do
this full time. We need you.
I'm not cut out for this.
But thank you.
If you change your mind,
you know where to find me.
Mom.
Mom. Mom! Mom!
- Letty!
- Mom! Mom!
Ava, I need to talk to you about your dad.
Mom, no.
You should have seen the look on
his face when I told him I was pregnant.
- Stop it.
- He was so happy.
Then why did he leave?
He didn't leave. He... he vanished.
Something happened to him.
And the police, they never believed me.
But I know that he
would not have left you.
Hey, but he did. He's gone.
He's been gone for 15 years, mom,
and lying to me about it isn't gonna help.
Honey, I'm not lying to you.
I'm telling you that he would
not have done that to us.
Then stop lying to yourself.
I want a raise. Add 30% to your offer.
No, add 20% and childcare.
You figure that part out.
Is that it?
If I work for you, you work for me too.
I need you to find someone.
His name is Roman sinquerra.
And he vanished 15 years ago.
The police say that he just skipped
town, but I know that he didn't.
So, I need help.
Please help me find him.
You got a deal.