Nah, nah, nah, nah, nah.
Yo, too damn sloppy on the heel
stand to hop, shuffle, ball change.
Here we go. A two, a
one, two, three, four.
What do you think? Too
much for my first day?
Not enough.
Yup. Always on the
same page. I like that.
Okay, what do you think?
You're pleased?
Great. As long as you are happy.
Let's do it. Yeah.
You're my best advocate...
- Am I in a dream?
- Chocolate chip pancakes.
Eggs à la Elliot.
- Which are what exactly?
- Scrambled eggs.
Sausage pucks.
Freshly brewed cup of coffee.
And a squeezed forever ago oj.
You guys, I don't even know
what to say. You're the best.
We wanted you to be ready
for your first official day doing...
What exactly are you doing?
Helping the cops solve cases.
Do you get your own squad car?
No, but I will be making enough money
that we can get our actual car back.
You know, speaking of more money,
we should talk iras at some point soon.
Simple, sep and roth.
Yeah. Let's not get ahead of ourselves.
The point is this job, you
guys, if I don't quit or get fired,
is gonna help us out. In lots of ways.
Okay, gotta run. Thank
you so much again.
- Don't eat those.
- Wasn't planning on it.
Good morning. Dad!
You are just in time. And
good news, she's a barfer today.
Barfy baby. I got her.
- Thank you.
- You're welcome.
Now that the LAPD
is paying me to Manny.
I love you!
- Bye, mom. Love you.
- Love you.
Samson, you busting
out the monk straps?
What the heck? Who's the lucky lady?
She's a florist. Loves chess, lives close.
You dog.
I better be invited to that wedding.
Let's hope.
Aren't you our cleaning lady?
Not today. Check back in with me
tomorrow after we see how this goes.
We're really doing this?
We're doing it.
Damien Ross. Fell
three stories onto his car.
911 got an anonymous call from
someone who heard the impact.
Emts rushed him to county general.
He's in surgery now,
not sure if he'll make it.
At first blush, I'm
thinking suicide attempt.
Strange as it may sound, Damien
was found wearing tap shoes,
so maybe he jumped
after one last dance.
"" What?
No, nothing. Just... I mean... you know.
No, I don't know.
Morgan, if this is gonna work,
and I can't believe
I'm actually saying this,
you have to say what you're thinking.
Okay. I think we need
to get up on that roof.
Okay. See how easy that was?
Okay, so... let it rip.
"Let it rip"?
I thought you were gonna hit me
with a bunch of obscure scientific
or historical details about
rooftops or something.
Okay, well, "lay it on
me" would work there.
Okay.
Was anything attached to this
when you guys first got here?
No, the techs haven't been up
here yet, so we're first to the scene.
Okay.
- Morgan.
- What?
Gloves, please.
Yes, gloves. How
could I forget the gloves?
So, if something were
attached to this tripod
and it got knocked over, it would be...
Looks like you found Damien's phone.
I don't know if this was Damien's.
So, you think someone
else was up here with him?
Well, I certainly don't think he
was up here dancing by himself.
Whoever's phone this is was left -
handed based on the smudge patterns.
We'll dust for prints.
I don't know who this little guy is.
De perros de Tijuana.
Mexican baseball team. They
won the title a few years back.
Hey, so you're good for the
obscure sports references.
Got it. What are you doing?
- Turning on the phone, Morgan.
- I can turn the phone on.
I'm sure you can.
It is possible that Damien was a
left-handed baseball fan, you know.
Michelangelo's 1487 painting,
the torment of Saint Anthony.
It's a glorious depiction
of the struggle suffered
by the patron Saint of lost things.
Well, maybe Damien was a catholic.
Until we know for
certain that this phone is
you know, karadec, normally I
drive a 1970 oldsmobile vista cruiser.
It's in the shop right
now, but I love that car.
I love it so much it loves me.
We take good care of each other.
It's probably the healthiest
relationship I've ever had.
Damien loved his car.
He was obsessed with it.
If he was trying to take his own life,
I am not buying for a second that he would
take his beloved '81 cutlass with him.
And you may very well be right, Morgan,
but that's still just a theory. I need
evidence! You need your evidence.
You love your evidence. I'm learning that.
Have you ever seen tap dancing live?
It's captivating. Here's what I think:
Damien was up here
dancing under the stars,
fully immersed in the intoxicating
art of improvisation that is tap,
when someone pushed
him over the edge.
So I just checked in with CSI to see
if Damien had his cell phone on him
when he arrived at the hospital.
And?
He did. This phone
belongs to someone else.
So now we pray to Saint Anthony
that he helps us find whoever
pushed Damien off this roof.
Daphne, I need an update on Damien.
On hold, county general. Stand by.
Oz, talk to me.
Fast-tracking CSI
evidence from Damien's car.
Good. Karadec and Morgan are
in transit with the suspect's phone.
I want it processed within the hour.
Selena.
Lieutenant melon, to
what do I owe the pleasure?
You feeling generous today?
I need an extra pair of
hands in robbery-homicide.
Well, it's your lucky day because we're
just hanging around here in major crimes
with a whole lot of nothing to do.
This is serious.
Six jewelry stores hit
in the last two months.
I'm getting hammered in
the press, cap's all over me.
I'm even catching
heat from my girlfriend,
'cause she's too scared to go
shop for an engagement ring.
Aren't you supposed to
shop for the engagement ring?
I need to catch this guy before
someone gets hurt or killed.
You know I wouldn't ask if I
didn't really need the assist.
'Cause if there was a scuffle on the roof
we can assume our suspect's gonna have
have scratches. I get it.
Well, not just scratches. I
mean, based on this photo, look.
That's an ass pattern.
An ass pattern.
Yeah.
Listen, I've fallen a lot in my life,
and trust me, whoever made those
marks has lacerations all over the buns
and likely a bruised coccyx. Tailbone.
I know what a coccyx is.
- Daphne, what's the latest on Damien?
- Still on hold.
Hey, melon alert.
"Melon alert"?
All right, listen up. Teamwork
makes the dream work.
And right now, our friends
in robbery need our help.
Beggars can't be
choosers. I'll take anyone.
Except the cleaning lady.
You owe me one.
I'll ride with lieutenant melon.
Damien's out of surgery,
but on life support.
It could go either way.
All right, so starting right now,
we treat this as a murder case
because if this young man dies, it will be.
Daphne, pull all security footage
from surrounding buildings.
We need eyes on everyone
who was there that night.
You two go to the hospital.
See if this boy's family knows
anyone who might want him dead.
I'll be right there.
- Hey, can I talk to you for a second?
- Of course.
So, when I agreed to take this job
I promised to look into your missing ex.
S... Roman sinquerra.
Yeah. I'm assuming you might
need more than just his name.
You said he disappeared 15 years
ago. Can you tell me what happened?
Yes. He went out to buy diapers for Ava,
my oldest. She was just a baby back then.
He was driving a 1995 Mazda
rx - 7, California plates aahq729.
That's the last time I saw him.
Had you and Roman been
fighting? No. Listen, I
know what it sounds like,
like he went out for milk
and never came back.
It's a cliché for a reason.
That wasn't Roman.
All right. I'll see what I can find.
Thank you.
You know what the best part
of my day has been so far?
Am I gonna be flattered or offended?
Hopefully neither.
The best part of my day was
showing up to that crime scene
and not seeing a body on top of that car.
Pretty sure I don't have
to tell you why. But now...
Now we don't know
what we're walking into.
You know, in this line of work,
Morgan, you have to hope for the best
but be prepared for the worst.
It's your first day, so if you
wanna wait in the waiting room
I'm good.
Okay.
Ms. Ross.
Please, call me winnie.
Winnie, I'm detective
karadec. This is Morgan gillory.
She's assisting me on your son's case.
We are so sorry about what happened.
How's he doing?
The doctor said they don't
know if he'll survive the night.
And if he does, they don't
know if he'll walk again.
But growing up where he
did, he's beat the odds before.
He'll do it again.
I know this is a very difficult time, winnie.
We believe somebody pushed Damien
off that roof and, well, I have to ask
I know what you're gonna ask,
detective, and the answer is no.
There is nobody in this world
who would wanna hurt my boy.
You know, on the way over here,
I had the opportunity to watch your
son tap, and it took my breath away.
Your kid can really dance.
When Damien falls in love
with something, watch out.
Passionate and stubborn, that one.
I wonder who he gets that from.
Damien has made his share of
mistakes before he started working at bsb.
But they helped him get his life together.
I'm sorry, I'm not familiar with bsb.
Body shop brothers.
It's a custom auto shop.
They hire at-risk youth
and ex - cons to fix
up cars and get their lives back on track.
Damien is saving the money he's
making from working at the shop
for a plane ticket to New
York. He's Broadway bound.
If he can just p-pull through
this time, if he can just...
Beat the odds again, like you said.
Mama Ross?
Pardon me a moment.
I see two lefties.
And at least one catholic.
Not exactly a smoking gun.
- The phone was his.
- Whose?
The one who's got his
arm around Ms. Ross.
You see that elbow scar tattooed
over to look like baseball stitching?
That's from a Tommy John
injury. From a torn ulnar ligament.
And he was a pitcher.
For de perros de Tijuana.
Sorry to interrupt.
I'm detective karadec. Can
we talk? It'll just take a minute.
Damien. Quite the talent.
He's next-level, no
question. Good-looking too.
So, Roland, how
jealous of him were you?
Jealous enough to push him off a roof?
- I told you, I didn't push him.
- But you fought with him.
- That's when you dropped your phone.
- No!
Damien and I never fought.
Check his coccyx!
- Sounds like you have a suggestion?
- They gotta check his coccyx.
I know this looks really bad, but
we have reason to believe there's bruises
and lacerations on the suspect's backside.
We could get a warrant and make
you show us, or you could just tell us.
Make the right choice for us all, please.
You're right, we were up there last night.
But Damien, he's like a brother to me.
We met at the shop. When I told him I
used to dance, he offered to teach me.
He helped me get my life back together.
Then what happened on the roof?
Someone else pushed him.
Roland, do you actually
expect us to believe that?
I don't know where the
guy came from, okay?
He must have been
waiting there or something
because one minute we
were dancing and then...
He knocked me on my ass.
By the time I got up, Damien
was gone, him too, so I ran.
And let me guess, it was too
dark for you to see his face?
Without a witness who actually
saw Roland push Damien,
we barely have enough to hold him.
Daphne, what about eyes in the sky?
Well, security camera across the street
showed Damien's car pull in at 1:42 A.M.
- Any cameras in the alley?
- No. Got 'em everywhere else though.
It's an old office building.
No occupants since last year.
Maybe squatters took up
residence in the building
and didn't like noise
coming from upstairs.
We checked. They got
this place locked down tight.
No one going in or out in the last week.
So either our third guy teleported
in and out, or he doesn't exist.
He might.
What did you guys
do with Damien's car?
See I'm not the only one who
likes a little color on the nails.
What have we got here?
Mushroom mimosa?
- Biscotti body, but close.
- Ooh.
Boy.
Okay, I'm sorry. I'm not the
one who names nail polishes.
You've got three very patient officers
with you here in the impound garage
and I can tell you that at least one of
them would like to know the reason why.
Well, the reason why is
plasma chameleon paint.
See, plasma chameleon paint is
known for its color-changing properties
because the pigment makes the color change
depending on the angle and the lighting.
And that is why it is used
sometimes for nail polishes
and sometimes for custom
paint jobs for luxury cars.
Now, your lab... well, our lab found
our lab found traces of
paint in the trunk of the car,
which didn't surprise us
given that he does work
in an auto body shop that paints cars.
But Damien loved this baby so much,
there's no way he wasn't vacuuming
every square inch over the weekends.
That is correct.
And since there's not a trace of
that paint on the outside of the car,
and I highly doubt any of
those men hopped into the trunk
and painted his nails... Anybody?
You think whoever pushed Damien
off the roof worked at the body shop
and hid in the trunk of his car.
Yes, I do.
Roland was telling the truth.
There was a third man on the roof
and that man hitched a ride
to the scene of his own crime.
That would explain why we didn't
see anyone arriving on the scene.
The assailant got out of the car in
the alley and then followed them up.
It's a good theory, Morgan. The
only problem is that this is an '81 regal.
The trunk release safety feature
wasn't introduced until the mid-'80s,
which means if someone
did sneak in the trunk,
- they wouldn't have been able to get out.
- I thought about that too.
But what if one of Damien's coworkers
decided to give him a
little unwanted trunk job.
Sounded grosser than I wanted to.
Morgan, you are not helping.
- Close me in.
- I don't think that's a good idea...
That was aggressive.
This is getting weird now.
Okay, yeah. Give her a minute.
Yeah, there's no more
minutes for this, I'm...
Yep, found it. Little
rigged latch release thingy.
Turns out, trunk job it is.
Looks like you and Morgan have
to go see the body shop brothers.
Am I helping now?
Detective karadec.
Knox, right?
Chased you through
echo park a few years back.
What was it? Stolen
property? Identity theft?
Both.
- What are you doing here, detective?
- Just doing my job.
Now we have reason to believe
that the person who tried to
kill Damien works here too.
Detective,
if you're insinuating what I think you're
insinuating, we don't appreciate that.
I'm not here to earn
your appreciation, Knox.
I'm here to find out
who tried to kill Damien.
Then go find him already.
I have an idea.
Hear me out. What if we did a trade?
Brought yourself a
random hot blonde, man?
I don't know about random.
She's a consultant.
Let me handle this, please.
What kind of trade?
You guys tell us where
you were last night,
and we get Damien's
car back to the shop asap.
It's at impound. That takes months.
What if it doesn't have to?
We're listening.
I bet detective karadec
here could call in a favor
and get Damien's car back
faster than he ran you down, Knox.
Which isn't really saying much, but.
- Morgan, I actually... I can't just...
- that way you guys will have time
to fix up his car and
get it all ready for him
when he wakes up and
comes home from the hospital.
I didn't know the guy,
but I'm getting the sense he would
do the exact same thing for you.
Damn right he would.
Excuse me.
Okay. Give me two
minutes with these guys.
For what?
Two minutes and I will get their alibies
right quick, right here on the spot.
You promise?
Can you go just make a phone
call to see if you can get the car?
Otherwise, we're not getting
anything out of them, you know that.
Two minutes.
Okay.
Getting the sense that
some of you are very angry
about what happened to your
friend. Or numb. Heartbroken.
All very reasonable
emotions to have right now,
but wouldn't you guys
feel a little bit better
if you could help us find
the guy who hurt your friend?
You guys gotta tell me
where you were last night.
'Cause if you don't tell me right now,
the cops are just gonna waste
time talking to other people,
like you, who did
absolutely nothing wrong.
Go ahead, man.
Yeah. I guess I'll go first.
Okay.
First up is Dane.
Dane was on his fifth and,
hopefully, final date with Lola last night.
The woman sounds like a nightmare.
I hope he makes a good
choice, but he's young and stupid.
Then we got big bear Knox.
Knox was in big bear with his dad.
They have a family cabin.
They go there pretty much
weekly to vamp it up a bit.
Fun perk of the job, I did
get an open invite to visit.
Not a perk of the job.
Not for you.
Then we got slappy. Tall
drink of water, handsome fella.
Tough nut to crack, but I tell you what...
Morgan. Is it safe to assume you
have this kind of info on all these guys?
Yeah. That was the job.
And where were you?
So, slappy was on a date with his
Morgan, hold up.
But I'm in the middle
of painting a picture.
You guys keep interrupting, I have to say.
And I'm sure it's as
stunning as the sistine chapel,
but we really don't have time for this.
I'm sorry, you don't have time to give
these gentlemen the benefit of the doubt?
Did you all hear that?
Interesting. Is that because they have
a hard time with authority? Who doesn't?
Lots of people. Just download
Daphne with the details.
I'll make a case file to
share with a four-person team
that will track and trace the movements
of every suspect as part of our acp.
Acp?
Alibi confirmation protocol. Come on.
Great.
She's a lot more fun than you.
All right.
We got our work cut out for us.
I wanna find out which one
of these body shop bros is
our prime suspect by sunrise.
And since it turns out Roland was
telling the truth about the third person
I'll process his release.
Did you know that in 13th - century Sweden,
anyone could put a thief to death? Anyone.
Say I caught Ava
swiping my rubik's cube.
I could chop her head
off and it would just be like,
"hold on. Why is the head
rolling around the floor?"
"Don't know. I guess she
must've stolen something."
Ava, did you take Elliot's rubik's cube?
Yeah, mom. I lust after that rubik's cube.
When are we getting the car back?
I'm tired of leaving 45
minutes early to take the bus.
As soon as I can afford
to get it out of the shop.
You've been saying that forever.
I know I have, Ava.
And every single time I have to
say it again, it kills me a little more.
Ava got an a on her art project.
You did?
That's great. Why didn't
you tell me? Let me see it.
I think it shows some
real cubist influence.
Look. It's whiskers.
Buddy, that is really good.
It's okay.
Follow me.
What are you showing me?
This.
What are they?
They're murals painted
all over Los Angeles.
Aren't they great?
Yeah, they're pretty cool.
Your father painted those.
Awesome. Thanks
for showing me these.
Hey. You've been upset that
you didn't inherit my talents,
but look, you got your dad's.
I got the talent of the guy
who walked out on us. Cool.
He did not walk out on us,
Ava, okay? I know it in my bones.
He just didn't do it. He loved us.
And now I've got the full
weight of the LAPD looking into it.
We're gonna get to the truth.
How about they work on
getting our car back instead?
So, what? Just because you
can't sleep, I don't get to either?
Do you remember
how Damien's mom said
no one in the world
would wanna hurt her son?
Sometimes even moms
get it wrong, Morgan.
Maybe this time we did. Let's dance.
- What are we doing?
- Come on.
Okay.
We thought the third man came
up onto the roof to kill Damien.
- And now you don't?
- Well, maybe.
But the best place for the killer to hide,
where he wouldn't be seen by the dancers,
is over here behind this structure.
So when Damien is close to the
edge, that is the killer's moment.
He's got to move without
hesitation. He bolts forward.
He knocks over the tripod,
the cell phone goes flying.
All of which we already know,
Morgan. So what are we missing?
We forgot to look up.
Are you familiar with
the opposition effect?
Remind me.
The opposition effect is an
astronomical phenomenon
during the first and last quarter
phases of the moon cycle.
That is when the moon is at
a 90-degree angle to the sun
and that's when it's at its brightest.
And that happened last night?
Not only that. Roland
called 911 at 2:14 A.M. right?
So let's say he needed ten, 15
minutes to get down off the roof,
get himself safe, pull himself
together and make a phone call.
Which would have placed the
time of impact shortly after 2:00.
Which places the moon right there.
So, what do you think the killer saw?
Roland and Damien were in full shadow.
The moon was shining
right into the killer's eyes.
Moving fast under these conditions, he
couldn't see who it was he was pushing.
Damien's mom was right.
No one wanted to kill her boy.
Our assailant pushed the wrong guy.
He meant to kill Roland.
We released him from
custody a few hours ago.
If someone still wants him
dead, they can try again.
We gotta find Roland
before the killer does.
Yeah.
- Hey, momma.
- Hey. Everybody's okay back there?
We're good. I already put Chloe to bed.
And our son's mandarin
is really coming along.
Though I guess I wouldn't know.
Yeah. Ava's okay?
She is still in her room.
She came out for some ice cream.
And acknowledged me with
a grunt, which is reassuring.
Daphne just texted me Roland's
number and home address.
Ludo, I gotta go. I'm gonna be
later than I thought. I'm so sorry.
- Yeah. Is everything okay?
- Yeah. No, I'm fine.
Don't worry about me,
okay? Thank you so much.
Mor... yeah, she's gone.
- Yeah?
- Roland, it's detective karadec.
- Who?
- Can you turn the music down, please?
- Not my call, bro.
- He's not at home.
It's detective karadec with the
LAPD, Roland. Where are you, buddy?
We need you to get
someplace safe.-What?
We believe you are in danger.
Sorry, man. Can't hear you.
This is Roland. Leave a message.
I'll have Daphne see if she
can locate him with a trace.
I think he's at gateway towers.
- What?
- It's a warehouse that hosts parties.
And you think he's there?
Yeah, I heard the song change
from flip fantasia to culture beat,
so I googled '90s remix party and
the only one that came up for tonight
- was at gateway towers.
- At gateway towers.
It's a little crime-fighting
tool called Google.
Might be a good time to call for backup.
They're on the way, but
we don't have time to wait.
Okay. When Roland left the precinct,
he was wearing a green hoodie,
black-and-white Adidas
superstars, and a red casio watch.
Let's hope he didn't change.
Hey! Hey! Where's Roland?
- I don't know.
- Is he here?
Hey, what's going on?
They're looking for Roland.
How many times can you
arrest a guy in one day?
We're trying to help the
young man. Where is he?
I don't know, man. He was
here. I hadn't seen him in a minute.
Please help us find him.
Okay.
I'm going this way.
Excuse me.
God. Feel like I'm on the bus.
Roland!
- Hey! Roland!
- No, I'm John.
Nice to meet you, John. Excuse me.
Yo, yo. He's over here.
Roland! Roland, come on, man.
We gotta get you outta here. You...
You know, Morgan, what happened
tonight is just part of the job.
It's the worst part of the job.
I wish I could tell you it
gets easier, but it does not.
We didn't get here fast enough,
not tonight, but next time, we will.
And when we do, I know we're
gonna have you to thank for it.
'Cause what you did on that
roof tonight, that was something.
I can't really take all the
credit for it. I had an assist.
Yeah?
Yeah, my daughter
Ava, her dad's a painter.
Was a painter. I don't
know if he still paints.
I haven't seen him in a long time, but...
He used to tell me that light was
the most important part of the job.
Hey, guys. Found something
you're gonna wanna see.
- Hey, if this is too much for you...
- no. I'm good. Let's find this guy.
All those people and nobody
noticed a man being shot?
Too loud. Plus all the lights.
The gunshot was just
one more flash in the dark.
But if we look closer...
Looks like Roland knew his killer.
And the killer knew everyone there
would have a phone on so he hid his face.
And this is all we got?
Yeah, for now.
Any update on Damien?
Last we called the hospital,
it was still touch and go.
You okay?
Yeah. Well, I'm just
gonna take a little walk.
There is nobody in this world
who would wanna hurt my boy.
In this line of work, Morgan,
you have to hope for the best
but be prepared for the worst.
Yes?
Do you have this on surveillance?
Yeah.
Play it. Excuse me. What are you doing?
Play the robbery.
Okay.
You take orders from her
now? This is highly inappropriate.
Hang on, hang on.
Stop. Right there.
You see those sparks
after the muzzle flash?
The color and the trajectory.
That is a very old gun.
Now you're ammunitions expert.
I'm not, but I took my
kids to pioneertown once,
and the gunsmith went on and
on about guns in the wild west.
- What's going on?
- Come here. Look at these sparks.
Okay, these sparks occur when
there is copper or lead left in the barrel.
Usually, a very old or
poorly maintained gun,
and they cause a flash
like the one in this robbery
and in the one that killed Roland.
So, great. Our robber
is at the o.K. Corral.
So you're saying you think that his
robber and our killer are the same guy?
I'm saying same gun.
What do you think?
I think you should give her
some time with your board.
You serious? My board?
- Coming through. Thanks.
- Excuse us.
Eyes up.
Lieutenant melon has
terrible handwriting.
The worst.
Hey, you really think
his robber is our killer?
I don't know. But I know
we gotta figure it out.
Okay, so where do we start?
We start with why.
Why would this guy
wanna murder Roland?
You believe this?
The cleaning lady's
rearranging my boards.
You see a cleaning lady. I see more.
Okay, sparkles. That's enough.
Morgan, what do you got?
I noticed something. We've
got five robberies, right?
The first three are here, here and here.
And at each site,
an eyewitness saw the robber
get into a different getaway car.
A red Camaro, a blue
mini... An orange corvette.
She gonna read my entire
case board back to me?
Now, at the fourth and fifth site, there
was no report of a getaway car at all.
So, it's possible the driver
could've parked farther away?
- Or something happened to the car.
- Or practice makes perfect.
They got faster and no one saw him go.
What do you think?
I think the robber lost his getaway car.
More importantly, I
think he lost his driver.
Now, see what these last two
jewelry stores have in common?
Okay, I'll give you a clue.
Now she's drawing on my map.
Really? Does no one take public transit?
Okay, well, guess who does. This
guy. So let me walk you through this.
This is the red line. Right here
are two stops along the red line.
These are two jewelry stores that
are within one block of those two stops.
You think the robber was on foot?
Yes, I do.
And I think the missing getaway driver,
someone who had access to multiple cars,
was Roland.
Think about it. He worked at the shop.
Any of the cars that stayed there
overnight, he would've had access to.
And the robber started hitting
stores on foot a month ago.
Right. That was around the same time
that Damien helped
Roland escape a life of crime,
and they started posting
their dancing videos together.
That's right, so Roland
tells the robber, "I'm out."
But the robber can't trust
that Roland won't out him.
He knows that Damien and Roland
are dancing on rooftops all over la.
He decides to rig Damien's
trunk to push Roland off the roof.
But he pushes the wrong guy.
Now he's gotta find Roland at the club.
And to make sure he
does it right this time,
he brings his gun.
Look, this is great police work,
Morgan, but do you know who this guy is?
No, I don't.
But I do have an idea
about how we can find him.
All units 6837, we have
a 187. Respond code 3.
Repeat, all units 6837, we
have a 187. Respond code 3.
- Hands in the air! Nobody move!
- LAPD! Put your hands up!
- Drop your weapon!
- LAPD!
Put the gun on the ground
slowly. Lay down on the floor.
Belly on the floor now. Down.
Hands behind your back.
Let's go.
He looks confused.
- Are you confused, griff?
- Lawyer.
You don't wanna talk. I
get it. You don't have to.
But I bet you're wondering
how we knew you'd be here.
- Can I tell him?
- Tell him.
See, I think you really were upset
about what happened to Damien.
The red eyes, the tears, those were
real 'cause you didnt't mean to hurt him.
But you see, mixed in with that
sadness, I saw something else: Guilt.
Side note, contrition
gonna be helpful for you
when you're talking to the parole board
after you're convicted
of murdering Roland.
So, how did we manage to
show up and spoil your party?
Well, joke's on you, it's our
party, bud, and we invited you.
Because we noticed that every
time you would Rob a jewelry store,
it would happen right after a code
3 went out on the police scanner.
You figured the fewer units available,
the likelier chance you'd
have to be able to get away.
But, luckily for the
residents of Los Angeles,
there's no actual code
3 happening tonight.
Just a 211, yours.
Let's go.
Heard a little rumor. Somebody just closed
their first official case with the LAPD.
So I did help.
You had your moments, which is
why soto asked me to give you this.
First official paycheck. Lands early.
No way.
Wow.
Karadec.
Yeah. Got it.
That was the hospital.
Damien's awake.
Please come on in.
- Hi.
- There's somebody I want you to meet.
These are the people I told you were
trying to figure out what happened.
Thank you.
- Damien moved his toes today.
- No way.
The doctors believe with some
work, he'll be dancing in no time.
That's right.
You know, because of you, I was able to
find out this guy's never seen a tap show.
What? You got something
against a good time?
No, no. I love a good time.
Then one day I'll get you
some tickets. Both of you.
Least I could do.
I heard about Roland and griff.
It's over now though. Don't worry.
Nah. I'm just getting started.
Now, what the hell
are y'all still doing here?
Get your ass, get back to
the shop and fix my car. Now.
- Okay.
- Gosh.
That's what I said, for the record.
- Yeah.
- Take care.
I need some wheels.
You know, that's not too
bad for your first case, gillory.
I'm just glad I was able to help.
Have you thought about quitting
while you're ahead, you know?
Kinda go out on top.
You do not want me to quit.
You're having way too much fun.
- I am?
- Yep.
Like driving you all over town.
No. No, that does have to stop.
No way!
I'm so sorry to just pop by, Morgan.
You're firing me in the
comfort of my own home?
That's a classy move. I respect that.
- You wanna come in?
- No, no, that's okay. I had some news.
You were on my way home.
I thought you'd wanna hear it.
- What is it?
- I followed up on Roman's car.
Turns out it ended up in police
impound three days after he disappeared.
It was abandoned in a costco parking lot
a couple of miles from
where you both lived.
In the short inventory of items
discovered in the car was a box of diapers,
which of course begs the question,
if Roman really wanted
to abandon your family,
why would he stop and buy diapers first?
You believe me.
We're gonna find out
what happened to Roman.
I promise.
Thank you.