19 years for a loaf of bread.
Aaargh!
My guess, you'll be back in here
before another year's gone by.
And next time it'll be for life.
You can never win.
Do you promise you'll be
good to me, Felix?
On my life.
Three galloping horses
will be carrying us home
to our mamas and papas.
We are leaving. We have left.
Oh, Cosette, whatever
are we going to do now?
Rich pickings here. Aargh!
Ooh!
You saved my life. Who are you?
Thenardier, sir.
Jean Valjean, my brother,
I have bought your soul with that
silverware and these candlesticks.
You belong to good.
Did you see my 40 sous, monsieur?
Get lost! Go on!
You've got my money.
You're a dirty thief!
Petit Gervais!
Maman, I'm tired.
Two, three…
Oh, there's a good girl.
All right.
Maman loves you.
Very much.
♪ Si le despotisme conspire
♪ Conspirons la perte des rois
♪ Liberte
♪ Liberte… ♪
You have two lovely children
there, madame. They are.
They are, though I says so,
I shouldn't.
Eponine and Azelma.
My pride and joy, ain't you, girls?
But you've got a lovely
little one too.
And such fine clothes.
Do you want to come and sit down,
take the weight off your feet?
Thank you, madame. Look, your
little girl can play with mine.
What's her name? Cosette.
Have you come a long way?
You look ever so tired. From Paris.
I'm on my way to Montreuil.
I've heard there's some good work
to be had there.
Where's hubby?
Erm…
He's… He's dead.
Oh, dear.
So you've had a hard time of it,
I dare say.
Yes, I have.
But once I get into a steady job,
I'll soon be on my feet again.
Yeah, of course you will.
Still, it's not easy holding down a
job with a little one in tow, is it?
No.
Do you keep the inn here?
Yeah, that's right, dear.
Thenardier's the name.
See that sign there?
That's my husband.
He was the hero of Waterloo.
He saved a colonel's life.
Carried him on his back
through a hail of bullets.
Was your hubby a military man
at all?
No.
A poet. Oh!
Very nice.
Not a lot of money in that though,
I shouldn't wonder.
Oh, look at that!
Children make friends
in no time, don't they?
Maman!
If you walked past that,
you'd swear they were three sisters.
Could you look after my child
for a while, madame?
Oh… You see, you were right.
It's hard to get work, especially
when you have a child with you.
Yeah, especially when
you're on your own.
When I saw your little ones looking
so pretty and well cared for,
I knew that the good Lord
had guided me here.
Will you?
I could pay.
Six francs a month.
Seven.
Good morning, mademoiselle.
Monsieur.
It'll have to be seven. You wouldn't
want us to skimp on her meals,
so that's seven francs,
six months in advance.
I'll be back before then to
get her, I'm sure, monsieur.
In that case we'd refund you, but
those are the terms, regrettably.
We can't make any exceptions
or where would we be?
Six sevens, that's 42 francs.
Yeah.
And we'll have to think about
initial expenses too, of course.
Shall we say a nominal sum
of 15 francs?
15 and 42, that's 57 francs.
57?
I'll pay it.
You will look after her
and love her like your own?
Oh, we love her already,
don't we, Thenardier?
Of course we do. How could we not?
Come here. Come on.
Believe me, mademoiselle,
your little darling will want
for nothing in our loving care,
yeah.
Thank you.
Come here. Come here, little ones.
Come and play with Daddy.
Oh, look! That's a lovely cup
of tea you've got there, eh.
Cosette, now you're to be
a good girl,
and this kind lady and gentleman
will look after you for a while.
No.And Maman will be back
for you very soon.
No, Maman.
It's all right, my darling.
Maman! Maman!
Maman, please!
Maman.
Maman. I'll be back, darling.
It's all for the best, you'll see.
Please, no!
Can't let them have all their
own way, can we? Maman!
All right, bye, Maman. Maman!
Maman, please! Please!
Come on.
Maman!
Monsieur Madeleine.
Pere Madeleine, as he is known
by many of you,
came to Montreuil three years ago.
On the very day he arrived,
he rushed into a burning house
and brought out two children,
saving their lives.
He has brought new industry
to the area
and his factory has turned
the fortunes of our town around.
We are all better off
because of Pere Madeleine.
He has been a wise
and generous employer.
Ever reluctant to put himself
forward,
he has at last been persuaded
by the grateful citizens
to accept the office
of Mayor of Montreuil.
Mesdames et Messieurs,
Monsieur Madeleine.
Monsieur Madeleine!
Citizens of Montreuil,
my friends…
…I thank you for the, erm,
trust that you've, you've…
you've shown in me.
Good day.
Monsieur Madeleine!
Excuse me.
I'm looking for some work.
Come.
Come. Nothing to be frightened of.
Sit here.
Your name?
Fantine, monsieur,
Fantine Thibault.
And you are new in the town?
Yes.
I was living in Paris.
What work were you doing there?
I was a seamstress
at a dressmaker's.
Well, the work here needs
nimble fingers too,
so, you think you can learn it?
Yes.
And if you take me,
I'll work very hard.
You won't regret it.
Good.
So what are your, erm,
family circumstances?
I am alone in the world, sir.
No husband? No.
No lover?
No children?
As I said, sir, I'm…
I'm alone in the world.
It's very important to me
and to you, Fantine,
that you're completely honest
with me.
You don't believe me?
Why should you care about my life
anyway? I care about all my workers.
So…
…all alone in the world?
Yes, monsieur.
I'll take you on
a month's probation.
And if you work well,
you can prosper here.
Thank you, monsieur. Thank you.
Madame Victurnien,
will you show her to a table?
Are you are able to begin
right away?
Yes, of course, Monsieur Madeleine.
Good.
Well, go now.
Thank you again, monsieur.
Thank you.
His bedhead's supposed to be
solid gold.
Carved angels, wings - everything.
I wouldn't mind spreading
my wings in his bed.
What?!
Be a bit gentler, Fantine.
You don't want to snag it.
That's good, Fantine.
You're getting the hang of it.
Monsieur le Maire!
All right, boys?
There you are.
All right?
Here, take that. Good boy.
And I hope this finds you well,
Monsieur and Madame Thenardier…
…and that my Cosette has been
a good girl for you.
Tell her Maman loves her
and sends her a thousand kisses,
and hopes to be able to fetch
her very soon. Collect her.
Collect her.
Thank you.
And she sends you a thousand kisses.
Mwah!
And hopes to be able to
collect her very soon.
"I remain your very humble…"
Oooh!
Et cetera, et cetera.
Very fancy language!
She sent the money, eh?
Sent a bit extra to buy the dear
little thing some treats.
That won't be happening. If she's
got enough to send a bit extra,
it's time to raise the rates.
What do you reckon? 12 francs?
No, 15. I'll write to her today.
I could do with a treat, Thenardier.
And you shall get one,
my little pigeon.
All in good time,
when things look up a bit.
Any spare cash has got to go
towards the bills.
I don't know what it is,
but whatever I do,
nothing seems to prosper. Oh!
The Wild Duck down the road
gets plenty of custom. Why not me?
Back in your corner, Gavroche!
Come on, you little beast,
and out of my sight.
Do you know, it's a strange thing,
Thenardier,
but I've never been able to
take to that one.
I could do anything for my girls,
but that nasty little creature
doesn't bring any maternal
instincts out in me at all.
Born under a bad sign, love.
Nothing you can do about it.
Do you know, Thenardier,
you know you said how
it's funny this place never
seems to prosper? Yes, my dear.
Have you ever considered, my love,
that people talk?
And the coachman, like,
he might say,
"Oh, don't go in there, sir, cos
Thenardier waters down the beer
"and short changes you
into the bargain!"
I've often thought you could have a sign outside
saying, "Come in here if you want to be swindled."
You shut your mouth.
When I want your advice,
I'll ask for it, yeah?
Go!
What are you looking at?
You want some too?
Monsieur le Maire,
the new Chief of Police
is here to see you.
Monsieur le Maire, I thought
we should become acquainted.
My name is Javert.
I arrived in Montreuil last night.
Please take a seat, Inspector.
Can I offer you a drink?
No, thank you, Monsieur le Maire.
Forgive me, is that how
you prefer to be addressed?
I have heard you called
Pere Madeleine?
No, Monsieur le Maire will do.
You have a fine establishment here.
Thank you.
I am told you have restored
the prosperity of the town
by giving employment to all those
who are willing to work.
Consequently, there's very
little crime here.
Yes, I like to think
that that is so.
But a thief does not steal
because he is poor and desperate,
he steals because he has
a criminal mentality,
because he is degenerate,
because he is, to put it simply…
…wicked.
Well, there I have to tell you
that we disagree.
Really?
I believe most of us are capable
of good and evil,
and how we turn out depends
on our circumstances
and how we are treated.
And has your own experience
led you to that conclusion?
Yes, it has.
Monsieur le Maire,
I look forward to many interesting
discussions on this topic.
For now, let me assure you
that as your Chief of Police,
I shall do everything in my power
to seek out, apprehend and punish
every single wrong-doer
in your fine town.
Glad to hear it, Inspector.
I think your task won't be too
demanding here in Montreuil.
Perhaps.
On cursory inspection,
your citizens seem to be contented
and well ordered.
So, why does an ambitious man
choose a posting like this?
You deduce that I am ambitious.
Since I left the Prison Service,
I have dedicated myself
to pursuing not only
the obvious offences,
but the hidden ones.
Not only in the present,
but in the past.
Sometimes a man may be seen
to be rich, successful,
prosperous, virtuous…
…while all the time he may be
harbouring a secret.
Something rotten in his past.
Is it right that such a secret
should remain hidden?
Is it right that such a man
should continue to enjoy the fruits
of his wickedness undiscovered?
You think there is such a man
here in this town? Oh…
There are such men everywhere,
Monsieur le Maire.
That's what makes my work
so fascinating.
Of course, one must have
incontrovertible proof of guilt.
And that takes time.
Well, I don't want to keep you.
It's been a pleasure to make
your acquaintance. Likewise.
You know, I've been thinking,
as we've talked,
you remind me of someone I used
to know rather well at one time.
He stole from a child
and never paid for his crime.
I can't recall his name now.
Ah, well.
Goodnight…
…Monsieur le Maire.
I still can't believe
he didn't invite me.
Fabs would, wouldn't you, Fabby?
Shut up!
Has anyone ever been up there?
I bet he'd let Fantine in though.
Why me?
Cos he likes you
and we've seen him looking.
I bet he'd let you in his room.
Let you in his bed!
Would you, if he asked? No!
All right, hoity-toity.
What's that, Fantine? That's pretty.
It's nothing.
Look, Fabs, it's a little bird!
Ah, that is nice.
Who's it for? No-one.
Look out, Vicky's coming.
What's this?
Show me.
Who told you to do this?
No-one, madame,
but I'd finished my quota.
You're not here to amuse yourself
when you finish your quota.
You ask for more work.
Sorry, madame.
I've a good mind to dismiss you
on the spot. Please, no, madame.
Please.
Consider this a final warning.
Nasty old bitch.
"I know your little girl's health
and happiness is as dear to you
"as it is to my dear wife and me.
"A trifling sum…" A trifling sum?
This fellow writes abominably.
"A trifling sum of 15 francs
a month."
15 francs a month?!
I can't pay that!
Do you want to hear the rest
or not?
"We expect to receive this money
due to us
"very promptly."
She was some kind
of a prostitute, you say?
Well, I don't like to speak ill
of anyone, but, yes,
and no doubt the little girl
was conceived in sin
and had become some sort
of encumbrance.
Doesn't bear thinking about,
does it?
These people don't lead
natural lives.
She's probably forgotten all about
the little girl now.
She still writes to you.
Oh, yeah, I mean, now and then,
when she thinks about it.
"I hope you're looking after
her proper", and all that,
but what good is that to us
or the little girl?
I think…
…you have been taken advantage of.
You're right there, madame. Are you
thinking of staying a night or two?
We have a lovely room on the front
that's vacant just now.
I've taken a room at the Wild Duck.
The coachman recommended it.
Ah!
I was one of the heroes of Waterloo!
I was awarded the Legion d'Honneur
by Napoleon himself.
Would you care to examine it?
No, thank you.
No… yeah. Good day to you.
Thank you for your time.
Miserable old cow, eh?
Tant pis!
Oh, shut up!
Vive Napoleon!
Napoleon Bonaparte
did more harm to France
than all the armies of Britain,
Russia and Austria combined.
Hear, hear. A barbarian, a savage,
and thanks be to God,
now a despised exile.
But here is a young man
who thinks in the right way.
Gentlemen,
my grandson…
…Marius Pontmercy.
Napoleon was a traitor
to his country
and my father was a traitor
to his country too.
I spit upon them both!
Vive le Roi! Vive la France!
Good boy.
Monsieur, this letter
has just arrived.
Well, young man,
it seems your father
is on his deathbed.
Now, what do you say…
to that?
Good! Ha-ha!
And so do I!
So do I!
Well, off you go, my dear.
The boy should see his father
before he dies, monsieur.
It's only right.
Well, I won't forbid it,
if he wants to go.
Do you?
If you don't, you might be sorry
your whole life.
It's all right, I'll go with you.
Hm?
Women!
You have to love them, don't you?
You're a liar, aren't you?
Monsieur le Maire, come quickly!
Monsieur Madeleine! Madame…
Monsieur… No, please!
No, I have to go.
Monsieur! Monsieur!
Help me!
Unload that cart!
Control that horse!
Someone untether the horse.
Help me!
Aaargh!
Hold on, Constable,
we'll get you out!
Get someone to get it!
That's 20 minutes from here.
He'll be crushed to death by then!
It's all in hand, Monsieur le Maire.
Help me!
Aaargh!
Argh!
Congratulations, Monsieur le Maire.
Most instructive.
And witnessed by so many.
Monsieur Madeleine.
Not now.
This immoral young woman
is a disgrace to the factory
and the town.
It's not true. I'm innocent!
I regret to say, monsieur,
she is no better than a whore.
She has a bastard child
she abandoned at Montfermeil.
I never abandoned her!
I never abandoned her.
I send 15 francs per month.
More than half my wages. Lying
little whore. You're a disgrace!
Monsieur le Maire, believe me.
My Cosette is all I care about.
Lying little whore!
This is what she does when
she's supposed to be working.
A toy for her little bastard.
Believe me…
Enough, both of you! Enough!
Fantine Thibault?
Yes, monsieur.
I remember I asked you about
your family and you said
you were alone in the world.
I thought if I told you about my
little girl you'd turn me away.
You lied to me!
There was no harm in it.
I was frightened of you.
Don't listen to her, monsieur.
She's an immoral woman.
I am not! I am not.
But the child is yours?
Is that a crime?
And she abandoned it.
No, I didn't!
Please believe me.
I can't believe you!
You're dismissed.
But what am I going to do?
There's 50 francs. I advise you
to leave the town, mademoiselle.
But I can't leave this town.
I owe people money here.
Well, find some other employment!
They said that you were
a kind and good man.
And I thought you were.
But you're not.
You're a monster! A monster!
That's enough! That's enough!
How dare you insult
our good Pere Madeleine?
Out now!
This minute!
Come on!
Come on! Come on! Steady!
Chief Inspector, my name is Javert.
I have just taken charge
in Montreuil.
Inspector Javert,
what are you doing in Paris?
I've identified
a dangerous criminal.
I've come to consult you on
how to proceed. Who is this man?
His name is Jean Valjean.
I knew him years ago
at the prison hulks at Toulon.
He stole from a child within days
of his release and fled.
A man of exceptional strength
and brutality.
He's now posing as the Mayor
of Montreuil.
You're mistaken.
I tell you, I know the man.
Jean Valjean is in custody.
He was arrested four days ago
in Ailly-le-Haut-Clocher.
In due course, he will stand trial.
Has this man confessed
to being Jean Valjean?
Not yet, but he will.
He has been identified.
But monsieur…
And bear in mind,
it's a very serious matter,
making accusations against
important public figures.
I'd advise you to be more careful,
Inspector Javert.
Evening, Monsieur le Maire.
Mon pere?
You came.
Good boy.
You will be Baron Pontmercy now.
The honour was bestowed on me
by Napoleon himself at Waterloo.
Now it is yours by right.
There's a man…
…called Thenardier.
He saved my life.
If you ever meet him,
do the best, you can.
The child has caught
a miliary fever.
Oh, my God.
They're asking for money
for medicine. 40 francs.
My poor child.
Why not go and fetch
your daughter here?
And have her share my wretched life?
I don't want to bring shame
on her head.
She's better off where she is.
Though God knows how I'll find
the money for her keep now.
Well…
…you're a very pretty young woman.
There's always ways…
that a pretty young woman can…
…make a living.
If you know what I mean.
Bonsoir, monsieur.
I'm buying and I'm selling,
I'm selling and I'm buying tonight.
If you're bald and toothless,
you can change your life.
I'm selling and I'm buying tonight,
ladies and gentlemen!
I've got golden,
I've got glossy black,
I've got curly, I've got straight,
I've got long and I've got short.
Here, have a feel of this one.
Is that soft as silk?
And teeth!
How'd you like to go home tonight
with a lovely new set of teeth?
And I'll take what you've got
in part exchange.
Can't say fairer than that now,
can I?
Oh, I say, there's a beauty.
Make way, ladies.
Let her come through.
That's it, my dear.
Now, that is as lovely a head of
hair as I've seen in a long while.
Let it all down, my dear.
Are you selling, dear? How much?
Ten francs. Is that all?
That's the top rate.
You won't get more anywhere.
But if you was thinking of parting
with those lovely white teeth, now.
Just the two front ones even.
I could give you
two Napoleons for those.
40 francs.
50 altogether.
Just five minutes' work.
What do you say?
All right.
A short intermission,
ladies and gentlemen.
Don't go away!
Sit yourself down there, my love.
What's your name?
Fantine.
Lovely.
Look at this, mother.
We don't often see anything
as good as this, do we?
Now, are you quite sure you
want to go through with this?
You're allowed to change
your mind, you know.
I'm sure.
Here we go, then.
That's it. Nearly done.
Goody good, mother.
There. It'll soon grow again,
I dare say.
Right, help me hold her still,
Mother.
Aargh!
Aaaargh!
It's coming.
Aaargh!
Yes! Aargh!
Argh!
Number one.
Aargh! Aargh!
Shh, it's coming.
Argh!
That's more like it.
She must be rolling in it!
I don't think we've been asking
for enough, what do you think?
The poor little girl's
at death's door
and the doctor's demanding,
what do you reckon?
100?Yes!
Go on, do it properly.
"We beg that you do all you can
for little Cosette.
"Thenardier."
Tell them I'll send it
as soon as I can.
And how are you going to
raise the money, hm?
I've sold my hair and my teeth.
I might as well get on with it
and sell the rest.
Ah, mademoiselle…
…what a shame. You think so?
You've gone about it
the wrong way round, my dear.
You should have gone on the game
before you sold your pretty hair
and your lovely white teeth.
Who's going to take you,
looking like that?
Hm?
Get out!
Fantine? Is that you?
Fantine?
Fantine. Leave her.
Evening, ladies!
Lovely night for it. Indeed it is.
Oh, my God!
What have we got here?
What a sight!
And how much do you charge, baldy?
Whatever you think it's worth,
monsieur.
How about nothing, then?
You hear that, gentlemen?
How about nothing?
That's all she's worth! But I have
to live, monsieur, the same as you.
The same as me? You cheeky cow!
Did you ever hear the like of it?!
You think I do this for fun?
I do it to feed my little girl.
So, if you don't want business,
do me a favour…
and move along.
Oh.
Oh, I stand rebuked.
I humbly beg your pardon,
mademoiselle.
Might I ask your name, mademoiselle?
Fantine, monsieur.
Bonsoir, Fantine.
I hope I am forgiven.
Bonsoir, monsieur.
Fantine, something for you.
Help!
You, come with me.
This is an outrage
that cannot be tolerated.
A respectable property-owning
citizen
attacked by a common prostitute!
Take this whore to the cells.
Yes, sir. You've got six months.
Six months? But what about my child?
That's no concern of mine.
Take her away.
Please, Monsieur Javert!
I wasn't always like this!
I was a good girl… Take her away!
She stinks of degradation.
One moment!
Monsieur le Maire.
Monsieur le Maire?
Ha!
Seize her, you fool!
You see this man here?
You see this monster here
that you call Monsieur le Maire?
It's all his fault!
He's supposed to be so good.
What did he do?
He threw me out on the street.
And you know why? Because I tried
to care for my little girl!
Monster of a mayor!
Monsieur le Maire, a monster?
You understand now.
You'll let me go now?
I'll be a good little whore now.
They can do what they like with me
and I won't complain.
All I want is to be able to work
to feed my child
and fetch her from Montfermeil.
Please, I can't… I can't breathe.
Feel it. Get away from me!
No! I will take her into my care.
You have no right!
Fantine, I was wrong to dismiss you.
I was wrong.
Perhaps it's too late,
but let me try to make amends.
I'll pay your debts, I'll find your
child so that you can be together.
You need never work again.
I'll take care of you, I promise.
You mean it?
It's not a joke?
Let me take you to the infirmary.
Come on.
Come with me. No, I forbid it.
This woman has been sentenced
and she is going to prison.
Take her to the cells.
Don't touch her!
Monsieur Javert, in municipal
matters, I outrank you.
I warn you,
don't cross me over this.
What exactly does this woman mean
to you, Monsieur le Maire?
Someone who needs my help.
A common whore?
She is the lowest of the low.
You would risk your good name
to help a creature like that?
She's one of God's creatures,
Monsieur Javert,
and she has suffered grievously
through no fault of her own.
I injured her myself, and now
I want to make amends if I can.
You astonish me.
Now stand out of my way.
What are you doing here?
I'm…
I'm praying for you.
And for myself.
Will you…
…send for my daughter…
Cosette, please?
Yes, of course.
If necessary,
I'll go for her myself.
I've been a… a sinner.
But when I have Cosette with me…
…it will mean…
that God has forgiven me.
Inspector Javert is here,
Monsieur le Maire.
Sit down, Inspector.
Thank you, Monsieur le Maire.
I prefer to stand.
As you wish. What can I do for you?
I have come to report
a serious misdemeanour
by an officer of the police.
Which officer?
Myself.
I have come to offer my resignation.
For what reason?
Firstly, I'd like to apologise
for my conduct earlier and…
I denounced you to police
headquarters in Paris.
I suspected you,
wrongly as it turns out,
to be a notorious felon, once known
to me as Prisoner Number 24601.
A man named Jean Valjean.
But you were wrong.
Yes.
It seems I was.
What, erm…
What made you change your mind?
Monsieur le Maire,
the real Valjean…
has been found.
What?
He's about to stand trial in Arras
for a number of offences,
including the theft of a coin
from a child
who went by the name
of Petit Gervais.
Petit Gervais?
Petit Gervais.
Does the name mean anything to you,
Monsieur le Maire?
Has this man confessed?
No.
No, but no doubt his lies
will be exposed in court
and he'll be sentenced
to penal servitude…
for life.
It's over for him.
The trial is tomorrow.
I'll take the coach to Arras tonight
and that will be my last duty
as Police Inspector.
Goodnight, Monsieur le Maire.
What can I do for you, Sister?
Our patient, Fantine Thibault,
the prostitute. Don't call her that.
The doctor wanted you to know
that she… She's very weak.
She has very little time left
on this Earth
and she speaks constantly
of seeing her child.
Yes, yes, I know that.
The doctor says if she is to see her
child before she dies, the child…
Yes, I understand, Sister!
I beg your pardon.
Thank you, Sister.
Please do your best for her.
Now there are things that I
have to attend to. Excuse me.
You've got it,
haven't you? You've got my money!
You're a dirty thief!
A curse on you!
Argh!
Aaargh!
Madame Victurnien.
Monsieur Madeleine!
I have an errand for you,
if you'd be so kind.
You remember Fantine Thibault?
Indeed I do.
She's in hospital, she's very ill.
I need you to go to Montfermeil
and fetch her little girl.
Bring her here.
I'd go myself, but I…
There's somewhere else I have to be.