T-minus 15 seconds,
guidance is internal.
12... 11... 10... nine...
- Ignition sequence starts...
- Damn it, turn that vacuum off!
- Hattie!
five... four... three...
two... one... zero.
All engines running.
Liftoff.
We have a liftoff.
32 minutes past the hour.
Liftoff on Apollo 11.
Boy.
Oh boy, it looks good.
You know what?
Why don't you swing down to Irvine?
We have a lot more
groves down there.
Can we go to Tijuana?
I'm tired at looking at oranges.
There's more to look at
than the ground.
Imagine what it's like
for the astronauts.
They're probably scared.
Why?
Maybe they won't make it.
All their problems will be over.
You know how to fly this thing?
What are you doing?
See that spot along 66?
Probably Claremont.
Good spot
for smoldering wreckage.
- It's not funny.
- Turn it back on this minute!
You wanted to go up in the plane,
we went up in the plane.
My God, we're gonna die!
Well, I thought I'd talk to you
privately first,
because your next call is going to be
from Pete Campbell.
Have him call me.
I'd love to hear his version of it.
Well, Pete says that Sunkist
called him distraught.
Severely distraught because apparently
you cut the engines
and scared them half to death.
And also expressed a real
feeling of wanting to die.
You used to fly.
Didn't you ever feel that?
Over Dresden?
I wanted to live.
And the clients
want to live, too, Ted!
I thought this was private.
He's leaving.
Look, Jim, I don't want to die.
I just don't want
to do this anymore.
- Do what?
- Advertising.
I wanna do something else.
Somewhere else.
- I don't think that's possible.
- Sure, it is.
You're gonna buy me out.
Ted, you don't know
what you're saying.
I've made up my mind.
Good-bye.
Mr. Avery's here.
Send him in.
Just wanted to say
Commander cigarettes is dead.
Leo Burnett says they're rolling it up
with the rest of Philip Morris.
Oh, well, that's too bad.
But I suppose now people will know
we're in the tobacco business again.
- And that's good.
- Oh, sure.
There's a cork-tipped
Newport in the works.
Shall I invite them
to "Don Draper Dinner Theater"?
Maybe a matinee?
10 years I've built
a tobacco resume
and one meeting
turned me into a joke.
I'm gonna crawl outta this place
with nothing left to show.
We don't owe you anything!
You're a hired hand.
Now get back to work.
Bobby! Sally! Get down here!
You're being rude!
But I know I put it in the car.
Neil, that's enough.
"The case of the missing telescope."
Neil can bunk with Bobby,
and there's a daybed
in the sewing room for Sean.
Sean, Neil,
this is Bobby and Sally.
- Where's your little brother?
- My goodness, Sally.
You look like your mother
freshman year.
Carolyn, you're the one
with the fully grown men.
- You have such a lovely home.
- Where are we supposed to put these?
I'll show you.
Don't let the lady carry a bag.
Oh, it's fine.
I'm strong.
Let me get it.
Follow me, Rick.
Bobby, show Neil your telescope.
It'll give you an excuse
to take it out of the box.
You can't see anything
during the daytime.
That's not true.
Come on.
Of course, now that my partnership
is on the table,
Jennifer has stopped
talking about divorce.
She's postponing the conversation.
Yeah, till after I get that money.
Don, can you be impartial?
What do I hold out for?
Don't negotiate,
just accept the deal.
Should we take it from the top?
"Welcome, welcome.
Indiana's beautiful this time of year."
I tell a joke, everyone laughs.
Then Harry gets up and doesn't squander
the good will I've just generated.
- I have a joke, too.
- No, you don't.
"Local buy, national buy,
outdoor."
I tell them about
the IBM 360, but...
I don't show them a picture,
because we only show pictures of ads.
Peggy.
We were scared until we knew
the genuine superiority of Burger Chef.
More general flattery,
research, research.
"Without further ado,
Donald Draper. Don?"
ls that what you're going to say?
Don't worry about
what she's going to say.
I was going to say that...
"every great ad is a story,
and here to tell you that story
is our creative director and partner,
Donald Draper.
Don?"
"I don't know
about your dinner table,
but I know about mine.
- When I get home--"
- That's fine.
Now we just have to pray
everything goes smoothly on the moon.
Hello?
Oh, I'm sorry.
Where's Kazmir?
He had to run downtown.
Oh.
Well, it looks like
you're doing a good job.
Once you get the grid up,
you just try not to break the tiles.
I'm Peggy, by the way.
I'm Nick.
You've got a lot of books.
It's so hot in here.
Would you like some iced tea?
Kaz should give you a discount.
Your son was a big help.
MY Son?
Oh, Julio.
No, he's my neighbor.
I own the building.
By yourself?
I was very clear I am not paying
before it's finished.
That's my number.
In case you have any odd jobs
too small for Kaz.
Well, thank you.
- Good night.
Good night, kid.
Can I have a Popsicle?
I only had one today.
Sure.
So then Rutgers promised him
a generous athletic scholarship.
It was nice he had choices,
but I don't see any passion.
I don't remember dreaming
of anything but Paris at his age.
Paris and Ty Power.
How did I marry Rick?
He has no eyelashes.
So...
I have to ask.
Do you ever see Don?
Only when absolutely necessary.
I'm starting to think of him
as an old, bad boyfriend.
Someone a teenage
anthropologist would marry.
- Is there any oatmeal?
- Good morning, mister.
Good morning, Mrs. Francis.
Betty.
Go get decent.
- Hey. Sorry.
- I'm sorry, I'm late.
What can I get you?
She gets to eat in a bathing suit?
- 'Cause I swim in these shorts.
- I can't eat anything
because I'm a lifeguard
and I can't wait an hour.
Go.
Bye, everyone.
She is so beautiful.
Particularly today.
She's never worn lipstick
to the pool before.
Because before they reach
the surface of the moon,
they're gonna throw down
an anchor.
And what if that
sinks right into it?
Hmm?
What if it's quicksand?
- Am I late for something?
- No.
May I speak with you?
What's going on?
You got this letter this morning
and it's very upsetting news.
Are they firing you?
I don't know.
What does that mean,
"breach of contract"?
This is from the agency's attorney.
Why didn't they call me?
Look at you.
You're so confused.
You never even met
with Commander cigarettes.
I would have known.
It doesn't matter.
I want you to listen to me.
I know you're feeling vulnerable,
but I am your strength.
Tell me what I can do.
You can get my attorney
on the phone.
And we can't do this.
You're right.
Not right now.
You think you're gonna throw me
out of my own company?
Madeline, I've got it.
Todd, could you excuse us?
Don has a habit
of walking into meetings
unannounced.
- Should I reschedule?
- Get out!
It was cut and dry.
You broke the stipulations
of the addendum to your contract.
You set that meeting
to force me out of the agency.
What was I supposed to do?
You know, Ted and I,
whenever we would hear
that your agency was involved,
we'd always be so intimidated.
"What was that man up to?"
Such a cloud of mystery.
Now that I've been backstage?
I'm deeply unimpressed, Don.
You're just a bully and a drunk.
A football player in a suit.
The most eloquent
I've ever heard you
was when you were blubbering
like a little girl
about your
impoverished childhood.
What? You wanna
take a swing at me?
It would save us all
a lot of trouble.
- ls he in?
- He hasn't read it.
I just got it.
Hey!
Get out here!
What's going on?
I just got a breach letter
with your name on the bottom.
- What?
- Joan! Get out here.
Joan! Could you get
Cooper out here?
- What's going on?
- Find Pete.
- No one knows about this?
- I saw it.
Then why did you say,
"What's going on"?
I want you to calm down.
I just called Jim.
We're going to get
to the bottom of this.
- Is there a meeting?
- Have you seen this?
Is this a partners' meeting?
You're not a partner yet.
This is outrageous.
You know we're going to be
at Burger Chef on Monday.
I vote against this.
Right now.
It's not subject to a vote.
The contract was very clear.
You wanna play
parliamentary procedure?
Let's play.
Everyone who wants to get rid of me,
raise your hand.
Fine.
I have Ted's proxy.
You had no right
to put my name on that.
Anyone else?
All opposed?
Motion denied.
That is a very sensitive
piece of horseflesh.
He shouldn't be rattled.
He's a pain in the ass.
You knew about this?
No, but I'm tired of him
costing me money.
We all set those stipulations,
and he signed them.
You shouldn't have done that.
Can I watch TV?
I'm sorry, you can't.
I'm working.
Wait, get in here.
This is a suit and it has a skirt
and it has grey in it,
which is what men wear.
And this is a dress and it's pretty,
but I might be sweating
and not just because it's July.
- Forget it.
- I gotta watch Sunday.
That's when
they're supposed to land.
I'm sorry, but I'm going to be
in Indianapolis.
Why?
Because we're presenting
to Burger Chef Monday morning.
I know the astronauts may not make it,
and then what are we gonna say?
Oh.
I'm sorry.
They're going to be fine.
- It's not fair!
- You know what?
I'll give you the key and you can
come down and watch yourself.
Just don't use the stove again.
I don't wanna go to Newark.
Nobody does.
My uncle has a house
and he got my mom a job.
I don't wanna leave!
You're moving?
Well...
well, that's okay.
Maybe you'll have a yard.
You want your mom
to have a job, don't you?
She don't care about me.
Yes, she does.
That's why she's moving.
I'll visit you all the time.
No, you won't.
- You can watch TV while I pack.
- Okay.
Hello?
Hello.
What are you up to?
I'm going to the movies with Jill.
I think we're gonna see
"The Wild Bunch."
I wanna see that.
You want me to wait?
When are you going to Indiana?
I don't even know if I'm going.
What happened?
They're going to fire me.
I'm sorry.
I thought if I kept
my head down and...
did my job--
I guess that's not what they want.
What do they want?
They want me to move on.
Well, maybe you should.
Aren't you tired of fighting?
Yes.
I guess I could see it
as an opportunity.
I could finally move out there.
Megan?
I'm here.
Is that what you want me to do?
Don...
I'll always take care of you.
I'll be fine.
Well, until you are.
Whatever you need.
I owe you that.
You don't owe me anything.
Good-bye, Don.
- What are we gonna do about Cutler?
- Sit, take off your shoes.
I don't feel like it.
- Whoever is in control is in charge.
- We're in control.
We've got the votes,
except for Benedict Joan.
Don cost her a million dollars
when we didn't go public.
So you want him out, too?
Do you understand Don Draper
can work anywhere?
No man has ever come back
from leave, even Napoleon.
He staged a coup, but he ended up
back on that island.
So why didn't you vote him out?
Because I'm a leader
and a leader is loyal to his team.
Don doesn't understand that.
But I do.
And you have talent and skill
and experience.
But you're not a leader.
And Cutler is?
He has a vision,
but he's not on my team.
So, "let's have another cup of coffee,
let's have another piece of pie"?
Ladies and gentlemen,
we'd like to ask you now
to extinguish your cigarettes
as we prepare for takeoff.
I'd like to say that we'll be
sharing the sky today
with one other notable aircraft,
and I'd like to wish fellow pilots
Neil Armstrong,
Buzz Aldrin and Mike Collins
godspeed and a safe return.
Why did you have to do that?
Now I feel like we're in danger.
If they don't make it,
we're going to have to postpone
this thing for a year.
You're going to go in there
and you're going to win this.
And if Cutler doesn't
like it, I'm sorry,
but the Don Draper show is back
from its unscheduled interruption.
I appreciate that,
but I'm not rattled.
Well, you're sighing a lot.
What do you say
you come out to California?
It's possible if all goes well
that I could be spending
part of my time in New York.
And Ted's going to run that place
into the ground.
He's off the deep end.
Lane Pryce.
There's no reason to go to L.A.
ls Megan moving back?
Marriage is a racket.
It's happening!
Come on, come on.
Let's go, let's go!
Come on.
Indiana's dry on Sunday.
I had to buy these
off the night clerk.
Getting back up to that first step...
He came out.
...not even collapsed
too far, but it's adequate...
- Two beers?
- Roger. We copy.
It takes
a pretty good little jump.
So there's a foot on the moon.
Stepping down on the moon.
If he's testing that first step,
he must be stepping down
on the moon at this point.
Buzz, this is Houston.
F2-1/160 second for shadow photography
on the sequence camera.
Okay.
I'm at the foot of the ladder.
The LEM footpads are only
depressed in the surface
about one or two inches,
although the surface
appears to be
very, very fine grained
as you get close to it.
It's almost like a powder...
down there.
It's very fine.
Boy, look at those pictures.
Wow.
It's a little shadowy, but--
Hot damn.
Armstrong is on the moon.
Neil Armstrong.
38-year-old American,
standing on the surface of the moon.
On this July 20th, 1969.
That's one small step for man...
one giant leap for mankind.
Bravo.
I think that was Neil's quote.
I didn't understand.
Well, "one small step for man,"
but I didn't get the second phrase.
Roger. We got you boresighted
but back under one track.
It's just incredible.
I'll tell you what's incredible.
It cost $25 billion.
Be quiet, Sean.
'Cause there's no problems
back on Earth?
I can't hear it.
It's probably Nixon
calling for Henry.
Sally.
Okay.
...underneath it says,
"Here Man
from the Planet Earth..."
- Francis residence.
- Hello, sweetheart.
Hi, Daddy.
Isn't this something?
I guess.
So you're unimpressed?
It's such a waste of money.
You don't really think that, do you?
We'll be going there all the time
while people go hungry down here.
Don't be so cynical.
You want your little brothers
to talk that way?
No.
- Are they up?
- I'll go get them.
Neil, this is Houston.
After you've got the core tubes...
Just leave it alone.
Hello?
Yes, this is he.
Oh, shit.
What is it?
Hello?
I'm so sorry.
- Well, this is unfortunate.
- Yes.
Roger, my condolences.
He was a giant.
Thank you.
He was a wonderful man.
I'll have the obituary
ready in an hour,
and I suppose we can
divide up the clients
and start calling them.
It's 1:00 in the morning.
The agency and the world
are closed tomorrow.
Do we have to do this now?
Well, as tragic as this is,
I for one am happy
that we have a chance to have
a conversation with the clients
about the future of this company.
And to give Don Draper
a send-off along with Bert.
Excuse me?
I hate to remind you
that with Harry's partnership
and without Bert, Don's dismissal
is a foregone conclusion.
Cooper's been dead an hour
and you're prying his hand open?
Roger, I know what this company
should look like.
Computer services.
Media buys pinpointed
with surgical accuracy.
We can offer the services
beyond our clients.
It's the agency of the future.
Is this what would happen if I died?
Are you the only one out here?
Yes. ls that okay?
Yeah, I don't want them
giving me shit for smoking.
Smoking causes cancer.
How does it look?
- Can you see it?
- The moon?
Nah, it's already set.
Then why aren't you watching TV?
I don't wanna listen to them
or the reporters.
Besides, there's other things
to look at.
Like what?
Polaris.
It's a star.
Take a look.
I can't see anything.
Do you see your eyelashes?
Yes.
Okay.
Tilt your head back
and open your eyes really wide.
Okay.
I think I see it.
Isn't that better than TV?
It is.
What do I do now?
Neil, honey?
Where are you?
I'm outside.
Get in here!
It's bedtime!
Neil, this is Houston.
Did you get the Hasselblad...
- Hello?
- Figured you'd still be up.
Roger?
How'd you find me?
Your itinerary
was on Caroline's desk.
I'm at the office.
Bert passed away.
A couple hours ago.
He was in his living room
on the couch.
Roger, I'm so sorry.
I know what he meant to you.
Well, now I'm gonna lose you, too.
We don't have the votes anymore.
It's the first thing Cutler said.
Well, he's consistent.
Poor Bert.
I should've realized
it was the end.
Every time an old man
starts talking about Napoleon,
you know they're gonna die.
Is his sister still alive?
He was hard on me, you know?
But maybe he was right.
The last thing I said to him
were the lines to some old song.
Come on, Roger, you know
he was very proud of you.
Give 'em hell tomorrow.
Okay.
Okay, the hatch
is closed and latched...
May I speak with you?
Of course.
ls something wrong?
May I come in?
There's been a change of plans.
You're gonna give
the presentation tomorrow.
Did Harry tell you
about my dream?
What? No.
We have a couple hours.
You can practice it with me
and still be fresh.
- Are you serious?
- You're gonna be great.
No. Stop messing around.
It's not funny.
You must have heard
that they're trying to get me out.
If I win this business,
and then I go,
you'll be left with nothing.
They're trying to get you out?
I thought everything
was finally back to normal.
Me, too, but...
sometimes actions
have consequences
and one of them
is I can't present tomorrow.
You win this business
and it will be yours.
No, Don.
It's tomorrow.
I'm unprepared.
You've been listening
to me for weeks.
Well, I can't just say
what you've been saying.
I'm a woman.
I'm the "voice of moms," remember?
Maybe that's better.
Maybe that's the way it always
should have been.
Well, Pete won't stand for it.
Pete's pregnant.
He has to do what we say.
No. Cancel it.
What about the moon landing?
- It was a success.
- No, Don.
I have to talk to people
who just touched the face of God
about hamburgers!
I wouldn't do this
if I didn't know you could.
You've never even
seen me present.
I've overheard things.
We have no liquor.
Good morning.
Did you see we landed
on the moon?
ls that right?
Neil Armstrong, what are you going
to do with the rest of your life?
Screw every girl in Florida,
I guess.
So you called me at sunrise
to discuss the meaning of life?
No. I just want to know
if Buick had left you yet.
Why would they do that?
Because we've built
a relationship with GM
and they know we can
handle a bigger car.
And our Chevy account man
just moved there.
Uncle.
So, you made the overture.
What did you have in mind?
Well...
we'd want the whole Chevy team.
You, Jim Cutler, Don Draper,
and Ted Chaough.
We both know you're
in the acquisitions business.
I think... you should buy
the whole company.
Because I have a vision.
All our accounts,
our cutting-edge computer,
and the employees
that I know to be worthy
as an independent
subsidiary of McCann.
You just lost Burger Chef,
we may win it.
Then you'd still have it.
And I'd have my company--
without Jim Cutler
and all that baggage from CGC.
That's an interesting idea.
But this is still all about Buick.
You have to bury the hatchet
with Ted Chaough.
Why?
Because GM thinks
he and Don Draper are one person.
I don't know if I can do that.
Well, then, I don't know
if I can help you.
I'm gonna be bold and say
that no one in this room
knows more about
the Burger Chef customer
than Peggy Olson.
She has visited 20 restaurants
in nine states,
interviewed hundreds
and is obviously
uniquely qualified
to craft this modern campaign.
Every great ad tells a story.
Here to tell that story
is Peggy Olson.
Thank you, Don.
That's a lot to live up to.
Because I certainly
can't tell a better story
than the one we saw last night.
I don't know what was
more miraculous--
the technological achievement
that put our species
in a new perspective
or the fact that all of us were doing
the same thing at the same time.
Sitting in this room,
we can still feel the pleasure
of that connection,
because, I realize now,
we were starved for it.
We really were.
And, yes, we'll feel it again
when they all return safely.
And, yes, the world will never
be the same in some ways.
But tonight, I'm going
to go back to New York,
and I'll go back to my apartment
and find a 10-year-old boy
parked in front of my TV,
eating dinner.
Now, I don't need to charge you
for a research report
that tells you
that most television sets
are not more than six feet away
from the dinner table.
And that dinner table
is your battlefield and your prize.
This is the home
your customers really live in.
This is your dinner table.
Dad likes Sinatra,
son likes The Rolling Stones.
The TV's always on,
Vietnam playing in the background.
The news wins every night.
And you're starving.
And not just for dinner.
What if there was another table
where everybody gets what they want
when they want it?
It's bright and clean,
and there's no laundry,
no telephone, and no TV.
And we can have the connection
that we're hungry for.
There may be chaos at home...
but there's family supper
at Burger Chef.
That's beautiful.
That's nice to hear
because that's the name
of the spot.
We open on a bird's-eye view
of a typical kitchen table.
- Welcome home.
- How'd you get in here?
Money.
But he wouldn't open the door.
I need to talk to you.
Cooper still dead?
His situation hasn't changed,
but ours has.
Can I get a drink?
- How'd it go?
- Great.
Is that why you're here?
We got an offer from McCann Erickson
to buy the agency.
Hear me out.
We'd be a subsidiary,
separately operated.
We keep our name, our offices,
you keep your job--
your real job--
and I'll be the president.
- Of McCann?
- No, of Sterling Cooper.
They know we're primed
for a big car,
and they don't want
to compete with us.
Did you forget we started this agency
to get away from them?
Yeah, I know that,
but a lot's happened in between.
Most of it good,
but some of it very bad.
Without Cooper, Cutler's gonna
lock you out by the end of the week.
- I don't want to work for McCann.
- You're gonna work for me.
Don't fool yourself.
You know they're not
gonna leave us alone.
They did with Marschalk.
And they're buying 51%.
You're gonna make a fortune.
Fine, you have my vote.
What's that gonna do?
You can't even save my job.
How are you gonna sell the company?
I'm working on it.
You're of essence to the deal.
But so is Ted Chaough.
Ted Chaough?
What are you doing?
They want the guys
who won Chevy.
Roger, I just wanna do my work.
I don't wanna deal
with business anymore.
And what about everyone else?
We all send out resumes?
Cutler's not gonna stop until the firm
is just Harry and the computer.
That means everybody goes.
And you know it.
Ted, welcome back.
Well, I'm sorry it's under
these circumstances.
I've instructed Don
to gather everyone at noon.
Did you want to discuss
the remarks?
I thought we would begin
with a poem of memorial for Bert.
"O Captain, My Captain"?
Then we have a lot
of pressing business here
with finalizing
Don's departure and--
And I have an announcement
of my own.
We don't need
to deal with that today.
I haven't heard anything.
- About what?
- Burger Chef.
- Good morning.
- I'm glad that you're here.
Would you please all have a seat?
There's coffee.
I have some rather urgent business.
I insist.
I'm coming to all of you
with an incredible opportunity.
McCann Erickson wants to buy
a 51% stake in SC&P.
We'll be independently operated,
and all they ask are five-year contracts
from everyone.
- Including Don?
- Especially Don.
And you'll be our king.
Well, I did put it together.
The details have
to be worked out,
but we'll keep our office,
our name, and our clients.
Why would they do that?
Because we finally turned this place
into a legitimate threat
and they'd like to neutralize it
with cold, hard cash.
- How much?
- When did you do this?
Since you asked,
I'll use you as an example.
Let's say they value the agency
at $65 million
and they buy 51% of it.
That means your 5% share
is worth a little over $1.5 million.
- 25% of that upon signing.
- Oh, my goodness!
I've got 10%!
Keep counting those chickens.
I hope you all realize this is
a pathetic ploy and a delusion.
It is until everybody votes on it.
Sorry, just heard
about the partners' meeting.
- Perfect timing.
- He hasn't signed.
He missed the boat.
- What's going on?
- None of your beeswax.
- I'll take the deal.
- Good-bye, Harry.
Don't worry about it.
Well, I won't do it.
That's fine because
you're not of essence.
And you are?
Yes, all they care about
is me, Don, and Ted.
Don, you're gonna sign a contract
to work at McCann for five years?
Well, I've given this a lot of thought.
I'm sure you did.
And I agree with Roger
that we should do everything we can
to keep Jim from breaking up
the agency.
You mean, save your hide.
Look, I don't want to stand in the way
of everyone making all this money,
but I am done with advertising.
Your 20% share will be worth
at least $6 million.
I'm going to have
plenty of money
from selling my partnership
as it stands.
Can't you do it without me?
You don't think I tried that?
If I sign a contract for five years,
that'll be the rest of my life.
You've got to be kidding me.
You're not just pathetic,
you're selfish.
Well, I'm sorry, Roger.
You may have the votes,
but you don't have a deal.
Now can we dispense
with this nonsense,
go outside and say
a fond farewell?
Ted...
what if I told you
you could just write copy
and fight clients
and not worry about
partnership votes or stock prices?
You could just go back
to creative.
I have that right now,
and I'm miserable.
No, you don't.
I really lost this last year
and I realized I would do anything
to get back in.
And I did anything.
I wrote tags,
I wrote coupons.
Things I haven't done
since I first got my start.
I know you.
I know the man
who I walked into Chevy with.
You don't have to work for us,
but you have to work.
You don't wanna see what happens
when it's really gone.
You remember the last time
he talked you into something?
I don't know.
- So, I'd move back to the city?
- Ted's in. Let's have a vote.
- Hold on.
- Let's have a vote.
Everyone in favor.
Really?
It's a lot of money.
I just got off the phone
with Burger Chef.
They couldn't find anyone.
We got it.
Well, they heard what I heard.
Where are you going?
Back to work.
Excuse me, everyone.
If I could have your attention.
Mr. Sterling would like to make
an announcement.
Thank you, everyone.
It's difficult that at this moment
of national pride,
we have to deal
with some sad, personal news.
On Sunday night we lost
our founder Bertram Cooper...
Don, my boy.
- Bert?
- ♪ The stars in the sky ♪
♪ The moon on high ♪
♪ They're great for you and me ♪
♪ Because they're free ♪
♪ The moon belongs
to everyone ♪
♪ The best things in life
are free ♪
♪ The stars belong to everyone ♪
♪ They gleam there
for you and me ♪
♪ The flowers in spring ♪
♪ The robins that sing ♪
♪ The sunbeams that shine ♪
♪ They're yours, they're mine ♪
♪ And love can come to everyone ♪
♪ The best things in life are free ♪
♪ The moon belongs
to everyone ♪
♪ The best things in life are free. ♪