I thought you were going to open it up.
I got a hell of a shaker on 130.
What are you afraid of?
- That was fast.
- Apparently not.
So, what do you think?
Can we go to El Mirage?
You and your record books.
You gotta take care of that shimmy.
You won't lose control, but I bet
it creates drag.
You know an awful lot about cars
for a guy who hasn't got one.
We just need a stake.
A couple hundred bucks for
a flatbed rig, some parts.
Beer and gas.
Drive from O'Hare Airport
to breakfast with Sears Roebuck
senior vice presidents.
Then, the Chicago Ad Club.
12:30 luncheon, 1:30 speech.
I translated your speech into Pig Latin.
That was a joke.
And?
And I've arranged for that package
to be delivered to your suite
at the Stanhope tomorrow.
What package?
The package from Canada
with all the luggage?
She knows about Marie.
She's Megan's mother.
I'm going to leave you two alone.
Do I have to?
Yes.
Sweetheart, I have some sad news.
Is he dead?
Don? No.
I don't think so.
I think we would have heard about that.
That said, our secret plan here
has been discovered.
They know I don't need two secretaries.
I'm sorry.
I really thought he'd be back by now.
Well, I hope he's in a better place.
He's not dead. Stop saying that.
There are a lot of better places than here.
I'll give you the recommendation
he would have.
I know you'll land on your feet.
I always do.
So, that covers Del Monte, Roman Meal,
and Diamond Walnuts.
Bon appetit.
That is all the accounts, all assigned.
And don't ask me again about
S.O. Research and Engineering.
It's over.
Why did they take us off Chevalier?
Did Ted say anything to you about it?
Ted's not the creative director.
They moved it to David's group.
Does David know they took us off?
There's plenty to go around.
It's done. You have four good accounts.
Get to work.
Lorraine, do you have a moment?
Not really.
Why are we off Chevalier?
Because Stu Riley took over
from Pete Campbell
and he has his favorites.
I thought David wanted us on it.
I guess he didn't.
Well, does he know?
I don't know.
Why don't I call David
and let him know you're unhappy?
You know what, Lorraine?
Call David.
In fact, why don't we go over
and see him right now?
I'm sure he'd love to get involved.
Fine. You want it, you can have it.
Thanks so much.
You hung up my jeans.
I like having a man to take care of.
My wallet didn't happen to fall out, did it?
What the hell does that mean?
Should I go look?
Maybe I wanted to know who you were.
Everybody thinks you're from Detroit,
come to steal their secrets.
Did you leave me anything?
You've never paid for it, huh?
I have and I will. I just like it to be voluntary.
Get your purse.
Could have asked me.
That's never worked.
Whose ring is that?
Weren't you gonna steal it?
Thank you.
We're leaving tomorrow.
You know we're going
to beat those postcards home.
I want them to say Key West.
Who gave you cocaine as a birthday present?
My old partner. It's all over Malibu.
We said we'd try everything.
Okay.
I think you're supposed
to sniff it off your fingernail.
Okay, my turn.
That's fast.
I feel like someone just gave me
some very good news.
You know, we could live like this all the time.
You just enjoy corrupting me.
Not the cocaine.
I'm talking about
taking advantage of all I have.
All you have.
You should be spoiled.
I couldn't be more spoiled.
The way I've been living in New York,
it's hard to tell when the vacation started.
Kevin's going to school soon,
so I know you have to be in one place,
but, if you think about it,
why does that place have to be New York?
There are good schools everywhere
and you hate your mother.
I don't hate her.
Is that all you heard?
You're cheating yourself. That tiny apartment.
I don't wanna make plans,
but we could get a place in the mountains
or the country.
Or a place in the mountains and the country.
Have you been looking for a place?
It's a hobby.
I mean I guess what I'm trying to say is
I want you to let yourself
have a future with me.
Do you wanna get married?
Sure. If you do.
But it seems to me, your life
is undeveloped property.
You can turn it into anything you want.
It's got a hell of a view.
Do we have to get married?
Hell, no.
I want you so much right now.
I'm sorry. I got held up.
No, I'm sorry.
Samsonite is shooting tomorrow
and they changed everything.
I feel horrible, but I'm afraid it's just
you and Harry for lunch.
That's my going away present?
What else did you get?
The account girls got a little sentimental.
Sarah baked cookies.
And this is a cactus.
What's that have to do with Kansas?
I don't know. Do you want it?
I have a five-year-old.
Let's go. I'm starving.
She's not coming. She has work to do.
Don't do that.
You know who I was gonna have lunch with?
Someone important?
Doesn't anything mean anything to you?
Here, this will hold you over.
I'll meet you by the elevator.
He acts like we're the Three Musketeers.
We've never had lunch.
I just wanted to say
that I'm very happy for you.
And everyone's going to miss you,
who doesn't hate you for getting that big job.
Well, you're doing fine.
Keep it up, you'll be
a creative director by 1980.
God, that sounds like a long time.
I'm telling you, it will happen.
They just have to get used to the idea.
Someday, people are gonna brag
that they worked with you.
What am I supposed to say to that?
I don't know. No one's ever said it to me.
A thing like that.
I'll be back.
That thing better be alive.
So, you're in Utah?
I sent you a clipping.
They broke the land speed record
right up in Bonneville.
622 miles an hour in
a car that looked like a jet.
Sally?
I'm glad you're having fun.
Sorry, I already went to high school.
I got to go.
Hold on.
What's wrong?
It's nothing.
Boy problems?
I'm not supposed to tell you.
What?
Mom's dying.
Look, your mother's a hypochondriac.
Don't go off the deep end.
Dad, listen to me.
She has lung cancer.
The doctors gave her six months to live.
What?
She doesn't want you to know,
but I just thought...
No, you did the right thing. I'm coming home.
No, I'm telling you because she wants
Gene and Bobby to live with Uncle William.
Don't worry, you're all going to live with me.
I promise.
Let me finish.
I've thought about this more than you have.
You have to tell her that
you think it's best that they stay with Henry.
No.
Daddy, it's going to be
so hard for them already.
They should at least be in the same bed
and at the same school.
Sally, grown-ups make these decisions.
Do you understand
I'm betraying her confidence?
I'm not being dramatic.
Now, please, take me seriously.
- I have to go.
- Hold on.
Please, I can't talk right now.
Sally, wait a minute.
Francis residence.
I have a person-to-person call
for Betty Francis
from Donald Draper.
This is she. I'll accept.
Hello, Don.
- Don't you want the boys?
- No.
You know I talked to Sally, don't you?
Yes, of course.
I'm coming home.
You are definitely not!
I want to be there. The kids need me.
I don't want to upset them.
It's my business.
I didn't even want her to know,
but no one can keep their mouth shut.
I don't want you to worry about them.
They'll going to come live with me.
You don't even have to ask.
I wasn't going to.
Please don't let your pride
interfere with my wishes.
I'm their father.
What they really need is a woman in their life.
A regular family.
Living with my brother and Judy
is in their best interests.
You don't have the right to decide.
What am I supposed to do?
This way you see them exactly
as much as you do now,
on weekends and...
Oh, wait, Don.
When was the last time you saw them?
Betty, I didn't know.
Don, honey, I appreciate your intentions.
I really do.
But I'm not going to waste the rest of my time
arguing about this.
I want to keep things as normal as possible
and you not being here is part of that.
Birdie...
I know.
I have to go.
I'll talk to you soon.
Okay.
Let me get you a glass.
- How was Florida?
- Compelling.
I assume you held on to your Rolodex
when you retired?
Can I taste the wine first?
You know, you look great.
Thank you.
What do you want?
Every department at Dow department
has to make an industrial film
for the national sales meeting,
and our script just came in.
I fell asleep on page two of thirty.
How long is this film?
See? You know that.
The producer's as drunk as a skunk.
I have to replace him.
Do you remember the name of the guy
who produced Birds Eye?
I'm sure I have his number somewhere.
It's $50,000 for eight minutes.
A good producer could pocket half of it,
but he has to know writers and directors.
And I need it yesterday.
Joan, I can't be eclipsed by plastics
and packaging again.
Relax, Kenny.
For that kind of money,
there'll be ten men for the job.
Great. So, how's the family?
Wonderful. How's Eddie?
He's a little weird, actually.
I think there might be
something wrong with him.
Come in.
We can't ask him for money like this.
Don.
You don't have to come along,
but you promised to stake us.
I'm coming. I'm coming.
Should we pack you?
I'm packed. You can drop me in L.A.
Hello, big shot.
I was hoping we could grab lunch
or a drink and catch up.
It's so good to hear from you.
I thought you forgot about me.
How about the end of next week?
I can't wait. Is your weekend busy?
You really want to catch up?
Well, I ran into Ken, and...
Oh, how is he? Did you tell him I said hi?
Why would you do that?
Dow needs a script yesterday
for an industrial film.
You know the account and, well,
we both thought of you.
I don't have time to moonlight.
It's $1,200 for a ten page script.
Well, anything for a friend.
We can chat when I drop off the research.
Obviously, not there.
Of course.
Dick.
Hello.
What are you doing here?
How'd you find me?
I was in L.A. I called your folks.
They told me you were in town.
And they sent you here for what?
They didn't tell me anything
but your address.
Patty's pretty mad I gave you money.
Well, that's more than she did.
Do you have any liquor?
I've been drinking beer all night.
Sit down. I'll make coffee.
What's going on?
Nothing much. I'm retired.
Been on the road.
Just wanted to see how you were doing.
Meet the little one.
This is bullshit.
Did they fly you in from some drunk tank
to make me feel guilty?
Stephanie, no.
What happened?
He's not here.
He lives with Ronnie's parents. His dad.
I understand.
Listen.
I also thought...
This should be with you.
Megan and I are, well...
I'm sorry about that.
Anna always wanted you to have it.
Come on, Dick.
What am I going to do with that?
Fine. Sell it.
Is that the problem?
You need money?
I appreciate you trying to help me out,
but I'm pretty sure
you're the one who's in trouble.
A lot has happened.
You're welcome to crash here.
I'm going away for a few days.
I don't wanna put you out.
Just need a shower and a shave.
Where you going?
Up the coast.
It's some kind of retreat.
Why don't you close your eyes?
I'll open a can of stew.
Okay.
Are you trying to kill me?
I'm trying to make you happy.
That was our agreement.
Du Maurier. They taste like le shit.
I miss them.
Too bad.
You're done with Canada.
My children live there. You'll learn to love it.
As long as I don't have to see
what's-his-name.
Poor soul. He suddenly
discovered that he wants me.
You saw Emile?
Oh, he was such a tragic figure.
I hope you told him it's too late.
Not everything is your business.
Wait. Did you sleep with him?
Don't raise your voice.
You're not my husband.
You went up there to divorce him.
I forbid you to see him.
You are the one that'll throw me over
and leave me for your secretary.
You know what a low blow is?
All I got was "suitcase."
Yell at me slower or in English.
You live in a hotel.
Go get another room.
- What?
- Out!
Sleep on the sofa.
The television's in there.
That is your friend.
You're coming with me.
Hi, Genie.
Hi, Sally.
I didn't know you were coming home.
I missed you guys. I took the train.
Is it going to happen now?
Is what going to happen?
Gene, go watch TV.
No.
Get out of here.
Where are they?
Henry's still at work. She's lying down.
That's all she can do.
I don't know what she thinks I think,
but I heard everything
before they stopped fighting.
I don't know how long she has,
but I'm not going to Madrid anymore.
She's not going to like that.
What happened in here?
Smells like a fire.
I was making dinner.
Get the frying pan.
I'll show you how to do it.
- There's someone in here.
- It's more communal this way.
Sun salutation's at dawn,
with yoga and tai chi.
A silent meal at 7:00 a.m.
and the seminars begin at 9:00.
Get some rest. Tomorrow is
going to be beautiful.
You are so generous.
Where are we?
"Psychotechnics?
Anxiety and Tension Control?
"Divorce: A Creative Experience?"
Be open to this. You might feel better.
She took my money. That's a good sign.
Good night, Dick.
Careful. He's a little sticky.
I had pancakes.
- Do you have a minute?
- Of course.
Look, I've been revising my will,
and with Margaret lost,
I'm dividing most of my estate
between Ellery and...
Roger.
I know you don't want it, but it's for him.
I don't want it to put you
in an awkward position
when some man you used to work with
leaves your son a small fortune.
The good doctor, for example.
Greg had twins with some nurse.
As far as he's concerned,
Kevin never happened.
So, he knows?
No, he's just a terrible person.
What about the guy
you've been hiding from me?
Richard is a man of the world.
Roger, this is an expensive way
to mark your territory.
What? No.
I've just been thinking that
you get to a point in your life
where it's the last chapter...
Are you ill? Is everything okay?
For the time being, but I'm getting married.
Well, those skirts are pretty short at McCann.
Nah, I met her through Megan Draper.
She's old enough to be her mother.
Actually, she is her mother.
That's spectacular. What a mess.
You'd be surprised. Nobody cares.
I guess somebody
finally got their timing right.
So, you'll accept?
If this is what you really want,
I'm not going to say no.
It would be a relief to know that,
no matter what, our beautiful
little boy is secure.
Good.
Get over here.
Little rich bastard.
He really is, I guess.
Thank you.
I didn't want to leave it in the room.
Be open.
Let's go.
That's right. Just walk around the room.
No aiming.
No purpose,
other than to move your legs.
That's it.
Stop.
Look at the person nearest you.
What does that person make you feel?
Now, find a way, without words,
to communicate that feeling
to the other person.
Does hugging feel honest?
So happy to see you.
Me, you, as well.
That's not the only reason I came.
Can we get a couple of Bloody Marys?
Holy shit.
That's the tip of the iceberg, Peggy.
I never know if that's good or bad.
The director, Jeff Dole,
has two more industrials
and he's asked me to produce them.
And they both need scripts.
And when Ken turned your idea in,
they put him in charge
of the corporate presentation.
It's got a $60,000 budget.
I already have a very demanding job.
Do you have a contract?
I really thought you'd be on a beach by now.
I've been to the beach.
But when I talked to Ken,
I realized it would be easy to turn this
into an actual production company.
Eventually, I could hire writers to help you
with the work load.
Slow down.
Harris-Olson.
You need two names to make it sound real.
Are you serious?
Could you give us a minute?
We won't answer to anyone.
It'll be something of ours,
with our name on it.
I'm so flattered.
So?
I don't know.
I can't believe you're hesitating.
How can you work at that place?
It's a huge decision.
Well, you can think about it,
but I need to find someone
by the end of the week.
Find a partner?
Find a writer.
The partnership is just for you.
You don't have to say why you're here.
Why don't you tell me
how you're feeling right now?
I feel like
everyone's judging me.
And how does it feel to tell us that?
Like I'm a little girl
and my parents are looking at me
the way that they look at me now.
Like all I do is screw up.
"You shouldn't have dropped out of school.
"You shouldn't have been with a lowlife.
"Shouldn't have gotten pregnant.
"You should have loved being a mother."
Life is full of "shoulds."
Yeah, but I made a mistake,
and I just want to get it together now.
So you can be with your baby?
What? No.
See? They are judging me.
Why don't you tell Angie how
it feels to hear her say that?
It makes me feel small
and insignificant, Angie.
What I feel when I hear about your baby
is sadness.
My mother left, and I can tell you
that your baby is gonna spend
the rest of his life
staring at the door
waiting for you to walk in.
Stephanie, is it okay if I tell you
how this is making me feel?
Don't listen to them.
You think this is a big laugh, don't you?
You weren't raised with Jesus.
You don't know what happens to people
when they believe in things.
It's true. You think that
I don't want to hear the truth?
I could help you.
I could move to L.A.
I don't know what you're doing.
You show up with some family heirloom.
You're not my family.
What's the matter with you?
I just know how people work.
You can put this behind you.
It'll get easier as you move forward.
Dick, I don't think you're right about that.
I have to lie down. I'll see you after dinner.
I'm going to split.
Well, I'm going to sit here
and look at these four walls.
If you're not gonna work,
I can try and catch up.
Get the door.
Do you like it here?
Yeah. It's grown on me.
Joan said she wants to go into business.
She's going to be a producer
and I'd be her partner.
You don't like that?
I can have my name on the door,
be my own boss.
That's not a good reason.
You think it'll fail?
No. You have such a rare talent.
Stop looking over your shoulder
at what other people have.
You don't think I can do it.
I said the opposite.
You're just excited about being in charge.
Working for a producer?
That's not even what you do.
You have no ambition!
I'm just very happy being good at my job.
I've got nothing else to prove.
Spoken like a failure.
I hope you're really drunk,
because you're going to need an excuse.
Stan.
There's more to life than work.
Coffee.
Is the coast clear?
Who'd you think I was talking to?
They're gone.
I could eat a dozen eggs.
I'm sorry, but I just found out
I can't go to Old Lyme this afternoon.
I just wanted you to look at a boat.
Sounds lovely,
but Jeffrey says Nathan's Frankfurters
wants to show me around.
Coney Island. We can make a day of it.
It's a business meeting.
Because you've started a business?
We'll see.
What are you doing?
It's just a couple of little projects.
Don't you want to be with me?
Of course.
But I don't know,
it seems like this might be
a chance to build something.
It's going to take all your time,
all your energy, and all your attention.
That's not true.
It is. I did it.
And you loved it.
I want to be with you
and I don't wanna be rooting for
you to fail so that can happen.
Do you want to get married?
We can get married.
No, I don't want to be back where I was.
This can be different.
We're different people.
I want you in my life.
You really want to answer that, don't you?
No, but I probably should.
You act like this is happening to you
but you're making a choice.
I can't just turn off that part of myself.
I would never dream of making you choose.
When something's wrong, it's always wrong.
Hello. Joan Harris speaking.
Could you please hold for a second?
Richard. Wait. You're being silly.
Good luck, Joan.
Well, hello, Jeff. Sorry about that.
Have you seen Stephanie?
She took off a few hours ago.
Did she say where she was going?
I'm sorry. I would have asked
if I'd known you needed to know, man.
How do I get out of here?
My friend took the car.
We can get you a car and driver
with a couple days' notice.
Or you could hitch,
but you'll be standing there all day.
You can thank Charlie Manson for that.
Damn it.
I'm sure you can get a ride back with
someone by the end of the week.
You're all paid up.
People just come and go
and no one says goodbye?
I'm sorry, but people are free
to come and go as they please.
I have a person-to-person call
for Peggy Olson
from Donald Draper.
This is Peggy Olson. I accept.
Where the hell are you?
Somewhere in California.
Do you know how angry everyone is?
Did everything fall apart without me?
It's not about that. You just took off.
People were worried.
What have you been doing?
I don't know.
I have no idea.
Look,
I know you get sick
of things and you run,
but you can come home.
Where?
McCann will take you back in a second.
Apparently, it's happened before.
Don't you want to work on Coke?
I can't.
I can't get out of here.
Don, come home.
I messed everything up.
I'm not the man you think I am.
Don, listen to me.
What did you ever do that was so bad?
I broke all my vows.
I scandalized my child.
I took another man's name
and made,
nothing of it.
That's not true.
I only called because I,
realized I never said goodbye to you.
I don't think you should be alone right now.
I'm in a crowd.
I just wanted to hear your voice.
I'll see you soon.
Wait.
Rizzo.
It's me.
What do you want?
I just got off the phone with Don.
Are you kidding me? Where the hell is he?
California.
But he didn't say where.
I'm really worried about him.
He always does this
and he always comes back.
He's a survivor. He's going to be okay.
You didn't hear him.
He wasn't making any sense.
You've got to let him go.
It doesn't mean you stop caring about him.
I'm sorry I said those shitty things to you.
I don't believe them.
Look, you're going to do great
no matter what you do.
I think you were right.
I mean, I'm going to stay.
Good, because I didn't want you to leave.
Then why didn't you just say that?
Because every time I'm face to face with you,
I want to strangle you.
And then I miss you when I go away.
And I miss you, I call you on the phone,
and I get the person I want to talk to.
That's not true.
Yeah, well, I don't know what it is,
but when I'm standing in front of you,
I bring out something terrible.
I think about how you came into my life
and how you drove me crazy, and now
I don't even know what to do with myself
because all I want to do is be with you.
What?
What did you just say?
I want to be with you.
I'm in love with you.
What?
I love you, Peggy.
Oh, my God!
That's what I thought you said.
I don't know what to say.
I feel like I can't breathe almost.
I mean, I don't even think about you.
Uh, I mean, I do all the time,
because you're there.
And you're here.
And you make everything okay.
You always do.
No matter what.
I mean, I must be.
Because you're always right.
I can't believe this.
I think I'm in love with you, too.
I really do.
Stan?
Are you there?
What were you saying?
I love you.
Are you waiting for a phone call?
What?
Have you taken something?
You know what? Why don't you
come with me to my seminar?
I can't move.
Sure you can. I'm late.
I don't want to walk in by myself.
I guess what I feel is I had my hang-ups.
She had her hang-ups,
but one of us was willing
to reduce the conflict.
How would you feel about
starting with that next time?
My name's Leonard
and I don't know if there's anything
that complicated about me.
Which is why I should be happier, I guess.
Do you remember what I said
to Daniel about "should?"
Well, it's good for him. He's interesting.
But I've never been interesting to anybody.
I work in an office.
People walk right by me.
I know they don't see me.
And I go home
and I watch my wife and my kids.
They don't look up when I sit down.
How does it feel to say that?
I don't know.
It's like no one cares that I'm gone.
They should love me.
I mean, maybe they do,
but I don't even know what it is.
You spend your whole life
thinking you're not getting it,
people aren't giving it to you.
Then you realize they're trying,
and you don't even know what it is.
I had a dream I was on a shelf
in the refrigerator.
Someone closes the door
and the light goes off,
and I know everybody's out there eating.
And then they open the door
and you see them smiling.
And they're happy to see you,
but maybe they don't look right at you
and maybe they don't pick you.
And then the door closes again.
The light goes off.
Welcome aboard!
Holloway-Harris. How may I help you?
Of course. Please hold for Joan.
This is Joan.
Look at them. One day that will be us.
Yeah, tomorrow.
Mother Sun, we greet you
and are thankful
for the sweetness of the Earth.
The new day brings new hope.
The lives we've led,
the lives we get to lead.
A new day,
new ideas,
a new you.
Om.
I'd like to buy the world a home
And furnish it with love
Grow apple trees and honey bees
And snow white turtle doves
I'd like to teach the world
to sing
- Sing with me
- In perfect harmony
Perfect harmony
I'd like to buy the world a Coke
And keep it company
That's the real thing
I'd like to teach the world
to sing
In perfect harmony
Perfect harmony
I'd like to buy the world a Coke
And keep it company
And it's the real thing
Coke is
What the world wants today
Coca-Cola
Is the real thing
Coke is
What the world wants today
Coca-Cola
Is the real thing