Erstwhile on Fargo...
We need to find Rye,
bring him home.
Yes, ma'am.
He known to you?
Ed? Yeah. He's a butcher.
I ran over him! Hit and run!
His name was Rye Gerhardt and
his family hurts people for money.
If you did something, you
made a mistake, you panicked,
maybe covered it up,
now's the time to say.
But that window's closing
and you may already be dead.
We're asking you to leave.
Management says acquire the
territory, we acquire it.
Whether that's cash down or
sending bodies to the morgue,
that's up to the krauts.
Joe Bulo says hi.
Your counter has been rejected.
And now we're lowering our
price by two million.
Anything other than
unconditional surrender
and we'll wipe every last Gerhardt
off the face of the earth.
My father was a salesman.
Ladies' shoes.
It's fair to say, during the
Depression, that he struggled.
Like a lot of people on the
Rock River, in Dixon, Illinois.
But I've never been one
to focus on life's downs.
I was a lifeguard
in high school.
And where some saw a drowning
man, I saw a life to save.
Which I did 77 times
in five years.
They put up a plaque
after I became governor.
Well, I'd have to say I'm prouder
of that than just about anything.
I'm gonna call you Chief
Wigwam, you bring that thing.
Any man can fire a gun.
The longbow is an art.
Everythin' okay?
Just a little housekeeping.
Let's kill ourselves some deer.
My friends, we have in
our lifetime fought harder,
paid a higher price for freedom,
and done more to advance
the dignity of man
than any people who
ever lived on this earth.
But if you look around, you may not
see many signs of that dignity.
Crime is up, jobs are scarce.
You have to stand in a line
just to fill up your car.
How?
He was run down in the street, then
finished off at a second location.
You're sure?
Who?
Butcher.
A butcher?
Down in Luverne.
Like the law said, Rye followed
the judge, shot up the place.
Got killed after.
By a butcher?
That's his name.
Butcher of Luverne.
That's what they call him.
He's a contract man out of...
Out of Kansas City.
I wanna hear it from him.
Kid was marked.
Probably the day he left.
Butcher ambushed
him after the judge.
Tried to grab him, probably.
He got in some licks.
Things went downhill.
Why?
Ma, it's war. You said yourself.
They're jackals.
Came here talkin'
about a settlement.
Meanwhile the kid
is already dead.
I'm askin' him.
He's a bargaining
chip, yeah? Rye?
Kansas City thinks
if they grab him up,
then come to you
with that leverage,
you'll sell for sure.
Instead, they kill him,
then panic, cover it up,
knowin' once you find out,
sale's dead, no question.
See?
The citizens of this great
nation want leadership, yes,
but not a man on a white horse
demanding obedience to his commands.
They want someone who believes they
can begin the world over again.
I'm sayin' the age of the
local mom and pop is over.
And what comes next,
Commissioner,
the era of big business is gonna
make a lot of people very rich.
I like the sound of that.
And you're sayin' you can deliver
leaders on the state and local level?
Joe, there's not
a politician in this state
wouldn't take my call
in the middle of dinner.
Well, then you and me, we're
really gonna be pals.
A leader who will unleash
their great strength
and remove the roadblocks
government has put in their way.
Watch and learn, Joe.
I believe this nation hungers
for a spiritual revival.
Watch and learn.
What the... Move!
Gerhardts!
That we, all of us, hunger
to once again see honor
placed above
political expediency.
To see government, once again
the protector of liberties,
not the distributor
of gifts and privilege.
Government should uphold and not
undermine those institutions
which are custodians
of the very values
upon which civilization
is founded,
religion, education,
and above all, family.
Weak.
We who are
privileged to be Americans
have had a rendezvous with
destiny since the moment in 1630
when John Winthrop, standing
on the deck of the tiny Arbella
off the coast of Massachusetts,
told that little
band of pilgrims,
"We shall be as
a city upon a hill."
A troubled and afflicted
mankind looks to us,
pleading for us to keep
our rendezvous with destiny,
that we will uphold the
principles of self-reliance,
self-discipline, morality,
and above all, responsible
liberty for every individual.
That we will become that
shining city on a hill.
My friends, I believe
that you and I together
can keep this
rendezvous with destiny.
Thank you.
Thank you very much.
Everyone, thank you.
God bless you.
Son of a bitch is
charismatic, I'll give him that.
But I'm not shakin' his hand.
Why not, Karl?
Because, Sonny, the man
made a movie with a monkey.
It wouldn't be dignified.
Well, hello. How are you?
I loved you in
Cattle Queen of Montana.
Well, thank you. Not many
people liked that film.
Hello, little girl.
Governor, I'll be escorting
your bus to the next stop.
So, whenever you're ready.
Well, all right.
You got drafted?
Yeah, Captain called.
I offered we had
murders to solve, but...
He knows best, probably.
Said he did anyway.
Anyway, just got to take this
as far as the state line.
So, be home by dark. Okay.
Bye.
If you get the chance, ask him if it's
true that Joan Crawford had crabs.
Yeah, I'm not gonna do that.
We got 'em.
Bulo too?
Oh, yeah.
Milligan?
No, he wasn't there.
You can bet they're gonna
come back at us hard.
I thought they'd negotiate.
That's the feminine side, Mom.
It was always gonna be war,
them knowing Rye was dead.
Killin' him, I mean.
I want this Butcher dead.
In Luverne.
No mercy.
I'm sending Virgil.
Hon.
Hon?
Sorry, are we out of coffee?
What?
Did you...
You weren't in bed, so I...
I know, I was just thinkin'...
What?
What we should take.
Take where?
When we go?
Where are we goin'?
To California.
What are you...
What are you talkin'...
When we run, I mean.
Ya heard what Lou said.
I mean, if we've
just messed things...
If I've just messed
things up from the start?
If this is still not over?
Just the tail of the snake.
What are you sayin'?
I mean, what was he even doin' in the
road, for shit sake? That fella.
All those dead people,
and he had a car,
so why was he
standin' in the road?
I don't know.
But...
Constance saw.
Saw what?
The car...
After you cleaned it, but
before we crashed it again.
She knows about the accident.
She drove me home the night I...
The night you got rid of the...
And had to use the bathroom.
I was gonna walk her right out,
but then I heard music
comin' from the garage...
And she came up
behind me and saw.
I mean, what did
she say, though?
I...
I don't think she'll tell, but how
can we know for sure, you know?
And plus now with the law enforcement
askin' questions, suspectin'.
And these ghouls on
the come, Lou said.
Hon, we can't stay here.
No.
Hon.
You said... We agreed.
Clean it up and
everything'd be...
I know, hon...
No.
We did this for a reason, Peg.
For the shop and the kids.
For a reason, so we could stay.
That's the only... That's...
Hon, you got to be realistic.
No. No!
I... We're stayin'.
That was...
Whatever comes, we'll deal with
it, or it'll deal with us.
But I'm buyin' the shop
and we're startin' a family.
But how?
It's too late to get the
money back for the course.
And you said Bud had
to have it by Friday.
We'll figure it out.
That's what people do.
They figure things out,
stay together, make it work.
I can help.
Do your chores, kid.
I'm serious. Playtime's over.
I can do it. You saw.
Luverne, Minnesota.
Ed Blumquist.
He's posin' as the town butcher.
This is baloney.
I'm not just some crippled kid
can't shoot straight.
Ask your dad.
If he says you can
go, you can go.
It should be us.
A Gerhardt.
He killed a Gerhardt,
so it should be one of us.
A real boss would know that.
You're takin' the kid.
You're the boss.
You walk him in.
He pulls the trigger.
Anything goes wrong, you
fix it, you understand?
Where do you think you're goin'?
Got an errand.
Send one of the boys.
I can run my own errand.
It's not safe.
God damn it!
Some people are made of plastic
And you know some people
are made of wood
Some people have
hearts of stone Whoa!
Some people are up to no good
But, baby, I'm for real
I'm as real as real can get
if what you're looking
for is real loving
Then what you see
is what you get
Ha! What you see
What you see
ls what you get
Yeah?
And?
Is what you get
I said what you see
is what you get
It's getting ugly out there.
You okay?
My mother could find the cloud
in every silver lining.
That's cute.
Mine smiles all the
time, like some ghoul.
I think it's 'cause Dad hits
her when she looks sad.
I see Thing One.
Where's Thing Two?
Dead.
Your Indian killed him.
Killed a lot of people.
I didn't know that
was happening.
Nobody told me.
You believe me.
Right?
What are we in your mind?
Romeo and Juliet?
No.
I don't know.
She was a true gloom, my mother.
We used to eat in the dark.
For a laugh, I wrote
on her tombstone,
"Here lies Barbara Milligan,
happy till the end."
Me, on the other hand,
I'm an optimist.
So, when I see this...
Oh.
I don't think
the sky is falling.
I think, that, sir, is the
sound of opportunity knocking.
Not so much my young friend.
It's not my fault.
They had a meetin' without me.
I would've said.
If you want me to
take you seriously,
you have to be a serious person.
Have a beer, do a line,
blow your load,
all that's fine,
but it's not the point.
What's the point?
I wanna know what they're
gonna do before they do it.
Every time.
Otherwise, you can die
with the rest of 'em.
Okay, car 1-8, come in, over.
This is 1 -8. Go ahead.
I got Fargo PD on the
line lookin' for you.
Yeah, okay. Patch it through.
Hey, how's your day then?
Peachy. You?
Oh, it's a shit
sandwich up here.
Got 12 dead in the woods.
Half Gerhardt, half Kansas City,
plus a local zoning commissioner
with half his face
in the bushes.
Good Christ.
Yeah.
This thing's gonna get worse
before it gets better.
Well, on my end, we think we know
what happened to Rye Gerhardt.
Run over by a local beautician.
Got stuck in her windshield.
We think she and her husband panicked
and dumped the body someplace.
Meanwhile, we've had
visitors from both factions,
most likely lookin'
for revenge, so,
a little like the
Cuban Missile Crisis.
Well, my captain thinks
I should try to intervene,
seein' as how my
mom knows Floyd,
and maybe cooler heads
can prevail, et cetera,
which, well, you saw how well
that went over last time, huh?
Sounds like maybe
I should come up.
Wouldn't mind the company.
Well, I'm stuck
on this Reagan detail today.
So, assumin' we survive the night
here, I'll drive up first thing.
Thanks.
Okay, I'll try to keep the pot
from boilin' over in the meantime.
Yeah. Over.
No, I... Yeah,
that's... I understand.
It's a recession...
No, I appreciate it, and...
Okay.
Okay, say hi to
Aunt Velma for me.
Nothin'?
Personally, not sure why
you're makin' all this effort.
Gonna buy the shop,
be my own boss.
And?
And what? That's
the American Dream.
What's the point?
Just gonna die anyway.
What do you mean?
Camus says knowin' we're all
gonna die makes life a joke.
So what, you just give up?
You could kill yourself.
Get it over with.
Okay, that's not...
I mean, come on. You gotta try.
No.
You go to school, you get a
job, you start a family.
Die. That's...
Would you please
stop sayin' that?
I'm gonna live
a long, long life.
My grandpa was 96.
At which point he did what?
Died.
Noreen.
Well, okay, I'm goin'
to go in the back now,
away from this nonsense.
Would you please let
me know if Bud's back?
I will.
Unless I'm dead.
What are you waitin' for?
You want that I should
carry you over there?
No, I was just...
Well, do I, you know, shoot
him in the head or in...
Don't overthink it.
Just point and shoot.
If he keeps movin',
shoot him again.
Simple.
Kid.
One more thing.
No witnesses.
Oh. Sorry. Didn't hear ya.
What kind of meat do you want?
We got pig meat,
cow meat, chicken meat.
Bud won't let us sell fish, even
though Jesus says eat it on Fridays.
The...
Lookin' for the butcher.
Blumquist.
Yeah, he's not the butcher.
More the assistant butcher.
Though, that's gonna
change, I think.
Buyin' the place.
Not that you need to...
He's in the back. I'll buzz him for you.
Oh, hey, I read that.
Oh, yeah?
Last year.
It's pretty depressin'.
Really?
See, I think it's beautiful.
But then everyone always says,
"Noreen, you're morose."
Halloween is my
favorite holiday.
I like Easter.
'Course.
The resurrection.
It's like why
everyone loves Rocky,
even though it's
a boxin' picture.
The comeback.
Except, he loses in the end.
Well, now you ruined it.
Sorry.
Just kiddin'.
Oh, here's Ed now.
Sorry, was just in
the middle of a hog.
So, what can I do you for?
Let's find each other tonight
Everything will be all right
Don't hesitate now
Let's find each other tonight
If you need some company
Mama, take a chance on me
Don't hesitate now
Let's find each other tonight
You don't wanna be
like those other dreamers
That dream about love
and never love
You wanna be a screamer
So, honey, I'm hopin'
Honey, I'm hopin'
If you need some company
Mama, take a chance on me
Don't hesitate now Let's
find each other tonight
Hey ya, Peggy.
I just...
I'm here for my car.
Yeah, so she's all fixed,
front and back.
Put a new windshield on her.
She's a sweet car, really.
Okay.
So, is that gonna be cash or...
I wrote out a check.
Maybe don't cash it 'til the
end of the week though, huh?
Payday.
Oh, yeah, that's no problem.
You goin' somewhere?
Well, I guess so.
You know, for the best.
Best what?
Just...
Wait till the end of the month
to cash that check, okay?
Yeah, sure thing.
You take care.
You wanna buy my car?
What do you mean?
Well, you said it was sweet,
and, you know, we
gotta buy the shop?
The butcher shop?
So, we could use the money.
What about your trip?
Decided not to go.
Just now?
Moments ago.
Well, I couldn't give you
any more than $700 for her.
Okay.
Are you sure?
It's worth at least 14.
Yeah, well, seven today
is better than 14 tomorrow.
So can we do it now,
like, right away?
Wash away my
troubles Wash away my pain
With the rain in Shambala
Wash away my sorrow
Wash away my shame
With the rain in Shambala
Ooh, yeah
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah
How'd it go this mornin'?
Killed a few, lost a few.
But you delivered the message.
I want to thank you for your
service to this family.
Me and Mom.
Ever since my dad took you
in, eight, nine years old,
you never complained
or made demands.
Though it might not feel
like it all the time, to me,
you're part of this family.
Not that Dodd would
ever tell you that,
which I know you're mostly his
guy, but I just want you to know,
there's a place for you at our
table, with or without him.
All you gotta do is
be straight with us.
I am straight.
Well, of course. It's just...
We just escalated this war
on account of what you...
The information you
found out about Rye.
Mom's real upset,
but I have to just double-check
the veracity of...
Before it's too far
over the breach.
My daughter back?
What the hell are you doin'?
Get back to work.
That's my man.
You need to talk to him,
you talk to me first.
Last time I checked, everyone
here worked for one person. Ma.
You actually like it, huh?
Takin' orders from a woman.
Is that how it was in the
bedroom with Kathy?
Don't you talk about her.
She strap one on,
bend you over the bed,
and show you who's boss?
There'll be a reckoning
one day, brother.
All souls are called to
account for their actions.
In the end, we all
get what we deserve.
You keep tellin' yourself that.
The eyes of
all people are upon us
so that if we shall deal falsely with
our God in this work we have undertaken
and so cause Him to withdraw
his present help from us,
we shall be made a story and a
byword throughout the world.
A troubled and afflicted
mankind looks to us.
My friends, I believe
that you and I together
can keep this rendezvous
with destiny.
Thank you.
God bless you and
God bless America.
Oh!
Oh, that's good.
Been holding it
since Ortonville.
My wife puts this potpourri
in the bus toilet,
can barely breathe in there.
They do like their scents.
Where'd you serve, son?
Mekong Delta, swift boat patrol.
Two tours.
Well, I sure
appreciate your service.
Every generation has their time.
I remember back in '42, America
had just joined the war.
I was working on Operation
Eagle's Nest for Paramount.
I got dropped behind enemy lines
trying to rescue Jimmy
Whitmore and Laraine Day
from this SS commando.
Bob Stack was on
loan from Selznick.
That Nazi bastard
had us cornered.
We were done for,
but in the end,
with a little
American ingenuity,
we managed to...
No, now wait a minute. Um...
Come to think of it, I don't think
we made it out of that one.
Or did we?
Oh, shit, I can't remember.
Well, either way,
it was a fine picture.
Um...
Governor, I don't mean to...
What we did over
there, the war...
Um...
And now, my wife's got lymphoma.
Stage III.
And lately, the
state of things...
Well, sometimes, I...
Late at night...
I wonder if maybe the
sickness of this world,
if it isn't inside
my wife somehow.
The cancer.
I don't know what
I'm sayin' except,
do you really think we'll get
outta this mess we're in?
Son, there's not a
challenge on God's earth
that can't be overcome
by an American.
I truly believe that.
Yeah.
But how?
Mommy. Sorry.
Poppa's here.
Your dad is?
No.
No, just me.
Saw Molly in the window.
I knocked, you didn't hear?
No.
Well, got worried,
so I let myself in.
You feelin' okay?
Oh, sure.
Little tired.
Yeah, just talked to Lou,
probably got another two hours
on this Reagan detail.
So I thought, you know, I'd just
stop by and make a nuisance.
Are you hungry?
I can fix you somethin'.
You're sweet.
I was just now tryin' to decide
if I'm hungry or
if I wanna throw up.
Don't normally confuse the two.
Well, nausea's a side effect
of this drug they gave me.
Which would mean they actually
gave me the drug, and not candy.
There's candy?
Eat somethin' green
and we'll talk.
So we're rootin'
for nausea, then, huh?
Well, okay. Um...
I'm just all left thumbs when
it comes to this stuff...
You're doin' great. Dad.
No, I don't know about that.
If your mom were here,
she'd know just what to say.
Me?
I can fix the toaster.
Well, maybe just...
Do you think maybe you could
watch Molly for a bit?
I just don't...
I'm not sure if I can keep my eyes
open right now, for some reason.
Watch who?
Me.
Who?
Oh, what the heck.
Thank you, Dad.
Yeah, sure. You get some rest.
We'll just be here
eating sugar cereal
and playing with
my service weapon.
Now, what the heck is that?
Rhinoceros?
Yeah, it's Charlie.
I'm lookin' for Dad.
Well, is he...
When's he comin' back?
No, that's...
Just... Just tell him that I'm
ready for school... To go back.
I wanna go, like he said.
Okay then.
Ed!
No, no!
Noreen.
Noreen, you okay?
You okay?
Come on. Come on.
Ed.
Ed!
Come on! Leave him, leave him.
No, no, he's still alive!
We've got to take him.
Ed. Okay.
Okay.
Call the fire truck!
I saved the kid.
Didn't I?
Didn't I? Yeah.
And he shot first?
Can you tell the cops that?
And the big guy, he came at me
and that it was self-defense?
Yeah? Yeah.
Of course.
But...
Ed!
Where you been?
I just met a friend.
Mmm.
You think you're
grown? Is that it?
What?
With your clothes and
your hair and no bra.
Like you know somethin'
about the world.
Bein' grown's got a price.
Kid gets a slap when he's bad.
When you're grown,
you get the fist.
Or the knife.
Son.
You let that girl alone.
Get upstairs now, darlin'.
Hon? Hon?
Hon, where's the luggage?
We need to pack.
Hon!
Hon, we, we...
Hon.
Yeah, we... We need...
I got a surprise for you.
That's... Okay,
but we need to...
No, we don't gotta go.
No, listen. I wanna talk to ya.
I've been thinkin' a lot
about what you said
and how I've been and... Sit.
Sit.
That... That...
No, this is important!
What I'm tryin' to say
is you were right.
I mean, we were both right,
but you also is what I'm...
Not just me, in other words.
And what you said about
the shop and the money,
that was... It was
selfish of me to...
I mean, without even askin'.
And also, we gotta fight,
fight for what we want.
Okay, but... You know.
And I can see that now.
So... Hon, we...
- Hon!
- Ta-da!
I sold the car. What car?
My car.
I went to the shop and Sonny, you
know, he said how much he loved it,
and so I... And I know that I
could've gotten more for it,
but it's enough is what matters.
Enough to buy the shop.
You, you...
Because you were right.
This was our dream, you know.
And so now, we can do it.
The shop burned down.
What?
And I killed another
fella, maybe two.
And Lou... Lou was right.
They came.
They came. The other fella
that you hit, his family?
They came.
So, this is...
That's great,
you know, thank you.
But we gotta go.
You need to pack.
Okay, okay?
Look at... Okay.