Am I, uh...
What are we waiting for?
What?
The arrows.
Gayle's putting in
the arrows on Reagan.
Yeah, I know, it's...
But they said...
Jenny came by the trailer.
She said five minutes, so...
Well, there's a lot of arrows.
So...
Should I just go back to my.
. . No.
No, it's, uh... Jenny said...
What did Jenny say?
They're... They're
putting in the arrows.
Yeah, I know, but how long?
Doll! Just find out, will you?
'Cause the chief
is wearing moccasins here.
It's goddamn February.
So, what's he like, anyway? Who?
Dutch, Reagan.
Ronnie? Ah! He's a prince.
He's a real class act.
Yeah.
Can I get a blanket?
This is the actual field,
they tell me.
What? It's the
actual battlefield.
Massacre at Sioux Falls?
I think 300 of your people, braves,
died here, what, 100 years ago?
I'm from New Jersey.
Sure, but...
Yeah, you're...
You're an Indian, right?
So that's gotta be, uh...
Gotta be what?
No, I'm just saying.
This battle, you know, was the last
big battle before the end of...
And what came after...
Whew, look, I'm a Jew, so
believe me, I know tribulation.
Yeah. Smoke?
Any minute, he'll be out.
Right. Nobody moves.
Everybody is still dead.
It is a crisis of confidence.
It is a crisis that strikes
at the very heart and soul
and spirit of our national will.
We can see this crisis
in the growing doubt about the
meaning of our own lives.
And in the loss of
a unity of purpose.
Is he kidding me?
...has
been taken out of the home
of John Wayne Gacy and...
The erosion of our confidence
in the future...
...is threatening
to destroy the social
and the political
fabric of America.
That's what I'm trying
to engage with here,
is this untapped
potential of yours
to sort of think a little bit.
Confidence in the future
has supported everything else.
Hey there.
Sorry.
Are you kidding me?
You said noon, yeah?
Now, hold on now...
I said 11:00, not noon. What?
Say that again. Okay.
Say it again.
Okay, okay.
Where's the goddamn money?
Gave it to Ollie,
like, yesterday.
Don't lie.
I mean, I'm getting it.
It's just a little late.
The hell you say,
I did the rounds.
Everybody paid.
Of course
they're gonna say that.
So you got the money?
Well, you know, maybe I needed
it for me, for something I...
No, you earn for the family,
not for yourself.
Yeah.
But you're the oldest and then
there's Bear, and that's the throne.
What am I ever gonna be except
the kid you send out for milk?
You're a Gerhardt.
That's like Jupiter telling Pluto,
"Hey, you're a planet, too."
What?
If I'm this royalty,
how come you got me doing bullshit
collections like some nobody chump?
Everybody earns. That's the law.
Yeah, but what if I got
ambitions, you know?
You wear short pants
till you prove you're a man.
I'm a man.
You're the comic
in a piece of bubble gum!
Well, I mean, says you.
You got till tomorrow to bring
the collection money you owe.
Or what?
You make me wait for you
again, I'll cleave your skull.
This is
the month's cash, all in.
You'll see the problem
right away.
Light?
Mmm.
About time.
Give me a break.
Soon as you ladies
are done dancing...
You're right. We're light.
Even though the transport
dollars went up.
It's the local business.
Gambling and drugs. And whores.
Aren't any good at this, huh?
Don't pin this on me.
Or me.
We earned.
- But not Rye.
- No.
But even without his nut,
we shouldn't be this short.
It's like we're a balloon
leaking air all over.
Spit it out.
What are we talking about here?
Tell me, God damn it.
Another outfit.
I'm taking care of it.
From the south.
Don't know where.
- I said I'd handle it.
- They're coming hard.
Son, I am the iron fist of God.
There's not a sane man in three
states who would dare to...
Some pissant crew
from south no-place?
You bring me these
hirnlose Mutterfotzen
and I'll grind their bones
to make my...
Otto?
Otto.
All right? Hear me.
I'm saying tomorrow has never
been closer than it is right now.
It's 11:00 in the morning.
Metaphorically, I mean.
Hi, friend.
Be with you in a... Check
never came is my point.
I'm owed for work I done.
Me and the boys, we're owed.
Giddy-up there, cowboy.
Wait your turn, short round.
What'd you say?
You heard me.
Jesus! Just, uh...
It's in the mail, okay?
The check.
Just... If it hasn't come by
Tuesday, I'll write you another.
Yeah, that's right.
You better run.
Come on now!
He could call a cop!
He's not calling anybody.
Guys like that, they're
just big on the outside.
So, where's this
miracle contraption?
Behold the future. I'm talking
money, hand over fist.
A typewriter.
A self-correcting IBM Selectric
Two electric typewriter
with patented
high-speed typeball.
They're not just
for women anymore.
And you're sure
we're the only...
Sole distributor,
Midwest region.
Assuming you're willing to forget
certain debts owed to your family
from the, uh... Gambling.
Yeah, which, you know,
I'm not proud.
So soon as you talk to the judge
and she unfreezes the accounts,
well, then, we can turn
on the money spigot.
The what?
The spigot? It's like
where you hook up a hose?
Like a fire hose?
Any hose.
I'm saying once we get those typewriters,
the money, there'll be no stopping it.
Ah, which judge again?
People of the
Earth, can you hear me?
Came a voice from the sky
on that magical night
And in the colors
of a thousand sunsets
They traveled through the
world on a silvery light
You're the comic in
a piece of bubble gum!
The people of the Earth
stood waiting
Watching as the ships
came one by one
Setting fire to the sky
as they landed
Carrying to the world
children of the sun
Welcome to Waffle Hut!
Shit, lady. Table or booth?
Just, uh, the counter.
Special's tuna melt and fries.
Pie's humbleberry.
Just coffee.
Everything's
taken care of, I see.
Sugar?
Uh, ma'am, you're
freaking me out a little.
So, now he squeezes and the
mustard goes all over his shirt.
He didn't have another shirt
to wear, so...
I'm gonna pay up now. I'll
meet you at the counter.
How was everything?
Real good. Oh, good.
I'll get your change.
There you are. Thank you.
Hi. No.
What do you mean, "No"?
Whatever you're selling,
I ain't buying.
First of all,
I'm not selling anything.
And second... You need
to make me another burger.
This one's a coaster.
Yes, ma'am.
Hey. Your Majesty.
You're gonna change your mind
about something. A case.
Or what?
Or you'll find out is what.
This isn't one of those optional
"check A or B" scenarios.
I'm gonna change your mind.
One day the Devil
came to God and said,
"Let's make a bet, between you
and me, for the soul of a man."
And from on high they looked down
on Job, a devout man, religious,
and the Devil said,
"I can change his mind
"and make him curse your name."
And God said, "Try and
you will only fail."
So the Devil begins.
He kills Job's herds
and takes his fields.
He plagues him with boils and
throws him on the ash heap.
But Job's mind
remains unchanged.
So I ask you, son,
if the Devil couldn't
change Job's mind,
how the hell are you
gonna change mine?
What?
You're a little dim, aren't you?
Listen, this is...
There's two ways this can go...
Is one of them the hard way?
Easy... You know what?
There's a fella who needs to get
his hands on some typewriters.
And you're gonna... Ah,
Christ, you're with that fool.
Yeah, you're...
Son, you have three seconds to pick
your ass up and get out of here,
or I'm gonna
squash you like a bug.
Okay, look, bitch.
I'm the one doing...
God damn, my eyes!
Now scram before
I call the cops!
Oh, crap.
Shit.
"'Oh, Wocky, ' cried Joe. 'See
what you've done, Polly Pepper?'
"But Polly didn't hear.
"Over the big,
flat door stone she sped,
"and met Ben with little
David coming in the gate.
"His face was
just like Franzie's.
"With a cold,
heavy feeling in her heart,
"Polly realized
that this was no play.
"Oh, Ben, she cried,
flinging her arms
"around his neck
and bursting into tears.
"'Don't, please.
I wish you wouldn't.
"Franzie's got them
and that's enough.'
"'Got what?' asked Ben.
"Well, Davie's eyes grew to
their widest proportions.
"Oh, measles, cried Polly,
bursting out afresh.
"'The hatefulist,
horridist measles.
"'Now you're taken.'
"Oh, no, I ain't,
responded Ben cheerfully.
"Who knew what measles were?
"'Wait, now Polly, I'm all right.
"'Only my head aches
and my eyes feel funny.'
"Polly, only half-reassured,
gulped down her sobs
"and the sorrowful trio
repaired to Mother.
"Oh, dear me,
ejaculated Mrs. Pepper,
"sinking in a chair
at the dismay
"at the sight of Ben's red face.
"'Whatever we do now..."
This is a funny book, huh?
Yeah. Yeah.
Phone call, hon. It's the shop.
Okay, you. Sleep, huh?
- I'll be back in a minute to tuck you in.
- Okay.
Murder, Eunice says. Three of them.
Over at the Waffle Hut.
Hey, uh, you had
your thing today?
Yeah, this morning.
You feel okay?
Compared to what? Love Canal?
Hmm?
Solverson.
Yeah, okay.
Tell him not to go inside.
- Hank on his way?
- Yeah.
Called and he says he'll meet you there.
Have a good one.
Okay, you, too.
Gotta go, hon. You okay
getting her to bed?
Yeah, she's six.
Not, you know, Pol Pot.
Okay. Call if you
need, you know, whatever.
I left my rig there.
I hope that's okay.
I'm the one
who called it in, see?
Stopped for waffles, you know.
With the blueberries?
They come frozen this time
of year, I know, but...
I put my coat on her.
Seemed only right.
Yeah.
Yeah, it's okay
about the coat, or...
Yeah.
Well, this is a deal.
I count three dead.
Saw the waitress in
the parking lot? Mmm.
Think she caught one there,
then staggered out.
Gunman followed,
made things permanent.
That's Henry Blanton.
Got the single-season touchdown
record in 10th grade.
Thirty-one.
Still stands.
Yeah. Don't know her.
North Dakota plates
on the Mercedes outside.
Tourist, you're thinking?
Mmm.
How's Betsy?
You mean you didn't call
her before you came over?
Well, yeah.
Just being polite.
Give you a chance
to talk about your feelings,
should you be so disposed.
She's good. Yeah.
Ordered this kit of recipe cards.
Saw it on the TV.
So now every night, we eat
delicacies of the world.
Hmm. Some men like that.
Variety. Mmm.
She put a soufflé
on the table last night.
Perfectly good casserole. Then lit
it on fire with a kitchen match.
Huh?
Oh, which reminds me, you're
invited for dinner tomorrow.
6:00? Mmm-hmm.
I'll bring you a suit of armor.
Skid marks.
Yeah, I see them.
Of course, connecting those
to this deal here
would be what we call
jumping to a conclusion.
Based on the number of bodies,
I'm thinking we got one car
too many in the parking lot.
Yeah.
So, the shooter's got a wound or
two in him from the steak knife.
Two blood trails lead out, one
to the waitress, now deceased,
the other to the road here,
where he absconds,
leaving a few dollars behind.
Uh-huh.
Why not take his own car?
Unclear at this time.
There's a shoe in that tree.
There sure is.
So, uh, this a local matter
or the state police want it?
We do not.
Local matter it is.
Of course, any support
the state can provide...
Yeah, of course. Mmm.
See you tomorrow night, then, eh?
6:00.
Be ready for anything.
That's a shoe, all right.
Okay then.
Noreen?
Mmm?
Ed's leaving.
Okay then.
Oh, hey, you may as well
take these with you.
Boolie Hendricks paid,
but never picked them up.
Chops. Mmm.
Wasted meat's a crime.
Or it should be.
Okay then. Okay then.
Okay then.
B-8.
So, Ho Chi Minh...
Jesus, kid, keep up. Ho Chi
Minh was just a front man.
Enemy number one, straight
out of central casting.
AKA a stuffed shirt for the
military industrial complex.
The what's that now?
Jesus, Mary and Joseph.
Ike's farewell address? The
military industrial complex.
Wheels inside wheels.
Special interests.
N-33.
I thought there'd be
a band tonight.
- Boys. I-17.
I-17.
Balls.
Tell this dipshit pissant
about Ike's farewell address.
You mean the military
industrial complex?
See? He knows.
Of course, we've been to war.
Nothing complex about it.
How come you're in uniform then, Lou?
Didn't you work this morning?
Three dead at the Waffle Hut.
No shit.
Yeah, a real mess. Women, too.
Hank's thinking botched robbery.
Oh, sure. That's what
they want you to think.
Who?
They.
B-11.
You know, the powers that be.
It's a classic story.
Oswald acted alone. The girl
in the polka dot dress.
The what now?
The girl in...
After Kennedy,
the other was shot.
Robert, in LA.
People saw a woman
in a polka dot dress
running out of the hotel
yelling, "We got him."
But who do they arrest?
Uh...
- An Arab.
- Oh, yeah.
Racist pricks.
It's a diner robbery
in Minnesota, Karl.
Not a presidential
assassination.
Oh, sure, that's how it
starts, with something small.
Like a break-in
at the Watergate Hotel.
But just watch. This thing's
only getting bigger.
G-53.
Well, I better get home.
Betsy had her chemo today.
God!
What is it, Karl?
It's just...
God damn.
Unacceptable is what it is.
A woman like that
in the prime of her...
With a young daughter.
N-40.
Tell her if John McCain could hold
out for five-and-a-half years
against Viet Cong thumbscrews,
she can beat this cancer
bullshit in her sleep.
I'll make sure to mention that.
I don't worry
Long as you're by my side
- Hey, hon.
- In the kitchen.
Boolie Hendricks paid for
chops, never picked them up.
So I figured...
Hi. Hi.
Uh, hon, you're getting
blood on the tile.
Sorry, I'll put them
in the fridge.
Hamburger Helper?
And Tater Tots. Yum.
Should I...
Oh, hon. Don't.
I just got that stuff organized.
Yeah, but it's my chair.
Where am I supposed to...
Well, sit there, huh? Yeah.
I'll move that
stuff tomorrow. Promise.
Bon appétit. Mmm.
So, you think there was
an accomplice in a getaway car?
Your dad called.
You know him.
He likes to talk things through
before he goes to bed.
We got glasses.
Tastes different in a glass.
Molly go down okay? Mmm-hmm.
You know, I forgot earlier.
She made you something
at school today. Yeah.
She knows I don't smoke, right?
You could start.
Your dad said he'd be over
Sunday in a suit of armor.
Ugh, jeez. You light one soufflé on fire.
So, I'm getting excited
about this seminar.
The which?
You remember, hon. It's next weekend.
Constance is taking me.
Lifespring. Everybody's doing it.
Oh, yeah.
I really think this course is gonna
help me actualize, you know, fully.
Re-examine old reflex patterns.
The ones that keep
my life from working.
From...
'Cause we're doing great, yeah?
Oh, yeah.
I just mean me,
you know, as a person.
Yeah. Yeah.
Well, Bud asked again if I was interested
in maybe taking over the butcher shop.
Mmm.
Said he's thinking
of retiring end of the year.
Just had the end
of the year, huh?
Yeah, I guess
he means this year,
but wouldn't that be great?
Me owning the shop.
And maybe you take over
the salon one day,
you know, unless we got a
whole litter of kids by then.
Yeah, that's...
We talked about that.
We're trying, but it
takes time, you know?
Yeah. Yeah, of course.
Though, uh...
Hon...
"Trying." I mean...
Last time I checked, there's just the
one way to make a baby, you know.
Did that last weekend,
didn't we?
It was Bear Lake last weekend.
You said you didn't wanna...
Not with Kevin and Sally. Hon...
I just... I just...
I just love you, is all.
So, so much.
And, come on,
our kids would be amazing.
Oh, shoot. Here.
Hon, let me. No, it's fine.
I'm such a bumble sometimes.
What the heck?
I love you too, hon.
So, so much.
Maybe we should
maybe do it right now.
Here? No, silly. In the bedroom.
Come on.
Jeez. I better go see
what that...
We can... I'll wear
that nightie you like!
What the...
Hon?
Didn't I tell you?
I kind of hit a deer.
You hit a...
Well, you okay? Yeah.
No. I'm just,
you know, shook up mostly.
Jeez.
Well, insurance
should cover most of...
Actually, I think I need
to sit down, hon.
Can we go in the kitchen?
Heck, hon,
did you bring the deer home?
Hon, don't.
Hon.
Hon!
Come back. Hey.
Don't.
Jeez.
There's a...
There's a man...
There's a man in the...
Call the...
Call the police... Call the...
Oh, my God.
Hon? Jeez, hon!
Sorry. Are you okay? No. It's...
I'm fine.
Who... You gotta believe me.
I thought he was dead.
What?
When I hit him, I thought he was.
. . You hit him?
You hit him with the car?
You said a deer.
You hit him.
Why didn't you go to the
police or the hospital?
He ran out into the road, hon.
What was I supposed to do?
Yeah, so you brought him home.
You made dinner.
Hamburger Helper.
I panicked, okay?
Yeah, well,
you gotta call the police.
- Why didn't you call the police?
- No.
- We gotta... Maybe he's not...
- No, no.
No, I... Hon, listen to me.
I ran over him! Hit and run!
And then you stabbed him
with a gardening tool.
The cops, do you think
they're gonna believe us?
I don't know, but people
are gonna look for him.
But, look, look, I was careful.
I drove the back way
all the way home.
You drove the...
Hon, a man's dead.
Look, that's why
we have to clean it up.
And tell people
I hit a deer, or...
We could run!
What?
Go to California!
No.
We have a life here, hon, a family.
I'm gonna buy the shop.
Okay then. Okay then.
Okay then.
And we're gonna start a family.
Well, start again, I'm saying.
I don't want to.
Okay, then...
Then, hon, look at me.
If we're gonna get
clear of this,
then we're gonna
have to clean it up.
Pretend it didn't happen.
'Cause if this comes out...
If this... Then all
the things you want,
that we want, that's over.
I go to jail,
and maybe you also.
And then there's no shop
and no family.
No kids.
Okay.
Okay then. We...
We clean it up.
Well...
Should we call that Saturday?
Suppose we better.
She'll be up at 5:00 anyway,
wanting to play dolls.
And I know how fond you are
of your doll-playing time.
Good night, Mr. Solverson.
Good night, Mrs. Solverson,
and all the ships at sea.
Otto?
No!
Otto!
Hold him!
Go out front! Go now!
Now! Otto!
Call a doctor! Go!
So, as you see on page 16
of the prospectus,
the main component of our
Northern Expansion Strategy
involves the absorption of the
Gerhardt Family Syndicate,
headquartered in Fargo, ND.
Now, the Gerhardts control
trucking and distribution
for the entire northern Midwest.
It's a family business started
in 1931 by Dieter Gerhardt.
Now deceased, and taken over
in 1950 by his son, Otto.
Now, not in the report, but
of relevance to this meeting,
old Otto had a stroke yesterday
on the family compound
in North Dakota.
Leaving who in charge?
Unclear.
His wife, Floyd, she's tough,
but, you know, a girl.
And then there are the three sons.
Dodd, Bear and Rye.
And of course, they all want
their shot at the throne.
Which the boys in Research think
provides a tactical opportunity
for us to move aggressively to
acquire or absorb their operation.
And if you can't,
and the current
business owners resist?
We liquidate.
Approved.