Erstwhile on Fargo...
I'm not afraid of a war.
But are you with me?
We're not gonna
make the first move.
But if these Kansas City mooks
come at ya shootin',
we'll cut the goddamn
nose off their face.
Your Indian killed him.
I didn't know
that was happening.
I wanna know what they're
gonna do before they do it.
Otherwise, you can die
with the rest of 'em.
You sent my goddamn son?
The kid said it should be family
that pulls the trigger,
which is true.
He's 17.
Sheriff? Go inside now, Peggy.
When I find you, darling,
I'm gonna make you bleed.
And that,
there's a word for that.
It's called "managing up".
Which, if you want to rise to any
kind of power in this organization,
is something you'd better learn.
Because they'll say to you,
"Go out, do the job,
"and don't worry."
But in fact, what they mean...
Is talk them through it.
You understand?
It doesn't matter if
it's washing machines
or cocaine,
whores or horseradish,
they, the powers that be,
they need to know...
In the shuffling madness
Of the locomotive breath
Runs the all-time loser
Headlong to his death
Oh, he feels the piston scraping
Steam breaking on his brow
Oh, thank God,
he stole the handle
And the train
it won't stop going
No way to slow down
Oh, oh
He sees his children jumping off
At the stations, one by one
His woman and his best friend
In bed and having fun
Oh, oh, he's
crawling down the corridor
On his hands and knees
Old Charlie stole the handle
And the train
it won't stop going
No way to slow down
Hey, hey
We waited.
I don't like funerals.
Nobody likes funerals.
We wanna thank you boys from coming
out from Buffalo, helping us out.
We couldn't have fought
them off much longer.
Forget about it.
I'm seeing cows, horses,
what do you have... Chickens?
It's like wild goddamn
kingdom in here.
We got ups and downs.
Tell me.
Go see to lunch.
I'm grown. I can hear.
We got five of theirs.
Including management.
But they felled
Roost and Seymour.
That means South
Dakota's turned.
Which Bear now tells
me is where they got
the presidents' faces up
on the side of a rock?
So we should get that back.
Nothing from Hanzee? Nothing.
Two days.
What about my dad?
Gonna need a third
hole is my feeling.
Have some respect.
My lion didn't raise that boy to
be killed by small-town muscle.
Thought that about Rye.
Now there's nothing
left but clothes.
They're just men.
What are you saying?
I said,
it's not like my dad's
the shark in that movie,
we're gonna need a bigger boat.
He shits and sleeps.
I swear, I thought your
father was the problem.
His nature, and towards women,
but you're two of the same.
You're porcupines! You're half
crazy, always looking for a fight.
This family
deserves the ground.
I got this.
Hey, porcupine.
Hey. Where you running?
I shouldn't have hit her.
Hitting is the least of it.
Not enough of us left
to start telling the truth.
Go to hell.
Last stand? Make a run for it?
Benjamin.
Floyd.
It's funeral day.
I know.
We waited till the dirt settled.
But, now I need
you to come with us.
It's me you should be taking.
No. You're good.
Floyd.
How's my boy? State
pen, awaiting trial.
You should visit.
Where's your brother?
Found Jesus.
Mmm.
Joined a monastery.
I just bet.
Phone.
Take a message.
You're gonna wanna
take this one, bro.
The prick says he
knows where Dodd is.
Take the message.
Tell me one more time.
Why is Floyd Gerhardt
sitting in my interview room?
Sir,
Trooper Solverson and myself,
we're tired of playing cleanup.
Officially.
Thought we'd apply some
pressure to both sides.
Let them know all this killing
isn't going unnoticed.
What about this butcher?
We've got an APB out on both Blumquists,
Ed and Peggy. So far, nothing.
Could be on the run.
Could be dead.
I should have
checked on that girl.
Eliot Ness himself deputized my
daddy, ATF, during Prohibition.
He used to tell stories
of tommy-gun bloodbaths
and heads rolling in the road.
Never thought I'd see it in my lifetime.
But here we are.
This thing's just
plum out of control.
What do you think?
I think I wanna
live in a world where
people leave
the front door unlocked.
Probably, we're just
wasting our breath.
Okay.
You two go see the out-of-towners.
Leave the old broad to us.
I'm gonna smoke.
Ma'am, I'm Sheriff Larsson,
Rock County.
Had some differences with
your oldest boy yesterday.
How'd that go for you?
Let's call it a draw.
On account of your
Indian sucker-punched me
before I could make a showing.
Yeah, he does that.
Sorry to hear about Otto.
They shot him in his own home,
these Kansas City hosenscheißer.
Children sleeping upstairs.
Savages.
My wife passed last summer. We were
up in Brainerd visiting my sister.
The last thing she said to me,
"Do you smell toast?"
Different roads.
Same destination.
I suppose.
But the question is,
for you I mean,
how far does it go?
Husband dead,
plus your youngest.
Grandson in jail. And now,
Dodd's missing, we hear.
Old timers had it worse.
Used to be 10 born,
two survived.
Consumption, scalpings,
smallpox, wolves.
Well, it's a question of what
you can live with, I suppose.
How many ghosts.
I shot a man through the teeth
in Vichy France.
I still see his face
every night before bed.
Our back is to the wall.
You see that, yeah?
Yeah, except I'm the guy in the
next state who got shanghaied,
and your sons are the ones
that took the drive.
The Butcher of
Luverne killed my boy!
On orders from Kansas City.
I've known Ed Blumquist
since short pants.
If he's working for the Kansas
City mob, I'll cut off my toe.
What's it they call those Russians?
"Sleeper agents?"
I'm saying, you think you know
someone, but what do you know, really?
I even had a kid in
here the other day,
stabbed his parents
to death in their sleep.
When I asked him why,
he couldn't say.
Just come over him
all of a sudden.
Stories used to be
simpler, that's for sure.
This, then that.
And now, I don't know where
it starts or how it ends.
I truly don't.
Without being simplistic,
this thing's over
when you say it's over.
No. They won't stop. My boys.
They've lost too much.
They're too proud.
Well, okay, then.
How about you help us out?
You know these
Kansas City fellas.
Point us in
the right direction there.
You know,
weaknesses, indiscretions.
Give us something actionable,
and maybe,
we make this whole northern
expansion unpalatable.
Snitch.
Well,
you said yourself,
hard to be simple
in times of complication.
The sundown shinin' in
I found my mind
In a brown paper bag within
I tripped on a cloud
and fell eight miles high
I tore my mind on a jagged sky
I just dropped in to see what...
Son of a bitch.
Argh! You son of a bitch.
Yes, sir. Maybe "under
control" was the wrong phrase,
given what's happened.
You said,
when they killed Bulo, you said
this Gerhardt outfit
was a stuffed shirt.
Now I'm standing here
with blood on my socks?
I can handle it.
The hell, you say.
Braverman stood for you.
Said, "He's not like the other darkies.
This one's smart. Capable."
Sir... But that is
not what I'm seeing.
And I appreciate
the opportunity, sir,
believing as I do,
like the good Dr. King said,
"A man should be judged on
the content of his character,
"not the color of his skin."
Yeah, he's dead. You're gonna
need a different quote.
I can break this family.
Two weeks.
You got two days, then I'm
sending The Undertaker.
Yes, sir. Thank you, sir.
You son of a bitch!
"Freedom, that terrible word inscribed
upon the chariot in the storm."
What?
You want me to repeat it?
Is that a quote? Maybe.
What do you want, little girl?
You were supposed to kill my
dad, not the old cripple.
What's the difference?
What?
To quote Louis XVI,
"Est-ce une révolte?"
"Non, Sire,
c'est une révolution."
The Duke of La Rochefoucauld.
Are we gonna talk or are you just
gonna quote the thesaurus at me?
I mean, if the goal is to
kill those who oppress you,
what does it
matter who goes first?
Because, I said...
Now, ironically,
in astronomy, the word
"revolution" means
a celestial object
that comes full circle.
Did you know that?
Which, if you think about it,
is pretty funny,
considering here on Earth,
it means change.
You're nuts.
I'm talking about a promise.
You could have killed me, shooting
up the house. Or Grandma.
Argh!
Unless...
Would you say you're her favorite?
Who?
The materfamilias.
In my experience,
the first-born
granddaughter, well,
she's always
the shine on the apple.
Oh, God.
Help!
Wow.
You okay there, miss?
I am now.
Walk her out, huh?
What about you?
I'm not saying don't come back.
I'm a big girl.
You don't have to nursemaid me.
Floyd know you're here?
Yeah.
Yeah, I've seen you around.
Up at the compound.
Seen me?
Or watched me?
I'm aware, I'm saying, that
the last place you should be
is in a hotel room
with those fellas,
especially given
what's happening.
You won't tell though,
will you?
I don't have to.
Oh, Jesus! Jesus!
Oh.
If I'm going to the
noose, I'm going.
But I'm done lying down for men.
Oh.
Hey.
I uh...
I just...
I was out of weed,
so I bought
a dime bag from Packy?
You know with the uh...
Not safe around here for us.
Yeah?
Wow.
No one tells me nothing.
But I'll...
Look, I can score
weed at other places.
Thanks for the, uh...
Come on, I'll give you a ride.
Got my car.
Ricky'll drive it back.
You two have fun, huh?
Seatbelt on.
So,
is this a conversation about how it's
time for me to pack up and go home?
No.
Don't have to go home.
It's a big country.
Just maybe don't be here.
Are you familiar with the
phrase "manifest destiny"?
Yeah, but see, here's the thing.
I own two pairs of shoes.
A summer pair
and one for winter.
We're not meant to have
more than we can handle,
is what I mean.
So, this need for conquest,
you know,
trying to own things that
aren't meant to be owned...
Like people?
That's an example.
But also places.
Believing we can tame things.
That's a problem, right?
Not a solution.
You're saying
capitalism is a problem?
No.
Greed.
Making this
thing all or nothing.
What happened to you?
What happened? Mmm?
What happened? Let's
just get this over with.
So, you got a response
to my "all-or-nothing" line?
Sometimes...
There's a man.
What? What man?
Just a man, works in a factory.
One day the boss
gets it in his mind
that this man is
stealing from him.
So, every night at the gate,
the guards search
his wheelbarrow.
But they never find anything.
Pat him down.
Oh, they do that.
Strip him naked.
Nothing.
So, he's not stealing.
Of course he is.
Wheelbarrows.
Thank you. That's right.
He's stealing wheelbarrows.
What?
My point is,
sometimes the answer
is so obvious,
you can't see it 'cause
you're looking too hard.
See, we can't leave
because we're the future,
and they're the past.
The past can no more
become the future
than the future
can become the past.
Okay.
We said our piece.
Just don't be offended next time
if I don't say
"hello" before I shoot.
Jeez... Huh?
Karl Weathers! That is a good
way to get yourself shot.
Your lesser half gave us a key.
Asked us to look out for you and
the little one while he's gone.
Do I strike you as someone
who needs looking after?
You do not.
But he asked. So here we are.
I'll sleep on the sofa. Sonny's
already called dibs on the floor.
Wait, did what?
I'd give you the sofa,
see, except for my back.
What's the matter
with your back?
It hurts when I
sleep on the floor.
Eggs are done, pancakes
are warming in the oven.
You can fight me on
are-we-gonna-stay-the-night,
or you and the kid
could grab a plate,
and see why they call me
the Breakfast King of Loyola.
Any word from Grandma?
I saw they took her. The police.
She's tough, though.
It's not like they'd...
And like I said, I was just...
You know, I...
Dodd told everybody on our
side not to sell to me.
Weed, you know. And so...
I mean, sometimes a girl just
wants to bust a nut, you know?
How come you don't
ask about Charlie?
What?
You ask about Floyd and your
dad, but not about Charlie.
Well, I mean,
yeah, sure, how's he...
State pen, waiting for trial.
Well, we should, I mean, visit.
Except, maybe Dodd...
Dad.
What?
His name's not Dodd
to you. It's Dad.
Bullshit.
After everything he did?
That you've seen him do to me,
which you don't even wanna
think about what he does...
Not defending him.
...If you're not around.
Just telling you
what he is to you.
What's he to you?
Where are we going?
Come.
No.
That's not...
Come.
You're scaring me.
Stop.
He took my boy.
What?
Used his snake
tongue and took him.
Walked him right out the door.
That's what your dad is to me.
Look, I didn't...
It wasn't against you.
What I did...
I didn't mean for...
Doesn't matter what you mean.
It's what you do.
Sleeping with the enemy.
In France, after the Second War,
they shaved a lady's head
for bedding the Germans,
then they ran her outta town.
Or worse.
I can help.
They trust me.
I could...
I don't know,
I could give them information.
Fake information,
and you could...
Not our way.
Yeah, but...
I mean, they're...
How many dead now?
They're kicking our ass.
That's on you.
Your uncle,
your own grandfather.
That's you.
No.
You, don't do that.
Put this on me.
Grandma wanted to negotiate,
but Dodd...
Dad wouldn't let her.
He did this.
He made it war.
He's a snake, like you said.
A rat. He took Charlie, not me.
I was just...
I'm the victim here.
What was I supposed to do?
Kneel down now.
Please.
It's not...
We're family.
None of us are family anymore.
Please!
Please. Please, just...
Banish me.
Like you said, shave my head.
Run me out of... I'll go,
I'll go away and never...
You don't have to...
Hush now.
It's already done.
Oh, Danny Boy
The pipes, the pipes are calling
From glen to glen
And down the mountain side
The summer's gone
And all the roses falling
it's you, it's you must go
And I must bide
But come ye back
When summer's in the meadow
Or when the valley's
Hushed and white with snow
And I'll be here
In sunshine
Or in shadow
Oh, Danny boy
I love you so
Guy called for you again.
What guy?
Says he knows Dodd, where he is.
What did you say?
I told him you were out.
Argh!
Did the men hear? They know?
No.
Shit, man. I don't say
nothing unless you tell me.
There's no Dodd,
you hear? Not anymore.
He calls back,
this guy, you tell him
to sell that
shit someplace else.
We got all the crazy
we can handle.
Kind of cold, don't you think?
What?
Nothing.
Family business.
Not my place.
People think it's morbid,
but I think it's beautiful.
I got it.
Solversons.
Yeah, it's me.
Still breathing?
Thank God.
The boys there?
Do you mean
the King of Breakfast?
Huh?
I don't need
looking after, you know.
How long we've been together?
Well, it's all hands
on deck, hon.
You don't know how
bad it is out there.
Nope, tell me.
Well, I'm telling you.
Is Karl drinking?
Karl, can you read
me another story?
Not unless beer counts.
How's Molly?
Short.
And Noreen? She still there?
Yeah, she's good.
Molly likes her,
and she's helping.
And you? You feel okay?
Better than some.
Worse than others.
Well, can you rest?
How am I supposed to rest? You keep
telling me how bad things are.
Ask Karl about
John McCain's thumbscrews.
What?
He said to tell you
that if John
McCain could survive
five years in Viet
Cong thumbscrews,
you could beat cancer.
Well, yeah, I don't know about that...
My daughter?
But I'm trying.
Your dad says hi.
Say hi back.
Yeah, tell her
don't forget to feed my cats.
He said to tell you...
Yeah, yeah, I heard.
Come home soon.
Okay?
I will.
Everything okay?
Oh, yeah.
Well, looks like
Floyd's gonna flip.
Yeah? Yeah, took some doing,
but we convinced her
the only way this thing was
gonna end up in the win column,
was if she puts us in the game.
Hmm.
Okay, first, I want...
I want it on the record that
this is a road of last resort.
My husband...
Second,
I need assurances that
none of my children,
or my grandchildren are in
line for any repercussions.
This is my choice.
My war. They're just
doing what they're told.
Capital crimes excluded.
What's that supposed to mean?
Murder in the first
and the like.
What's the point of the damn
deal if it doesn't cover murder?
From this point forth,
he's saying.
New crimes.
Now, time you tell
us what you know.
Don't you look at
me with those eyes.
None of you are mothers.
Kansas City
runs most of their dope through
an outfit called Legit Truckin'
out of Cincinnati.
My information is they hide it
in the tires.
Here in town, they store their
gak in two different places.
There's a nail
salon on Robertson.
And an auto
repair shop on First.
And check the air pump inside.
Also, I hear they got weapons
stashed on the roof.
Hello.
The Undertaker's coming.
You're done.
Okay? Yeah.
Get word to Hanzee.
Tell him to come in.
And find Dodd.
How?
Don't care how.
War's almost won.
Gotta finish them
while they're reeling.
What do you think?
I think we just chose a side.
Indian shot two troopers
in South Dakota.
What? What Indian?
Ours.
Description matches the
Gerhardt's man, been missing.
Where? Sioux Falls.
Witness said the
Indian shot up a bar
and that he was looking
for a young couple.
Man of which being a redhead.
Peggy and Ed.
It's South Dakota's problem,
it sounds like.
That's one way
to think about it.
So, the Indian,
probably he got away, yeah?
Oh, yeah. Yeah.
One trooper dead,
one clinging to life.
Still, pursuit means
they could be close.
Right? Peggy and Ed?
Holed up somewhere.
Or on the road.
If we're lucky, yeah. The
troopers got road blocks set up.
Then there's Dodd.
Usually where the Indian
goes, Dodd's there.
Witness just saw the Indian.
Except remember,
we just promised to give
the Gerhardts a free pass.
You better run it by the captain.
That's all I'm saying.
You're a shit cop.
You know that, right?
Getting promoted next month,
so how bad could it be?
Stay then.
Maybe we'll go see if
we can save the day.
Stop it.
I'm fine. I feel fine.
Good.
He worries too much.
Like this, sending you over.
Mmm.
Men.
Shut up.
He was supposed to marry
my sister, you know.
Lenore, the older.
After high school.
She used to say, "I'm gonna
marry that boy someday."
But then there was Vietnam
and he joined up,
and she never was very good at waiting.
So he got me.
The dud.
Listen, if I was building
an ark and they said,
"You can only take two people,
man and wife,"
I'd take him and you
over him and her any day.
You'll look after them.
Right?
My dad'll help, but he'll need
looking after too, before too long.
You got the new pills.
Xanadu.
No.
They gave me the sugar ones.
I'm pretty sure.
Tell him if he needs to get
married again, it's okay.
Just not Rhonda Knutson.
Her eyes are too small or too
close together or something.
It's weird.
Listen, if John McCain could...
Karl Weathers.
Don't you be silly now.
John McCain was a fighter pilot.
I live in a starter
house in Minnesota
and dream of
having chickens one day.
Just make sure
he feeds her more than jerky.
And stop drinking,
Mr. King of Breakfast.
It'll kill you.
Okay. Mmm-hmm.
Snowball?
Tell Simone to come see me. I
wanna apologize for yesterday.
She left in a hurry
when you were took.
Don't think she's back yet.
Hey.
Sorry, missus, but uh...
What? What is it?
It's for your son, ma'am.
Supposed to talk to him directly.
It's okay. We'll go
into the barn.
No. No secrets here.
Well, what is it, kid?
Spit it out.
Your Indian, he's on the phone.
Hanzee. Says he found Dodd.
I'm sorry.
O, Death
Won't you spare me
over till another year
Undertaker's on his way up.
Well, what is this
that I can't see
With ice cold hands
takin' hold of me
Well, I am death, none can excel
I'll open the door
to heaven or hell
Whoa, death someone would pray
Could you wait to
call me another day
The children prayed,
the preacher preached
Time and mercy
is out of your reach
I'll fix your feet
till you can't walk
I'll lock your jaw
till you can't talk
I'll close your eyes
so you can't see
This very hour,
come and go with me
I am death
I come to take the soul
Leave the body and leave it cold
Where's this eggplant who
can't stop shitting the bed?
Gentlemen.
Bag them and drop
them in the woods.
We tell the boss
the Gerhardts got them.
Hello?
Mike Milligan?
Yes.
Today's your lucky day.
I've got Dodd Gerhardt in the
trunk of my car. You want him?