Previously on Dexter...
Travis,
you killed Gellar?
If the cops find Gellar,
they'll focus the hunt on Travis.
This way, they'll find
Gellar's fingerprints, too.
He recently delivered
flowers to a Jessica Morris.
- Who sent them?
- Thomas Matthews.
Jesus Christ.
Every time the shit hits the fan,
I go to him.
- Dexter?
- Yeah.
He's your safe place.
- "Wormwood."
- What the fuck's a wormwood?
This is wormwood.
I think I found a new lead.
My wife Beth and I have been chosen
to be soldiers in the final battle.
I'll call Quinn, go check it out.
You're too late.
Wormwood can't be stopped.
Dexter, you have to call the police.
Hurry. They have poison gas.
"Miami Metro Homicide."
That's where
God wants us to stage wormwood.
What are we waiting for?
Those guys.
That doesn't look good.
We got an anonymous tip
that DDK is using this boat.
- Plus, there's poison gas.
- Poison gas?
I know, right? That's all we need.
Part of me was hoping that
this tip was bogus,
but the uni that we sent down found
a body floating near the boat,
so here we are.
All clear!
What do you got?
Chemical traces
of two toxic substances.
Put 'em together,
you got something a lot worse.
Poison gas?
Release it in the right place,
say, a closed environment,
like a bus or a building,
you could kill a lot of people.
Fuck me.
That's Holly Benson.
That's the girl DDK kidnapped
and let go.
Multiple stab wounds...
Looks like they weren't done with her.
There's more inside.
This is where
they were handling the stuff.
From the looks of it,
they knew what they were doing.
Wormwood, the next tableau,
is supposed to represent
a meteor falling to Earth.
And poisoning mankind.
- Could this be wormwood, right here?
- I doubt it.
These people weren't killed by gas.
This looks like where
wormwood is being prepared.
So what's DDK planning to do?
Release poison gas on people?
We can't just sit on this.
We have to alert Homeland Security.
- Should I notify LaGuerta?
- Do it.
What's his story?
Upper abdominal stab wound.
Looks like it happened right here...
Bled out, fell to this position.
Expired.
There are fingerprints on the knife.
Travis' fingerprints,
since it's the knife Travis used
to kill Holly.
Holy shit, Steve Dorsey.
It's Doomsday Adam.
- Oh, wow.
- What?
I found a video blog post
by him yesterday.
He was going on about how he'd been
chosen to be a soldier
in the final battle.
- Why didn't you tell anyone?
- I did. I told Sergeant Batista.
He was going to Dorsey's apartment
to check it out.
Where is Angel?
You don't understand, but you will.
When this is over
and the new world begins,
you will wish you had faith.
I do have faith. I believe in God.
Well, then you better start
praying to him and fast.
Look at me.
There must be something
very special about you, Beth,
because it is no accident
that you are here.
Out of all the people in the world,
God chose you to carry out his will.
God reserves a place for those
that sacrifice themselves
in his name, and it is a place
too beautiful to describe.
And I envy you,
because you get to see it
before I can.
- Now, did you pray?
- Oh, yes.
Then we're ready.
Everything is in place.
After I do the switch,
how long before it goes off?
A couple of seconds
to let the chemicals mix.
Now, remember,
when you enter the building,
you'll see a door with a card reader.
You will take the sergeant's keycard
and buzz open the door.
It's the only way
to bypass the metal detector.
All right, OK. I understand.
This is a great day.
It's the beginning of the end.
Yeah?
It's me. I've been calling you
for five minutes.
Yeah, I just heard it ring.
- Is Batista with you?
- No.
Why the fuck not?
I figured I'd meet him
at the crime scene, OK?
- What, he isn't there?
- No.
Louis said that
he went to Steve Dorsey's
to check out a Doomsday suspect.
You're his partner,
you should know that.
Yeah, I missed a few calls
from him this morning.
Jesus Christ, Quinn!
What the fuck's going on, Deb?
Doomsday Adam, the guy
that he was going to check out,
just turned up dead.
OK, I got the address.
I'm turning around.
Send backup.
Fuck! Fuck! Fuck!
Fuck!
Dispatch,
this is Lieutenant Debra Morgan.
I need all available units
at 1203 North Gordon
for a probable Code 40.
Copy that.
You think Angel ran into Travis?
Well, it sure as fuck
wasn't Steve Dorsey.
I'm sure he's OK.
If Travis is there,
we've gotta catch him
before he does God knows what
to how many people.
- Hello?
- It's me.
I made it.
- Are you in Homicide yet?
- I'm on my way right now.
Remember, it's Lieutenant Morgan
that is leading
this attack against us.
You must get to her.
I will.
God bless you, Beth.
I'll see you on the other side.
Can I help you?
I have information regarding
the Doomsday Killer case.
Fill this out, and we'll send
an officer out to interview you...
No! I have to speak
to Lieutenant Morgan in person.
Tell her it's wormwood,
the next tableau.
- "Wormwood"?
- Tell Lieutenant Morgan that.
Lieutenant Morgan's
out in the field right now,
- I'm not sure when she'll be...
- I'll wait.
Take a seat.
I've kept you alive
in case we ran into problems.
Everything's going perfectly.
So you don't need me any more.
No.
I'd still like to get that prayer.
Go ahead. Pray.
Your time is up.
I'm all right. It's Travis Marshall.
He went out the window.
All units, we got Travis Marshall
heading west on foot on McNulty,
he's armed.
- I'm OK, go after him.
- Fuck you.
We have a tentative match
on the knife fingerprints.
- They're Travis'.
- I don't get it.
If Doomsday Adam was working
with Travis and Gellar,
then why kill him?
Maybe he was done with him,
and the knife was
his severance package.
Tough gig.
Homeland is putting
their regional teams on alert,
and they're sending
agents to the station.
Sounds like
they want to take over the case.
Well, it wouldn't fucking surprise me.
It's what the Feds do best.
Morgan.
Angel's OK.
- Thank God. What happened?
- Travis Marshall had him.
He took off on foot.
Got a head start,
but I got unis setting up a perimeter.
Order up as many men as you need.
- Angel?
- He's fine.
Did we find Travis?
No, he got away, but there's
still a chance we might catch him.
At least Angel's OK.
Thank God we got that anonymous tip.
She's right.
If I hadn't brought in the police,
Angel would most likely be dead.
You know that dead call girl,
Jessica Morris?
What about her?
I think I know who the john was.
- Who?
- Matthews.
- Matthews?
- The fucking Deputy Chief.
I don't know what the fuck to do.
He was one of Dad's best friends,
he was practically my mentor.
I can't just bust him.
I owe him more than that.
- You want to know my opinion?
- Yes! That's why I'm talking to you.
Put this on the backburner
until Travis is in custody.
You need to focus on DDK.
I'm having dinner
with Matthews tonight.
I can't just sit there
and talk about the salad.
OK, so bring it up,
but maybe Matthews has a reason
for what he did.
Yeah, ass.
No, I mean about leaving the scene.
There are worse secrets
you can have, Deb.
I'm just saying, maybe
you should keep an open mind.
Yes, I get what you're saying.
The hunt for Travis has hit a wall,
but maybe there's a way around it.
Steve Dorsey, a.k.a. Doomsday Adam,
Travis' recently deceased acolyte.
There might be something
in your history
that can lead me to Travis.
Or lead us to Travis,
since anything I find,
I'll report to Deb.
Unfortunately, Dorsey has led
a squeaky clean life.
Mostly.
He's a potential mass murderer with
eight outstanding parking tickets.
Hey, any update?
No, nothing yet,
but search teams
are expanding the perimeter.
Which means Travis Marshall
most likely got away.
- We don't know that.
- I'm not trying to be critical,
I'm just trying to get
a lay of the land.
Homeland Security
will be here within the hour.
They'll need an update,
and they've requested
all relevant materials on DDK.
Which means Travis probably isn't
the only thing I've lost today.
However it shakes out,
we'll handle it.
- Excuse me, Lieutenant?
- What is it?
There's a woman here who says she has
important information about DDK.
Which is?
She insists on speaking
to you personally.
She says it has to do
with something called wormwood.
- Wormwood?
- Yeah.
How the fuck
would she know about that?
- Send her in.
- Yes, ma'am.
What did stalkers do
before the Internet?
Is this wormwood?
Thank you, again, for coming.
Get everyone out of here!
Evacuate the building! Go! Now!
Dex, she's gone. Let's go.
I'll give you everything you need.
I just need to go check on my brother.
I'll be right back, OK?
Homeland Security?
Yeah, you were right.
They want everything we have on DDK.
It'll slow us down to a crawl.
Is he all right?
I'm fine.
I love you,
but I wasn't talking to you.
I mean, he was lucky.
The exposure was very mild.
But this gas attacks
the upper respiratory tract.
You could get nosebleeds
followed by extreme dizziness,
especially after physical exertion.
- You need to get to the hospital.
- Got it.
- You gonna go to the ER?
- On my honour.
Stop with the sarcastic bullshit,
all right?
No bullshit, I will. Really.
OK.
How did you know
that crazy bitch was a threat?
Just luck, I guess.
Fuck luck, I'll take you.
Dex, you saved a lot of lives today.
You saved my life.
I'd never let anything happen to you.
Come here.
It's just for a little while, OK?
Daddy's gonna miss you
every second of those 48 hours.
If Travis can attack Miami Metro,
he can find his way to me.
I can't take that risk.
I've always known
something could happen to me,
but now it's more than my life
I have to worry about.
Hey, thanks for coming back.
I knew I shouldn't have left.
Sorry to ruin your date
and your weekend.
It's OK.
It's not every day
your boss becomes a bona fide hero.
Yeah, well,
I'm not feeling too heroic right now.
I'm starting to feel the side effects
that that doctor was talking about.
I realised
I'm probably not best person
to be in charge of this little guy.
Well, it's no problem.
You just get some rest.
I'll keep him out of your hair.
Better idea, I booked you guys a room
at The Ritz, in Coconut Grove.
Sweet!
Have you picked your animal yet?
Must've slipped my mind.
At the pageant,
every child is paired with a parent
to bring
the story of Noah's Ark to life.
I think Harrison's a little scared
of the whole thing.
Don't worry, buddy.
Daddy will be there. I promise.
And you should pick
one of the good animals soon,
or you'll end up being
rats or turtles or something.
King of the beasts.
Something feels right about that.
Travis has one tableau left,
who knows how many people
he'll try to kill next.
And he might go after Debra again,
just like he did with Holly.
So you're changing your plan
about working with Miami Metro?
Miami Metro has been sidelined
by Homeland Security.
It's time for my dark passenger
to take the wheel again.
According to the seven keys,
the next tableau will be
the lake of fire.
"And Satan, who is the beast,
"was thrown into the lake of fire,
which is the second death."
It says, the beast gathers the kings
of the Earth and their armies,
to prepare for war against God.
And he's responsible
for killing the two witnesses.
Gosh...
You really should have
gone to the ER, Dex.
I don't have time.
I have to find Travis.
You have no leads.
He could be anywhere.
It's time for a Hail Mary.
I'm gonna make Travis come to me.
Maybe it takes a beast
to catch a beast.
That's for you.
Pick up an OpenX today, and never...
You don't need help operating...
I'm standing outside
the Miami Metro headquarters,
where earlier today,
a local woman, Beth Dorsey,
attempted a poison gas assault
on the station's Homicide Department.
Channel 9 has learnt no officers
were hurt in the brazen attack.
The only casualty was Miss Dorsey.
It's OK. It's... It's OK.
It's gonna be OK.
Her sacrifice will be enough.
It must be what God wanted.
It's up to me now.
My time has come.
I must pass the test.
Half the stuff on here
costs more than my rent.
My treat.
For a job well done
despite some enormous challenges.
Yeah, it would be a lot easier
if Homeland Security
wasn't breathing down my neck.
Well, just don't let them
become a distraction.
I know only too well how easy it is
to get bogged down in your job.
That call girl from the hotel
is a perfect example
of what I'm talking about.
I think I'm gonna have the duck.
I have to admit, I was a bit puzzled
when I heard
you were still looking into that.
What kind of wine goes with that?
You know,
some cases are better left alone...
Fuck.
I can't do this.
- I know you were one of her clients.
- Excuse me?
Jessica Morris.
I found a card for flowers
sent to her the morning that she died,
from Thomas Matthews.
Were you the one in her hotel room
the night she died?
White.
You should order the white wine.
Sir...
You can talk to me.
You don't know what it's like, Debra.
Since Maggie died...
I've been alone for a very long time.
I went to the hotel. We...
And when I came back into the bedroom,
I found her lying on the floor.
I saw the drugs.
I tried to revive her,
but...
she just wouldn't breathe.
911 wouldn't have helped.
She was dead.
And I couldn't change what happened.
So...
What do you intend to do?
I don't know.
Debra, I've known you
since the day you were born.
You cried in my arms
the night your father died.
I've always looked out for you,
and I made you lieutenant,
and now I'm the one
who needs a favour.
I want to help you,
but what do I tell that girl's father?
You tell him you found nothing.
She overdosed.
No one needs to know any more.
It's not gonna help anyone.
It'll only hurt me.
I'll call Mr Morris in the morning.
Good.
Jeez.
You sure it's safe to be here?
Relax, sidekick.
Hazmat gave brass the all-clear.
I think I prefer "intern".
Bukkakee, bukkake.
The point is, me as boss needs you
in Evidence for the next few days.
We're suffering
from a serious case of backlog.
I'm on it.
Whoa, Amazon, 9 o'clock.
OK, everyone, listen up.
This is agent Hubbard
from Homeland Security.
They'll be taking over
our DDK investigation.
Temporarily.
Until my team and I can assess
all known associates of the Dorseys.
So what,
we're just supposed to sit on our ass
for the next four days
until the world ends?
You want to take that one?
I understand your frustration,
but this police station
came under a gas attack yesterday.
In the government's eyes, that poses
a potential on-going terrorist threat.
Steve and Beth Dorsey
weren't terrorists.
They were nut-jobs
following a bigger nut-job.
Let me and my team
be the judge of that.
I promise, this will go faster
if everyone cooperates.
They all hate this.
Can't say that I blame them.
Please make yourself available
for interviews.
I'd like to start
with Sergeant Batista,
since he was the last one
in contact with the suspects.
Can I set up in your office?
Right this way.
This whole thing's fucking bullshit.
They have one hand tied behind
their backs, but I don't.
Not when I have Gellar's.
- Hey.
- Not a good time, Quinn.
Yeah, I know you got that interview,
but this'll just take a sec.
Not now.
Look, I'm so, so sorry.
Look, you saved my life,
and for that
I will always be grateful.
But this is a job of trust.
And I can't have
a partner I can't trust.
You've been talking a lot
about your department this morning,
but how are you doing
since the attack?
I'm fine.
Pretty much, I mean...
I'm worried about Dexter.
He wouldn't go to the hospital.
He keeps saying he's OK.
You must be very proud of him.
He saved everyone's life.
Including mine.
It all happened so fast, you know?
If that canister
had gone off any sooner...
Your brother holds a very
important place in your life.
He's really all I have.
You think I'm crazy now,
I can't even imagine
what a fucking mess my life would be
without him.
I don't think you're crazy.
Can I get that in writing?
From what I do know about you,
you feel things very deeply.
Like your bond with Dexter.
Where do you think that stems from?
Maybe because
he's the only guy in my life
that I haven't dumped, or cheated on,
or...
...isn't dead.
Is it possible
that your feelings for Dexter
are the reason that
you've chosen men in the past
who have been
either inappropriate or unavailable?
Because they're what? Not Dexter?
That's insane.
Is it?
He's my brother.
Yet you're not biologically related.
- So?
- It would be understandable,
given the past traumas
the two of you have shared,
for you to develop
complex feelings for him.
Why the fuck are we
even talking about this?
You mentioned Dexter.
He comes up in these sessions a lot.
Aren't you curious as to why that is?
He's a huge part of my life.
That's it.
End of story.
You getting upset?
Fuck, yes, I'm becoming upset,
because you're making it sound like
I want to...
...be with him or something.
Well, do you?
Look...
I love my brother,
but I am sure as shit
not in love with my brother,
if that's what you're getting at.
We're done here.
Travis got everyone's attention
by staging his tableaus.
It's time I got his
by staging one of my own.
I stashed Gellar's hand in the morgue,
now I need it back.
Hey, Dexter!
I was looking for you in your lab.
Heading home.
Looks like you got a minute.
Haven't we done this before?
I just wanted to thank you
for being so honest with me
the other day about my video game.
Glad I could help.
You just made me realise that
I have spent my whole life
on the sidelines,
playing make-believe games,
and now I want to get out there
and make my life count for something.
- OK, I really should...
- Yeah, go. Go.
All right.
I hope you're feeling better.
I have no idea where Travis is hiding
or what he's up to.
The lake of fire is his next tableau,
but mine doesn't require a name,
just the right message.
And the best way to get Travis
to pay attention to that message
is if it comes from me.
Sorry about this.
The hand is bad.
I've had my tongue in places
that smelled better.
It was on ice for three years
along with the rest of Gellar.
Decomposition will accelerate faster
the longer it's in the sun.
Looks like the cut was made just above
the palmar carpal ligament.
666, the sign of the beast.
What's up with that?
Travis will know.
- What do we know?
- Street cleaner called it in.
I checked security footage.
If Travis and Gellar did this,
they were out of view.
Well, Travis worked in the museum,
so he would know
every inch of the square.
- Hey, guys.
- What is it?
All right, cue the music,
hold the applause.
Shoot him.
The hand belongs to Gellar.
What?
It's a positive match.
Why the fuck would Gellar
cut off his own hand?
Well, the cut looks
to have been made post-mortem.
Gellar's most likely dead.
So student offs professor? Why?
Good way to get rid of an accomplice.
- I mean, look at Steve Dorsey.
- Travis is a psycho.
He may not even be sticking
to the Enesserette game plan,
cos if this is supposed to be
the lake of fire, I don't get it.
Let's have the unis sweep the area,
maybe we can turn up Gellar's body.
It might lead us to Travis.
Not likely.
I left Gellar in pieces in the swamp.
Right on time.
My tableau should send Travis
right to me.
Now he just needs to know where to go.
...if they have any leads at all.
And now we go to Museum Square
for this breaking news.
Authorities are still baffled
by what appears to be yet another
bizarre end of days tableau
plaguing the city of Miami.
We warn you,
these images are very graphic.
Investigators made
a gruesome discovery
early this morning in Museum Square.
Blood covered the angel statue
in the square's fountain,
and also contaminated
the fountain's water.
A human hand was found
nailed to the angel's chest.
On the forehead, the numbers 666...
- The beast.
...were also written in blood.
Channel 9 has learnt that the hand
depicted in these startling images
may in fact belong to
one of the suspected Doomsday Killers,
Professor James Gellar.
No. No. No!
Mark this day, witness.
The end is not upon the world,
it's upon you.
You know who I am. You know what I am.
The beast is coming for you.
"Slice of Life."
Close the door.
- Everything...
- God damn it, Debra.
I thought we had an understanding.
- I'm a little confused here.
- Don't get cute.
Chief Lane has somehow come
to learn about my indiscretions.
He's asking me to retire!
Is this how you repay me
after all I've done for you?
I was at a crime scene all day.
I haven't talked to anyone.
It doesn't matter.
You just wouldn't let this thing go!
Your father would be so disappointed.
So would your late wife.
All due respect,
I didn't do anything wrong here.
No?
What you did was screw over
the only person that can protect you
from a job
that you are clearly not ready for.
Good luck.
You're gonna need it.
You wanted to see us?
- Is everything OK?
- Agent Hubbard just called.
Homeland Security has concluded
that the Dorseys
have no ties to terrorists.
No shit.
They want to be kept in the loop,
as does the FBI,
- but we're back in control.
- That's good news.
It would be
if I hadn't just read your reports
on what happened
at Steve Dorsey's apartment.
What the fuck?
Seriously, I should
write both of you up.
That was all my fault, Deb.
It's Lieutenant.
And I got that.
You guys, we have two fucking days
to catch Travis Marshall
before he does God knows what
in something called the lake of fire.
We just got this case back.
I cannot afford
to have this department
falling down around me right now, OK?
No more fuck-ups.
We get Travis Marshall, you got it?
I made sure the Slice of Life
was in the video I sent Travis.
He'll be expecting
to find me on my boat.
Not this one.
The owners use it twice a year,
but I only need it once.
For Travis' final tableau.
Captain!
Morgan.
You going to pick out blinds
for Matthews' office?
- You heard the news.
- From Matthews.
Because he thought
that I ratted him out,
but we both know that
it was you, right?
Rumours do have a way of spreading.
So Matthews comes to you
and asks for help,
and you go along with it,
until Jessica Morris' father shows up.
Now, is that about the time
that you realised
you could stab him in the back?
Interesting theory,
but I have no idea
what you're talking about.
Fucking used me to take him out
and help yourself.
Don't be so naive, Morgan.
This is how the game is played.
Did you really think that
Matthews made you lieutenant
because you were ready?
It was all politics to get back at me.
And that was his last mistake.
How do you sleep?
Very well, knowing that from now on,
you'll do what I say when I say it,
or I'll find a lieutenant who will.
So LaGuerta's going on and on, and...
I'm dying inside.
And all of the sudden,
I have one of those...
those moments where
everything sort of comes together.
- An epiphany.
- Exactly.
And I realise that I have completely
fucked myself into a corner.
What would you have done differently?
Ignored a grieving father?
Kept a case closed
that didn't sit right with you?
No. And fuck no.
And I was trying
to give you a compliment.
You've grown so much.
You made the best
out of a bad situation,
because now you see...
Everything isn't always
so black and white.
Did you try the noodles?
You have always blown at that.
And you're so good? Show me.
It's this finger, dumbass.
- Like this?
- Yeah.
Your hand's shaking, what is it?
This.
One minute, everything's perfect.
And the next minute...
The next minute what?
You're rushing off.
Deb...
I am always with you.
Right here.
Oh, fuck.
It worked.
Oh, no. Not now.
You didn't really think
you could foil God's plan, did you?
This was how
it was always meant to be.
I will wait on a pillar of light
for God's return.
And you'll burn in eternal hellfire.
It is finished.
I thought
I was headed in the right direction.
My dark passenger
back behind the wheel.
But if I was so sure
I knew where I was going,
how did I get so lost?