WWW.MY-SUBS.CO
One new message.
Hey, Ruben. It's Dr. Monica.
Thanks for doing overnights this week.
I'll hire another vet tech
as soon as I can.
Sure you will.
And just a reminder: do not
turn on the overhead lighting.
The reptiles need 12 hours of
darkness, so you need to man up.
I've lowered the dosage for Coach Romeo.
He's a lot livelier now.
Give him his meds
while he's in the tank.
That's everything. Talk to you tomorrow.
Thank you, buddy.
Okay.
There you go.
Romeo?
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
Buddy.
Romeo.
Come on.
It's okay. Hey.
Dr. Monica?
- Synced and corrected by synk -
- www.MY-SUBS.com -
Dad's here.
Not during working hours.
During morning hours,
the LAPD is paying
Manny Ludo to watch my kids
because daddies do not qualify
for childcare payments, do they?
Okay, this was supposed to be
a delicious breakfast burrito,
but I ran out of tortillas.
So instead, it's a delicious
scrambled egg sandwich with salsa.
Good morning, my delightful daughter.
Good morning, darling mother.
- What did you just swallow?
- Orange juice.
What did you swallow
with the orange juice?
I don't know, air? Nice boots.
Dad, now that you're a fake manny,
are you done teaching driver's ed?
Give up the biz? Me?
No way. I just move
my appointments to later in the day.
I got two jobs now. I'm a hyphenate.
I'm a fake manny-driving
school instructor.
Okay. Got a dead body. Gotta go.
- Stop trying to outcool me.
- Thank you.
Good. Good to see you.
- Good luck with the dead body.
- Thank you.
Hi, baba.
Who asks someone to hold their bag
when it's covered in sticky stuff?
The world is a disgusting place, okay?
Those free weights at your gym
have about as much fecal
bacteria as a public toilet.
I am not listening to you
for the rest of the day.
- I'm trying to free you.
- What do we got?
Dr. Monica Davis, a vet
specializing in exotic animals.
Twenty-eight, single, no kids.
Her lone employee found her body
when he showed up
for his overnight shift.
- Anything on this employee?
- Alibi checks out.
According to the ME, it looks
like a simple cardiac arrest.
Laser printer, however, seems
to have a different opinion.
That's a new one.
Why did she go through the
trouble of using the printer
to declare herself a murder victim?
There's plenty of pens
and notepads nearby.
The ME say anything
about the blotches on her hands?
He said it looked like some kind
of allergic reaction.
But he'll run more tests once
we get the body back to his lab.
Here you go.
Thanks. But I have to wash these first.
Guys, he touched something that
may have touched apple juice.
We're all very concerned.
Beware of the poisonous dart
frog. One touch can be deadly.
Karadec, wait!
Wait!
I said wait.
How you doing, big fella? How
many fingers am I holding up?
A lot.
I had to shoot him
before he got soap on his hands.
I'm serious. There's a poison
in that soap dispenser
that would paralyze him.
That is why our victim
had to use the printer
to declare that she was murdered.
She couldn't pick up a pen
because she was paralyzed.
The printer's gotta be voice-controlled.
Printer, print "Morgan
saved Karadec's life."
On it.
See?
Tray one is empty.
Okay, well, if it hadn't blown its load
on all that "Murder" confetti,
- that would've been very cool.
- Get back to the poison bit.
- Yes. Okay.
- Yeah.
A frog aquarium is bolted
and locked because it is home
to two poison dart
frogs, Wilma and Fred.
Poison dart frogs secrete
deadly toxins from their skin.
Now, the bolt is there,
but the lock is loose.
More importantly,
Wilma's poisonous buddy
is nowhere to be found.
Wait. What?
Oh, yeah. So, you got a missing frog.
We have a hand rash, a
reaction to the batrachotoxins.
We've got a wadded up
paper towel next to the victim
because she was drying her hands
when she became paralyzed.
So...
Fred's in the soap dispenser.
Yep. Here's dead Fred.
So, do you guys think
he caught any of that,
or are you gonna
wanna fill him in later?
I think you mean, "Is he okay?"
He's okay.
The tranquilizer was for a
snake. He's gonna be fine.
You're gonna be fine.
Hey, Lieutenant.
How's he doing?
- A tad sluggish, but...
- He's alive.
Good. You and Daphne
keep processing the scene.
When Karadec is okay to drive,
I need him and Morgan
to head to a salon on Grant.
A friend of Dr. Monica's
reported her missing last night,
a Bethany Reid.
I'm texting you the address.
Yeah.
- You guys got all that?
- I got it.
I don't think he got it. I'll drive.
How you doing over there?
I am still not talking to you, Morgan.
That's fair.
You did just miss a call
from someone named
Aubrey Brown-Eye Bumble.
I'm sorry, did you answer my phone?
It was connected to your car. I
didn't want the ringing to wake you up.
She says that Saturday at one o'clock
at Coast Grill sounds perfect.
I put it in your calendar for you.
Thanks.
How you doing? I know it kinda
doesn't seem like it right now,
but I do feel really bad
about shooting you, you know.
Morgan, I totally understand
why you did what you did.
- If anything, I guess I wanna...
- You don't have to thank me.
I want to thank you.
Okay, go ahead.
I just thanked you.
Well, you are welcome. You
think you can walk on your own?
I think so.
Look at all these bees.
My son Gavin had a karate
tournament last night,
and Monica promised to be there.
So you called the police?
Only after I wasn't able
to reach her for hours.
It was just so unlike her not to show.
That's a quality friend. Shows
up to all your kid's stuff?
I'm sorry.
No. No, no, no, no, no, no, no.
No hugging.
We don't hug. We don't do hugs.
Okay. Bethany,
Detective Karadec would
like to ask you a few questions.
How did you know the veterinarian?
We met about two years ago
in a yoga class.
He's gonna need a little more.
Well, we bonded over both being
so hopelessly bad at yoga
and decided to meet
up for hikes instead.
And our friendship just grew from there.
And it is so hard to make
female friends as an adult.
Bethany, had you noticed
anything different about Monica lately?
Actually, I did.
I went to meet Monica
for breakfast yesterday,
and she seemed distracted, nervous.
So I asked her if something was wrong,
and she just said guy troubles.
Was she dating someone?
That's what was so weird.
She never mentioned anyone.
Hey.
Sweetie.
Sorry, honey.
He just really wanted his mom.
I can't believe I'm
never gonna see Monica again.
I know, sweetie.
Do you think that man hurt her?
Which man?
What man, sweetheart?
When we were at Monica's clinic
a couple of days ago,
I heard her fighting with a man,
and the man yelled at her.
You mean the day we
brought Monica lunch?
Honey, I was there with you.
I didn't see any man.
He came when you went to get coffees.
Did you see this man
who yelled at Monica?
So, you don't know
what color eyes he had?
What about his nose?
Was it big, not big?
Is that an Avengers comic?
- Yeah.
- Yeah. I knew I liked you.
Hey, let's make a bet.
I bet you a lollipop of your choice
that our favorite is the same guy. Okay?
One, two, three.
- Hulk.
- Hawkeye.
Okay.
Hey, you said the man talking to
Dr. Monica had a beard, right?
Was it a beard like Tony Stark's
or a beard like Thor's?
Tony Stark's but not as pointy,
and it was brown.
Okay.
Was he tall and big
or tiny like Ant-man?
We've been estranged from our
daughter for over ten years.
Twelve years.
You said you lived in Reseda?
Monica lived in Westwood.
You were eight miles apart,
and you never saw each other?
Like I said, we were estranged.
Monica drifted away after she left home.
Excuse me, Lieutenant.
Do you know that guy?
His name is Shane Siger. He was...
He was the worst thing
that ever happened to my family.
Monica was 16 when she
took up with him. He was 21.
I tried to get her to stop
seeing the creep,
but, you know, what can I do?
A year into their relationship,
Shane was arrested
for robbing a convenience store.
Idiot wore flip-flops, slipped
and accidentally fired his gun.
Shot a hole into a soda display
and went to prison for armed robbery.
Moron.
Imagine what my neighbors were saying.
My teenage daughter dating a criminal.
Well, there's nothing in
his file about flip-flops,
but he did go down for armed robbery.
Well, Shane's in
prison. He's not our guy.
Shane Siger was released
from prison last month.
I don't know, Shane.
I mean, we tell you that
Monica's been murdered,
and you don't seem at all surprised.
Or sad.
Surprise, sadness?
You guys were really expecting
a wide range of emotions, huh?
Monica and I broke up,
like, 12 years ago.
Most I got for you is a "Yeah, and?"
Yeah, and an eyewitness places
you at the clinic with Monica
five days before her murder.
Now, do you have any insight
to offer us on that?
You know, not really.
- Why were you guys fighting?
- I don't remember.
You have an alibi for last night, Shane?
Nothing springing to mind.
You know what I think?
I think you got out of prison
and wanted to pick things up
where you left off with Monica.
And she just could not
wait to say, "Hell, no."
She was educated and successful.
Pretty sure she knew she could
do better than a smug ex-con.
Because women never go for
the bad boy, right?
I think maybe 48 hours in
a holding cell will help
jog Mr. Man-with-no-alibi's memory.
Ankle monitor was a condition
of my release from prison.
I'm allowed out of the house
during the day to go to work.
I'm a personal trainer down
at Muscle Beach
if you ever wanna swing by for a sesh.
The monitoring station
confirmed Shane's story.
Well, he can't be a murderer
if he was at his own place all night.
We gotta cut him loose.
Do you think that there's any way
the parents could be involved?
The dad maybe, but did you see the mom?
That woman was devastated.
Monica hadn't spoken to her parents
in a dozen years, grieving mom included.
Besides, my mom's threatened
to kill me hundreds of times.
Well, I've been doing this
for a little while,
and I can tell you that filicide
is one of the rarest forms of murder.
You have time for
a quick non-work-related,
potentially overly-personal question?
Nope.
- Do you ever snoop on your kids?
- No.
That was definitive.
It's not snooping
when a concerned mom does it.
I like to think of it
as responsible parenting.
Yeah.
- Hey.
Chloe's still napping.
And as suspected, avocado...
not a big hit.
You're home early.
Yeah. I just had to check on something.
Ava took a pill this morning.
- What kind of pill?
- I don't know.
The sneaky kind that you swallow
behind your mom's back.
Did you come home to snoop?
It is not snooping when
it's a concerned mom doing it.
It's called responsible parenting.
Morgan, stop.
Snooping is a slippery slope.
Once you invade someone's
privacy, there's no going back.
No more communicating.
It becomes your go-to mode.
What if she's microdosing?
Or she's macrodosing?
I mean, she could be buying Adderall
off that Shelby character.
Nah, Shelby's gunning for Yale.
She wouldn't be selling her Adderall.
Maybe Ava just had a headache.
She could've taken an aspirin.
Yeah, well, you don't
hide aspirin from your...
- Oh, God. It's birth control.
- No, it's not.
It certainly looks like all the
birth control I forgot to take.
I'm not emotionally prepared
for this. Yes, I am. I am.
Okay. Okay, here's what I'm gonna do.
I'm gonna sit here in the dark,
and when she walks in,
I'm gonna hold up the evidence,
and I'm gonna turn on
a single light bulb.
Or both of us forget this ever happened
and never speak of it again.
No, I'm gonna do my light bulb move.
Yeah. It's okay. It's okay.
I'm in an interrogation room
half the day.
- I can handle this.
- Or another option,
you do that annoying grown-up thing
where you hold on to information
and don't do anything with it.
Let her come to you.
Once you break her trust,
you're not going to get it back.
I don't wanna break her trust,
but parenting comes
with major consequences.
And she has a boyfriend.
I make one wrong move, I
don't step in when I should've,
and her whole life is screwed.
I mean, that...
What are you guys doing?
We gotta talk to you about something.
We need to know if you think
your room will fit
one of those swinging chairs
that you love.
It totally would.
Yeah. Yeah. Yeah, like, the
rattan one from Urban Outfitters
would be so perfect for right here.
Hey, Oz. Come check out these
reviews for Monica's clinic.
What have you got
on our veterinarian murder?
Okay, there's something curious
about Monica's vet clinic.
The reviews online were exceptional
up until about six months ago.
Then she started to receive
a string of one star reviews.
Okay, this one guy... he
goes by the moniker Asmodeus...
he paints Monica out to be
some kind of monster.
A monster who needs to be stopped.
"This so called veterinarian is
gonna pay for what she's done."
Track down this Asmodeus person.
Pay him a visit.
Do you know this woman?
Really? She sent the police?
That chick's got some nerve.
That chick was murdered yesterday.
- Why are you talking to me?
- Glad you asked, Rodney.
We've got a couple
of threatening online reviews
you directed at Monica
under the name Asmodeus.
How'd you find me?
We did a reverse image search
on your profile pic.
You don't exactly blend in.
So, what did Dr. Monica do
to deserve all the threats and anger?
She killed Fernanda.
Okay, that's crazy.
I have the exact same tattoo.
Dr. Monica killed your pet spider?
Fernanda was a Peruvian
glass-haired tarantula.
She wasn't some pet. She was my baby.
I took Fernanda to the clinic
for a routine visit.
Dr. Monica insisted I leave her
for an exam.
Then later, Dr. Monica called
and said that Fernanda was infectious
and needed to be incinerated.
I never even got to say goodbye.
She was my best friend.
But I swear... I swear I
didn't kill Dr. Monica.
I just wanted to ruin
her reputation online
because people needed to be warned.
And yeah, maybe...
maybe I took it too far.
Took it too far how?
I followed her home one night.
To scare her, that's it.
I'm guessing you're the only dude
in Brentwood with a face tat?
I didn't follow her to Brentwood.
I followed her to an apartment
in Hollywood.
Digging those French
tips, Valorie. Very old money.
There was a Good Times Roll bag
at the murder scene.
It was delivered to Monica
at a Hollywood address.
But she lived by the
clinic in Brentwood.
Exactly.
So why would Monica have food
delivered to a Hollywood apartment
when she lived and worked
on the other side of town?
Daytime stakeouts are less cool.
I mean, I feel gross eating Swedish Fish
and Pringles while the sun's out.
Pay attention, please.
I can chew, regret my choices
and stare at a building
all at the same time, Daph.
Do you think Karadec stops for snacks?
I probably think about what
Karadec does a lot less than you do.
I just have a lot of respect for him.
Morgan has such a great
learning opportunity right now.
Here, you're the only one learning.
Is that a gun?
Hey! Watch the road!
What are you, crazy?
Freeze! Police!
More cops?
What are you guys doing he...
Did you call for backup?
You said I could call
for backup next time.
This is Larry, the building super.
We thought we saw him pull a weapon.
Did you pull a weapon, Larry?
I just took out my drill.
I'm supposed to fix
that busted ceiling fan.
Larry, you dog.
You got a holster for
your drill? I like it.
Didn't Morgan's text say we were
meeting the building's super?
I didn't get a text from Morgan.
Yeah, you did. I texted
'cause Karadec was driving.
Yeah, it's right
here. Daphne Lewandowski.
That's not you. That's not you.
In my defense, who's got
two Daphnes in her phone?
- You know what I mean?
- Yeah.
Wait, how did you find this place then?
I checked the reviews
for Monica's clinic online.
Tracked down a disgruntled
spider owner who threatened her.
Got him to admit that he
followed her to this apartment.
- What about you?
- Morgan found a receipt
on the Good Times Roll
bag at the murder scene
and the address was on it, so...
Great minds.
Guys, you're gonna wanna check this out.
Hey, Oz. Come here. Is that...
Fernanda. That is definitely her.
What was she up to?
Looks like Monica Davis,
doctor of veterinary medicine,
had a secret life
as an exotic animal trafficker.
Pastel butter python, 7,500 bucks.
Palm cockatoo, 15,000.
Think I've got something.
Looks like some kind
of coded list, right?
This first line. 3912
Lamer, 2381, 9424?
Lamer could be Lemur misspelled.
Okay, this last part could be a price.
Why is Monica getting into
the black market?
I mean, what does she need
the money for?
She's operating a one-woman clinic.
That can't be cheap.
These are not codes for animal sales.
It's abbreviations for house listings.
3912 Lamer is the address.
Then it's square footage, lot size,
bedrooms, bathrooms, garage size
and the date of the open house.
Monica needed money for a house.
Okay.
Daphne, I want you
to dig into the trafficking.
See if you can find
anything on the buyers.
Oz, you get Dr. Monica's patient files.
See if you can connect any of
these animals to the clinic.
Morgan and I are gonna go have
a little chat with Ty Williams.
She started out looking
for a home way up in Orland,
but she had a partner and it
wound up being too far for 'em.
- Did you ever meet this partner?
- No.
Do you have a picture
of the property she was buying?
Of course.
Well, thanks for
coming by, Mr. Williams.
If you're ever looking to move
out of the city, give me a call.
Okay.
According to Bethany,
Monica said she was having guy troubles.
Maybe it wasn't Shane.
If there was a man in her life,
we need to find him.
I don't think she had a man in her life.
Bees.
- She had a bee in her life?
- Follow the bees, Karadec.
The garden. See how these tall
flowers are clumped together?
That is a pollinator garden,
like the one outside of the salon.
The salon that had flowers
and bees all over the sign.
They're planted like that so the bees
can quickly go from flower to flower.
Bees are the reason
Monica originally wanted to
find a house in Orland.
It's the bee capital of California.
And do you see these
little pastel roofs?
Those are the top of apiaries
for beekeepers.
Monica wanted to find a house
for the woman she loved.
Bethany.
Bethany, you lied to us.
Why don't you just head back
and Jen will get you rinsed out.
You and Monica
may have bonded over bad yoga,
but you were more than friends,
weren't you?
Yeah, we were.
Yeah. And she was
buying a house for you?
She was buying a house for us.
For the three of us, okay?
I was leaving Nathan, and Gavin
and I were gonna move in with her.
A house she was purchasing
using the proceeds
from her illegal
animal trafficking business.
What?
No, Monica would never...
She was stealing
clients' animals from the clinic
and selling 'em on the black market.
Why would she do that?
My guess is because she loved you.
We saw the brochure from the new house.
It was a bee lover's heaven.
Seems like she really wanted
to make you happy.
Bethany, did your husband
know about this affair?
Did he know you were
planning on taking his son away?
Yeah.
Nathan saw some of the text messages
that Monica had sent me.
He wanted to work on things,
but he knew I was leaving him.
You don't think he...
No, Nathan would never...
I'll be with you in a minute.
- Yeah.
- Sorry.
Mr. Reed. Thanks for coming.
Yeah. Sorry, I was
picking Gavin up from karate
- when I got your call.
- Yeah.
You said you just had a few questions?
Yeah, it's no problem.
Is Detective Oz here?
He's not, but I am.
And I happen to know about
a secret stash of gummy bears
in Detective Karadec's desk.
Don't tell him.
I'll take care of him.
- Let's go.
- Check out my new belt.
No way.
It is understandable you
had some anger towards Monica.
I really didn't.
She was taking your wife, your family.
Did you confront her?
Look, I never...
Yeah.
You wanna tell us about this?
Did you really think we wouldn't find it
hidden in the bottom of your tool chest?
Did you really think that we
wouldn't check the table of contents
for poison dart frogs?
No response. Okay, how about this?
I'm guessing you're a coffee man?
All right, I did it.
I killed Monica.
Everyone did some nice work.
It wasn't just me.
It was a... a team effort.
Friday. Time to tie
one on. Who's in, huh?
- Bobby, come on.
- I gotta get home.
Karadec? Morgan?
- One drink.
- Yes.
Something's not quite
sitting right with you
about Nathan's confession.
Same. The pieces just aren't quite
clicking together in my brain.
Yeah, well, Nathan's wife
was leaving him for Monica.
He did confess to the murder,
but I don't know.
Won't hurt to look at it
with fresh eyes on Monday.
- Monday?
- Yeah.
No, I can't go into
the weekend like this.
I won't be able
to stop thinking about it.
And you got your big
date to distract you.
What date?
Aubrey Brown-Eyed Bumble.
Tomorrow at one o'clock, Coast Grill?
You don't remember who she is?
How many dates did you arrange?
I... I cast nets, okay?
Morgan... Morgan,
you have exactly one second
before I arrest you for theft.
- Give...
- You left your interests blank?
I did. Okay? There
needs to be some discovery.
I'm a... a cipher, a man of mystery.
I can't give you this phone back
until I know you have interests
other than punctuality and hygiene.
Thank you.
And I'll have you know, I have
plenty of very normal interests.
Football. You know,
history. Working out.
So you're a cover model
for Generic Bro Weekly.
I also play a lot of Scrabble.
Oh, my God. Okay, listen.
I say this as a concerned citizen, okay?
You gotta loosen up a little bit.
Have some fun.
Step out of your comfort zone.
Morgan, in the interest of
our professional relationship,
do not say another word.
- I'm just trying to...
- Not one more word.
Okay.
That doesn't count.
But while I'm at it, wear
your dark blue shirt tomorrow.
It brings out your eyes
and makes you seem less uptight.
Also, something's off with his
timeline, so the case isn't over.
Do you remember how Bethany said
that she had been friends
with Monica for two years?
- Uh-huh.
- You know I found that picture
of Bethany and Gavin
in Monica's apartment.
Well, Gavin had his yellow belt then.
He got his purple belt today.
So as you get older and better,
you test to earn new belts.
It starts with yellow, then
orange, green, blue and purple.
So even if Gavin went to karate
twice a week,
it would take him longer than two years
to go from yellow to purple belt.
And I didn't really see
his face in the picture,
but he was certainly much shorter.
So are you saying that
Monica was stalking Bethany?
Either that or Gavin
had an insane growth spurt
and is a karate prodigy.
Yeah, well, like I said, let's
just dive back in on Monday.
No, but my brain's
spitting ideas out now.
Why'd we stop at this Swift Mart?
It's, like, forever out of the way.
'Cause you two had to pee,
and about a decade ago,
some meathead robbed this place,
so I wanted to check it out.
Whatever.
Nobody move! This is a robbery!
What kind of idiot robs a store
wearing flip-flops?
I told you. He's a moron.
Hang on. How did you know
he was wearing flip-flops?
Hi, guys.
Who wants to go to the beach?
Is there food there?
Are we coming with you
to interview a murderer?
No.
Don't worry, sweetie. Just an
ex-con with an airtight alibi.
Good. Push.
Okay, make yourselves comfortable.
We'll go for tacos after.
Wow. One earbud, huh?
How annoying and on-brand.
Hey, good hustle. Get out of here.
What do you want?
Why didn't you tell the police
that Monica was your accomplice
in the convenience store robbery?
She was a minor. She would've
gotten a short sentence.
I know she was with you.
Her father gave details of the crime
that weren't in the police report.
Yeah, like I care what he has to say...
I'm sorry, can you take this stupid...
Hey, are you crazy?
She was pregnant.
The last three months were bananas.
I spent all my free time studying.
But I finally got my SHRL certification.
Congratulations. SH...
What... What is that? I'm sorry.
Sorry. Not everyone's in HR, Aubrey.
It's an advanced credential for
human resource professionals.
Yeah, that's... Wow.
This burger's perfect.
Just how I like it.
Not too much stuff on it.
I usually only eat red meat
right before sex.
Karadec, here you are.
Oh, my God. I'm starving.
Can I please have some fries?
Absolutely.
She promised us tacos, but I
don't think that's happening.
- Hey.
- Do you know this woman?
Yeah, I think so.
I'm his wife, and these are his kids.
And this, Adam, is not you
playing squash with your buddies.
I thought we agreed that we were only
gonna splurge on hookers as a couple.
I'm just messing with
you, Aubrey. I'm his partner.
- We're not partners.
- Nonromantic partner.
We're not partners. She's
actually just a consultant.
We work on cases together
in a "partnerly" fashion.
All right? Does that work?
And I've got a theory about
the one we're working on now.
And boy, is it a doozy.
Bethany's son, Gavin,
is definitely adopted.
And I'm more than pretty sure
that Monica and Shane
are his biological parents.
- Wait, wait. How do you...
- Should I...
So Shane and Gavin both have
preauricular sinuses, aka ear dimples.
Some biologists think that ear dimples
are a vestige of fish gills.
- What?
- It's not important.
The point is, they're super rare.
Only 0.1% of the population has them,
and it's even rarer
to have them in both ears.
So if you do, it is 100% inherited.
So when a daddy with two
ear dimples loves a mommy,
the baby will also have two ear dimples.
And that is exactly how
we know that Gavin
is Shane and Monica's biological potato.
- Potato?
- Child.
Sorry, we're all hungry.
Bethany and Nathan... no dimples.
Shane and Gavin... two dimples each.
- I swung by and talked to Shane.
- You did what?
She talked to Shane
with the ear dimples.
He basically confessed, facially,
that he was covering for Monica
the day of the convenience store robbery
because she was pregnant with his baby.
A teen pregnancy.
That's why Monica's dad
was ashamed of her.
That's why they were estranged.
Yes. And I think
Bethany learned the truth.
She's not the person Monica
wanted to keep in her life.
It was Monica's biological son, Gavin.
Yeah, see? Look, right there.
They're so tiny,
you have to really look closely.
I don't need to see any more
photos of ear dimples. I get it.
So now you're saying
that the husband confessed
to a crime he didn't commit?
My guess is he's devoted to
his wife, trying to protect her.
Or I'm so good, I got an
innocent man to confess.
I came as soon as I got your message.
Is there news about my husband?
Look, he's innocent, okay? I know it.
Bethany, I think it's best that we
move someplace we can talk privately.
Detective Oz will take care of Gavin.
Bethany, what was your reaction
when you found out that Monica
wasn't really in love with you?
Monica's parents forced
their pregnant teenage daughter
to give her baby up 12 years ago.
Monica didn't just happen to
bump into you at yoga, did she?
No. No, she sought you out.
She befriended you, and she
pretended to fall in love with you
to get close to the person
that she really loved:
Gavin.
And the person who loved you...
your husband, Nathan...
confessed to a murder
he didn't even commit.
Now, maybe you're fine with that.
I mean, you did sneak that
frog book into his tool box.
But, Bethany, can you really live with
sending an innocent man...
the man that you married... to
prison for the rest of his life?
I destroyed my marriage for
Monica, and it was all a lie.
That day that Gavin heard
the horrible man
arguing with Monica, I was there.
Only I didn't know Gavin
overheard it at the time.
And he was yelling at her
for giving up their son for adoption.
In that moment, I knew two things.
Gavin was Monica's biological child,
and Monica seduced me to get to him.
She was trying to steal my son!
And it was working.
Gavin loved Monica.
They had a connection.
He wanted to be a vet like her, and...
One of the reasons
why I fell in love with Monica
was because of how amazing
she was with Gavin, and...
and now I can't stop wondering
if maybe it was the same for her.
That maybe it only
just started out as a lie.
Do you think...
Have them release Nathan.
Bring that man to his son
as soon as possible.
You... Watch out... You
gotta watch out for the red...
- That dragon guy. You gotta...
- Yes.
- There you go. All right.
- They're all red.
- There's a big guy coming.
- Look, that guy.
- That was...
- Excuse me.
I got turned around. I'm here to
collect my daughter's effects.
I... Sure. I can find
someone to help with that.
Hey, buddy.
Why don't you go get yourself
some snacks
from the snack machine, okay?
Come on. Go.
Just have a seat here.
I'll go find an
officer to help you, okay?
Thank you. Okay.
Hey. You seen Hoffy?
No, but Bethany confessed.
She found out that Monica
was Gavin's biological mother.
She thought Monica
was stealing her son from her.
I'm... I'm so sorry to bother you again.
I just wanted to let you know
that I'm gonna come back tomorrow.
- I'm not up for it tonight.
- Okay.
- No problem. Whatever works.
Hey, Oz. Could you bring
Nathan up from holding?
- Yep.
- Thank you.
I'm sorry I jumped the gun.
What I don't get is why you confessed
to a crime you didn't commit.
I grew up without a mom.
It was hard.
I didn't want that for my son.
Me? I wouldn't have wanted
to grow up without my dad.
This sucks. Doesn't feel like we won.
Yeah.
Hate to tell you,
but it's like that a lot.
Here you go, sweetheart. Try that.
Finally. Thank you.
Well, the bill was just too wrinkled.
That's why the machine
kept spitting it out.
What did you get?
Sour Cherry Tsunamis.
My daughter used to love sour candy.
- Gavin.
- Dad!
Hey, bud.
Oh, man.
You all right?
Let's go.
Be with you in a minute.
I don't think your friend here
is that patient.
Fernanda?
Fernanda!
You're awake.
It's not even noon
though. Is everything...
- Are you feeling okay?
- What are you doing?
Brought you some mango juice.
Thanks.
You know this room service thing
is kinda sus, right?
Yeah.
I did something really awful,
and I'm scared that you're
not gonna forgive me for it.
Did you shrink my Lululemons?
No.
I snooped in your room
and I found your birth control.
I saw you being stealthy
and swallow a pill,
and my mind just
kinda ran wild. And I...
I should've asked you.
- Can't believe you did that.
- I know.
I want you to trust me, and
then I didn't trust you. And...
I just... I messed up.
And that's why I'm coming clean.
But it kills me that you thought
you had to hide that from me.
I knew you'd freak out.
Yeah, I'm gonna freak out.
And then I'm gonna pull it together
and come to my senses
and have your back.
- Always.
- I know.
I'm serious.
I'm your ride or die.
Your bury the bodies
and ask questions later.
I know, Mom.
I'm sorry.
I should've just told you.
And I was going to,
but it just seemed stupid.
No, it's not stupid. I get it.
My skin just got so bad,
and you just kept telling me,
"Oh, you look so pretty."
And, "No one will notice."
What?
My skin. My whitehead situation.
Jennifer J. started taking birth control
and her acne is, like, gone.
So I saved up all my babysitting
money, and I went online and...
Wait, you went on birth control
for your complexion?
Yeah.
Wow. Okay, good. I...
But you see how cool
and supportive I was
when I thought you were having sex?
- That's...
- Well, no.
I am having sex, but that's
not why I got the birth control.
Yeah. Yeah. And that's
something that we can t...
- What?
- My gosh.
Mom, you're so easy.
I hate you. What... I hate you.
Don't laugh at me.
- No!
- I'll beat you
with your own birth control pillow.
- Mom, stop. That's... Get out.
- I'm so mad at you.
You're grounded!
- Synced and corrected by synk -
- www.MY-SUBS.com -