Hey!
- Go, go!
- Come on, guys. Don"t do that.
Freaking kids.
Hello?
There are three borders in Africa.
Not if you station all your troops in Egypt.
What do you think?
- Totally.
- Can I have a yes day if I win tonight?
Give me a minute with your brother?
Wait, no. You guys could
be arguing about it for hours.
All right. Yeah, we"ll
do a yes day if you win.
- You"re my witness.
- Elliot. If you are trying to employ
the Russian"s strategy during
the patriotic war of 1812
- I am.
- Well, then you"re making a big mistake.
Napoleon led 630,000
strong into Russia,
not realizing he"d been drawn into the
perfect trap by Alexander the blessed.
Elliot, you child.
You"re conflating a real war with a
game of plastic men and cardboard.
- How so?
- Here it comes.
Well, once you take away
insufficient access to resources
and the strategic efforts
of the French military
and you distill it all down to
which continent on the board
would be the best place
to gather all of your troops,
you"ll only come up with one conclusion,
- Australia.
I win.
Nicely done, young lady.
Yeah, that was way off.
How did we let this happen?
I mean...
Listen, I was in a Northern
Europe kinda mood, and you"re ten.
So, as I roll my way
to world domination...
My...
Mom, you"re off work tomorrow, right?
Because I have big plans for our yes day.
All right.
I know you probably think my
itinerary for today is too much.
Well, it"s pretty.
"Visit mom" s work, venice
beach, the pier, the grove,
saks fifth Avenue, rodeo drive."
Okay. It"s a yes day, right? Not a week.
"We only have today. Let us begin."
- Someone famous said that, right?
- Yeah. Yeah. Mother Teresa.
- Yeah.
- Okay. Let"s do it.
So, if you calm down, I can
understand you much better.
- If I can just...
- just a minute.
Yes, you"ll have to calm down.
Buddy, I Don"t even know if we can
afford to use the bathrooms at saks.
Mom, trust.
Twice a year, saks offers free makeovers
to the first 25 people who sign up,
but it"s incredibly hard to get on the list.
And we"re on this list?
We"re on the list.
Were any rules broken to get on this
list? Because I do work for the police now.
Elliot did some computer
stuff and made it happen.
I promised to save up and
get him a calculator in return.
I have a package for major crimes.
I"m so sorry. He gets excited
my god. He"s so cute.
Cancel all our plans.
I have to pet that guy.
- Okay. Well, hang on.
- Hey. Yes day.
I kind of assumed
that the phone number
written with cheesy fingers was yours.
Well, maybe if you had
called it, you would know.
- I did call.
- Did you?
Yeah. A woman named
edna picked up the phone.
Nice lady.
76-year-old bowling buff
with plenty of stories to tell.
Well, lucky edna. Sounds
like you"re a good listener.
I"m decent.
Yeah. Maybe next time I"ll try
writing with something other than food.
No. It totally worked out.
Edna invited me to her bowling
league tomorrow night, the gutter gals.
- No.
- Yes.
Now, I could see if I
could bring a plus-one.
Are you asking me out on a date with
a bunch of old ladies who like to bowl?
- I think I am.
- I"m 100% in.
- Mom, we have to get a dog.
- No.
Cute kid.
Yeah. Caught her stealing again,
so time to press formal charges.
Smart. Never too early
to scare "em straight."
- See ya.
Yeah. Right outside my
apartment. He just came at me.
- You got a look at the guy?
- Yeah.
This is called the bullpen.
That "s Daphne. She" s my favorite.
My daughter.
Hi.
I feel like this tour should
include some snacks.
Yeah. Let"s see what you got.
I"ll have... Anything but the yogurt.
Those are lieutenant soto"s, and I
Don"t wanna mess with her probiotics.
It wasn"t my stash, man.
- Whoa.
- Okay. Save it for the judge. Let"s go.
Morgan, I thought you were off today.
I am off today. I"m just
showing my kid around.
And this is Ava.
Yeah. You remembered.
Yeah. How could I forget?
What a fun surprise.
It"s a yes day. So, anything Ava says
she wants to do, I have to say yes to it.
Okay. I see. Well, in that case,
all laws still apply, young lady.
- Where"s your desk?
- I Don"t have a desk.
We"re gonna go drop this perp off
downstairs and then question a witness,
but enjoy your day off.
Good to see you again, Ava.
So, everyone has a desk but you?
I Don"t need a desk. I kinda pop
around and help everybody out.
Right. "Cause you" re just so
smart, everyone needs your help.
- I mean...
- Okay. I"m going to the restroom.
Okay. It"s right down the hall and then...
You are a teenager and
you already know everything.
I understand. Yeah, I didn"t know.
Yeah. Well, for now
on, you have to tell me...
- Thank you.
- Yeah, you bet.
- Blue eyes. That"s helpful.
- Actually, they were brown.
Everybody, stay put!
What?
Don"t do that.
Don"t do that!
Forget everything
you"ve been trained to do,
otherwise that box right over there
goes boom.
And that"s just the one you can see.
There are others in this
building that are there
to keep your brothers and
sisters in blue at bay. Understood?
Get over there with the rest of them.
You too. Get up.
Not you. Stay. Sit down.
Stay there. I"ve got a job for you.
No!
No more of that from anybody. Got it?
Weapons, phones...
Now.
Now!
Pull your weapon.
Weapon. Hurry up.
Hey, phone!
You too.
The people in this room stay.
Everyone else in the building has
two minutes to leave. Make the call.
This is detective Daphne forrester.
We have a report of
bombs in the building.
Requesting immediate evacuation.
Move. Over there. Now.
I know you"re all scared and
wondering why we"re here, so I"ll tell you.
An innocent man is about to spend his life
in prison for a murder he did not commit.
We"re here to do for him what
we know he would do for us.
Which gives you a second
chance to find the real killer.
Nobody walks out of
here alive unless you do.
So, who"s your best detective?
I am.
Get an officer on every exit!
Open the Charlie side!
Quickly!
Go to the east side!
No one"s answering.
It"s only been 27 minutes.
Keep calling until we get through.
- Hey.
- What"s going on?
Two people entered the precinct
and announced they had bombs.
We evacuated the building,
but they have hostages.
These are my detectives,
karadec and oz.
SWAT captain cliff halloway.
My team has already cleared
the area and secured the perimeter.
- What about the hostages?
- We think at least a dozen
based on our tally of who
went in but hasn"t come out.
A few members of the public,
but mostly our own people
in the major crimes bullpen.
We have all the exits covered, and we"re
staging at various points of advantage.
Any idea who we"re dealing with here?
They signed into the building
using their own names,
and we got their files from army cid.
Staff sergeant Brooke kirkman, 32,
from Bakersfield. No known priors.
Same for sergeant Jeremy
Davis from Colorado.
Both served together in the us
army until Davis transferred last year
- to the national guard.
- So they"re trained.
So is my team. We"ll be prepared
to handle them if it comes to that.
How did they get
explosives past security?
We"re still trying to figure that out.
We haven"t been able to
talk to anybody on the inside.
But we did tap into our
security system and found this.
What happened to the
cameras in the bullpen?
They blew them up.
I"ll get eyes on them as soon as
my guys are in position of the roof.
Good. But remember, our primary
goal is the safety of those hostages.
Of course.
Let"s try to keep the media
out of this as long as possible.
It"s melon.
This is lieutenant soto with the
LAPD. Who am I speaking with?
"Staff sergeant Logan
hanson is an innocent man."
Charged with a crime he did not commit.
The LAPD got it wrong.
Today, they have one
chance... To make it right
"or everyone in here will die."
Is everyone there all right?
Stop.
- Done.
- Go.
Lead the way.
Did she make it out? Ava?
Yeah. She had to. The whole
building was evacuated, right?
What are they thinking?
That if they can prove
Logan hanson is innocent,
maybe he goes free and
they only do a little time.
- Who worked the case?
- Detective lavely. Get him here now.
- Yeah.
- Has lavely ever got one wrong before?
Not in the 20 years I"ve known him.
- Detective lavely.
- Lieutenant soto.
- This about the frank Webber murder?
- I need to know everything.
I arrested Logan hanson myself.
Last I checked he was
locked up in men"s central.
Da thinks he"ll get 25 to life.
It"s an open-and-shut case.
- Not according to those who knew him.
- You checking my work now?
If it keeps the people inside from
getting caught in a cross fire, yes.
Because right now our only chance
of resolving this situation peacefully
- is to prove Logan hanson was innocent.
- And if he isn"t?
Then this situation will get a lot
more dangerous than it already is.
Frances Webber, 62.
He was a retired master sergeant
who returned as a contractor
to teach at joint forces
training base, los alamitos.
The guy was a legend.
Trained generations
of soldiers in the army.
- Did you find it?
- We found it.
Webber was found dead last
week when a runner spotted his rv
in a park in palos verdes
with the door kicked in.
I remember this case.
Shot with his own gun, right?
One to the chest.
You recovered the weapon?
In a trash can. Less than
a mile from the scene.
Killer tried to wipe it clean,
but we were still able to lift
solid partials from the barrel.
- Both a match to Logan.
- And acetone?
Which Logan was using
in a home Reno project.
Report says the trajectory
of the bullet"s consistent
with a shooter about
six foot, maybe 6 "1"?
Logan"s height.
Witnesses placed Logan and
frank at a bar together in long beach
- the night before murder.
- Bartender reported they seemed tense.
- What is it?
- It"s a transcript of the interrogation.
Read it.
He waived Miranda.
Blah-blah-blah. Blah-blah-blah.
"Where were you Tuesday night?"
I was with my girlfriend Brooke.
You two were home alone?
No calls, no visitors. Right?
- Alibi?
- Brooke confirmed the alibi, but
girlfriends never lie.
Our investigation found that Logan
was up for a prestigious overseas post.
Logan claimed he turned it down.
I"ve given my life to the service,
but I wanted a life of my own.
A life with Brooke.
"And what did frank Webber
think of that decision?"
Or frank told Logan he was
being passed over for the post,
which sent Logan into a
rage, and he killed frank.
So, Logan has motive, no reliable
alibi, and his prints are on the gun.
Like I said, case closed.
But Logan claimed he and frank went
to the shooting range the day before.
And claimed frank let him his use
his gun to explain away the prints.
Delusional hostage takers
are the most dangerous.
But the pair inside are
convinced Logan is innocent,
it "s unlikely they" ll listen to reason.
Neutralizing the targets may be the
only way to protect those hostages.
Look.
I wish I could say there
was something they missed.
- Better do more than wish.
- It"s all here.
I Don"t see...
Lavely and his team
did a very thorough job.
I"ve given my life to the service.
All the evidence still points to Logan.
Wrong answer.
Try again.
I wanted a life of my
own. A life with Brooke.
- I think...
- think fast
- excuse me.
- Who are you?
- You a cop?
- No. I"m a consultant.
Listen. Lieutenant melon, he"s right.
All the evidence does point to
Logan, but something"s missing.
Keep talking.
Look. Okay, do you see the blood?
Look at the blood. Look where it stops.
That"s a perfect corner. Something
was there when frank was killed.
And then gone before the police arrived.
That"s right. A piece
of paper or something.
Whatever it was, the killer
wanted to take it with them,
and we gotta figure out why.
I gotta make a phone call.
- This is soto.
- Hey, lieutenant.
- Morgan.
- Yeah, I am just in here helping out.
Hey, can I talk to karadec, please?
"Yeah, Morgan, I" m
here. Are you all right?
Yep, I"m okay. What about you?
Are you enjoying your yes day?
Ava"s not with her.
Get all officers looking
for her outside the building.
We"re gonna look for
a reason to celebrate.
Hey. Stop messing around.
- Listen, I need... I need an assist.
- How can I help?
Is frank"s rv still in impound?
- Yeah.
- What kind of paper?
- We"re not sure yet.
But wh-whatever it is, it
could help us find frank"s killer.
- Like, something he printed?
- Yeah. I... Maybe. I Don"t know.
I think I have a desktop. Hold on.
Looks like the last thing frank
opened on his computer was a form.
Dd form 458.
It"s a charge form.
Brings a soldier in front
of a military tribunal.
- Frank was gonna write up a soldier.
- No way.
"Which could" ve
resulted in his discharge.
It couldn"t have been Logan. He
was a model soldier in every way.
Okay, so if staying in the
army wasn "t Logan" s motive,
then maybe it was somebody else"s.
- Who"s there?
- What"s going on?
Show me your hands
now or I start shooting!
Come here.
Give me that.
My god!
Hey, hey, hey, hey.
Whoa! You got something to say?
Seems to me you"ve got bigger worries
than a mother hugging her daughter,
considering the situation we are in.
So, yeah, I had something
to say, and I said it.
All right. It"s okay.
I got him.
Both of you, come sit down now.
Lauren, we are sorry to
have to drag you into all of this
about your father, frank,
but we really need your help.
Can you think of anyone
your dad had an issue with?
Maybe someone he was planning
on writing up for misconduct.
If there was, he wouldn"t have told me.
He believed his role was to
support and protect his soldiers.
That meant guarding their
privacy like it was a national secret.
He took his responsibilities seriously.
He was more than just a superior officer.
He was like a father to those guys.
That must have been
hard, having to share him.
I didn"t mind. He always
made sure we got time together.
No matter what he had going on, he
came over for dinner every Monday.
6:00 to 8:00. Like clockwork.
The Monday before he died,
did anything seem off to you?
I wish that I could tell you.
But last Monday was actually the
first dinner he canceled in years.
Did he tell you why?
He just said that he had
something he needed to do,
that he loved me and
he"d make it up to me.
I"ve got no eyes outside,
no clue what"s going on.
Mom, I tried to do what
you said. I really tried.
I tried to get out. I"m
sorry. I couldn"t leave you.
Baby, listen to me. It"s okay.
I"m not gonna let
anything happen to you.
- Okay.
- It"s okay.
Shh.
Answer it.
This is detective karadec.
Can I speak with Morgan, please
what do you got?
Hello, Brooke. Frank missed a dinner with
his daughter the Monday before he died.
Do we have any idea where he went?
"No, his car doesn" t
have a navigation system,
but his cell phone should
be inside that evidence box.
You.
I"ll be right back. Okay?
I got it.
His password is my birthday, 9484.
- You hear that?
- Yep.
Got it. Monday evening
looks like, at 5:47 P.M.,
he looked up an address
near 4th and spring.
- That"s pershing square.
- Back when I was in vice,
we"d catch drugs,
prostitution there every night.
My... my father would never.
He didn"t even drink.
At my wedding, he had sparkling
apple juice instead of champagne.
Wait. Frank input a second
address 40 minutes later.
1487 north east man Avenue.
It"s a private detox
center in boyle heights.
So, frank picked someone up
downtown and got them help?
I told you.
My father treated his team like
family. He would do anything for them.
"kay, he only made
one phone call that night.
It was to a Lauren Webber.
And the call didn"t go through.
I
I turn my phone off when I
sleep. He must"ve tried to call me.
We"re gonna find out what
happened that night. I promise you.
I"m gonna call the facility now,
find out who frank dropped off.
Good. Oz, look into the personnel
files of anyone frank was training.
See if one pings on a prior drug charge.
Yeah. On it.
Star community detox.
Yeah, this is detective
karadec with the LAPD.
You guys had a patient dropped
off there Monday about 7:00 P.M.
I "m sorry, but I" m not allowed
to provide any information.
I understand, but this
patient might"ve killed a man.
I still can"t provide you a
name. I have a responsibility
listen, I know you are
just trying to do your job.
But you could be protecting a murderer
and putting the lives
of my entire team at risk.
I hope everyone is okay.
Hello?
- We"ll get a warrant.
- We Don"t have time.
I"m on the phone with the da.
Come here.
- Something"s not right.
- Yeah, you need to relax.
You"re not listening to me.
Hey.
I can take him. Can you two take her?
Fast enough to stop her
from triggering that bomb?
I"m fast, but not that fast.
All she has to do is press that button.
I Don"t think she will.
I got a bad feeling, okay?
Relax. The police do not want
people to die. They will get the warrant.
When? Tomorrow? All while
they"re making moves out there?
Hey. Stick to the plan.
Logan goes free, and
nobody gets hurt, right?
I Don"t trust cops.
And neither should you.
They"re planning something.
I know it.
Nobody move!
Come on!
Jeremy!
SWAT"s almost in position.
Shots fired.
- Are you sure about that?
- Confirmed.
I just got reports of a shot fired.
From inside the bullpen?
- That "s what I" m hearing.
- We have eyes in there yet?
Almost.
My team is on standby,
lieutenant. Just give the word.
We have to give Morgan more
time. Just hold off a little bit longer.
Until when? We hear another gunshot?
Would you rather hear a bomb?
If we spook them, things
can go south real fast, Selena.
- Lieutenant?
- Hey!
Those are our people in there. They
know what they"re doing. Do you?
- All right! Enough!
- Our guys on the roof lowered a camera.
Hey, who"s that on the
ground? Hey, he"s not moving.
People inside are like my family
too. But we can only wait for so long.
- Your team goes on my call.
- No, wait! Lieutenant, right there.
He"s moving. Yeah, right there. See?
The gun went off because of
you, okay? Everybody saw it.
I know how you cops spin
things, try to pin it on me.
You should"ve listened to us.
You okay?
Keep breathing with me.
The bullet must"ve hit an artery.
I need your shirt.
All right.
You think this is gonna keep me
from my bowling date with edna?
It might.
It"s too bad. I was really
looking forward to it.
Well, then we better both
get out of here in one piece.
That should slow the bleeding.
All right. We just need to elevate my leg
and then check my distal
pulses every three minutes.
Tom"s at night school for nursing.
I need a box.
No, what are you doing?
As long as they cooperate, no
one gets killed. That"s what we said.
One, two...
All right.
Let"s lay you down.
- Please.
- Consider it done.
Selena, let"s have unis canvass
any bodegas within walking distance
- of that rehab facility.
- What for?
Because if frank
dropped our killer off there,
then the killer probably
doesn"t have a car, right?
Patients can come and go,
but every addict I"ve ever known
goes for the same thing every morning.
- Coffee and cigarettes.
- Cigarettes and coffee.
And you"re going to these
stores to ask them what exactly?
To ask "em if they saw a
male on Tuesday morning."
Six feet tall, military haircut, maybe
looking like he"s jonesing a little bit.
Picking up a cup of Joe
and a pack of smokes.
- Sounds like a long shot.
- You got a better one?
Hurry.
We gotta get him to a hospital now.
Nobody"s going anywhere.
If this man doesn"t get medical
attention in the next 15 minutes,
he could go into shock and die.
How do you know that?
When I became pregnant
with my daughter, I was terrified.
The only thing I wanted in the
entire world was to keep her safe.
I took about a thousand first aid
classes, and I am telling you now,
this man needs medical attention.
Did it help? Taking all those classes?
The second she was born, everything
I learned went out the window.
It"s Ava who taught
me how to be a parent.
Just like your baby will.
What are you talking about?
Logan didn"t wanna be stationed overseas
because you two are starting a family.
Prenatal vitamins can
cause dryness of the skin.
And the spot where fertility
hormones are injected
can become swollen and even painful.
Logan was renovating that
room to be a nursery, wasn"t he?
Look at me. I know you didn"t
mean for anybody to get hurt.
It "s okay. You" re just
trying to help the person
who"s gonna be the
father of your kid someday.
Please.
You"re having a kid?
I"m not pregnant, but
Logan and I were trying.
Why didn"t he tell me?
I Don "t know why he didn" t
tell you, but why does that matter?
"cause everyone" s lying to me!
No one is lying to you.
Update me on that.
Okay.
Tell me you found something.
Tuesday, 8:36 A.M. clerk remembers
a blonde grunt about six feet tall
- buying a pack of smokes and a coffee.
- You got a name?
No, but security footage from an
atm by the register got a look at him.
Now, it"s not great, but,
but it"s something. Text me
the photo. Good work, detective.
Pull up facial recognition.
See if we can ID this guy.
Yeah.
What?
Wait. Is that a field jacket?
You think he"s a friend of theirs?
Worth a try.
My god.
You gonna get that?
- They might"ve solved the whole thing.
- Shut up.
This is lieutenant soto.
We"ll be sending you a
photo of someone with no ID.
We wanna know if you recognize him.
9484.
That"s it? That"s what
we"ve been waiting for?
A blurry photo of some random nobody?
We"re doing everything that we...
Hey, if he dies, you"re gonna
go away for first-degree homicide.
I told you to shut up!
- Hey, soldier, focus.
- Do you see what"s going on?
They"re never gonna tell the truth
about what"s happened in here.
- We"re on our own.
- You need to remember
what we"re doing here,
who we are here for.
The man who saved your life
is behind enemy lines right now.
And he needs you to keep your cool.
I witnessed everything. I got you.
Got me? You"re in it just as deep.
They"re playing us, Brooke, until
they turn the tables and shut this down.
I won"t stop.
I will not stop investigating until I
find the real killer. I promise you.
But we have got to get Tom to a hospital.
No. No. No.
Jeremy, he doesn"t look good.
I have seen worse.
We said no one gets hurt.
What are you, best
friends with her now?
Brooke, he can"t get out
of here by himself though.
He needs somebody to take him.
You.
You, walk him out.
With all due respect, lieutenant,
we have to follow protocol.
Shots fired changes the game.
They had plenty of
time to listen to reason.
Hold on. Something"s happening.
Okay.
What am I supposed to do? I Don"t...
Listen to me, okay?
When... When that elevator"s
open, and you go out the door,
I want you to open it slowly, and you"re
just gonna keep your hands up in the air.
No, I can "t do... I can" t do it.
- Yes, you can.
- I"m not gonna leave you.
No... my love.
I would never.
I would never ask you to do something
that I didn"t know you could do.
You are so strong, and that
man needs your help. Okay?
But what if... what if
something happens to you?
Guess what? I"m not going anywhere.
I"m not going anywhere.
Not for a really long time.
Certainly not today. Okay?
Okay. Almost there.
Okay. You got it. It"s
okay. We"re almost there.
Just a couple more steps. There we go.
Okay.
Okay. Hey.
That"s my girl.
You care more about
these people than Logan.
Don "t say that. It" s not true.
That girl was our insurance policy.
There"s no way the cops would risk
her getting hurt, and you let her go.
She was just a kid. I had to.
Look, they"re cooperating with
us, and we"re cooperating with them.
You only think that
because you listen to her.
She"s blowing the case wide open.
She "s not even a cop. We" re not
doing these people any more favors.
I took an oath to a fellow
soldier to protect him.
I"m putting my life on the line for
him, and you are turning soft on us.
Jeremy, right now, all we need to do
do what? Do what?
Sit here like idiots while
they make more phone calls?
What... what are they actually giving us?
Nothing. They"re feeding
us worthless intel to buy time.
Why can"t you see that?
- There was no phone call.
- Enough!
- If you say...
- let her talk!
What do you mean
there was no phone call?
I saw frank "s phone. There wasn" t a
phone call that came in on the Monday night
he canceled on his daughter.
No incoming call to tell him
to go downtown from the killer.
No text saying that
whoever it was was in trouble.
- Okay, so?
- So, how would frank know where to go?
- What are you trying to find?
- Something I saw. Right here.
Two weeks ago, frank
bought a luggage locator tag.
- What"s that?
- It"s exactly what it sounds like.
- If you lose your luggage...
- stop talking.
Except there was nothing in the phone to
indicate that frank had any travel plans.
- So, what was frank trying to find?
- Not what, who.
Frank wanted to know if the soldier
he cared about was doing drugs.
When he saw that the tag had gone to
a place that was known for selling drugs,
frank drove there to pick him up.
He wasn"t tracking a package.
He was tracking a person.
Frank must"ve slipped the tag onto
that guy the last time they saw each other.
Exactly.
And you really think
that"s gonna help us?
If the person who killed frank
didn"t know he was being tracked,
he might still have the tag on him.
Most tags have an app that keep
a history of where they"ve been.
And according to this,
the tag was in frank"s rv
on the date and time of the murder.
The killer knew he"d be
dishonorably discharged
if frank wrote him up
and exposed his drug use.
Yep. And that"s why the
killer took dd form 458,
the one that frank had filled out right
after he shot him with his own gun.
So, who the hell is this guy?
I Don"t know, but I can tell
you where he is right now.
- You can?
- You ready for an address, lieutenant?
Yep. - 8700 so la no Avenue.
According to city records, the tag"s
at the residence of Ben spoelstra.
Looks like we got our guy.
Was he in military?
Let"s see. Army reserve,
private, currently on temporary duty
at joint forces training base, los alamitos.
- Where frank taught.
- Hey, guys? He"s on the move.
Freeze!
LAPD! Do not move!
On the ground right now!
- Do it now! Do it slow!
- Hands in the air.
Wanna interlace those
fingers behind your head, sir?
Thank you very much.
What do we got?
Hey, man. I"ve never seen
this before. This ain"t mine.
I "m sure it" s not yours.
What"s that?
This? This means you"re under
arrest for the murder of frank Webber.
Get him out of here.
We got him.
So, they"ll let him go?
Yeah. He didn"t do it. So, yeah.
Jeremy, did you hear that?
We did it. We saved him.
Thank you. Thank you for believing us.
Yeah. Of course.
Why Don"t you put those down, and
we"ll figure out the rest together, okay?
Okay, okay, okay, okay.
I got it, okay? Okay?
You.
Are you gonna say nice things
about me too? I Don"t think so.
And you. You said I"m going
away for first-degree homicide, right?
Wrong. Wrong!
This isn"t over until I
get what I want, okay?
Okay.
She"s breathing.
You, come here. Call your lieutenant.
You tell her I want a deal
now, or I press this button.
No, he won"t.
The hell I won"t.
Morgan, what are you doing?
He presses that button, the
only thing that could happen is
maybe a garage door
goes up somewhere.
Although, I doubt he"s in range.
This bomb will level this place.
They"ll find you all in pieces.
It might. If it was real.
You"re bluffing.
I "m not. I" m just remembering.
Remembering what?
Mainly how ever since the
1991 Montreal convention,
all manufacturers of
plastic explosives in the us
are required to include
a detection taggant.
It "s a substance that
humans can" t smell,
but it acts as an irritant
to the noses of dogs,
both trained and untrained.
Whatever is in that box, it sure didn"t
seem to bother the dog I saw this morning.
It"s homemade. Brooke built it.
Yeah? Did you see her build it,
or did she just tell you she did?
That"s what I thought.
Because there"s no way a
woman who"s trying to get pregnant
is gonna risk handling the toxic
chemicals that it requires to make a bomb.
You guys didn"t show
up here together, did you?
I remember seeing
you here when I arrived.
You wanted to get here a little
early "cause you didn" t want people
to know that you knew each other, right?
Hey, has anybody seen a
person just waltz into the precinct
and make it all the way up to the
fourth floor to deliver a package?
No? Nobody? Yeah, me neither.
Here"s what I think happened.
I think she arrived here
with a bag or a backpack.
"Skipped right up to this floor,
went straight into the ladies" room.
Whatever she had in that bag,
she put all together in this box.
Must"ve been heavy. It
does have some heft to it.
It does kinda feel like it could be a bomb.
She"s right.
There"s no bomb.
I lied to you. I"m sorry.
No, no! No!
He"s got a weapon on his back.
Got him.
Yes, and because we"re
still gathering details,
I"ll make an official statement later today.
Mom!
My god. My god. Are you hurt?
- Are you hurt? Are you...
- No. No. I"m okay.
Ava texted me from inside,
but then I didn"t hear back, so I...
Where are the kids?
- They"re with the neighbor.
- I"m okay.
- Are you sure you"re all right?
- Yes.
Are you okay?
I"m just glad you"re okay. Got
everyone out safely, didn"t you?
Good thing you"re so smart.
Here.
Rain check?
- I"ll be right back, okay?
- Okay.
Thank you. Great. Okay.
- Hey.
Thanks for the help.
Thank you for the help.
I "m sorry. I really didn" t mean for
I know you didn"t.
I"m glad justice was served today
and that an innocent man is free.
But you put my child in danger.
I hope that one day
you"re fortunate enough
to experience what
that feels like firsthand.
But until then, you just better thank
your lucky stars I"m not on your jury.
Think you can get your hands
on any more of that pudding?
Morgan. Hey.
Turns out this hospital
is on my way to work.
Is it?
Just wanted to make sure you"re...
- Alive?
- Yeah. Alive, yeah.
Yeah, just a little gunshot wound.
It happens.
- Occupational hazard.
- Sure.
How"s your daughter doing?
She"s good. Yeah.
It wasn"t exactly the day we had
planned, but Ava"s good. Thank you.
We like good.
Good. You"re here. An
arson case just came in.
Multiple coordinate attacks with
some very sophisticated methods.
Soto wants you on it right away.
- Just gonna dive right back in?
- Right back in.
Okay.
- Surprise!
- We wanted to surprise you.
The cop car that followed
me here, that was you guys?
Well, everyone wanted to
be here when you landed
to say thank you, and so did we.
- Come on, Morgan.
- Don "t be shy. Let" s...
- Yes.
- Receive your thanks.
Yes, yes, yes, yes.
- Great work.
- Thank you so much.
- Thank you.
- How"s your head?
- It"s not great.
Yeah, it doesn"t look great.
This is what my daughter should
see. Where was all this yesterday?
Very funny.
I think someone found something
for you down in robbery and homicide.
For me?
Yeah. We had an extra one, so...
So.
I Don"t know.
You got a desk.
It wasn"t my idea,
but... Are we good here?
Is this your way of saying "nice job"?
Well, how about if I quit
calling you "the cleaning lady"?
- I think that would be a good idea.
- Yeah.
How about I keep calling you all
the stuff I call you behind your back?
All right, all right, everybody.
Back to work.
I have a feeling you"re absolutely
never going to sit there, am I right?
I mean, probably not.
What are we working on?
Karadec. Yeah. Hold on.