Alice Morgan...
Has something happened?
I'm afraid she's dead, John.
I didn't put her down
or have her put down.
Why'd you steal
the phone I used to call Alice Morgan?
What did he do with the heart?
He ate it.
Animal like that,
he's always moving forward.
All the computers were
fixed by one man. A Steven Rose.
That's him.
Benny. Stop this.
Steven.
Can we salvage anything from this?
Too soon to tell, boss.
Sorry, guy,
she's asked for you by name.
Can I help?
Are you DCI Luther?
Yeah.
I have a message for you.
Message from whom?
Alice Morgan.
What kind of message?
She said to tell John
that Stacey has the owl.
When did she give you this message?
Last night.
So that's not true, is it?
‘Cause Alice is dead.
I know.
I'm sorry, who are you?
Look, I'm just here to help.
And how did you know Alice?
I don't.
So, what, she just appears to you?
Yes.
And did she say anything else?
Not really.
There was one thing.
Something I don't really
understand, I'm sorry.
Something like what?
Meep meep.
Put this woman in the car and cuff her.
Down there. Thank you.
What's all this?
Uh, don't ask. What's going on?
We've got another one.
How much of the brain did he eat?
Roberta Wise.
She was a professor of economics,
University of London.
A government advisor and...
And then this.
Look at her life.
Look at what he took from her.
This wasn't murder, this was theft.
Come again?
Oh, he's just a clever,
little, lonely man,
slowly falling apart, spending his
days watching the lives of others.
And you know what that's like.
Other people's lives seem
so much better than ours,
more interesting,
more attractive, more alive.
The way he sees it, they've
got something that he needs,
so he's just gonna take it from them.
All right, he's never gonna stop, he's
just gonna keep doing it and doing it.
‘Cause he'll never get back
whatever he's lost.
None of us ever do.
♪ My, my, my Delilah
♪ Why, why, why Delilah ♪
Don't stop, love. Drive on.
I can't. Look at him.
Then let's call the police,
they'll deal with it.
What if it was Declan?
Are you all right, mate?
Are you all right, love?
What's happened?
What have you done to yourself?
I'm so sorry.
Thank you for stopping.
No!
♪ Love is like a sin, my love
♪ For the ones that feel it the most
♪ Look at her
with her eyes like a flame
♪ She will love you like a fly
♪ Will never love you again ♪
DCI Luther.
Back on the beat Pete?
When needs must, isn't it?
Thanks for the hospitality.
Look, George, I just had to figure out
who killed Alice Morgan, all right?
I'm sorry it ended up the way it did,
but I'll put it right.
To tell you the truth
I am tempted to let it lie.
I mean, you're obviously a decent chap.
But you did what you did
in front of my son.
Once I've shown weakness to him,
well, it's nature's way, isn't it?
The Lion King. Hakuna Matata.
Uh, I think you're thinking
about the wrong song.
Well what one am I thinking of, then?
Oh, Hakuna Matata,
that's a happy one, right?
"No more worries," that one.
That's the one.
Then I'm definitely thinking
of the wrong song.
I've put a price on your head, John.
How much?
Out of interest, how much
do you think you're worth?
Well, probably not enough for
a good night out and a cab ride home.
Well, I'm honestly down
in the dumps about it,
but you did bring it down on yourself.
So, you're a dead man walking.
Toodle-pip.
Hey.
We've got Steven Rose
leaving the building at 21:32 p.m.
We follow him down here,
down here and then...
Well, he's gone. Off camera.
Yeah, how many bodies
have we got looking for him?
Oh, all of them, I think.
Aerial units, ground units, dog units.
Good.
They won't find him,
but, uh, keep looking.
"Cut the chatter, Red 2.
Accelerate to attack speed.”
What? What was that?
Sorry. Um...
Theo and me... DCI Bloom, um...
He quite liked the odd
Star Wars reference.
"Not this ship, sister."
Do you know any David Bowie?
Yeah. Um...
Yeah, I liked him in that film...
The one in the maze,
with the baby and the puppets.
We Are The Dead.
- I'm sorry?
- Well, there's this thing.
Cotard's syndrome, okay?
It's a delusional mental illness,
and the patient thinks that he's dead
and decomposing.
And the cannibalism, that's a symptom?
No, not usually.
I mean, I'm making a... A leap.
Well, it's a small leap.
It's more of a hop, really.
So how do we get ahead of him?
See, I think he's
like a feral dog right now,
trying to find a place to hide.
I think we lean into that,
I think we go public.
Put his name and face in the media,
force him into one place,
keep him still, and then...
Figure out what he does next.
And you think he's rational enough
for us to be able to do that?
He's delusional, but not deranged.
I mean, the way he sees it, he's
just gonna do what's necessary to...
To get what he needs.
Just to keep going.
You know?
How are we doing, Ben?
Like an anxiety dream.
I have to keep checking
if I'm still wearing trousers.
Well, we can't move without
knowing what's on them hard drives.
Guy, you got a minute?
Sure.
Jonathan Black, March 1999,
is lured into a park, suffocated.
All right. SIO had the killer down
as Brian Elda, local sex offender.
Next day, Brian Elda
drowns himself in the canal.
Jonathan Black's underpants
in his pocket. Slam dunk.
Is she in the file?
No, she's not, but I am.
See, I didn't think Brian Elda
killed himself, all right?
I don't think he did it.
I actually think this girl did it.
Stacey Bell.
Back then, no one was
paying attention to me,
I was still wet behind the ears,
but I was right.
When she was 17, she got
dumped for manslaughter.
She pushed her nan down
the stairs and let her die.
She just got out
two and a half months ago.
You know there's nothing to it,
this psychic drivel, right?
She knows something about Alice Morgan.
So you're a partner
in a corporate PR firm.
Yes, that's right.
So what are you doing here?
You're educated, financially stable.
I just don't get it.
I'm not sure what you're implying.
Well, clairvoyants are
confidence tricksters, aren't they?
Grave robbers preying
on the lonely and bereaved.
That's not what I do.
- No?
- No.
I don't broadcast this,
let alone profit from it.
In fact, most of my life
I've pretended
it wasn't happening to me.
Why?
Because it's horrible.
I don't want to be here doing this.
I don't want to be
humiliated and frightened.
I don't want this to be happening.
I woke up in the middle of the night
and she was standing there.
"Tell John that Stacey Bell
has the owl."
Who's Stacey?
I don't know.
What owl are we talking about?
I'm not sure.
Thing is, it does actually make sense.
Jonathan Black had a... A favourite toy,
and, uh, it disappeared
when he disappeared.
Of course, all of that
was kept from the press.
I mean, no one actually...
No one knew that.
So how do you know it?
She's here.
She's standing behind you.
Who?
Her mouth is moving
but I can't hear her words.
I can make out
what she's saying, though.
Yeah? What's she saying?
"Tell John that it's real.”
I can find a connection
if there's one there,
but, John, I don't think there is.
That pervy lad died years ago.
Alice died a couple
of days ago in Antwerp.
There's no connection.
So, because you can't believe
it's true, logically, it's false.
Is that really an argument now, eh?
Benny, listen to me.
I told Alice Morgan about this.
I told her about
Jonathan Black, Stacey Bell.
I told her how it made me feel.
How I couldn't...
How I couldn't put it right.
What did she say?
"Let's find Stacey Bell
and set her on fire."
Well, that's not the point.
I don't know...
I don't know what the point is.
The point is, I told Alice Morgan.
I didn't tell anybody else.
The only way that Megan could know that
is if Alice Morgan told her.
That's it.
Now...
She knows something.
I don't know what it is,
but I just need to know.
Well, if it can be done,
consider it done.
Are you getting anywhere?
Somewhere.
You all right there?
He killed Theo, Benny.
I want to find him.
I want to rip his heart out and eat it.
So hurry up.
- DS Lane?
- Boss?
I need you to go to
Steven Rose's place of work.
I want you to speak to his boss, his
colleagues, friends, lovers, whoever.
Find out what there is
to know about him.
See what there is on him.
What's this, busy work
to keep me out of your hair?
Nope. Chop-chop.
Morning, babe. You awake?
No, no.
No, everything's fine.
It's fine. I just, uh...
Well, I'm just calling
because I don't want you to worry.
Look, I'm gonna be home
the minute I can.
Yes, I will.
I promise.
I love you, too.
Sleep. Sleep.
Leave a message after the beep.
Mum, it's Declan. I just got your text.
Is everything all right?
- You all right?
- Yeah.
Actually, I don't know.
It's just a bit weird. It's me mum.
Do you mind if I nip off for a bit?
Nah, you go on, mate.
Cheers, Mohan.
Tara Black?
So, uh, how have you been?
I remember you. Constable Luther.
You were very kind.
Seemed to care about my brother.
Well, thank you. I did.
I don't wanna upset you or worry you,
but when someone approaches us
with fresh information,
we're obliged to review the case.
So that's what this is?
Fresh information?
During the investigation, we, um...
- Withheld information.
- Jon's owlie.
Yeah, I...
Have you been talking
to someone about that?
Not that I can think of.
Not any pushy journalist or anyone
saying that they're a psychic.
- No. Why?
- No?
Well, it's just, um...
Sorry, can I just look at that?
Do you remember this girl here?
Certainly, yeah. Stacey Bell.
Everyone's
favourite worst nightmare.
She made Jonathan's life hell.
Wicked little cow.
Is this about Stacey?
Um, why do you say that?
‘Cause you know they
moved her back here, yeah?
What, back here, on the estate?
Saw her down at the shop.
She, uh...
Asked me how I was doing,
I said it was fine.
She said it was a shame
about my brother.
And then she laughed.
You okay?
It's okay.
Stacey, is it?
It's not. No.
You sure?
‘Cause you remind me of someone I knew.
- Who, your mum?
- No.
No, this little girl
I knew a long way back.
I often wonder what happened to her.
Why is that, then?
You like to think about her when you
have a little play with yourself?
See, that's exactly
the sort of thing she would say
if she was here.
Except she's not here, is she?
Apparently not.
:::::: www.hiqve.com ::::::
Sorry,
we can't get to the phone right now.
So please leave a message
after the beep.
Mom, it's Declan.
I shouldn't be too long.
I'm just stuck in
a bit of traffic, all right?
I'll see you soon. Bye.
Wotcher?
George?
All right, John,
you're still with us then.
Just about. One of your boys
had a pop at me.
Well, obviously, I don't know
what you're talking about, Officer.
If I did, I'd probably say
they wouldn't be my boys specifically.
See, if you've been
green-lit, allegedly,
every would-be hitman
in London would be after you.
- How was it, by the way?
- Rubbish.
Whoopsie daisy.
So, how can I help?
George, just lay off.
I've got a nutjob running
around London eating people.
And I've got a dead kid.
What do you mean, "dead kid"?
Yeah. No, you and me,
we're old school, right?
We're on the same page
when it comes to dead kids.
What's this? Billy Bacon and the
Self-Centered Cockney Villain?
The thing is, George,
I think this dead kid
is connected to our thing.
- Alice Morgan.
- How?
Like I said, I'm not sure,
but I know it's connected.
What are we now, psychic?
Yeah. Funny you should say that.
And on the basis of this
funny feeling in your belly,
you're asking for what,
stay of execution?
They broke the mould after
you popped out, didn't they?
Yeah, that's what my mum used to say.
Your sainted mother?
Is this another appeal
to my maudlin eastern heart?
No, whatever.
Well, I hated my mother, John.
And green-lit is green-lit, I'm afraid.
It's out of my hands.
I'll see you on the other
side of the veil.
Mom? Dad?
Mom?
Was it there?
You ever hear of the
confirmation bias?
I beg your pardon?
We all do it.
Sort of see things in a way that
support what you already believe.
So, you, um...
Well, you form an opinion
and then you create a theory.
And then you work hard to prove it.
I don't follow.
Yeah, well, see...
Here's me thinking...
"She must really know a lot
about Alice Morgan.
"I mean, she must know Alice Morgan..."
You know?
"How else would she know
all those details?"
Jonathan Black.
The toy owl.
Stacey Bell.
Right?
But then, the thing is...
No.
You don't know Alice Morgan.
You don't know Alice Morgan at all.
It's Jonathan you know.
Wasn't it?
Jonathan Black.
And Stacey Bell.
You know them because
you were in their class.
Now, which one's you?
Which one's Sara Roberts?
So you do remember?
To be fair, you've changed a lot.
Do you remember the promise you made me?
She said that she would kill me
if I told anyone.
And I did tell someone.
Because you said that I could trust you.
I know.
You promised.
- You did nothing.
- That's not true.
I was 10 years old.
Too petrified to sleep.
Do you know what happens to someone
when they don't sleep, to their mind?
Yeah.
- You do?
- Yeah.
Good.
Because it was your fault.
She lied.
So that's it?
All this woo-woo bullshit, that's it?
That's it? This is your way
of putting all of that right?
Because you're petrified,
still petrified of Stacey Bell.
Do you know what it's like
to be haunted?
Megan, that is just
your guilt talking, okay?
The dead are gone.
No.
The dead aren't even dead, John.
I'm arresting you.
I'm arresting you
on suspicion of perverting
the course of justice.
No, you're not.
Sorry?
You can't arrest me for anything.
Now, why is that, then?
Because I know what you're planning.
You and Alice Morgan.
What's that supposed to mean?
Conspiring to sell uncut diamonds.
Running away with a wanted killer.
What would happen to you, I wonder,
if I were to tell?
Megan, did you break into my house?
Did you take something from me?
Like what?
A phone.
How long have you been listening
to me and Alice?
Long enough.
Long enough to know
what happened to her?
Was Alice talking to someone
I didn't know about?
Someone that...
Someone that could hurt her.
Megan?
I need to know.
Of course you need to know.
It would be inhuman not to.
I'll make good on my promise.
I make good on my promise to you,
and you help me out.
All right?
One step at a time, John.
I need to go.
Boss, we're in.
This is some guy, huh?
Right, what we got?
Steven Rose has been keeping tabs
on over 200 people.
We've been in contact
with as many as possible
and advised them accordingly.
Anything we can use to get ahead of him?
Oh, no contingency plans as such,
but there's a data list of bolt-holes.
Places all over London
he could hide out in.
Abandoned homes,
schools, swimming pools.
The problem is that
there are hundreds of them
spread over 600 square miles
of Greater London.
DS Lane, what'd you get?
He lives alone.
Has done for about seven or eight years.
Few girlfriends, nothing serious.
Not since a girl called Katherine.
- Katherine who?
- Meadows.
She and Steven were students together.
Prototypical first love thing.
Back when summers were endless
and whatnot.
She's long since married.
She's now Katherine Woodward.
Other than that, no flatmates,
no hobbies, no real friends.
No life.
This, uh... Katherine,
she's definitely not on the list?
Not listed, sir.
There's no Katherines on the list.
Kates, Katies?
Nope, she's not there.
Well, we need to talk to her.
- Has she got an address?
- Uh, yeah.
Police warn that
Steven Rose should be considered
extremely dangerous.
Members of the public
should not approach him,
but should immediately
contact the police.
Police are also appealing to anybody...
Hannah? Get the doorbell, please.
Owen, get the door.
Sorry, who died
and made you God?
Sorry, can't. Too busy having a life.
Can you get
your arse off the sofa?
- Door.
- Mmm.
These are live pictures
coming to us now...
of the urgent man-hunt
that is ongoing across the capital
for Steven Rose.
We will be updating you
as we get the information.
As you can see, there's been lots of...
Katie, did you call this lot?
Police helicopters
are overhead.
This is a full-scale operation.
Steven.
And I would like to repeat,
police have warned
Steven Rose should be considered
extremely dangerous.
No, no!
Woodwards are gone. He's gone.
Benny, I need you to go
through that list of bolt-holes.
Isolate a two-mile radius
from this point.
On its way, boss.
Red lights are
properties on the database.
If he wanted to kill her...
He would have just killed her here.
The fact that he's taken her away...
It tells me that he needs time.
To do what?
I think the thing of it is that
he's come back to get what he's lost.
With her husband, her kids?
How does that fit?
Katie loves them.
All right? And that's what Steven does.
He takes from others
what he hasn't got.
What's your knowledge of
crime-to-journey stats?
Uh, stats say that the...
Uh, the less familiar an offender
is with a given area,
the closer to home
he'll commit his crime.
Exactly.
That puts Steven within
a mile and a half of us.
Yeah.
Yeah... That's Benny.
I told him to send you
a list of those bolt-holes.
Okay.
Okay, so...
So, what, we isolate the properties
that fall inside that radius?
Yeah.
Looking for what?
Vacant houses for let, for sale?
No, too risky.
We know he needs time, right?
Renovations?
No, it's the same problem, isn't it?
Um...
Well, says here
he went on to the hospital.
Yeah. Okay.
Um, okay, so what do we do?
Well, we should call in armed response.
Yeah, we should do that.
Except last time you did that,
he got away.
So what do we do?
We do it right.
Good answer.
Please.
Don't.
Steven, please don't.
I want you back.
Oh, my God. Oh, my God.
Hey. Wait.
Emma.
Are you Owen Woodward?
Are you hurt?
- Where is he?
- He's...
Who else is he with?
My family.
Okay.
Okay, you need to get up. Okay?
It's going to be okay.
Quietly. It's going to be okay.
Whoa, whoa, whoa, Steven, Steven, stop!
Stop, just stop! Just stop.
Stop. Stop.
You've lost her, mate, okay? She's gone.
She's gone.
All right, but this thing that
you're feeling. This...
Thing, it's in your head.
It's a physical thing, you know?
It can be put right.
I died.
No, no. The dead don't come back. Okay?
Now, we think they do.
But, but they don't.
Steven...
Don't. Stop, stop!
Emma.
- Put it down.
- Mmm.
Put it down.
Gotta talk about that gun.
Yeah, I should have told you I took it.
Yeah, you should have.
You found it, all right?
It was Steven's gun and you found it.
It'll be all right.
It was a good shooting.
Hey, Ben.
Good work, Dirty Harriet.
Boss, can I have a word?
Yeah.
So, about that other thing...
I had them nosy around
Megan Cantor's financials.
Now, there's nothing massively
out of the ordinary.
But there is something,
it might be nothing.
No, everything's something.
Well, she does pay rental
on a safe deposit box.
Nice hat.
Nice coat.
Very sensible.
We find ourselves in a pickle.
We are! We're in a pickle.
What if I found a way to fix it?
For you to save some face
and make some money.
Quite a bit of money.
Well, as it happens,
I often find that money
has an elevating effect
on my frame of mind.
There.
That's what you wanted. That's what
you tried to steal from Alice.
Well...
Seems a bit unseemly
when you put it like that.
But, yeah, that's the gist of it.
Where'd you find it, by the way?
Inside her body, were they?
What, did she swallow them?
Do you want them or what?
Oh, are you being serious now?
You do know
what this lot is worth.
Yeah.
Enough to start a new life.
That's not gonna happen now, is it?
What am I gonna buy with these?
Shame she died.
You ever find out who did it?
Look, you've got your money now.
What are the chances
of you doing me a favour?
Here we go, then.
What'd you want?
Cocaine, heroin, pills.
Whatever's lying about.
Well, that's an unusual request.
I mean, given the day job.
It's been an unusual
couple of days, George.
Yeah.
And where did you come across
this information?
A tip.
From?
A source.
And this puts it to bed?
For good?
Yeah.
And will there be anything else?
No, boss. Thank you.
Get off of me!
Ow!
They'll do her
for intent to supply
and then they'll upgrade to murder
when they connect the toy to Jonathan.
Do you feel better, putting it right?
Did you hurt her?
Who?
Alice.
Did you?
Why would I?
‘Cause you wanted me to keep my promise.
Or just stop me from leaving.
Mmm.
It could be that.
Or perhaps, it could be
that Alice Morgan
was your blind spot.
You didn't love her.
Not really.
She frightened you.
And she excited you.
And you mistook that for love.
But you would have killed her eventually
if she didn't kill you first.
Perhaps that's why I did it.
But I didn't.
Megan...
Are you scared of me?
Clearly not.
Well, you should be,
‘cause I'm coming for you.
:::::: www.hiqve.com ::::::