‐ My God,
do you have fleas?
What's going on?
‐ No idea what you're
talking about.
‐
He's out of cigarettes.
That's why he's bugging out.
Kid has a serious
nicotine addiction.
‐ No, I do not.
‐ If you need to smoke that
bad, you know who has them.
‐ No, nope.
Not talking to her.
Plus, she's pissed at me.
Look, fellas, I am good.
I bet she'd bum a few
to Pudgie.
Least she could do
after stomping on his heart.
‐ No way.
I'm not talking to her either.
If you haven't noticed,
I'm not even saying her name.
Plus, I'm not the one
with a cigarette addiction.
‐ Neither am I.
Hey, wake up!
Wake up, God damn it!
Where's the stash?
Don't hold out on me!
‐ You are unravelling rapidly.
‐ I am watching you.
Where's it at?
You're supposed to be
my friend.
Not happening to me.
All these highlighters!
I want to apologize
for my behavior.
I'm not proud
of the way I acted
and I am ready to seek the help
I so desperately need.
‐ So you've decided
to ask Alaska for cigarettes?
Never.
‐ I thought we agreed that
we weren't gonna use her name?
‐ I tried to do this
cold turkey
and I am, admittedly,
too weak,
so we pool our resources
together and go to Coosa's.
‐ How is that gonna work?
You need to be 18
and you don't have an ID.
- ‐ But you do.
- It's never worked.
You never tried.
Because it will
never work.
‐ Lara might have an ID.
She's sweet and kind
and she was into me.
"Was."
Operative word, there.
Maybe find another girl
and leave Lara alone.
Already puked on her.
Isn't that enough?
Who cares
about Pudge's love life
when my lungs are burning
from all this fresh air?
Okay, fine.
We'll make a Coosa's run
ourselves.
We don't need
she who will not be named.
♪ ♪
Three packs
of Hurricane Lights.
‐ You got ID?
‐ This is Alabama.
There's white
and everything else.
♪ ♪
We good?
Pay the man, Mohammed.
Not even close.
To be honest, it's so bad
it just bummed me out.
You kids can either
buy yourselves some Twinkies
or get the hell out
of my store.
‐ Can't believe
you paid 50 bucks
for that piece of shit.
- My Jesus.
- She knows us well.
‐ If they're from Alaska,
shouldn't we just
leave them here in protest?
‐ And what?
Let the next guy
who comes along
reap the only benefits
of a shitty
ex‐friend's remorse?
‐ Might also be
our last, best chance
to save the Colonel.
By killing him slowly
one puff at a time.
‐ I'm good with that.
‐ Shit.
‐ That pleasurable experience
last exactly zero seconds.
‐ It's the assholes
we were looking for.
‐ What'd you guys buy,
some cheese?
To feed the rat.
What's your point, Kev?
Do you see Alaska here?
‐ Rumor has it that
some of y'all fed the rat
on Thanksgiving.
Spent the whole week
with her, too.
‐ That was a mistake.
One that won't be repeated.
‐ Well, if you want
to stay safe,
just stay away from her.
‐ No problem.
Well,
consider yourself warned.
Alaska Young's gonna get
what she deserves.
♪ ♪
Don't plan
on sitting here.
No rats.
There's Alaska.
Fucking shitbirds.
I almost feel bad for her.
‐ Whatever they got planned,
you know it's gonna be brutal.
Stupid, but brutal.
It's not like
we can do anything.
Agreed to ice her out, right?
‐ Maybe we could tip her off?
I mean, not stop what's
going downhill, obviously,
but let her know
something big is gonna happen.
‐ Maybe an anonymous note.
‐ Okay.
I had mentally decided
not to be a part
of this conversation,
but based on the direction
that it's going in,
I have to interject.
Alaska would be the first
to tell us
that's just reinforcing
the patriarchy
and that she can
take care of herself,
so let her.
Why is his arm
around her?
‐ Shit.
I was hoping it wasn't true.
I may have heard a rumor.
‐ And you didn't say nothing?
It wasn't substantiated.
‐ Plus, you guys broke up.
All right, everybody.
Eyes and ears on me.
Thank you, we're going
to get started.
I hope everybody
enjoyed themselves
over the Thanksgiving holiday.
Who's ready
to end the semester strong?
All right,
we have a few things
that we need to get to.
College applications
need to be emailed
by the end of next week,
so proofread those essays
before hitting "send."
Thank you.
And also,
as a reminder,
most of these applications
require a teacher's
recommendation
and I am available.
So, I, believe
that Ms. Moser‐‐
Ms. Moser‐‐
Holly has an announcement.
All right, welcome, Holly.
‐ Whoo!
Reminder,
Culver Creek:
the Winter Dance
is almost here.
Who wants to know
this year's theme?
Drumroll, please.
This year's theme is...
ugly Christmas sweaters!
Buy your tickets now.
All right, great.
Thank you, Holly.
- Thank you.
- ‐
‐ What, are they suddenly
Siamese twins
joined at the fucking hip?
‐ Look, she wants to dance.
I love to dance.
‐ That can't be true.
‐ And terrifying to imagine.
‐ Okay, fine, I don't dance.
But I'm willing to try for her.
‐ You should
think about it first.
No need to rush into anything.
‐ I'm not rushing,
I'm realizing.
I've been chasing after Alaska,
and maybe this whole time
the girl I was supposed
to be with
was right in front of me.
Maybe everything
that's happened
has led me to this moment.
To this dance.
‐ This should go well.
‐ One, please.
Um, allow me.
- ‐ Two tickets, please.
- What?
Miles,
you're cutting the line.
No, I'm not cutting.
- I'm paying for you...
- Come on!
‐ And for me,
so we can go together.
‐ You do this
without asking me first?
‐ Sorry, how many
and who's paying?
Um, one.
I'm sorry, Miles.
I just want to dance
with my friends
and study for my exams.
It is all the stress
I can handle.
‐ I'd like one, too.
I don't deserve to go
with you now, Lara.
I understand that.
But I hope that
by the night of the dance
I've won your trust
and you've changed your mind.
Prepare to be swept
off your feet.
If you're buying
for yourself,
you need to go
to the back of the line.
Right, yeah.
No, of course.
Sorry.
♪ ♪
Hey, Hyde.
How's it hanging?
Just enjoying
some fresh air.
And quiet.
‐ Yeah, well, this wasn't
my first choice either,
but I'm afraid
you're all I have left.
Finally, the kids
at this school
can agree on something.
They all hate me.
‐ Nice to know
I represent rock bottom.
‐ I fucked up.
Like I always do.
So...
now I'm all alone.
In hell.
So...
can I please
just sit here with you
and not be alone...
for as long as it takes
to finish my sandwich?
‐ Do you know why I'm drawn
to Buddhism, Ms. Young?
‐ ‐
‐ They don't believe in hell.
Or heaven, for that matter.
People don't have
eternal souls.
Instead, they are
a bundle of energy
reincarnating endlessly
until it eventually reaches...
enlightenment.
♪ ♪
Meaning, as painful as this is,
it will change.
♪ ♪
‐ I fucking love you, Hyde.
All right, Melville,
let's finally do this shit.
♪ ♪
‐ Stop staring.
Don't flatter yourself.
Your snoring is keeping me up.
I'm not snoring,
I'm reading.
Did you know
that during World War II,
Romania fought for both sides‐‐
‐ Fine, it's your breathing.
‐ I'm barely breathing.
Exactly, I keep feeling
compelled to check
and make sure
you're still alive.
It's very disconcerting.
‐ Are you sure that this
concern for my wellbeing
doesn't have to do
with anything else?
‐ Like what?
‐ Like guilt?
Knowing the Weekday Warriors
are planning to do something
and not doing
anything about it‐‐
‐ What is there to do?
I mean, you said it
yourself, Pudge.
Alaska Young is fully capable
of taking care of herself.
Plus, she started all this,
so whatever happens,
it's on her.
You know what,
I'm sick of arguing.
It's stuffy in here.
I need some air.
♪ ♪
‐
No, no, no, no!
♪ ♪
Not Márquez.
Motherfuckers!
♪ ♪
Alaska?
Move!
Pudge.
Man, relax.
Ain't nobody trying
to look at your little wiener.
It's about Alaska.
You ain't gon' believe
what they did.
‐ I told you,
I don't want to know.
‐ It's bad.
It's worse than I ever seen.
This is too damn far.
What'd I tell you?
Her Life's Library.
We can't let this shit
go unavenged.
If we do this,
we're letting her off the hook
for all of it.
‐ We don't have a choice.
Weekday Warriors
made sure of that.
Right, Pudge?
♪ ♪
‐ This is awful...
But I didn't cause it,
and so I can't be a part
of fixing it.
Sorry.
Man, screw him.
We got all the firepower
we need right here.
That's right,
the OG three.
Culver Creek's
original pranksters.
‐ We're about to pull off
the most epic prank
the Creek has ever seen.
‐ What did you have in mind?
♪ We get high
in back seats ♪
So we flash
a flashlight...
- ♪- ♪ We break into mobile homes ♪
♪ We go to sleep
to "Shake Appeal" ♪
♪ Never wake up on our own ♪
♪ That's the way
we get by ♪
♪ All that's the way
♪ To way we get by ♪
♪ ♪
♪ We go out in stormy weather ♪
♪ We rarely practice discern ♪
♪ We make love
to "Some Weird Sin" ♪
♪ We seek out the taciturn ♪
♪ That's the way we get by ♪
♪ To way we get by ♪
♪ ♪
I know you're stressed
about midterms.
Maybe this will help you.
It's the Miles Halter
Study Guide Starter Pack.
Still working on the branding.
It's got sharpened pencils,
No Doz, study snacks.
♪ ♪
♪ And that's the way
we get by ♪
♪ That's the way we get by ♪
♪ ♪
Hi.
‐ Hi.
Well, if that's it‐‐
‐ No, wait, um...
I had this whole plan.
I was gonna cook you
a romantic Romanian meal.
Um, I even did some research
as to what that would entail.
Apparently that would entail
an oven, which I do not have,
so I went to Maureen
in the cafeteria
to see if she would
maybe help me out
but she just laughed
in my face.
But she did give me
something much better
than Romanian cooking lessons.
‐
But it's not bufriedo day.
‐ You might wanna look
a little, closer
at the wrapper.
♪ ♪
‐ How could I say no?
‐ Okay.
‐
Okay, great.
I'll see you at the dance.
‐ Hello, Mr. Starnes.
‐ Good afternoon.
Just here to sign out
for a couple days.
Taking these rascals
home with me
to the trailer park
this weekend.
‐ That so?
‐ Yeah, Takumi here
just felt left out
when he heard about
Dolores' homemade pies
over Thanksgiving.
‐ Well, that makes two of us.
I just need to call your mother
and make sure she knows
you're on your way.
‐ Yeah, yeah, of course.
Sure.
It's like he barely lives here.
Apparently
his wife left him.
She's just waiting for him
to sign the divorce papers.
I have very good
sourcing on this.
‐ Poor man.
I just hope my mom plays along.
‐
- Hello?
- Hello, Mrs. Martin?
This is Dean Starnes calling.
‐ Okay, so what did he do now?
‐ No, ma'am.
No, Chip's not in any trouble.
Well, yet.
He tells me he's spending
the weekend at home
and bringing Mr. Hikohito
and Ms. Young with him.
Alaska?
That's just wonderful.
‐ Is it?
You sound surprised.
That son of mine,
he listens to his mama
more than he lets on.
Tell him that
dinner is in the oven
and I'll be expecting them.
Okay, thanks.
Lovely woman, your mother.
Although, it's too bad
you'll be missing the dance.
I for one have been
dusting off
some of my classic moves.
‐ You never go to the dances.
‐ No, true.
Historically,
I have avoided
school social functions,
but I find myself with an
excess of free time these days
and, I actually found
the perfect tie
when I was clearing out, um...
Well...
just in time
to shake things up.
I knew my moms
would come through.
Just hope she forgives me
when she finds out the truth.
Which is why
you need to call her.
‐ Yes‐‐or you could.
Women find you irresistible.
‐ Or we actually spend
the weekend at your mom's,
because from where
I'm standing,
this plan's a bust.
‐ Wait, wait, wait.
Wait. Wait. What do you mean?
‐ Did you not hear the man?
The Eagle is gonna be
at the dance,
and that was not
a part of the plan.
‐ Maybe this is
actually better.
I mean, everybody we need
to be worried about
will be under
one sad disco ball.
Could make things easier
for our lookout.
‐ We have a lookout?
‐ No.
No way.
Do you not see this ridiculous,
itchy sweater that I'm wearing?
‐ I literally couldn't
ignore it if I wanted to.
And trust me, Pudge,
I want to.
But what I'm about to ask you
is important.
‐ Yeah, so is my date
with Lara.
‐ I know.
You're completely over Alaska.
I'm almost buying it, but what
I'm about to ask of you
will not interfere
with your date.
If the Eagle, Longwell,
or Kevin leave the dance,
I just need you
to flash this little guy
into the computer lab twice.
Takumi will take it from there.
It's as simple as clicking
the on and off button.
‐ Yeah, you say that now,
but I know it's not gonna be
that simple‐‐
‐ Pudge, you're not
doing this for Alaska.
You wouldn't be saving her ass,
you'd be saving mine.
I'm doing this.
You know what I have
on the line
if this shit goes sideways.
♪ ♪
‐ Fine.
For you.
But don't tell Lara.
♪ Here's the thing,
we started off friends ♪
♪ It was cool
but it was all pretend ♪
♪ Yeah, yeah,
since you've been gone ♪
‐ Lee, I don't think
I've seen you at a dance
in all the years
I've worked here.
‐ To be honest, Brigid,
the thought of spending
another Friday night
in front of the Ghost Whisperer
made me want to put
a gun to my head.
For you, Lara.
How many cookies
do you think Lara's gonna eat?
‐ I just wanted
an assortment.
Choices.
Maybe later
we could play a game
and see how many cookies
we can eat at once.
‐ Sounds hot.
‐ ‐‐um, thank you.
♪ I'm so moving on ♪
‐ Yeah, I should
probably get back.
‐ You and Longwell.
‐ Yeah, what about it?
‐ It's just hard
imagining anyone measuring up
to the Colonel.
‐ You can tell your roommate
that I found someone
who doesn't feel the need
to punch the world
in the face, so.
♪ ♪
Bye.
‐ Would you like to dance?
‐ I probably
should have said this
before I spent the entire week
trying to get you to go
to this thing with me,
but, um...
I don't‐‐I don't dance.
‐...
okay.
♪ Yeah, yeah ♪
‐
‐ Gotta admit,
you pretty clever‐‐
for a rat.
‐ We are the most intelligent
of the rodents.
♪ ♪
♪ She like my
Dolce & Gabanna ♪
♪ I'm so cold ♪
‐
Very good.
‐ ‐
‐ That's very impressive.
Six, okay?
You ready?
♪ ♪
No.
‐
I‐‐I have a request.
♪ ♪
Why were you running?
‐ Um...
I was just, um‐‐
I wanted to request a song.
But then I‐‐I remembered
that I don't dance.
Um, can I have some
of that water?
‐
Yeah, okay.
‐ I have a reputation, sir.
I can't.
‐ Ms. Blowker, I don't want
to pull rank here, but I will.
I've made a request.
I'd like it honored.
Spin some wax.
‐ Fine.
- ‐ My request.
♪ ♪
‐ Do you want to Macarena?
It's a very simple dance.
And then poor Madame O'Malley
doesn't have
to humiliate herself.
‐ Um, yeah.
‐ Okay!
‐ Okay, why not?
♪ They all want me,
they can't have me ♪
♪ So they all come
and dance beside me ♪
♪ Move with me,
chant with me ♪
♪ And if you could
I'd take you home with me ♪
‐ You wanna get out of here?
Okay.
- ♪ Hey, Macarena ♪
- ♪ Hey ♪
♪ ♪
- ♪ Hey, Macarena ♪
- Hey!
‐ Um, Lara, I'll be right back.
I promise you,
I'll be right back.
♪ ♪
Hey.
Let's go back
to my room.
No, no,
I'm not getting caught
like Paul and Marya.
I know a better place.
♪ ♪
- ♪ Hey, Macarena ♪
- ♪ Hey! ♪
♪ ♪
- ♪ Hey, Macarena ♪
- ♪ Hey! ♪
There you are.
‐ I'm not the one
who keeps running off.
‐ I'm so sorry.
‐ Tell me the truth.
Did you really want
to bring me to this dance,
or is it just a cover
for whatever prank
you are clearly doing?
‐ I promise, Lara,
I really wanted to go with you
and I'm having
such a great time.
I just told Takumi
that I'd help him
with this one little
recon mission, and I did.
It's over...
and I'm really sorry.
‐ Next time, just tell me
the truth, okay?
♪ ♪
‐ I think I can
handle this one.
♪ ♪
Please.
♪ Hi up above
or down below ♪
♪ ♪
♪ When you're too in love
to let it go ♪
- ‐ Come with me.
- ‐
♪ ♪
♪ But if you never try,
you'll never know ♪
‐
‐ Am I doing this right?
‐ ‐
‐ Okay.
‐ Perfect.
♪ ♪
♪ Lights will
guide you home ♪
♪ And ignite ♪
‐ Wow.
- Sorry.
You're actually
a very good dancer.
‐ Yeah?
‐ ‐
‐ Cool.
The only other person
I've ever slow‐danced with
was, um, my grandma,
and even she said
I was no Fred Astaire.
‐
‐ We seem to be down
Mr. Chase and Ms. Harbart.
‐ Let them have their fun?
♪ ♪
‐ Okay, okay.
It's just...
Brigid, I've gone
two years in this job
without a teen pregnancy,
and it's not because
I let the kids have fun.
It's because I practice
eagle‐eyed vigilance.
‐...
♪ ♪
‐ You smell nice.
‐ Yeah.
You, too.
♪ Tears stream ♪
♪ Down your face ♪
♪ When you lose something ♪
‐ Shit, um, come with me.
Please.
This way.
‐
Can we go back
to the dance now?
Um...
We have to go
to Longwell's room.
I'll explain on the way.
‐ ‐‐
‐ I promise.
In my experience,
they usually try to go
to the girls' dorm first.
Could‐‐could you
slow down just a little?
These shoes are a bit hard
to walk in.
Yeah.
Sorry, sorry.
Well, I mean,
they are teenagers, Brigid,
so we don't have a lot of time.
Come on, Sara's dorm
is right down here.
‐ "One challenge I had
was during a debutante ball.
"I was about to escort my date
to the dance floor
"when I heard a gurgle emanate
from my belly.
"I thought it was indigestion
from too many protein shakes,
"but it was not.
"It was diarrhea.
‐ Okay, I learned that, A,
humans have the capacity
to make much more diarrhea
than you think,
B, diarrhea stains permanently,
and C, diarrhea has
a silent "h."
‐ "This is why I believe
Dookie University"...
‐ "Dookie."
‐ "Would be the perfect fit
for me and my large colon."
‐ That's brilliant.
What you doing here?
‐ Our lookout sent me
on a decoy mission
but Longwell and Sara
weren't headed
to the dorms after all,
so I thought I'd stop by
and see how things are going.
‐ Sara?
Where'd she go?
The woods.
‐ Like the old campfire spot?
I don't know, maybe.
‐ Dude, that is Colonel
and Sara's preferred location
for illicit activities
of a sexual nature.
‐ Shit.
‐ That's our fucking
spot, literally.
Takumi, take over the essay.
‐ No, no, he needs to go back.
This isn't the plan.
‐ That's our spot!
‐ Chip can be a real romantic
when he wants to be.
Where's he going?
‐ Um...
Ignore him, no time.
Eagle...
Eagle.
‐ Breathe, Pudge, breathe.
‐ The Eagle is on his way.
He is in Sara's room,
but then he is coming here.
The application doesn't
allow us to hit send
until it's fully finished,
and we still have
two more essay questions.
You know
that sign that says,
"Break glass
in case of emergency"?
I'm that glass,
but I require assistance.
Miles?
‐ Fine.
‐ Thanks, Pudge.
All right,
first thing's first.
Pudge, lose that sweater.
It's not stealthy.
We'll divert the Eagle
while you two write.
Rendezvous at the barn
when we're done.
‐ Lock the door.
Maybe they went back
to the dance.
‐ I appreciate
that optimism, Brigid,
but I could smell
the pheromones
coming off those two
at the gym.
We gotta go
to Longwell's room.
‐ You know, I think
I'll just head back.
‐ Damn it.
I'm doing it again.
I'm putting the job
before everything else.
This is exactly
what Lois accused me of.
Hey, no.
I meant because someone needs
to chaperone the dance.
‐ Yeah.
No, of course.
Right, yeah.
‐ Thank you.
You know, for my Macarena.
‐ Yeah.
Yeah, no, you're welcome.
Yeah.
♪ ♪
♪ When I dance
they call me Macarena ♪
♪ And the boys say ♪
♪ They all want me ♪
What are you doing?
‐ I was a goddamn Boy Scout,
Pudge, so I'm always prepared.
What the hell is that?
‐ It's my fox hat.
‐ Why are you wearing
your fox hat?
‐ 'Cause no one can catch
the motherfucking fox.
Light it.
♪ Hey, Macarena ♪
‐ Now, run!
Mr. Chase, Ms. Harbart.
I'm coming in.
♪ ♪
What the hell?
♪ Hey, Macarena ♪
Stop, I will
call the police!
He's bluffing.
He's scared of bad publicity.
♪ Hey, Macarena ♪
‐ Done!
It is a literary masterpiece.
Forgive my bragging.
A sympathetic portrait
of living with
irritable bowel syndrome.
I have one more,
but I'm stuck.
‐ Hit me, sister.
‐ "Who is your role model
and why?"
‐ "Tom Cruise."
‐ Okay.
"He never ages,
he has a great run,
and he probably
never gets diarrhea."
‐ "He never gets diarrhea."
- Yes, we did it!
- Success.
Now hit send and let's
get the hell out of here.
How was the dance?
Was it all ugly sweaters
and warm punch?
‐ It was lame,
but we were having
a really good time.
Um, I like Miles,
and I think he likes me.
I am good for him.
Come on,
I'll buy you a drink.
I think we lost him.
We're back at the lake.
Slight error
in navigation, but no biggie.
We'll just get
to the barn lakeside.
All right.
♪ ♪
The fox is not a fan
of the swan.
Come on!
Run, Pudge!
Run for your life!
So I creep
into the woods
and I hear them arguing,
so I start
waving my flashlight around
and start clearing my throat
like I'm the Eagle,
and then I hear them,
like, whisper‐arguing.
Then, all of a sudden,
Longwell takes off
with his fucking pants
around his ankles.
‐ He just left Sara behind?
Yeah, she had
to walk all the way back
to the dance by herself.
If Longwell was scared
of the Eagle,
just wait till
Sara get through with him.
I just I hope I didn't ruin
my own brilliant plan.
‐ No, Operation
Tell Duke About the Dookie
was perfectly executed.
Lara, an essay‐writing machine,
Takumi, a diversionary genius.
- Did you hear those fireworks?
- Casualty!
We have a casualty!
‐ What happened?
Our hero's
left butt cheek
was dinner for the swan.
And there ain't much
meat on that scrawny thing.
Miles might get
an infection or‐‐or rabies.
Do swans carry rabies?
No, but he could
get the bird flu, though.
‐ Don't worry, the fox has
a first aid kit.
‐ Wait, don't you think
we should get a‐‐
a medical professional
in case of the rabies
or potential bird flu?
‐ Pudge, if you go
to the hospital,
we all get busted,
so quit being a baby,
pull down your pants,
and let me wipe your ass.
‐ Yeah.
All right,
now the antiseptic.
Here it comes.
It may sting.
‐
COLONEL: Aww, man!
Does it need stitches?
I can sew.
Well, crochet.
‐ Wait, my ass is not a quilt.
I don't think so,
but it does look gross.
‐ No, Lara, don't look!
That's not date appropriate!
Sorry, I did not
see anything, Miles.
Anesthesia.
I have anesthesia.
There we go, Pudge.
Nothing a little
Strawberry Hill can't fix.
‐
I knew that was good
for something.
♪ ♪
Um...
‐ Squeeze my hand?
Squeeze my hand
until the stinging stops.
Man, that swan
was really no joke.
Well, at least
you are not concussed.
Yeah.
No, it's okay.
I thought I could
take you to the hospital, but‐‐
‐
Attention.
We are gonna play a game.
It is called
"Best Day/Worst Day."
‐ I ain't ever heard
of no game like that before.
‐ That's because
I just made it up.
The rules are simple:
everyone tells their story.
Whoever has the best one
doesn't have to drink,
then we keep going
until one of y'all quits.
Well, how do you know
it's gonna be one of us?
‐ Well, I'm the best drinker
and the best storyteller.
Pudge.
You may begin.
‐ Um...
can I have a second to think?
‐ Can't be that good
if you gotta think about it.
- ‐ Today's my best day.
- Come on, man.
‐ No, seriously.
Seriously.
I...
went on a date with
a pretty Romanian girl.
I watched the Eagle
do the Macarena,
I shot off fireworks,
and I was almost eaten alive
by a feral swan.
But now I'm here...
With all of you.
It feels pretty magical.
‐
That is so corny.
‐ Yeah, it is corny
and my butt is bleeding
and I probably have
the bird flu,
but today is my best day.
‐ My best day...
I was eight years old.
My mom and I went to the zoo.
I liked the giraffes
and she liked the gorillas.
End of story.
Best day ever.
‐ What?
That is so lame.
‐ What's wrong with that?
- Yes.
- I liked it.
‐ Which is why
you get to go next.
‐ Okay, um...
my best day
is the day I won
the sixth grade spelling bee.
We had just moved here
and my parents
barely spoke English
but they helped me practice.
And then when I won
it was like...
the biggest deal.
They stood up
and clapped so loud.
And I loved that feeling.
Embarrassed...
But proud.
All right, I lose.
My best day
was when I lost my virginity.
Twice.
And if you think
I'm gonna tell you that story,
you gotta get me a whole lot
drunker than this, suckers.
‐ Well...
my best day
hasn't happened yet,
but I can see it.
That's gonna be the day
I buy my mom a house.
A big fucking house
right in the middle
of Mountain Brook
right next to the
Weekday Warriors' parents.
I'll drive her there
and I'll hand her the keys...
Just like they do on TV.
I'ma just be like...
"We home, Ma."
Man, that'd be
the best day of my life.
Okay, Colonel.
You won that round.
Now what's your worst day?
‐ My worst day...
was the day my dad left.
I just...
Kept waiting for him to call
and explain it.
But he never did.
I don't know, I...
thought he might have wanted
to say good‐bye.
‐ Well, you got me beat.
I was 11‐‐...
and my mom made me sign up
for a soccer team,
but I sucked.
Like, I was really bad.
I was always riding the bench.
But then, this one game,
the coach put me in
for some reason
and I was so excited.
But I‐‐I didn't realize
that, um...
we switched sides
at‐‐at halftime.
Shit, Pudge,
you scored for the wrong team.
- ‐ Yeah.
The worst part
was, the bus ride home.
Sitting with all these kids
who hated me.
‐ So glad you were able
to put your life back together.
My worst day is,
June 9, 1999.
My grandmother died
in a car accident in Japan.
I was supposed to visit her
two days later,
spend the whole summer
with her.
The only time
I ever got to see her
was before she was cremated.
Damn.
We are a sad group of friends.
Minus you, Pudge.
‐ Thanks.
‐ Lara?
‐ Um...
My worst day
is the day we left Romania.
It wasn't until the day before
that my parents told me
I wasn't allowed
to bring Rukmina, my dog.
For six years she had been
my best friend
and I had to leave her
with strangers.
- ‐ Fucking dog stories.
They get me
every time.
All right.
It's your turn, buddy.
‐ The day after
my mom took me to the zoo,
I was upstairs
doing my homework...
When I heard a scream
from the kitchen.
And I ran downstairs and...
saw my mom lying on the floor
holding her head, jerking.
I freaked out.
I should have called 911
but all I did
was just scream and cry...
until she stopped jerking.
I thought she was just asleep.
♪ ♪
And that...
whatever had hurt her
didn't anymore,
so I sat down next to her...
until my dad came home
an hour later.
And he started yelling at me,
"Why didn't you call 911?"
And he tried to do CPR
but by then she was‐‐
she was plenty dead.
♪ ♪
Aneurysm.
Worst day.
I won, you drink.
♪ ♪
‐ Your dad blamed you?
‐ How could he not?
You were a kid.
‐ Kids can dial 911.
They do it all the time.
I just didn't.
♪ ♪
‐ Why didn't you tell me?
‐ It never came up.
♪ ♪
I need some air.
‐ Someone should go
be with her.
♪ ♪
‐
You wanted to know
why I ratted.
♪ ♪
And why I can't go home.
Well, now you know.
♪ ♪
Because I fuck everything up.
‐ That's not true.
You were just a little kid.
♪ ♪
Nothing's your fault
when you're a little kid.
That's what it means
to be a kid.
‐ I was afraid
of what you'd think
when you knew the truth.
Well, now you know.
♪ ♪
You're still here.
Why are you still here?
♪ ♪
- ‐ Because...
- ‐
♪ ♪
‐ I'm your friend.
‐ Cool.
"Friend."
♪ ♪
♪ People ♪
♪ They don't mean
a thing to you ♪
♪ They move right through you ♪
♪ Just like your breath ♪
♪ But sometimes ♪
You came back.
‐ Yeah.
Is that okay?
‐ Yeah, it's okay.
♪ ♪
Hi.
Can I kiss you?
Yes.
You can kiss me.
♪ I forget
I'm still awake ♪
‐
♪ I fuck up ♪
♪ And say these things
out loud ♪
♪ My old friend ♪
♪ ♪
♪ I swear I never meant for this ♪
Extracted from MKV & Synchronized By X Person
♪ Don't look at me that way ♪
♪ ♪
Extracted from MKV & Synchronized By X Person
♪ It was an honest mistake ♪
♪ ♪
♪ Don't look at me that way ♪
♪ It was an honest mistake ♪
♪ An honest mistake ♪
♪ ♪
♪ Never meant, never meant ♪
♪ I swear,
I never meant ♪
♪ An honest ♪
♪ An honest mistake ♪
♪ Don't look at me that way ♪
♪ ♪
♪ It was an honest mistake ♪
♪ Don't look at me that way ♪
♪ An honest mistake ♪