Extracted from MKV & Synchronized By X Person
Miles.
Miles?
Wake up, Pudge!
Morning.
‐
Gotta get a lock on the door.
Everyone but Alaska
can have a key.
I have the key
to your heart, Colonel.
That's all that matters.
That was so loud,
it hurt my feelings.
‐ You always sleep
in your clothes?
Pudge has PTSD.
He's afraid he might
get kidnapped
in his tighty‐whities again.
‐ I thought he looked cute.
You're crazier than I thought.
‐ That was a terrible way
to wake up.
How can I ensure that
that never happens again?
‐ Nothing you can do.
♪ ♪
♪ Right, wrong, what to do ♪
♪ Someday it will come ♪
‐ Did I miss an assignment?
‐ Don't worry about it.
♪ Hostile Indians ♪
♪ We named a summer camp
for you ♪
♪ ♪
‐ Don't worry about it.
‐ Didn't say a word.
‐ Fine.
If you must know,
Sara's debutante ball
is coming up,
and it's kind of a big deal
at this fancy country club.
I'm writing term papers
to pay for a new suit.
I left my Armani at home.
There.
Happy?
‐ I've never tried
grits before.
‐ They should just serve
bufriedos 24/7.
‐ Quickest way to ruin
a good thing.
‐ I object.
If something is so good,
how could you ever get enough?
Probably a better question
for Jake.
‐ Apparently Alaska's boyfriend
is a real sexual dynamo.
‐ You know that would be
complete bufried‐ification,
right?
The girls here would balloon
up to, like, 300 pounds.
So what if they did?
They suddenly wouldn't meet
your sexist adolescent fantasy
of what's an acceptable
female form?
Big is beautiful, Colonel.
‐ Small is appealing as well.
‐ Not when it says shit
like that.
That's my girlfriend.
Chip.
Longwell and Kevin
have something
they'd like to say to you.
Don't you, guys?
‐ Look, Colonel, you ratted out
Paul and Marya.
We retaliated.
‐ We're even now, so truce?
‐ Take it back.
I'm not the rat.
‐ You wanna say that
to my face,
'cause you're talking
to my sternum.
‐ Closer to your heart
when I rip it out.
‐ My God.
You are both so stupid
and so is this war.
Enough, okay?
‐ I'll make you a deal.
You pick one dead
American president.
If Pudge here doesn't know
his last words, truce.
If he does, you spend the rest
of your life lamenting the day
y'all pissed in my shoes.
‐ That's the dumbest thing
I've ever heard.
‐ Your best friend is Kevin.
I doubt it.
Those are the terms,
otherwise, nuts to your truce.
‐ If you even can name
a president.
‐
I summer interned
at the Cater Center
sophomore year.
Jimmy and Rosalynn have
actually
been to my house for dinner.
They ever been to
your trailer park, Colonel?
‐ The only Carter I acknowledge
is Shawn.
In or out?
‐ Fine.
Whatever.
‐ Don't blow this, Pudge.
‐ He won't.
All right.
Millard Fillmore.
‐ Shit.
Was that guy even president?
♪ ♪
‐ Um...when, um,
former president
Millard Fillmore was dying...
He was‐‐he was really hungry,
but his doctor was trying
to starve the fever.
Fillmore wouldn't shut up
about food,
so the doctor gave him
a tiny tablespoon of soup.
And all sarcastic,
Fillmore said,
"The nourishment is palatable,"
and then he died.
No truce.
‐!
Why would you try and drown
this man?
He's a goddamn genius.
Yeah!
‐
‐ Pudge, that was your first
truly badass moment.
When this war is over,
there may not be any survivors.
Goddamn, this is gonna be good.
‐
♪ I've got nothing to hide ♪
♪ I wish I wasn't so shy ♪
‐
Um, how did you do that,
knowing the last words
of dead people?
‐ Um...
I guess I just used to have
a lot of free time.
I mean,
Fillmore was pretty easy.
I'm just glad he didn't pick
Franklin Pierce.
No one knows his last words.
How come?
‐ I guess he died alone.
‐ That's sad.
We are all interconnected.
It's the true nature
of all beings.
At least, that's what
the Buddhists believe.
You, me,
his Holiness the Dalai Lama...
we all exist only in connection
to those around us.
Buddhists see the world
as an intricate web
of relationships to others.
They create communities
of practitioners
called sanghas,
who work collectively to attain
peace, happiness, and wisdom.
The only way to realize
true awakening...
♪ ♪
Mr. Halter.
The hope is that this class
will be your sangha,
bringing you enlightenment,
though apparently not today.
And here I am straining
my one remaining lung
for your edification,
and you've found
something outside
that captures your fancy
even more.
What have you discovered
out there?
‐
I was, um...
looking at the‐‐the trees
and‐‐and the‐‐the forest,
and I was just thinking
about how it's all connected.
You said‐‐sorry, I'm...
‐ I'm going to ask you
to leave the class, Mr. Halter,
so you can go out there
and discover
the relationship between
the "um, trees"
and the "forest."
‐ Wait...
you're kicking me out?
‐ Good‐bye.
‐ This has never
happened before.
‐ Pudge, those better not
be tears I see.
‐ Shit is looking moist.
‐ I'm sorry,
but that's bullshit.
You can't just throw him
out of class.
You drone on and on
every day,
and we can't even glance out
the window?
‐ Now you both may leave.
Now, to continue,
the only way to realize
true awakening
is by living in a way
that emphasizes
our connections
and relationships to others.
♪ ♪
‐ Oldest trick in the book,
but everybody falls for it.
Aww.
Let me guess.
Before today,
all your teachers were
card‐carrying members
of the Miles Halter fan club.
‐ Well, I never made cards,
but yeah.
‐ I need a smoke.
And then,
so his last words were:
"I go to seek a Great Perhaps."
‐ He was a French poet?
Any good?
‐ I never read him,
just his biography‐‐
well, the end of it.
‐ "Great Perhaps."
I like it.
It's just ambiguous enough,
unquantifiable.
Kind of magical,
hell of a metaphor.
It's also a pretentious way
of saying you wanna get laid,
but I don't need a dead
French poet to tell me that.
You know what your problem is?
‐
‐ You claim you want
this Great Perhaps,
but you're still afraid
to upset
your teachers and parents.
‐ Some might say
that's a good quality.
‐ Life's about disappointing
those in charge of us.
I learned that a long time ago.
Well, look who decided
to show up.
Thanks so much for the support
back there.
‐ You're never gonna win
by crossing Hyde.
He'll eat you alive
and piss you out slowly
through a catheter.
‐ I have no quarrel
with the old bastard.
He never accused me
of being a rat,
but those that have must pay.
We need a preemptive strike.
First, fast, hard.
Pudge, if you wanna walk away,
now's the time.
‐ What?
Why would I do that?
‐ You're still an innocent.
‐ Shit's about to get real.
‐ Hell of a lot realer
than getting kicked out
of some dumbass class.
‐ They don't think
you're ready.
I was afraid of that.
We're trying to protect you.
If you get caught,
you're on your own.
‐ Look, we do this
because we hate
what the Weekday Warriors
stand for.
We'll risk everything
to beat 'em.
‐ What are you willing to risk?
♪ ♪
‐ Seriously?
What about my life?
You remember how I was thrown
in the lake,
or did you forget about that?
And did you know
that the Weekday Warriors tried
to recruit me
in fucking Mandarin?
That's right, I could be
living the Weekday Warrior life
right now, but I said no.
Because I'm a part of this
sangha, whatever it's called.
I'm with you all until the end.
‐ Sounds good to me.
‐ Pretty damn convincing.
‐ You're in, Pudge.
‐ Was that a test?
‐ Everything's a test here.
‐ And you passed.
Your dead French poet
would be proud.
Free for a study date
after school?
I'll drive.
♪ I don't know
what you heard about me ♪
♪ But a bitch can't get
a dollar out of me ♪
♪ No Cadillac, no perms,
you can't see ♪
♪ That I'm a motherfucking
P‐I‐M‐P ♪
♪ I don't know
what you heard about me ♪
♪ But a bitch can't get
a dollar out of me ♪
♪ No Cadillac, no perms,
you can't see ♪
♪ That I'm a motherfucking
P‐I‐M‐P ♪
♪ I don't know what ♪
‐ What the hell is that smell?
‐ It's my dad's cologne.
He said to use it
for special occasions.
Do you think it's too much?
It's me, Chip.
I hope I'm not interrupting
you two
jerking each other off.
‐ Hey, Sara.
Nice to see you again.
‐ We need to talk.
Alone.
What the hell is that smell?
‐ Pudge has a special occasion.
‐ Which I should be off to.
Gonna try to air out
on the way.
Bye.
‐ Are you writing term papers
for money?
‐ How could you accuse me
of such a thing?
‐ Chip, do you know how much
trouble you could get into?
‐ It's fine.
I've been trading all of
my superior intellect for cash,
but only to assist
the dumbest among us.
‐ You wanna be the next one
to get expelled?
‐
Your debutante ball
is coming up,
and I gotta look sharp
when I'm walking across
that stage as your escort.
‐ As what?
‐ The debutante's date
is called an escort.
Did a little research.
‐ Chip... no.
No, shit, listen.
You're not gonna be my escort.
‐
What do you mean?
I'm your boyfriend.
Yeah, but that's
now how it works, Chip.
In order to be an escort,
your family needs to be
a member of the country club.
Longwell's my escort.
It's all been arranged, and...
‐ What?
‐ Y‐y‐you know
he and I grew up together.
‐ Why did you even invite me?
‐ Because, Chip,
it's important to me.
You're important to me.
And I'm sorry,
but these things,
they have rules
and regulations.
‐ I get it.
I've been getting it
my whole life.
‐ So that's it?
That's it?
You're just not gonna go?
- ‐ Is that what you want?
- No, asshole.
It's not what I want.
If it was, I just would have
never invited you.
‐ Of course I'm coming.
It's a big deal for you.
I wouldn't miss it.
‐ Thank you for understanding.
‐ Plus, there are
certain privileges I have
that Longwell never will.
Seriously?
We have one nice moment,
and you're using it to try
and get some action?
Oof.
♪ Go, go, go ♪
♪ ♪
‐ Hey, Pudge.
Jump in.
There's no seat belt
for you there,
'cause Lara's there.
Lara, Miles.
Miles, Lara.
You two remember each other,
right?
Hi.
Do you mind sitting on his lap?
- He can be your seat belt.
- If he doesn't mind.
He doesn't.
‐ I don't.
Okay.
Kids, meet Blue Citrus.
So named 'cause she's a lemon.
Jesus and Takumi
are my copilots.
It's an honor, ma'am.
‐
Shit.
Sorry, keys just digging
into my leg.
Here we go.
‐ Okay.
‐
Are you from Florida?
‐ Yeah.
‐
‐ You're from‐‐
um, you're from Russia.
‐ Romania.
Right, of course.
♪ What game is it ♪
‐
So, Pudge,
you know that girl
from the pre‐calc study session
last night, Lara?
Soft voice, says "thees,"
not "this"?
‐ Yeah, she sat on my lap
in the car.
‐ Yes, my idea, which paid off,
because she liked you.
You thought
she was discussing pre‐calc,
when she was clearly talking
about having hot sex with you.
‐ Might be
an overstatement.
Y'all talking
about that Lara girl?
She's got great breasts.
Colonel, do not objectify
women's bodies.
Sorry.
Perky breasts.
- ‐ Not any better.
- Sure it is.
Great is a judgment.
Perky is merely an observation.
Well, here's another one.
You only view the world
through your limited male gaze.
There's so much
you're missing, Colonel.
‐ But he does look damn good
in that suit.
♪ ♪
‐ Not too late to return it.
The tags are still on,
money back guaranteed.
‐ And why would I do that?
‐ So many reasons.
You could use that cash
for a down payment
on a computer
so you don't have to use
the shitty one
the school loans out.
Or you can give it to me,
so I can finally fix
the air conditioning in my car,
which you will also enjoy.
‐ You know what else I enjoy?
Compliments about my style.
Pudge, I didn't get one
from you.
‐ You look really nice.
‐ Made my choice, Alaska.
‐ The wrong choice.
This debutante shit,
it's‐‐it's paternalistic.
It's misogynistic.
It's literally the epitome
of white privilege‐‐
‐ Says the attractive
white woman.
‐ I'm white trash.
They hate me too.
Those rich white idiots,
they're not gonna accept you
no matter what you wear‐‐
‐ Jesus.
Do you have to ruin everything?
I'm going for Sara.
That's it.
End of discussion.
‐ He may be little,
but he is fierce.
‐ Hey, Pudge,
if you got anything black,
wear it tonight.
‐ Why?
‐ Because it's slimming,
and stealthy.
Tonight, we strike back.
♪ Ha‐ha‐ha‐ha‐ha! ♪
♪ Feel good ♪
♪ Sha, sha‐ba‐sha, ka, sha‐ba ♪
Come on, Pudge.
Let's lift, man.
Let's go, come on.
♪ Sha, sha‐ba‐sha, ka, sha‐ba ♪
♪ Feel good ♪
♪ City's breaking down ♪
♪ On a camel's back ♪
♪ They'll just have to go,
'cause they don't know wack ♪
♪ So all you fill the streets ♪
♪ It's appealing to see ♪
Damn those guys!
♪ 'Cause you're damned
and free ♪
♪ You got a new horizon,
it's ephemeral style ♪
♪ A melancholy town
where we never smile ♪
♪ And all I wanna hear
is the message beep ♪
♪ My dreams,
they come a‐kissing ♪
♪ 'Cause I don't
get sleep, no ♪
- Looks like they got him.
- My God!
♪ Windmill, windmill
for the land ♪
♪ Turn forever hand in hand ♪
♪ Windmill, windmill
for the land ♪
♪ Is everybody in ♪
♪ Laughing gas these hazmats ♪
♪ Fast cats ♪
♪ Lining 'em up
like ass cracks ♪
♪ Lay these ponies
at the track ♪
♪ It's my chocolate attack ♪
♪ Shit, I'm stepping in hotter
this year ♪
♪ Care Bear repping,
it harder this year ♪
♪ Watch me as I gravitate ♪
♪ Ha‐ha‐ha‐ha‐ha ♪
♪ Yo, we gon' ghost town ♪
Let's go.
♪ You in the blink ♪
♪ Gon' bite the dust,
can't fight with us ♪
‐ Hoo‐hoo!
Hot damn.
I didn't think you guys
could look any more handsome.
‐ Asshole.
My escort has blue hair now.
You're welcome, Holly.
I'm sure the photos
are gonna look fantastic.
Yeah, man, you really got us.
‐ No crying
in your protein shakes.
‐ You win, Colonel.
We submit.
‐ Hey,
I can't find my keys.
You haven't seen 'em anywhere?
Mr. Martin, Mr. Halter.
I'm not sure if you are aware,
but there has been an outbreak
of pranks on campus.
I hope you two are staying out
of trouble.
‐ Absolutely, sir.
I really hope you apprehend
those hooligans.
‐ Okay.
- See something, say something.
- We will.
♪ Sha, sha‐ba‐sha, ka, sha‐ba ♪
♪ Feel good ♪
♪ Ha‐ha‐ha‐ha‐ha ♪
We have to show no mercy.
A prank that ends the war,
that destroys their lives.
Or at least their tuxedos.
‐ No.
Colonel,
just as a point of pride‐‐
‐ I said no.
Sara's deb ball is off limits.
It's too important to her.
You just worked so hard
for that suit.
‐ It doesn't matter.
I have a few dollars left.
If I write two papers
overnight...
‐ I have a little l‐left
in my commissary account
I can easily get out.
Look, I can front you the cash.
Just one phone call
to my parents‐‐
‐ I don't want anything
from anybody.
‐ Good, because I sadly have
no cash to contribute.
Though I can offer
my impeccable fashion sense.
‐ Meaning?
You can't afford
Men's Wearhouse anymore,
but you can afford
the Pelham thrift shop.
Of which I am a loyal customer.
I can help you get something.
‐ You don't even want me to go.
But I love
a good thrift shop excursion.
Colonel, it's gonna be okay.
It's all gonna work out.
Longwell and Kevin
are the worst.
I wish they'd just choke
on their stupid protein shakes.
‐ Takumi,
you are a goddamn genius.
‐ No argument here, but why?
♪ All day, all night ♪
♪ I love to be in charge ♪
‐ Oof, sure hope your plumbing
starts working again.
‐ Yeah.
♪ You'll be my fall guy ♪
♪ Your love ♪
♪ You're standing in the cold ♪
♪ And your love ♪
♪ Your love ♪
♪ You will not speak of ♪
♪ ♪
‐ Shit.
Shit.
I'm sorry.
♪ ♪
♪ Scarecrow ♪
♪ The bed ♪
♪ Until we had a nightmare ♪
Cheers.
- ‐ To a good night.
- And protein.
‐ I'm starving.
♪ ♪
‐ Last chance to come
to your senses.
‐ We've been through this.
‐ I know.
I'm just trying to stop you
from getting hurt.
‐ It's about Sara.
You don't give her
enough credit
for going against her tribe
to date me.
‐ First of all,
she's lucky as hell
you're willing to date her.
And honestly, Chip,
she kinda hates you.
‐
She does.
But she also kinda loves me.
And I'm gonna show her
I'm just as good
as any Weekday Warrior.
Can't you understand that?
‐ I can't.
But I do love you all the same,
and you do look damn fine
in that suit, my friend.
♪ ♪
‐ Thank you for everything.
See you back at school.
♪ ♪
Aww.
Don't you two look cozy
in there.
All right,
who's up for some fun?
♪ ♪
Chip.
You made it.
‐ Sara will be so pleased
you're here.
‐ Absolutely,
and let me just say
this place is truly majestic.
The bartender told me that
the ice cubes in the iced tea
are also made of iced tea.
Makes for
a very concentrated brew.
‐ Well, we appreciate you
being here.
‐ Well, if you need me,
I'll be at table 12.
‐ See, Preston,
it was a good idea.
Everything's gonna be
just fine.
‐
Hi, ladies.
Tell me I'm not late.
Father would never forgive me,
and after all, you know, today
is more about our daddies
than us girls.
Toodles.
‐ Hey, Holly,
have you seen my lip gloss?
You okay?
‐ I don't think so.
♪ ♪
‐ I'm like a motherfucking cat.
♪ Well, is it true ♪
I'm really
not feeling well, okay?
But Holly, dear,
you may miss being presented.
‐ I heard you, Mother,
but I do not have a choice
at the moment.
And I don't need an escort
for this.
Go.
I told you not to eat
anything today.
That dress isn't built
for bloat.
I didn't, just one
of Kevin's protein shakes.
Now get out.
It's an emergency.
♪ See the idiot talk ♪
♪ See the idiot
chalk up his name ♪
‐ That was close.
‐ Which means that stuff
is fast‐acting.
‐ So are we.
♪ ♪
Beautiful.
As many as these fancy dinners
as I attend, I always forget.
Is the bread plate
to my left or yours?
‐ Why are you sitting
at the kids' table?
You're not a kid.
‐ And you, sir, are very rude.
And for that, I will be
eating my roll and yours.
‐ That was mine.
They just called Justin.
You're up next.
I am not feeling well.
You're not the only one.
‐ Dude, come on.
‐ Actually, that was me.
I ain't going out there.
My grandma's here.
No, no, no.
It's happening.
No!
♪ See the robot walk ♪
♪ See the robot talk ♪
♪ Still you never learned
nothing ♪
♪ And nothing isn't over ♪
What?
Shit!
No!
Plastic wrap!
‐ So, we lost our exit.
Holly's still in there,
and it's not
a pretty situation.
Shit.
We have to find
another way out.
This way.
Lindsay Bryan,
who is escorted by
Hanna Sullivan.
There's no backtracking now.
All our exits
have been compromised.
Peggy Donovan...
The only way out is through
the belly of the beast.
‐ So we're stuck here.
Presenting
Sara Bankhead Harbert.
‐ Whoo!
To be escorted
by Longwell Chase.
Doesn't she look lovely?
We just need her escort,
Longwell Chase.
- ‐ Where are the boys?
- This is unusual.
- ‐
- Find them.
My God,
it's in my shoes!
Colonel's fucking dead!
‐ We need an escort
for the escort.
‐ Well, apparently,
Longwell is no longer able
to fulfill his duties today.
Perhaps we have a volunteer
who would like to step in.
♪ ♪
‐ Thank you, son,
but I got it from here.
‐ Sir, with all due respect,
doesn't it make the most sense
for her boyfriend
to be her escort?
‐ Chip, you wanted to be here,
we bought you a seat.
You should take it.
‐ I wanted to be here
because I'm her boyfriend,
and that makes me
more qualified
than that human hemorrhoid
Longwell Chase.
No offense, Dr. Chase.
‐ You're trying my patience,
so I'm just gonna go ahead
and say it.
There's no world in which
you escort my daughter
across that stage tonight.
Now, sit down.
It's a family matter.
♪ ♪
What a lovely
father‐daughter moment.
And that concludes
our escort presentation.
The debutantes will now join
their escorts on the floor
for a waltz.
♪ ♪
Teams are on it.
The country club
has been infiltrated
by pranksters.
You‐‐you get your guys!
You get your guys.
‐ Shit.
We gotta go.
♪ ♪
‐ I just walked
the south entrance.
I didn't see anything.
♪ ♪
‐
Help us.
♪ ♪
‐
‐ My God.
♪ ♪
‐ Should have known.
You ruined cotillion, asshole.
‐ One could argue
that it's always been rotten.
‐
You sound like Alaska.
‐ I've been called worse.
‐ Yeah.
It was pretty funny,
but you're still an asshole.
‐ Thanks, dick.
‐
♪ ♪
A toast
to one of the great pranks
in Culver Creek history.
‐ Hopefully,
those Weekday Warriors learned
a valuable lesson today:
look before you squat.
‐ I don't think I'll be able
to get their screams
out of my ears.
To success.
Indeed.
‐ I believe I was pretty
goddamn clear
that this event was off limits,
and all of you defied me.
You broke the chain of command.
But never have I been so glad
to have my orders ignored.
That was some funny shit.
And I'm not just referring
to what they had to hose off
the Weekday Warriors.
That was definitely
the nicest place
I've ever almost burned down.
‐ You're too good for them
anyway, Colonel.
Hell, you're too good
for Birmingham,
for all of Alabama.
Some folks describe me
as a visionary‐‐
‐ I'm pretty sure
that's self‐proclaimed.
‐ Because I see
the big picture.
And here's what I see.
We're all gonna get out of here
and do great things,
but the Colonel is destined
for the greatest.
‐ No kidding.
Don't come asking
for handouts when I make it.
I'm serious.
Shit, hide.
‐ Good evening.
Everybody enjoying
their Saturday night?
Mr. Halter, I just wanted
to check and make sure
that you could make it
back into your room
since you seem to be
missing these.
Keep up, Mr. Halter.
To the right.
God damn it.
How could he have been
so sloppy?
Turns out
Pudge's choice of key chain
was unfortunate
on a number of levels.
‐ Not sure
that's what matters here.
Disagree.
You know what they say.
Never trust a man with a need
to draw attention to his keys.
‐ I'm certain no one's
ever said that before.
It was a rough translation.
‐ I'm surprised to hear
that you're doubting Pudge.
Was he not a pivotal part
of one of the greatest
counterinsurgencies ever
carried out on foreign soil?
He was
the least coordinated
and expressed the most doubt...
But he was a key
to its success.
Pun intended.
This is true.
And he did just face off
against some explosive
and deadly assholes.
All puns intended.
‐ Wordplay while our friend's
future hangs in the balance?
‐ Look, I wish I shared
your confidence
in his ability to withstand
the Eagle,
but what do we really know
about Miles Halter?
Other than the fairly
damning fact
that he's from Florida.
‐ There is one thing I know
about Pudge Halter
that makes me think
he'll keep his mouth shut.
Yeah.
Good point.
‐ Well, what's that?
The Sunshine State.
I like that you have
so much pride in your home,
Mr. Halter.
‐ I just got it for, like, 99¢
with the purchase
of a Slim Jim.
‐ But surely
you must miss Florida.
No, not really.
I mean,
if my parents moved tomorrow,
I'd happily never go back.
‐ Well, then, let's hope
you don't have to return there
any time soon.
‐ Noted, sir.
Thank you.
Do you know
where you are, Mr. Halter?
You are in my home where
we can speak in confidence.
Actually,
it belongs to the school.
‐ I see, and are you
renovating the place
or you just move in?
‐ No.
If you must know,
my wife is moving out.
Well, she already moved out.
Quite hastily, if you ask me.
She sure didn't.
‐ I‐I didn't mean to pry.
‐ No, we were only together
for 13 years.
You know, it'll be fine.
I mean... eventually so.
But the good news is,
I have more time
to focus on my job.
Now, as you may already know,
there have been a spate
of pranks at Culver Creek,
all clearly related.
Now, the bad news for you is
that you are the only student
that I can connect
to these pranks.
Which means the full weight
of the punishment
for all of them will fall
squarely onto your shoulders,
unless you and I can come to
some sort of a deal.
‐ You mean, you want me to rat?
‐ No.
I see it did not take long
for you to get indoctrinated.
That's not a surprise
given that Mr. Martin
is your roommate.
"Snitches get stitches,"
as the kids say.
But here's one
you may not have heard.
"All that is necessary
for the triumph of evil
is that good men do nothing."
If you acted alone,
then you can just confess
to all of it,
and this matter will be put
before the jury.
‐ The‐‐the jury?
It's a panel of your peers.
Students with
a deep appreciation
for Culver Creek's rules.
You can avoid the uncertainty
of a trial
and receive
a far more lenient sentence
by simply telling me
everything that you know.
That choice is yours.
♪ ♪
So, convicted murderer
James French
was sentenced
to the electric chair.
To witnesses of his execution,
he yelled these last words:
"Hey, fellas, how's this
for tomorrow's headline:
'French Fries.'"
Yeah, it's a terrible joke,
but I always admired
that he kept his wits about him
in the face of such
dire circumstances.
‐ Pudge, what the fuck
are you talking about?
‐ I didn't tell him anything.
It wasn't easy.
He is a scary man.
The Eagle
is a sadistic son of a bitch,
all right.
I'm impressed.
- ‐ And I'm surprised.
- I'm not.
I'm proud of you, Pudge.
Another badass moment.
You better slow down, Pudge.
You may actually become cool.
‐ So, the Eagle
just let you go?
‐ I wish.
I have a hearing
in front of the jury.
Goddamn.
That jury is composed
of Culver Creek's
tightest sphincters.
‐ Well, it was nice
knowing you, Pudge.
‐ Everyone stay calm.
You can never give up hope
in the eternal struggle
of the good versus the naughty.
You may lose a battle,
but mischief always wins
the war.
♪ ♪
‐ No.
No, no, no.
Absolutely not.
This room is reserved
for jurors and the accused.
I get‐‐and obviously me.
♪ ♪
♪ Inspired by you ♪
‐ Have a seat.
You may now address the jury.
‐ Dear esteemed
fellow classmates
and the Honorable
Mr. Starnes,
I come today to throw myself
before the mercy of the court.
As disappointed
as you may be in me,
it pales in comparison
to the disappointment
I feel with myself.
Wow,
you ladies look slender.
Lost any weight?
‐ The only weight
I'm gonna lose is you,
'cause you're dead weight,
and you're dead.
Hold up.
I need to think about that one
for a second.
‐ I think we can all agree
what happened at the club
went too far.
‐ What happened at the club?
‐ No idea, not a member.
‐ You shouldn't be lecturing
anyone about going too far.
‐ Fine.
Maybe we took it too far
dumping Halter in the lake.
And the Colonel's suit.
‐ We didn't know
it was his only one.
‐ That sounded
dangerously close
to an apology.
‐ Not close enough.
‐ Right now, one of yours
is in front of the jury,
and the Eagle's on the warpath.
We may never know
who the rat was...
‐
Colonel.
‐ But we can all agree
we need to turn down the heat.
Now, we'll stop looking
for the rat
if you stop retaliating,
for real.
Truce?
‐ Who knows
that there even was a rat?
The Eagle could have
just gotten lucky, and‐‐
‐ Truce.
Peace be with you, Longwell.
‐ So, you're just
making decisions
without even consulting us now?
‐ I'm‐‐I'm sorry.
Was I unaware
that you recently bought
a winning lotto ticket?
Unlike those assholes,
we still need our scholarship
money to stay here.
And I don't know
about you boys,
but planning and executing
these elaborate
albeit brilliant pranks
is not really enhancing my GPA.
It's over.
We won.
‐ We haven't won yet.
Mr. Halter, please rise.
The jury has heard
your testimony
and has deliberated the facts
presented to them,
and they have come
to a decision.
Ms. Rowinksi.
‐ Given this is a first offense
and the fact
that no other students
have filed complaints
against you,
not to mention
your clear remorse,
we have decided on a sentencing
of two weeks cafeteria
cleanup duty,
mostly for the offense
of buying
that hideous key chain.
‐ To the rest of the jury,
do you agree
with this sentence?
‐ Yes.
‐ Very well.
You can report to Maureen
in the cafeteria.
She'll show you
where the hairnets are.
I do hope you enjoy
the smell of wet sponges.
And Mr. Halter, please remember
that the next time
you are in front of the jury,
you will not be
a first‐time offender,
so consider your actions
carefully.
‐ I got off
with a slap on the wrist.
I mean, I wasn't sure
how it was gonna go.
But I really spoke
from the heart,
and I think
the jury connected with it.
‐ Look at him,
so proud of himself.
‐ I almost don't even
wanna tell him.
‐ Then don't.
Just let him have this.
‐
Have‐‐have‐‐have what?
What's going on?
‐ I'm sure the jury let you off
because of your stirring words
and those puppy dog eyes,
but probably doesn't hurt
that I'll be writing
free term papers
for jurors two and five.
‐ Or that I agreed
to teach juror one
how to master "Halo 2"
and provide
all relevant cheat codes.
‐ And I promised
juror number seven
you'd go on a date with her,
Lara.
You might remember her
from our study group.
‐ Or her great breasts‐‐
perky breasts.
‐ You guys tampered
with the jury on my behalf?
Tell me they read
the part about your key chain.
It cost me extra,
but I just couldn't resist.
I told you, Pudge.
You're one of us now.
Don't start crying,
'cause you'll ruin everything.
♪ ♪
‐ Well, this is disappointing.
The trees with their branches,
the branches
with their leaves,
the tall grass that grows
in its shade,
all on display
out that very window.
‐ I'm sorry, sir.
I always pay attention
in class.
It won't happen again.
‐
So you are to never stare
at another window
for the rest of your days?
That's very sad news.
‐...
Apologies, but...
I don't understand
what you want me to say.
Good.
Stop thinking about
what's the right answer,
what you think I want to hear.
I don't want any thinking
from you whatsoever.
I just want you to be.
‐ Are you sure?
Life only exists now.
Time spent on the future
or the past
is done at your own risk.
Be present in this class.
And when it's over,
be present out there.
‐ ♪ My rhyme's old‐school ♪
♪ Sort of like
the ancient Romans ♪
♪ Colonel's beats are sav
like Arthur Miller's ♪
It's the only way
to actually connect
with others,
to see them as they truly are.
♪ ♪
‐ Why do you smoke
so damn fast?
♪ ♪
‐ Y'all smoke to enjoy it.
I smoke to die.
Extracted from MKV & Synchronized By X Person