Extracted from MKV & Synchronized By X Person
‐ I need y'all to go
to the gym now.
You're not in any trouble.
I just need you
to go to the gym now.
‐ What's the problem?
‐ Something terrible
has happened.
‐ Something like this
happened two years ago
when Mr. Harris,
dean before the Eagle,
died of a heart attack.
Given the age
of most of our teachers
and the poor nutrition
available to us
at the Culver Creek campus,
I'm surprised
this doesn't happen more often.
I bet it's Hyde this time.
Guess the old man really
only had a few breaths left.
Poor bastard.
‐ You look a little hungover.
Well, I guess I'm putting on
a good front, then, Pudge,
'cause I'm actually
a lot hungover.
And you look...
different.
‐
Alaska and I, we, ‐‐
‐ I wasn't that drunk.
‐
COLONEL: Come on.
Poor Dr. Hyde.
He was my favorite teacher
I've ever had.
‐ Then why don't you tell him?
I'm sure he'd be thrilled.
‐ Hyde's here.
‐ Where's Alaska?
- ‐ No.
- Pudge, where's Alaska?
Is she here or not?
Good morning.
Is, ‐‐is everybody here?
‐ No, Alaska isn't here.
‐ Is everyone else here?
‐ Alaska isn't here.
‐ Thank you, Miles.
I know it's early
and you are probably wondering
why we called you‐‐
Wait, we can't start
without Alaska.
♪ ♪
Please, sir.
Can we please just wait
for Alaska?
♪ ♪
‐ Last night...
Last night, Alaska Young
was in a terrible accident...
♪ ♪
And she was killed.
Alaska Young has passed away.
♪ ♪
She‐‐she's not dead.
She's not dead.
♪ ♪
Why are all these
people crying?
She's not dead.
She does pranks.
This is a prank.
She's really good at pranks.
‐ Miles...
Miles, I saw her.
And I'm sorry.
‐
What happened?
‐ It sounded like...
someone was setting off
firecrackers last night.
I ran out
to see what was happening
and I guess
she drove off campus.
It was late, it was raining.
There was a truck
that had broken down
and it was blocking both lanes.
The police had a car
on the scene
and she hit it.
The police said that
she hit it without swerving.
They believe that she must
have been very intoxicated.
They smelled alcohol.
I had talked to them,
the police‐‐it was, um...
it was instant.
The steering wheel
hit her chest and...
‐ You saw her?
How did she look?
‐ She looked like Alaska.
But she was dead, Miles.
‐ I‐‐I see, sir.
♪ ♪
Thank you.
‐ Mr. Martin.
I'm getting
kicked out, right?
So it's time to kick me out,
because if I wasn't
kicked out then,
then I'm definitely
kicked out now.
Is there a way
to be doubly kicked out?
Because if so, then that's me,
so kick me out.
You know, maybe
if you would have
did your goddamn job,
she'd still be alive,
but whatever.
I set off the fireworks.
'Cause she said
she needed to go
and I didn't know where.
She said she was fine to drive
and I believed her
and I let her go...
so it's all my fault.
So kick me out!
Just kick me out!
Kick me out, please.
‐ We gotta get 'em now.
Crawfish season
won't last forever.
Once we catch 'em,
we'll boil' em
and suck their heads.
That's where all
the good stuff is,
their heads.
♪ ♪
Come on.
Come on, help me out.
♪ ♪
Going for a swim?
‐ Turns out I'm not
getting expelled yet.
All that packing for nothing.
‐ So what the hell happened?
‐ She came into our room.
She was hysterical.
She said she needed
to get out of there.
We distracted the Eagle and...
she drove away.
‐ Why was she hysterical?
She wasn't making
a whole lot of sense.
Guess she was...
pretty wasted.
‐ And you just let her go?
‐ She told us to‐‐
‐ And you just do
everything she says?
‐ She's Alaska.
We all did.
‐ You should have stopped her!
She never thought
anything through,
she was so goddamn impulsive!
You had to watch her
like a three‐year‐old!
You do one thing wrong
and she dies.
How the fuck
could you let her go?
It hurts to breathe.
I'ma go for a walk.
I need to get some air.
‐ If you can't breathe, maybe
walking isn't the best idea.
‐ Bad ideas are my specialty
these days.
‐ We already feel guilty.
‐ You should.
♪ ♪
♪ Floating in the cold water ♪
♪ The ghosts of sorrow
haunt the deep ♪
♪ ♪
♪ Reaching down
to drag the ruins ♪
♪ ♪
♪ And roam
the lone deserted streets ♪
♪ ♪
♪ Of an old abandoned temple ♪
♪ Buried in
the narrow strait ♪
♪ Off the coast
of Tarifa, Spain ♪
♪ ♪
♪ Gypsies scatter
through the desert ♪
♪ Ooh ♪
♪ Across
the Atlas Mountain range ♪
♪ Hoarding remnants
from the Devil ♪
‐ Hello?
♪ From the Empire's
iron reign ♪
♪ ♪
♪ While cluttered down
the mouths of rivers ♪
♪ Ooh ♪
♪ Widowed lovers
bathe and clean ♪
♪ ♪
♪ Silken scarves embroidered
for their brand new queen ♪
♪ ♪
♪ And every time she rises up ♪
‐ Your parents called for you.
Not the first time.
♪ And like the moon
doesn't mind ♪
♪ If the sun doesn't shine ♪
‐ You okay?
♪ The sea doesn't care ♪
♪ If you're lonesome tonight ♪
♪ Ooh, ooh, ooh ♪
‐ Classes are cancelled.
I'm going to stay with you.
♪ Ooh, ooh, ooh ♪
♪ In its way
to comfort you ♪
♪ ♪
♪ Set adrift into her swarm
man o' war ♪
♪ Ooh ♪
♪ Caught up
in her dangling sting ♪
♪ Off the shore, ooh ♪
♪ Of a foreign
brown sand beach ♪
♪ As blue bottles cover you ♪
♪ ♪
♪ Many messengers
and rebels ♪
♪ Have come and gone
without a trace ♪
♪ ♪
♪ And many more
will come tomorrow ♪
♪ ♪
♪ And many more
will be erased ♪
♪ ♪
♪ 'Cause out beyond
the docks of Rota ♪
♪ ♪
♪ Upon the bottom of the sea ♪
♪ Like a lion don't mind ♪
♪ If a lamb takes her time ♪
♪ ♪
♪ A beast doesn't care
if you surrender tonight ♪
♪ Ooh, ooh, ooh ♪
♪ What she wants
all in good time ♪
♪ ♪
♪ Set adrift into her swarm
man o' war ♪
♪ Ooh ♪
♪ Caught up
in her dangling sting ♪
♪ Off the shore, ooh ♪
♪ Of a foreign
brown sand beach ♪
♪ As blue bottles cover you ♪
♪ ♪
Jesus, Pudge,
when's the last time
you stood up?
♪ ♪
All Maureen is making
is meatloaf.
It's neither meaty
nor loafy, but...
you should eat.
‐ We did not say...
"Don't drive, you're drunk."
We did not say...
"We're not letting you get
into a car when you're upset."
We did not say, "We insist
on going with you."
We did not say that
this can wait until tomorrow.
That anything
and everything can wait.
And as much
as I've thought about it,
I don't know...
why we didn't say anything.
‐ I'm sorry I blamed you guys.
‐ It was appropriate.
‐ How's the Colonel?
Where's the Colonel?
‐ I don't know.
I‐‐I haven't seen him
since the Smoking Hole.
What?
You‐‐you mean you haven't
seen him this whole time?
So he went for a walk
and he never came back?
He could have jumped
off a bridge, Pudge.
‐ Shit.
Shit.
‐ All right, all right.
First we get circulation back
to your lower extremities
and then we'll find
the Colonel.
‐ Okay.
‐ Are you sure we shouldn't
tell the Eagle or his mom?
‐ No, I don't want
to upset Dolores.
And if the Colonel
did go there,
I don't want to tell the Eagle
and upset him.
‐ We'll find him.
‐ Okay.
‐‐
Found him.
‐ Hey. You all right?
‐ Let's get you inside.
‐ How's that?
‐ Better.
Warmer.
‐ Okay.
Wait.
♪ ♪
Hold my hand.
‐ Okay.
But that's it.
No kissing.
♪ ♪
‐ Awful.
It is a law
that parents should not
have to bury their children
and someone should enforce it.
♪ ♪
Now, we're going
to continue studying religion,
but there's no doubting
that the questions
we'll be asking
have more immediacy
than they did
just a few days ago.
♪ ♪
What happens to us
when we die, for instance,
is no longer a question
of idle philosophical interest.
It is a question we must ask
about our classmate.
♪ ♪
So how are you guys doing?
Ms. Moser?
‐ Okay, well, this might sound
kind of strange,
but I had a mystical indicator
of Alaska's presence.
‐ You can't be serious
right now.
‐ No talking unless called on,
Mr. Martin.
I'm serious, Chip.
‐ Well, by all means,
please proceed.
‐ Well.
I was at Miss Anne's Diner
and suddenly
all the lights went out
except for, like
the light over my table,
which started flashing.
It would be, like,
on for a second
and then off for a while
and then, like, on
for a couple seconds
and then off.
And then I realized...
it was Alaska.
I think she was trying
to talk to me in Morse code
but, like, I don't know
Morse code.
She‐‐she probably
didn't know that.
‐ Mr. Martin?
I've been grappling
with the grave injustice
in the universe.
Heavenly Father...
how is it possible
that Alaska is gone
but we're stuck here
with Holly?
You know what, Chip?
You need to be open
to the universe
or you're gonna miss something.
‐ Well,
you know what, Holly?
I'm pretty sure the universe
is getting through to me
loud and clear, so thank you.
Okay, okay,
that's enough.
You may recall you were asked,
"What is the most
important question
facing people,
and how do traditions
we're studying
address that question?"
♪ ♪
This was Alaska's.
For your next paper I want you
to answer her question,
but for yourselves.
At some point in life,
we all look up
and realize we are lost
in a maze.
You probably all
feel that way now.
So how do you get through it?
♪ ♪
‐
‐ Hey, Chip.
Listen, I don't know
if you heard,
but after everything
that happened,
Kevin and Longwell's parents
are dropping the charges.
‐ I was wondering why I hadn't
been kicked out on my ass yet.
Been waiting.
That's nice of them.
‐ Listen, Chip,
I want you to know
you have someone
to sit with today
on the bus to the funeral.
We were all gonna bring things
to put on the side of the road
where it happened.
It's on the way,
so‐‐
Chip, I know how much
she meant to you.
I don't want you
to be alone right now.
‐ Thanks, Sara,
but,
we just gonna ride separately
in our own car,
but I'll see you there.
‐ 'Kay.
♪ ♪
‐ I‐‐I didn't know we
were driving separately.
‐ I'm not going that way.
We'll see if Lara can take us.
We just have to take
a long way.
‐ Good idea.
♪ ♪
‐ It's nice to know
you've taken notice
of my sartorial splendors,
Mr. Halter.
And here I was afraid
my understated elegance
was lost on you students.
Used to be one took pride
in one's appearance.
Now it's all
elastic waist pants
and‐‐dear God‐‐flip flops.
But you've come
to the right place.
♪ ♪
If you want a good knot,
you need a good tie.
And this is a very good one.
I wore this to Diego's funeral.
♪ ♪
Not that I was invited
to attend.
♪ ♪
His parents never accepted him
for who he was.
Or who he was with.
He gave me strength then.
And I hope it gives
you strength now.
Good.
♪ ♪
‐ Meriwether Lewis's
last words were,
"I am not a coward,
"but I am so strong.
So hard to die."
I'm sure that's true,
but it can't be much harder
than being left behind.
‐ Everything that comes
together falls apart.
Everything.
This chair I'm sitting on,
it was built,
and so it will fall apart.
I'm going to fall apart,
probably before this chair.
And you're going to fall apart.
Cells and organs and systems
that make you you,
they came together,
grew together,
and so they must fall apart.
Nothing lasts.
Not Alaska the girl,
nor Alaska the place.
Not even Earth itself.
‐ You're not one for pep talks,
‐ Do you remember what
the Buddhists said life is?
‐ Suffering.
‐ And suffering
is caused by desire.
The cessation of desire means
the cessation of suffering.
When you stop wishing
things won't fall apart,
you'll stop suffering
when they do.
Until then,
this will hurt.
But you will survive...
Until you don't.
♪ ♪
♪ I had a dream I stood
beneath an orange sky ♪
♪ ♪
♪ Yes I had a dream I ♪
♪ Stood beneath
an orange sky ♪
♪ ♪
♪ With my brother
standing by ♪
♪ ♪
♪ With my brother
standing by ♪
♪ ♪
♪ I said brother you know
you know ♪
♪ It's a long road
we've been walking on ♪
♪ ♪
♪ Brother ♪
♪ I said brother
you know it is ♪
♪ You know it is ♪
♪ Such a long road
we've been working on ♪
♪ ♪
♪ And I had a dream I stood
beneath an orange sky ♪
♪ ♪
♪ I said sister here
is what I know now ♪
♪ Here is what I know now
goes like this ♪
♪ My salvation lies
in your love ♪
♪ My salvation lies ♪
♪ In your love ♪
♪ My salvation lies
in your love ♪
♪ In your love
♪ In your love ♪
‐
‐ ♪ In your love
in your love ♪
‐ To be continued.
♪ ♪
‐ ♪ It's a start
you know I'm so weary ♪
‐ The phone rang.
- ‐ What?
- That night.
She got out of bed.
The phone rang.
She went to go answer it.
But she was fine
until the phone rang.
‐ Wait, that's why she had
to get out of there
because of the phone call.
Okay, so who
called her that night?
‐ So this is Vine Station.
‐ Alaska did not exaggerate.
Vine Station is a shit hole.
No wonder she wanted to get
the fuck out of here.
‐ You may be wondering why
the casket's closed.
Her momma had an open casket.
And Alaska told me after...
Said, "Daddy..."
♪ ♪
"Don't ever let them
see me dead.
♪ ♪
So that's that.
Anyway...
♪ ♪
She ain't in there.
She's with the Lord.
♪ ♪
‐ Thought I'd feel her looking
down on us, but...
♪ ♪
She's just gone.
I'm sorry, Alaska.
You deserved a better friend.
♪ ♪
‐ Stewart and Shanks.
All right, Tom.
♪ ♪
‐ You all right, sir?
‐ I just wanted you all
to listen to me.
Trust me,
respect me...
And even fear me,
if that's what it took...
So that I could protect
all of you and keep you safe.
God, I tried so hard
at this job,
it cost me my marriage.
I even grew
this stupid mustache
hoping that it would give me
some authority
you know,
so that you would listen to me.
But I was the one
that needed to listen.
She was in pain,
and I made it worse.
‐ We all made it worse.
Yeah, but you're
just kids.
You're supposed
to make mistakes.
I'm the adult,
and I failed all of you.
Most of all, her.
‐ It's not too late.
We could all really use
an adult right about now.
♪ ♪
And sir,
mustache didn't work.
‐
Yeah, I know.
Thank you, Mr. Chase.
♪ ♪
The Lord
is my shepherd.
I shall not want.
He maketh me to lie down
in green pastures.
He leadeth me beside
the still waters.
He restoreth my soul.
He leadeth me in the paths
of righteousness
for his name's sake.
Yea, though I walk through the
valley of the shadow of death,
I will fear no evil‐‐
HYDE: She said, "My dear,
"upon your altars I have placed
the marguerite and coquelicot
"and roses frail as April snow.
But here," she said,
"Where none can see,
I make an offering
in the grass of radishes
and flowers."
And then she wept
for fear the Lord
would not accept.
The good lord in his garden
sought new leaf
and shadowy tint
and they were all his thought.
He heard her low accord
half‐prayer and half‐ditty
and he felt a subtle quiver
that was not heavenly love
nor pity.
♪ ♪
‐ Each fingerprint is a way
of leaving your impression,
showing the deceased
that she mattered to you.
♪ ♪
‐ I love you.
‐ I know you did.
‐ No, not past tense.
I love you.
And I'm so sorry
for letting you go.
♪ ♪
I'm so sorry.
Come on.
Let's go.
♪ ♪
‐ She was just
trying to reach out.
Only wish I could
have understood.
You know Alaska
was the first girl I kissed
when I got to school?
When I stated so much,
she "profoundly regretted" it.
♪ ♪
You know,
if you think about it,
it's all his fault.
Her dad?
What does any of this
have to do with him?
‐ Are you serious?
The whole goddamn thing.
He blamed her mom dying on her.
He's the reason
she couldn't go home.
Look at that sad
fat fuck.
Over there getting drunk
like a piece of shit.
You know who else was
a drunk piece of shit?
My dad.
So I'm kind of an expert
on the subject.
‐ Maybe keep your voice down
just 'cause he's probably‐‐
You know, this all
started because she ratted,
but she only ratted because
she couldn't go home.
Her Life's Library got
destroyed because she ratted.
Everything bad that's happened
this year
is because her dad
is an asshole.
Hey, Colonel.
‐ Hey, you broke her.
Hey, you broke her!
If you were ever there for her,
none of this would
have happened!
She wouldn't have been so sad.
She wouldn't have drank
so much.
She would have had a car
with fucking airbags!
‐ I'll do the‐‐
‐ It should have been you!
- It shouldn't have been her.
- Hey!
‐ It should have been
fucking you!
It should have been
Get your goddamn
hands off me!
If you wanna grab somebody,
grab this drunk fuck!
What on earth
are you doing,
assaulting a man that
just lost his child?
‐
DOLORES: I'm sorry.
‐ He's right.
‐ No, sir!
He's upset.
He should not be paid
attention to.
‐ I lost her a long time ago.
What I did,
the things I said...
I didn't deserve her.
♪ ♪
And now she's gone.
And I could never
make it right.
♪ ♪
I'm so sorry, baby.
‐
Blessed Lord, have mercy.
‐ Not my proudest moment.
‐ Yeah.
Don't expect to get invited to
too many funerals after today.
‐ I'll take it.
‐ So, Pudge,
you a certified smoker now?
‐ It's what Alaska
would've been doing.
‐ She also would've
hated this funeral.
‐ That we can all agree on.
‐ Hey, fellas.
How you holding up?
‐ Shitty as hell.
‐ How are you doing?
As Alaska's longest‐lasting
and emotionally‐healthiest
relationship,
this must be hard for you too.
‐ Didn't know it was possible
to feel this terrible,
to be honest.
I just feel so guilty,
just...
like I should've known
or something,
or done something.
‐ I know the feeling.
‐ None of it makes any sense.
You know,
how could someone so young,
so alive, be dead?
So we blame ourselves,
thinking we have some control,
that we could've created
a different outcome,
that the world isn't
a completely fucked‐up,
random place
where a girl dies for no reason.
I'm Fiona.
I go to school with Jake.
I only met Alaska once,
but she made
quite an impression.
‐ Fiona.
You are clearly very wise,
but there has to be a reason‐‐
if not for why she died,
at least for why
she got into that car,
or who the hell called her
on the phone that night.
‐ You mean on the payphone?
‐ Yeah.
‐ That was me.
‐ Jake was the phone call.
‐ After that phone call,
everything changed.
‐ What did you say?
‐ Apparently, the wrong thing.
Hello?
Alaska?
Amazed you actually answered.
Um, it's good to hear
your voice.
I miss you.
‐ Yeah, Jake, I miss you too,
but it's kinda late.
I know, I know.
And I know we're not exactly
together right now,
even though I'm not sure why,
I...
I'll never let this day go by
without thinking of you.
Hopefully,
we get to talk on this date
even when we're old and‐‐
‐ Wait, what do you mean,
"this date"?
What day is it?
‐ It's our anniversary.
It's been two years
since the day we met.
‐ N...
♪ ♪
No...
It can't be.
Hey, it's nothing
to get upset about.
It's cool if I remembered
and you didn't.
I'm kind of a dork like that.
Alaska?
You still there?
Next thing I knew,
I was just sitting in
France Between the Wars
and someone tells me
based on the paper
that Alaska died.
‐ That's it?
That was the whole call?
‐ Wait, what's so bad
about your anniversary...
‐ Or forgetting it.
‐ That would just
make her flip out?
‐ I have no idea.
‐ She got off the phone with you
and got in your car.
‐ I understand.
‐ Why, Jake?
‐ Hey, he's told you
all that he knows.
‐ What else did you say to her?
‐ That's it.
‐ Why did she get in the car?
‐ He doesn't know, Pudge.
‐ I wish I did.
Sorry, man.
♪ ♪
Maybe it's right in front
of our faces.
She was upset about missing
the anniversary with Jake.
She felt guilt
about blowing him off.
‐ In that moment, she realized
how much Jake meant to her,
and how badly
she had treated him,
and wanted to apologize
in person.
‐ She was driving up to see him
to make up,
to get back together.
‐ It sounds obvious,
but it makes the most sense.
‐ What?
No.
That doesn't make any sense
at all.
She wasn't thinking about Jake
while she was kissing me.
There's no way Alaska wanted
to get back with him.
‐ Look, Pudge, after the call,
she didn't march back
to your room to snuggle.
She got super upset and
got in her car and drove away,
possibly to where Jake was.
The whole point of this exercise
is to start with the known,
and fill in the unknown with
the likely scenarios,
not pander to your fantasy
that Alaska was madly
in love with you.
You'd be a terrible profiler.
You're making it all about you.
‐ Yeah,
because it is all about me.
I was the last person
that she kissed.
She said,
"to be continued" to me,
which is the last thing that
she said before the phone rang.
‐ You're not special, Pudge.
Just because she got drunk
and you guys hooked up,
or whatever,
doesn't mean that she meant
more to you than she did
to any of us.
We all miss her.
‐ I know that.
♪ ♪
♪ I ♪
♪ Am thinking it's a sign ♪
♪ That the freckles
in our eyes ♪
♪ Are mirror images ♪
♪ And when we kiss ♪
♪ They're perfectly aligned ♪
♪ I ♪
♪ Have to speculate ♪
♪ That God Himself did make us ♪
‐ So Takumi overheard the Eagle
talking to Alaska's dad.
He's coming in the next day
or so to clean out her room,
so if you got anything
that's ours,
or any contraband
we don't want him to find,
we should take care of that.
♪ It may seem like a stretch ♪
♪ But it's thoughts like this ♪
♪ That catch my troubled head ♪
♪ When you're away ♪
♪ When I am missing ♪
This is unbearable.
I know.
But we have to.
‐
I can't.
‐ Don't make me
do this alone, Pudge.
♪ ♪
Miles, it's so good
to hear your voice.
School sent us an email, son.
We know a student died.
Poor parents.
‐ Parent.
The girl that died‐‐
did‐‐did you know her?
♪ ♪
‐ Yeah.
She was my friend.
She was my really good friend.
It was her, wasn't it?
The girl you stayed with
over Thanksgiving.
‐ Yeah.
Alaska...
w‐was her name.
That just sounds like
a real shock, son.
I know it's just awful.
Um, whatever you need,
we're here for you,
you know that.
‐ I know. Um...
But this is enough.
I just needed you to pick up,
needed you to answer, and...
and you did.
♪ Come down now ♪
♪ But we'll stay ♪
Well, well.
Look who decided to show up.
I'm here to help.
‐
Well, she sure didn't
leave any booze,
but, you know, she kept
every paper she ever wrote.
She didn't have much, but,
you know, it's like
every object is precious.
Thus, they should
be treated as such.
♪ ♪
‐ All these books
she'll never read.
Bought at garage sales.
And now probably
destined for another one.
Ashes to ashes.
Garage sale to garage sale.
We can't sell them.
That seems wrong.
‐ Well, the ones
that are too water damaged,
we'll bury in a literary grave.
TBD.
But you're right.
You know,
John Keats' entire will
was written in one line
of iambic pentameter.
"My chest of books
divide among my friends."
She'd want these
divided among her friends.
‐ Have you seen
The General in His Labyrinth?
I know it got flooded.
I'm sure the pages
are all messed up.
I want that one.
‐ Here it is.
You're not thinking about
reading it, are you?
It's not a biography.
‐ Historical fiction.
‐ I'll allow it.
♪ ♪
"He was shaken
by the overwhelming revelation
"that the headlong race
between his misfortunes
and his dreams
"was at that moment
reaching the finish line.
"'Damn it,' he sighed.
'How will I ever get out
of this labyrinth?'"
♪ ♪
‐ Colonel, come look at this.
‐ You skipped to the end?
You do that with
every book you read?
‐ The way out of the labyrinth.
"Straight and fast."
‐ Holy shit, Pudge.
Think about what the Eagle
told you how it happened.
The truck that was broke down,
the police car on the scene,
which she hit without swerving.
They said it was the booze
that caused the accident.
‐ I guess
there's one possibility
that we haven't considered.
What if it wasn't an accident?
Extracted from MKV & Synchronized By X Person
♪ No one ♪
♪ No one hears you calling ♪
♪ ♪
♪ Falling ♪
♪ Everything is falling ♪
♪ Falling, falling,
falling ♪
♪ ♪
♪ Do you feel alive ♪
♪ So ♪
♪ Jesus left you lonely ♪
♪ ♪
♪ Feels like ♪
♪ Nothing's really holy ♪
♪ Holy, holy, holy ♪
♪ ♪
♪ Salvation ♪