["Boombayah" by
BLACKPINK playing]
[effervescent, upbeat
pop music continues]
♪ BLACKPINK in your area ♪
♪ Been a bad girl, I know I am ♪
♪ And I'm so hot, I need a fan ♪
♪ I don't want a
boy, I need a man ♪
♪ Click-clack!
Badda-bing, badda-boom ♪
[BLACKPINK continue
singing in Korean]
[song trails off]
[Enid] Admit it.
This is the Wednesday Addams
you didn't know you needed.
[jauntily macabre
intro music playing]
[intro trails off]
[dour music playing]
I warned you about Tyler coming.
I told you to cancel the
remembrance procession.
What's your part in all of this?
I lured Tyler away
from the ceremony.
Wednesday had a
plan to control him.
It did not go well.
My plan was unfolding with the
precision of a Swiss watch.
Until that second Hyde showed
up and smashed the watch.
[Dort] Two Hydes?
You're dismissed.
The second monster,
who the hell's that?
Francoise Galpin,
Tyler's mother.
She's been dead for 15 years.
I was at her funeral.
Augustus Stonehurst
faked Francoise's death.
He was experimenting on her and
others in the basement of Willow Hill.
His daughter Judi never
wanted you to find out.
-[Santiago] Judi's been reported missing.
-Wow.
Why am I only hearing
about this now?
Francoise and Tyler are gone,
with no plans to
return to Jericho.
Francoise gave me her
word, and I believe her.
[Santiago scoffs] Hmm.
Sounds like our
problem solved itself.
I should arrest you right here for
aiding and abetting a murderer.
I make no apologies
for my actions.
You ordered your deputies
to abandon the school
so they could save
Normies at Pilgrim World.
Leaving Outcasts to fend for themselves?
How do you think the press will take that?
[Dort] Luckily, no one got hurt,
but in an abundance of caution I
am mandating a school-wide curfew.
Our gala is around the corner. So
why don't we all just take the win?
Wherever there's
murder and mayhem,
you'll always find an Addams.
With corpse bells on.
[jarring music building]
[music swells]
[slow clapping]
Bravo, Miss Addams.
You managed to release not one,
but two Hydes from the asylum.
I was hoping once Day
of the Dead was over,
you would sashay back
into the afterlife.
I don't sashay.
Ever.
Are the Galpins
still in Jericho?
Now I'm adding
bloodhound to my resume?
You're my spirit guide.
How about some actual guidance?
I can tell you your
vision hasn't changed.
Enid still dies, and you
are still responsible.
What do I need to do?
Finally, some
positive engagement.
[exhales]
Your psychic ability
isn't just inherited.
It's intricately tied
to your familial bonds.
The escalating and unresolved
tension with your mother
is what's disrupting your power.
That's absurd.
The Addams family lineage
has always drawn strength
from the unity of its members.
Like it or not,
you are part of that
spiritual heritage.
But that strength demands
emotional clarity.
I don't need to deal
with any emotions,
and I don't need to cater
to my mother's maudlin need to
insert herself into my life.
Your lack of empathy is what
makes you the weak link,
spiritually speaking.
I'm the only link that matters.
Leave Tyler and Francoise
to the authorities.
Focus on fixing the
relationship with your mother.
Miss Addams, who
are you talking to?
Professor,
did you ever teach
Francoise Galpin?
[gulps]
She was Francoise
Night in those days.
But science didn't hold her
interest, unlike her brother.
Francoise had a brother?
Isaac.
He was the most brilliant
DaVinci I've ever met.
I owe him my life.
He designed this
life-support system for me.
You two must have been close.
Ha. Ha!
Isaac didn't care about people,
but he loved to play God.
You said DaVincis loved
Augustus Stonehurst.
Was Isaac one of his students?
Stonehurst was his mentor.
He built Isaac that
secret lab at Iago Tower.
They were thick as thieves.
Until the night
the lab exploded.
What happened to Isaac?
His body was never found.
Some say he ran away,
others... that he's buried
under the Skull Tree.
That's just an urban legend, but
you're welcome to try and dig him up.
[tense, jittery music playing]
I'm running a special on the
answers for Tudor-Pole's math quiz.
How much?
Five bucks. Guaranteed
A, or your money back.
[music halts]
Store's closed.
Everybody out.
[students grumbling]
Your zombie. When's the
last time you saw him?
You know my waterboard
is in my closet.
Right next to her skeletons.
[threatening music rises, fades]
I saw him at
Pilgrim World, okay?
But Slurp's gone now. For good.
His name is Isaac Night.
Isaac Night?
And how do you know he's gone?
I might have let him go.
Don't tell Dad.
I kind of lied to him.
What a bold move for somebody
who has no poker face.
You think he knows?
Dig up everything you
can find on Isaac Night.
He's just trying to live his life
now that he's got a second chance.
Your heart is as
soft as your skull.
Can your pea brain
remember anything else?
He dropped this.
[unsettling music playing]
He's looking for his sister.
[music trails off]
Hey.
You sleep well?
I'm really here.
Your father built this
place after you were born.
He wanted some place close to
keep you safe in case I, uh...
Well, you know.
I remember your funeral
like it was yesterday.
Dr. Stonehurst lied
to your father.
To everybody.
[metallic rattling]
-You don't trust me?
-You unleashed your Hyde last night.
That's something you just
don't recover from overnight.
It... It was because you
didn't have a master.
So you're my master now?
Mm-hmm.
Well, you must be hungry.
[coughing violently]
Do you want some, uh, pancakes?
They were always
your favorite, right?
I'm not a kid anymore, so
stop trying to placate me.
-[grunts]
-[Tyler groans]
Never raise your
voice to me again.
Now I'm... I'm going to
make you those pancakes.
Sweetie.
You okay?
Yeah. Sorry.
Just didn't sleep very much.
[sighs] You did just
face off with a Hyde.
Yeah. I'm sure that's it.
[phone chiming, buzzing]
Your mom again?
[sighs]
[Enid] She's been
calling a lot recently.
Family drama back home.
I'll call her later.
You know you can talk
to me about that stuff.
Some things words can't fix.
[gentle music playing]
[Capri clears throat]
Professor Capri. I was
just checking on Enid.
I'm sure Enid's lips are fine.
You know boys aren't allowed
in the girls' dorm solo.
Want to tell me what
happened last night?
I know. We should have told
somebody about the Hyde.
No. Not that. What
happened after.
In the music room.
[sighs softly] I don't know
what you're talking about.
Enid, you transformed
into a werewolf.
Without a full moon. I saw you.
[delicate, introspective
music playing]
Enid, it's okay.
It... It means you
could be an Alpha.
[Enid gasps]
Wait. Me?
We don't know, but
look at the facts.
You're a late bloomer.
The first time you wolfed out
was under a blood moon, correct?
Those are all classic
signs of a potential Alpha.
They're the strongest
of our kind. Very rare.
If you are one, we
have to manage it.
[phone buzzing]
But don't Alphas
normally end up alone?
Sorry. One minute.
It's Principal Dort.
We're implementing a new curfew.
After dinner, everyone's
confined to their rooms.
Anyone fails to comply,
barred... from the gala...
Oh, Enid.
Don't worry.
There's a lot of
misinformation out there
about Alphas
becoming lone wolves,
but as long as we get this under
control, there's nothing to worry about.
Okay?
[music growing fearful]
[breathing shakily]
[music trails off]
Pull.
[Hester] Wednesday.
What brings you all this
way on such a dreadful day?
I need help restoring
my psychic ability.
The last time I intervened, your
mother burned that spell book.
Yes, but you're a Raven.
You must know another way.
Pull.
Every now and then,
I crank up my psychic sight
so I can spy on old enemies.
Just a few flashes of their
suffering. Usually brightens my mood.
You stopped using it after
what happened to Aunt Ophelia.
Is that what your
mother told you?
Doves can be so emotional,
always living in the past and
wallowing in their feelings.
I made a choice to
leave all that behind.
Women like us can't
be burdened by family.
We forge our own path,
dig our own grave.
This is one of the Hydes I
accidentally released at Willow Hill.
I need to find her.
[suspicious music playing]
Have you ever come across
the name Rosaline Rotwood?
Professor Rotwood was
a legendary Raven.
She taught runes and ancient
cryptology during my time at Nevermore.
I was an amateur tomb raider,
so I took to that class
like a leech to blood.
In fact, your parents are
slumming in her old cottage.
She used to hold secret
soirées in her seance chamber.
She may have served
stale sherry,
but her psychic sight
was extraordinary.
What does this have to
do with my situation?
Rotwood is buried in
the Nevermore graveyard.
Her headstone is imbued
with her dark energy.
If a Raven recites the
inscription etched underneath,
you will be granted
temporary sight.
Thank you, Grandmama.
I'm the last person to offer advice, and
you're the last person to accept any,
but... proceed with
caution, my dear.
Pull.
[bird squawks]
Aw.
Oh, there you are.
Dort turned dinner into
a campus safety TED talk.
Ugh, I had to escape.
-Where are you charging off to?
-The Nevermore graveyard.
Hello? Curfew!
If you're not back, the entire dorm
is gonna be barred from the gala.
You may have dropped
out of the orchestra,
but I've been rehearsing
my dance routine for weeks.
I'm not cowering away in the room while
Tyler and his mother are out there.
I'm going to find them.
How exactly?
That's on a need-to-know basis. After
last night, you don't need to know.
Did it ever occur to you that
we're all just trying our best?
Trying your best means you're planning on
failing and letting me know in advance.
The fact that you
can be so arrogant
and still make so many bad
decisions is staggering.
How was I supposed to know that
Tyler's mother was still alive?
You weren't! That's
the whole point.
Your arsonist-slash-firefighter complex
is right there in black and white.
You unleash chaos just so you can
stamp it out and then feel superior.
You think you're powerful now
because you finally wolfed out?
[breathing tremulously] You have
no idea what I'm capable of.
Now who sounds arrogant?
Have you ever put yourself in someone
else's shoes to see how they felt?
My shoes are filled with
broken glass and razor blades.
You'd bleed out after two steps.
[somber, melancholy
music playing]
[chilling music builds]
Capri's going house-to-house
doing dorm checks?
How long until she gets up here?
That's barely enough time to make
it to the graveyard and back.
I am not missing that gala!
I will literally drag Wednesday
back by her braids if I have to!
[dour, foreboding music playing]
[Wednesday] "In
the Raven's shadow,
grant me use of your
ephemeral sight."
"Be warned. Should my gaze be
broken, a deadly trick I will play."
[chanting in Latin]
[harrowing music spikes]
[gasp echoing]
How dare you enter
my chamber uninvited?
I'm a Raven.
One whose wings
have been clipped.
My grandmother told me that if I
read the inscription on your grave,
you would grant me second sight.
[chuckles]
Hester.
So desperate for my approval.
But she never had what it took
to be a truly great Raven.
She craved a family so badly, she
fell head over heels with a huckster.
I sense none of that
sentimentality in you.
No. The crack in your
monochrome armor is
overbearing arrogance.
You positively
reek of the stuff.
Tyler and Francoise Galpin.
I need to find them.
There's no time to waste. A
life hangs in the balance.
What are you willing to
endure to excavate the truth?
Hold your hand over the flame,
and your psychic sight will
be temporarily renewed.
But beware.
If you pull your
palm from the flame,
you will break the
Raven's gaze, and...
there will be a price to pay.
[suspenseful music playing]
[Enid, faintly]
Wednesday, where are you?
[Enid, echoing] Wednesday!
We have to go back!
[Rotwood] There will
be a price to pay.
[both exhale]
No.
-No, no, no, no, no.
-[shrieking]
[Wednesday] Enid?
What the hell happened to me?
[morbidly intriguing
music playing]
Why am I staring at...
me?
Because we've somehow
swapped bodies.
I don't understand.
We were at the graveyard, and now
we're here, and now it's morning.
How the hell did that happen?
You broke the Raven's gaze.
Now it's playing a dirty trick.
How do we swap back?
You always think you're the
smartest person in the room.
I'll let you figure
that one out.
Wednesday?
Who are you talking to?
Obviously, it's me. Keep up.
Okay, whatever you did, you need
to fix it. Right frickin' now!
None of this would've happened
if you'd left me alone.
You're seriously blaming me?
[Enid whimpers]
I feel so cold
and uncomfortable.
It's probably your
factory setting.
-And I'm warm and clammy.
-Werewolves run hot.
We're hot-blooded creatures.
Oh my god, oh my god, oh my god!
Watching my body contort to your
emotional outbursts is making me queasy.
Nobody can see us
like this, okay?
We'll pretend we have
a contagious disease,
and say we need
to be quarantined.
[wry musical flourish]
You are not walking
out this door.
I'm going back to
Rotwood's grave.
Wednesday?
I'm scared.
-You will get your body back.
-Promise?
[whimpers]
[Enid] What are we gonna do?
We tell absolutely no one.
This must remain our secret.
You need to stay
away from Bruno.
And you must avoid my
family at all costs.
Especially my mother.
We got this, right?
I mean, how hard is it to
act like Wednesday Addams?
[droll, macabre music playing]
[Bianca] Enid!
Over here. Saved you a seat.
Coming, guys!
[wry, perplexing music playing]
Get coffee. Sit alone.
Stay out of trouble.
I'll be back soon.
Hmm.
Your braids are fire, Elise.
And those shoes
are a vibe, Sophia.
Way to go, you little psycho.
I was just delivering your
morning coffee like I always do.
You do?
I mean...
Right. Of course.
I haven't been able to locate
Isaac Night's student files yet.
Who's Isaac Night?
Pugsley's zombie.
[gasps] Duh! Right. I'm clearly suffering
from extreme caffeine deprivation.
A rainbow furracino with an extra
squirt of steak sauce, please.
[quizzical musical flourish]
[dryly] I can tattoo my order on
your forehead if that would help.
I thought you were
allergic to color.
I mean, I just say that
to keep up the whole
tragic loner, goth
girl aesthetic.
I'll catch you later. Or never.
[quirky music playing]
[serene notes playing]
[gulps, sighs in satisfaction]
[suspenseful music pulsing]
Whoa, whoa. Enid, wait.
It's me.
[dour music playing]
You said you loved it
when I surprised you.
Try again and I'll treat you to
some real pain and suffering.
[slurping loudly]
[tense music playing]
[gasps]
This is insane!
I was actually
allergic to color.
Wednesday.
[shakily] I kinda
can't talk right now.
Oh, dear.
I haven't seen your
skin break out like that
since Pugsley colored the inside
of your favorite death mask.
Hmm. I have just the remedy.
[dour, uneasy music playing]
Wow!
This cream is amazing.
-What's in it?
-Beeswax, stinging nettles, and ash.
Ash?
Scraped from the bottom
of a crematorium furnace.
One of your grand
mama's beauty secrets.
Although it does give your skin
that wonderful corpse-like glow.
Well...
Thanks, Mom.
Mom?
That's new.
Hmm. Something's
different about you today.
I can see it in your eyes.
It's like your
spirit is lighter.
Well, I'm just trying to
embrace my inevitable decay
with a touch of enthusiasm.
Why didn't you take your
umbra mushroom pills?
You know you run the risk of an
allergic reaction if you skip a day.
Oh. Right.
My prescription ran out.
Well, luckily, I stopped by the
apothecary and picked up your refill.
This will clear it right up.
Got it. Bye.
-Since you're turning over a dead leaf...
-[gasps]
Perhaps you'd like to come for
family dinner at the cottage tonight?
[chuckling] Oh.
Uh, tonight's not great for me.
Pugsley's coming over.
And your father's
up from the city,
and you know how much family
dinners cool his heart.
I would love to come, Mom.
I mean, Mother.
But I can't.
Principal Dort just
issued a curfew.
Well, I've already
spoken to him,
and he's given you and
Pugsley a pass for tonight.
Isn't that wonderful?
Lurch will pick you up at 7:00.
Don't be late.
[cheekily distraught
music playing]
[groans]
[stifled screaming]
[grimly determined
music playing]
[Weems] Once again, you have
wandered into uncharted territory.
Can't say I didn't warn you.
Fine.
How do I undo this?
I haven't the foggiest.
But given my penchant
for meticulous research,
I did discover that
two other Ravens
had the audacity to embark on this
foolhardy endeavor before you.
-What happened to them?
-They were both dead within 24 hours.
Bravo, Miss Addams.
It appears you'll be responsible for
Enid's premature death after all.
As well as your own.
[harrowing music intensifies]
[music trails off]
[forlorn music playing]
[Isaac scoffs]
-Ready for another one, sweetie?
-Mmm.
-Good?
-Yeah.
-Like it?
-Better than I remember.
[Francoise chuckles]
[rapping at door]
No, it can't be.
It's impossible.
Francoise...
Is that any way to
greet your brother?
You died.
I held you.
In my arms.
Put the gun down.
Do you remember
the Fourth of July?
Dad caught you with
that Normie kid.
Dylan.
He slapped you so hard.
It was louder than
the fireworks.
That was the first
time you transformed.
[Francoise sobs softly]
I've spent my life
dreaming of this moment.
Praying that I
would see you again.
Tyler,
this is your Uncle Isaac.
[Francoise] Mmm.
[chilling music playing]
Hello.
Tyler.
Nice to meet you.
[coughs uncontrollably]
What's wrong?
[Francoise breathes heavily]
It's our condition.
Being a Hyde.
I've lived longer than most.
[Isaac] I could still help you.
It was always my dream.
To slay the monster inside you.
I only need the right equipment.
Resources.
Dr. Stonehurst
stole your diaries.
And he's built a version of
your machine at Willow Hill.
But he perverted it to give
our abilities to Normies.
His daughter Judi, she's
carrying on his research.
She's been hunting me.
Well,
Judi...
retired.
Permanently.
[Francoise laughing]
If that machine exists,
I can save you.
[Tyler] You can't be serious.
You want to go back to Willow Hill?
The place we all just escaped from?
[Isaac] Yes, I do.
But, first, I need to
visit an old friend...
at Nevermore.
[cello cover of Blue Oyster Cult's
"Don't Fear the Reaper" playing]
[Wednesday stops playing]
Enid?
Why didn't you
tell me you played?
I only do it when
I need to think.
Sounds like you're channeling
your inner Wednesday.
You have no idea.
We need to talk
about your situation.
My situation?
Denial isn't going to change it.
And there are added risks
for a potential Alpha
in their first lunar cycle.
Alpha.
Right.
Better get to the Lupin cages
before sundown. Just play it safe.
I know you're worried
about being a lone wolf,
but we need to know what
we're dealing with first.
[suspenseful music playing]
[Wednesday] This is
Rosaline Rotwood.
[Capri] Professor Orloff said she used
to teach in this room back in the day...
And lived in my
mother's cottage.
[Capri] What?
[Wednesday] I mean, Mrs. Addams.
In fact, I promised I would
drop by for tea this afternoon.
I'm already running late.
[Capri] Make it quick.
I want you locked in the
Lupin cages by sundown.
Mother...
Mrs. Addams?
[fixture clinks]
How could my mother
read this drivel?
[disembodied voice
whispering] Wednesday...
[jarring stinger]
Reckless child.
Tell me how I can
break this curse.
To reclaim your own flesh you must be
willing to die in this borrowed skin.
You have until dawn to
unravel the innermost secrets
of the life you've stepped into.
[Morticia] Enid Sinclair.
What are you doing in
here snooping around?
How dare you?
Mrs. Addams.
These books...
Did you write these?
That's none of your business.
It's just Wednesday's
never mentioned it.
Well, there are many parts of my
life I don't share with my daughter,
and I'd like to
keep it that way.
Wednesday put you up
to this, didn't she?
Hmm? Is this another attempt
to regain her ability?
Snooping around Rotwood's
musty seance chamber?
You can tell Wednesday we'll
discuss this at dinner tonight.
You can go now.
[Enid] I barely survived a
conversation with Mrs. Addams.
She'll see right through
me. You need to come.
You're going to a support group?
"Some of your parts. We help
make you feel whole again."
If anyone knows what it feels like
to not feel whole today, it's me.
[determined sigh]
Well, if I have to go,
I need to find
some Addams intel.
Wednesday's novel.
How bad can it be?
[Enid humming]
Evelyn. [chuckles]
That's the character
who's based off me, right?
"A trend-chasing, rainbow-loving,
social media addict,
whose... tastes in clothes and music
are a heinous assault on culture"?
"Despite her Lupin abilities, Evelyn
is feeble in both body and mind,
requiring... Viper's
pity and protection."
Is this really how
Wednesday feels about me?
[aching, distraught
music playing]
[bold, determined music playing]
That's it!
If Wednesday wants a heinous
assault... she's about to get one.
["Boombayah" by
BLACKPINK playing]
♪ BLACKPINK in your area ♪
[BLACKPINK singing in Korean]
Hi!
What the hell is going on here?
Looks like Wednesday
Addams has finally cracked?
[shrieking]
[Enid] It's worse
than last time!
[restrained seething]
[speaking in Tagalog]
Need to hang up now, my love.
[phone bleeps]
[ominous music playing]
Enid. Hey.
I was just talking to my
mom in the Philippines.
You and your mother
are awfully close.
[in Tagalog] "I miss you."
"I miss our walks
along the beach."
"I miss your sweet
lips most of all."
[in English] Or was that your
girlfriend you failed to mention
in an act of time-honored,
misogynistic deception?
How do you know Tagalog?
I picked it up when I was eight from
Datu, my Filipino fencing instructor.
He also taught me how to
castrate with a bolo knife.
I was going to tell you,
but it's complicated.
Then let me uncomplicate
it. We're done.
[in Tagalog] Never talk to me
again, you duplicitous Lothario.
[in English] Was that
clear enough for you?
Enid! Lupin cages, now!
You're late.
I can't go. It's a
matter of life or death.
It could be your life or death
if you don't. Come on, come on.
[sighs]
Hmm.
[Enid laughs]
[Enid whimpering in video]
So worth it.
Why are you on Enid's
side of the room?
It's none of your business.
What do you want?
As someone who's spent hours
obsessively studying you,
I know something's wrong.
Terribly wrong.
Your K-pop dance in the Link
was clearly a cry for help.
I'm guessing it's
PTSD from your coma.
Or maybe even a brain tumor.
I'm fine, Agnes.
There's no need for concern.
You know I prefer to
zig when others zag.
-[phone bleeps]
-[Enid chuckles]
When did you get a phone?
[Enid] Uh...
It's Enid's.
She left it behind.
Huh.
No electronics in
the Lupin cages.
It's probably smart.
No one wants their wolfing
out pics going viral.
Why would she be
in the Lupin cages?
There's not a full moon.
Capri stuck her in there. Right
after she broke up with Bruno.
Dumped that dumb dog like
yesterday's kitty litter.
She broke up with Bruno?
Why?
Tell me right now, you
creepy little creeper!
Why do you care about her
overheated YA werewolf drama?
If Enid knew you were trying
to keep her from dying,
then she might have
something to howl about.
What do you mean, try
to keep her from dying?
Your premonition... of course.
[Enid] Oh...
I can't believe she
would do this to me.
I'm starting to think
Enid is the problem.
Your obsession with saving
her has caused you to crack.
-Oof.
-Who can blame you?
Living with a clueless, boy-crazy
cliché like Enid Sinclair.
It's enough to put
anyone in a straitjacket.
Maybe it's time to cut her off.
Like a bad finger.
I'm certainly more than ready
to be best friends with you.
You don't know
anything about me.
You're just a sycophantic loser
that I use when it's convenient.
But we're not friends.
I don't even like you.
In fact, I wish you would
just stay invisible.
Forever!
[door opens]
[breathing unevenly]
[Orloff] As you may have heard,
Lisa is no longer in our group.
She's been reunited
with her torso.
We all support her decision.
But remember,
we are whole,
just the way we are.
[Agnes] Excuse me, I...
Sorry to interrupt.
I know I'm not
technically a body part,
but... the sign said,
"All are welcome."
And they are.
So please, share
whatever's on your mind.
I thought at Nevermore,
I would finally be seen.
[gentle, aching music playing]
Have real friends.
But the truth is,
I feel more invisible than ever.
We want you to know that
we all see you, Agnes.
Make yourself at home.
We have another newbie.
Welcome, Thing.
What would you like to
share with the group?
You don't have any idea
where you came from?
When you were found
by the Addams family,
the only clue to your past
was a silver signet ring.
Well, you're fortunate to have
people who care about you.
We may never know who
we were attached to.
You can't see yourself
as an appendage,
but as a whole person,
worthy of love and respect.
We are more than just
the sum of our parts.
But sometimes,
the parts are greater
than the whole.
-[Morticia gasps]
-[Gomez] Yes!
Bravo, Lurch.
You have outdone yourself.
[Gomez] Mm-hmm.
[Enid stifling gag reflex]
[cheeky, eccentric
music playing]
[Morticia] Delicious.
[Lurch growls]
Mmm.
Ooh, wow.
Yes.
[disgusted yelp]
Remind me what this is again?
Darling, don't you recognize
your favorite family dish?
-Roadkill pot pie.
-[Morticia] Mm-hmm.
Of course.
Yum!
-What's in it?
-[Gomez] Possum.
Little guy ran out
right in front of us.
Lurch backed up over it twice.
Tenderized it. Ooh, yeah.
He also added a little
leftover raccoon,
which gives that special
woodsy flavor you adore.
[weakly] Mmm.
[glass clinking]
[Lurch groans]
Now that we're all here together,
it's time for a serious discussion.
Your father and I have tried to instill
our family values in you children.
But we draw the line on lying.
I thought you said lying
was an important life skill.
Yes, like in business, politics,
jury duty... that's a big one.
You two have been lying to us.
And I'll give you one
chance to confess.
-There's still a punishment, right?
-Of course. Don't be silly.
I lied to you about Slurp.
I saw him at Pilgrim
World, and I let him go.
I'm really sorry, Pop.
So, um...
do I get the rack
or iron maiden?
We'll flip for it.
Come on. Let's go.
Please excuse us.
You ladies enjoy dinner.
Earlier, I caught Enid in Rosaline
Rotwood's secret seance chamber.
Any idea why she was snooping?
None, actually.
Hmm.
I see that bewildered
look in your eyes.
It's the same look I
noticed this morning.
-[Enid whimpers]
-And now it makes sense.
Your obsession for
getting your ability back
has finally made
you lose your mind.
What?
But don't worry.
I will have Lurch make
up the guest room.
No, that... that... that
really isn't necessary.
I sense your presence
again. Show yourself.
I demand it.
You're still as insufferably
bossy as you were in 10th grade.
Larissa?
-Who's Larissa?
-Shh!
Morticia, it's good to see you.
Oh, I just remembered. I...
Sit down.
I am Wednesday's
new spirit guide.
Wait.
If you're her guide,
why can't she see you?
[Weems] At your beloved
mother's suggestion,
Wednesday attempted to
gain temporary second sight
at Rosaline Rotwood's headstone.
That's why she dispatched
Enid to search for answers
in Rotwood's seance chamber.
Except that wasn't Enid.
It was Wednesday.
Enid?
Is that you in there?
Where's Wednesday?
Locked in the Lupin
cages until the morning.
It'll be too late.
They only have until
dawn to set this right.
We can't help them, Morticia.
They have to save themselves.
Mrs. Addams, I...
You must free Wednesday and
fix this together before dawn.
That's your only chance.
[grim, distressing
music playing]
[wheels buzzing]
[Isaac] I hope I'm not
late for the meeting.
Hello, Professor.
[shocked gasp]
Don't you recognize
your star student?
It can't be.
Isaac Night disappeared
30 years ago.
Correction, Professor.
I died 30 years ago.
Never underestimate
the power of science.
Isn't that what you told me?
Science has nothing
to do with it.
You're a perversion of nature.
Says the talking head in a jar.
But you're only alive...
because of me.
[chilling music playing]
My invention has given you
30 years of borrowed time.
[gears whirring frantically]
And now I've come to collect.
Isaac! Don't!
No! Stop!
Isaac!
[energy crackles]
[Orloff straining]
Don't worry, Professor.
I wouldn't let such a
great mind go to waste.
[chilling music intensifies]
[wet crunching,
smacking in distance]
[shrieks]
[jarring stinger]
[breathing shakily]
-[Isaac chuckles]
-[Francoise] Mmm.
What is that?
A power source for the
machine at Willow Hill.
Since their whole
electrical system was fried.
[bird cawing in distance]
[sinister music playing]
[whispers] Tyler.
Check outside.
[faint thud]
[jolting stinger]
[gasps softly]
Okay?
-It's nothing.
-Okay.
Seat belts.
Tyler.
Your little creeper told me
about your vision of my death.
Thanks for the trust.
I also know that if we
don't switch back by dawn,
we're both going to die.
And I am not checking
out looking like this.
[phone buzzing]
[Enid huffs]
[phone bleeps]
[Agnes] Wednesday... I know
we currently aren't friends,
but I found them.
I found Tyler Galpin
and Isaac Night.
I took a leaf out of
your detecting playbook.
I'm currently hiding in their
trunk along with a very...
very dead body.
At least somebody
stayed on task.
Agnes, are you insane?
Get the hell out of there!
No.
It's too late.
Sharing my location
with you now.
[phone beeping]
-They're headed to Willow Hill.
-We need to switch back.
After we save Agnes and
take down the Galpins.
[music fades]
[energy humming]
I can finally keep that
promise I made to you.
-[Francoise, fondly] Hmm.
-To free you from this horrible curse.
[Isaac] Here.
-We have to secure you for the procedure.
-Yeah.
You think being a
Hyde is a curse?
It's the most free
I've ever felt.
[Francoise] That so-called
freedom comes at a price.
Every transformation
has a human cost.
Until it finally
steals your life.
I designed this machine to
remove Outcast abilities.
If I can take away your
mother's Hyde side,
I can stop her from dying.
[phone bleeps]
[faint clink in distance]
Someone else is here.
[Isaac] Uh...
[Agnes gasps]
Little snoop is one of
Wednesday's friends.
What do you want
me to do with her?
Put her in a cell.
I'll need a snack once I'm done.
[Agnes straining]
This way! The lab is
through that door.
[Agnes pants] Ah!
[Isaac hums softly]
[Tyler] Make yourself at home.
We can deal with that
Nevermore brat later.
[Isaac] Ready, Francoise?
[machinery humming]
Wednesday!
[door opens]
Look who showed up.
-Don't forget about me.
-[Tyler grunts]
-[Wednesday] Leave her alone!
-No full moon to save you...
[Tyler grunts]
[panting]
[chains rattling]
[Agnes] Wednesday?
You need to calm down or
you're gonna wolf out.
Too late. Get out!
[flesh distending,
bones cracking]
[Wednesday groaning]
[machinery whirring
intensifying]
[Isaac sputtering]
[exhales] Wednesday.
[forceful pounding]
[pounding continues]
[heroic music swelling]
[Wednesday snarling]
Tyler, no!
Wednesday? Wednesday!
Wednesday, we have to go now!
[uncontrollable whirring]
[heightened, suspenseful
music playing]
Let's go!
[Francoise] Go! Gotta
get out of here!
[music trails off]
Are you okay?
[breathing heavily]
[delicate, emotional
music playing]
Thank you for saving my life.
I just asked myself,
"What would Enid do?"
So you guys did swap bodies.
I knew something was up.
You've been acting
really weird all day.
And you just called her
Wednesday back there, so...
we're still friends.
Well, don't worry. It's okay.
It's really hard for me too.
But we'll get used to this
whole new look together.
Not if I can help it.
Agnes, go back to Nevermore.
Um...
Where are we going?
[grim, imposing music playing]
Now what?
Rotwood said we had to unravel
the innermost secrets of
the lives we stepped into.
[scoffs] Fine.
I'll go first.
You know what I love
about being Wednesday?
Your fearlessness.
Except when it comes to
your mom. But... I get it.
[sighs] She can be a lot.
You're afraid she'll never
accept you for who you truly are.
That your darkness is even
too much for her to grasp.
You'll become the disappointment
she'll never want to speak of.
Just like your aunt.
I can feel it in your bones.
That's why you push her away.
But maybe she has more to
teach you than you think.
[introspective music playing]
The best thing about being
Enid is your quiet strength.
You think being an Alpha
will mean you'll be alone.
I won't let that happen.
You need to stop trying so hard
for people who don't deserve it.
Like Bruno, who mistook
your kindness for weakness.
It's not.
It's your power.
Which I could barely
handle for one night.
[chuckles softly]
[emotional music building]
I regret ever
underestimating you.
[emotional music swells]
[music trails off]
Oh my God.
Wednesday!
We're alive!
I feel so warm and fuzzy!
And I feel as cold as a cadaver.
Which means I'm me
and you're you! Ah!
[jolting stinger]
Enid.
Why don't you go back to
the dorm and get changed?
I'll be right behind you.
Good idea. I could
seriously use a bubble bath.
[moody, uneasy music playing]
The premonition of Enid's
imminent death is no more.
So why the dour face?
Your actions today have
put another life at risk.
Follow me.
[birds cawing]
[Weems] An Addams must die.
The question is...
which one?
[moody music intensifying]
[music trails off]
[jauntily macabre
outro music playing]