William Faulkner said,
"The past is never dead."
"It's not even the past."
In fact, it's all
still happening.
If Isaac's goal is
to save his sister,
why kidnap Pugsley?
All right. Spread out, guys.
-You, that way.
-Pugsley!
What does a
brain-eating genius need
with my half-wit brother?
No sign of your son.
Any idea why someone
would kidnap him?
It's a total mystery, Sheriff.
Can you think of anyone who has
a grudge against your family?
Could this be some
kind of revenge?
Are you blaming us for
our son's kidnapping?
The search parties will
run through the night.
Parents who were at the gala have
already left with their kids.
All other students
will be packed up
and on their way home
by tomorrow afternoon.
I'm sorry. We're doing
everything we can.
I sent your father and Lurch
out to join the search parties.
They won't find Pugsley.
Isaac's too smart.
You need to work together, and to pool
your psychic abilities to locate him.
My mother is a Dove who's
blind to malevolence,
and my psychic ability is currently
on an unauthorized leave of absence.
That's why you must turn to
the other Raven in your family.
My mother?
These are desperate times.
Mama, I appreciate you coming
back on such short notice.
Why would anyone bother
kidnapping Pugsley?
Not to cast aspersions,
but I know higher value
corpses than that boy.
His kidnapper isn't
looking for ransom money.
He's being used as a pawn to keep
us away, or a ploy to draw us in.
So many delightful
memories of this room.
I can still hear the terrified
shrieks of my classmates
during Rotwood's Advanced
Possession Class.
Scaredy-cats.
This does require actual
physical connection.
Now we must clear our minds
of all past grievances.
My past grievances are like fine
wine. They get better with age.
Likewise.
Doves and Ravens together ignite
With wings of darkness
and piercing eyes
Guide us to truth
through night and morn
To this let our powers be sworn
I didn't drive all this way
to hold hands in the dark.
How long do we have
to keep this up?
Mama! For once just be quiet.
We're trying to find Pugsley.
I feel something.
-I feel it too.
-Do you sense it, Wednesday?
Hurry, Gomez!
No one will ever
know we were here.
I saw you and Father burying
Isaac under the Skull Tree
back when you were students.
If there was ever a time to unburden
yourself of the truth, now is it.
You've wasted enough of my time.
The night of Isaac's accident,
your father and I
were at his laboratory
in Iago Tower.
Isaac was certain his machine
would permanently cure Francoise.
That she would never again live
in fear of turning into a Hyde.
But the machine required a great
amount of energy to power it.
And for that,
Isaac turned to his best friend.
Father.
What could Gomez have
possibly contributed?
Back then, Gomez was just
as electrifying as Pugsley.
And Gomez was more than
happy to help his friend.
But Isaac tricked him.
He needed more than a spark.
Unbeknownst to Francoise,
Isaac was willing to sacrifice
your father's life to save hers.
He even dug your father's grave
under the Skull
Tree in preparation.
By the time I arrived,
my darling Gomez
was close to death.
My sabotage sent the
machine into a frenzy.
Francoise, she
survived the explosion,
but Isaac didn't.
And as for your father,
the experience permanently robbed
him of his Outcast ability.
Hmm.
Why cover it up?
Because Augustus
Stonehurst threatened us.
We knew he built Isaac
the lab in secret.
If we breathed a word, he
would've turned us in for murder.
Hurry, Gomez.
No one will ever
know we were here.
So you buried Isaac in the same
grave he intended for Father?
Yes.
Isaac must be trying again.
This time using Pugsley
as the power source.
That Addams headstone, the
one I saw in my premonition,
must have Pugsley's name on it.
I think it's best that you and Thing go
with Grandmama until Pugsley is found.
For once, your mother
and I are in agreement.
These are our sins, Wednesday.
We will face them.
I won't put you in danger again.
Too late.
I'm sorry.
You deserve better than that.
I didn't realize we were
back on speaking terms.
It took me a minute.
But I'm ready to be friends.
If that's cool with you.
I'd like that very much.
Why the change of heart?
I realized that our
breakup wasn't about me.
You know, it's nobody's fault
that your feelings changed.
So I can either be angry about it,
or I can just accept it and move on.
Actually, Bianca told me that.
She can be very persuasive.
Please tell me that you're done
with lying wolves and beta-gorgons.
I put together a list
of potential boyfriends.
I already cross-referenced them based
on compatible social media profiles.
Once you've narrowed it down,
I can pay each one
an invisible visit.
See what they've left
out of their bios.
Hmm.
I appreciate the assist,
but I think I'm gonna rip a page
out of the Wednesday Addams playbook
and take a break from romance.
It's not very fun
to be tied up and
treated like a pet...
is it?
"Mystery meat sandwich!"
"Your favorite."
Conserve your energy.
You're gonna need it.
I wish I was at least in
one of these pictures.
I never understood your
desire for a Normie life.
But... knowing what Stonehurst
did to you in that lab...
Neither of us got the
end that we deserved.
That changes tonight.
Promise me,
no matter what happens,
you'll do it.
What we discussed.
I need your word.
I made Hyde tracks about 20 miles
north and dropped Pugsley's costume,
then made an anonymous
tip like you said.
Good, huh?
That'll keep the
cops off our trail.
Now, it's time to position
your old flame onto the board.
Wednesday will know
she's being played.
Yeah, an Addams... would never
sacrifice one of their own.
Not even a pawn.
And that emotional weakness
will be our checkmate.
Any Pugsley update?
Still missing. But he's alive.
Isaac is hellbent on
saving his sister.
I know he needs Pugsley. Just
need to figure out when and where.
Crap. He's here.
Who?
Isaac?
No. My dad.
He usually sends some ran
do assistant to collect me.
Your mom couldn't come get you?
She's busy with her new
Normie husband and baby.
I was the mistake that kept
her and my dad together
long past their sell-by date.
Gunpowder, penicillin, the rack.
Those were all mistakes.
I just want to say
that I love us.
We're like the three musketeers.
Careful.
Agnes!
Bye. See you next year.
I wish I could help, but I
have to get to the Lupin cages.
Capri read me the riot act.
Lock in early and stay calm.
So I have my meditation
app, my fave playlist,
and an extra supply
of colloidal silver.
What could go wrong, right?
I'll be there first thing in
the morning to let you out.
Promise?
You. We're waking
the dead again.
How long until your
corpse moths are airborne?
Unfortunately, they're
permanently grounded.
Corpse moths only have
a 36-hour life cycle.
Wednesday, I'm really sorry.
Pugsley wanted to be my
friend and I blew him off.
Maybe if I'd been nicer, he
wouldn't have felt the need
to become BFFs with a zombie.
I am my brother's keeper.
I simply should have caged
him for his own protection.
I'm heading to the Hummer shed.
Have to hibernate my bees early.
Wanna come...
Wednesday, I'm on my
way to see your parents.
A hiker found Pugsley's costume.
I'm redeploying the search
from Jericho to Burlington.
Sounds like a ploy to
draw you off the scent.
I follow evidence, not hunches.
Finally, I get my office back.
Dort's crashing downfall
has validated my legacy.
The board will now look back
upon the Weems era with fondness.
Nevermore clearly needs a
steady hand on the rudder.
A leader of impeccable
moral character.
You covered up Rowan's murder
and the existence of a Hyde.
Mistakes were made.
But that's all in the past.
I went out to the Hummers shed.
Slurp was there, except
he looks totally human.
He told me to give you this.
Said if I breathe a word to
anyone else, he'd come for me.
Wednesday, I'm scared.
Go back to your
dorm. Lock the door.
Now!
Isaac thinks he can lure
me out to finish me off.
When you get a clear shot...
put a bolt in his zombie brain.
Tyler warned me you
were formidable.
And now I've witnessed
the havoc you can wreak.
Give me my brother, crawl back into
your hole, and stay dead this time.
-I know what you did to my father.
-Yet I'm the one who died.
Thanks to him and
your dear mother.
Why don't you let your brother
pay for their mistakes,
and we'll call it even?
You don't have the machine.
Willow Hill and Iago
Tower have been destroyed.
It would take months to rebuild.
By the time you did, it'd be
too late to save your sister.
I... I applaud the effort.
You keep me talking
while your faithful right
hand takes his shot.
Gotcha.
Except he's never been yours.
He's mine.
Turns out your parents didn't
kill all of me that night.
Cute.
Imagine my surprise
when I saw my right hand
wandering the halls of
Willow Hill without me.
And a DaVinci... is nothing
without his right hand.
Your mother cut it off.
Causing my machine to go
out of control and explode.
The power surge must have
somehow animated my hand.
In your case, the part is
greater than the whole.
Now I am complete.
The Addams family
ends tonight.
Starting with you.
We have an appointment
at Iago Tower.
Your pathetic little life
will finally have a purpose.
Now we can finally
fix our family.
Hello!
Come on.
Take a deep breath
in, and slowly exhale.
Now visualize the wolf within.
A powerful but gentle spirit.
Be mindful that tonight
belongs to tranquility...
Enid! I need you.
-Agnes? I thought you left.
-I couldn't abandon Wednesday.
So I ditched my dad
when he stopped for gas.
Isaac buried Wednesday
under the Skull Tree.
And I can't dig her out.
What? Oh my God.
-Where's Thing?
-Longer story.
I'll fill you in on the way.
We haven't got much time!
Wednesday, we're
here! Hang on!
I hear a heartbeat,
but it's weak.
We aren't gonna
get to her in time.
No, no, no.
I'm not strong
enough like this.
You won't be able to turn back.
You're an Alpha.
I can't let her die.
Wednesday, wake up. Wake up!
Please. Please.
I enjoyed that.
Enid?
It was the only way to save you.
Go track her. Now!
Wednesday! Wednesday!
Thank the spirits.
Or just one in particular.
If you don't hurry, you'll
have nothing left to save.
Where's Pugsley?
It's all still here.
Good.
How are we gonna put
this junk back together?
We're not.
I am.
Even if you never told
me the truth about Thing,
why didn't you tell him?
Because sometimes the truth
is better left buried.
Thing had no memory of Isaac.
After everything Isaac did to your father,
why burden Thing with that knowledge?
I like to think whatever trace of goodness
was in Isaac somehow ended up in Thing.
Except now he's reattached to Isaac,
and he's about to kill your son.
Mad scientist,
cliché soundtrack.
Perfect.
Darling,
you call the sheriff.
Leave this to us.
Querida, save our boy.
Isaac, are you all right?
I'm fine.
Secure the power source.
I've been waiting for
this moment for 30 years.
Get ready.
We're about to fry your battery.
It's time, Isaac.
Do it now.
Now!
You promised me.
Wait! What are you doing?
Mom, we're here to save you.
It's too late for me, sweetie.
This is your time now.
We can save you from this life.
Give you a fresh start.
No, no, you have no right
to take my power from me!
Love you.
Don't do this. Please.
I love you, baby.
Mom!
You take the main staircase.
I'll take the ladder.
Mom, please!
Mom!
We have company.
Please, don't do this!
Kill me.
-Why?
-I missed.
Tyler, no!
No!
Isaac!
Isaac.
It's okay.
-Wednesday?
-Shh.
It's your mommy.
I haven't enjoyed a mother-son
relationship like this since Psycho.
Tyler? Honey?
Baby...
Hold on, Pugsley. Hold on.
Isaac!
You have something
that belongs to me.
Come on! Come on!
Go.
Go, go, go!
Mom. Dad.
Tish!
Help me. Help me with this.
I guess your premonition
didn't come true after all.
Because of you,
I lost the only person
I ever truly loved.
Isaac! Isaac!
It's over.
Let my daughter go.
Sorry, old friend.
Now you two will know
what real pain feels like.
One more step, and
I snap her neck!
Thing, we know you're
still in there.
Come back to us,
Thing. We love you.
We're your family!
This was never part
of your family.
It's a part of me!
You missed!
Come on, Thing.
What is happening?
-Ah!
-Doesn't take a genius to figure that out.
Time's up.
Welcome back, Thing.
Knowing you were cut from the
literal cloth of an evil genius,
it makes sense why
we're so compatible.
How does it feel finally
knowing the truth?
That you can't control the past.
But the future is in your own hand.
What's it going to be?
-What have you been able to figure out?
-This was on a wildlife cam this morning.
That's Enid.
She was heading north,
just five miles from
the Canadian border.
What about Capri?
Was she able to provide intel that
could tell us where Enid is going?
She's MIA.
Probably on the hunt
for her next job,
now that Nevermore is nevermore.
Hello, Tyler.
Whoever you are, just walk away.
We both know you can't
survive out here alone.
Not for long.
But I can save you.
Yeah, I'm done with
mothers and masters.
I'm not interested
in being either.
I'm offering...
a support system for
people just like you.
Fellow Hydes,
hidden away where the
world can't find them.
You'd be part of a pack,
creating a bond that transcends
the need for a single master.
What's in it for you?
You're a werewolf. I
can smell it from here.
My father was a Hyde.
This isn't gonna explode
in my face, is it?
A little snack for the road.
Don't forget to pace yourself.
Whoa. Thanks.
You know, I was thinking,
over the break, if
you're not too busy,
you could come for a visit?
Really? To your actual house?
That's what friends do, right?
Hmm.
Wednesday.
Wait.
I would like you
to have something.
Aunt Ophelia's journal.
Yes.
As I keep being reminded,
harboring secrets can
have deadly consequences.
Every family has dark
chapters, Wednesday.
Including ours.
Thank you, Mother.
It's gratifying to
see you two together.
Restoring your familial bond
was the first big step in
regaining your psychic ability.
Now that it's happened, I'm
taking a well-deserved sabbatical.
Whoever thought that the person to
keep my spirit alive would be you?
Until we meet again, Wednesday.
Whoa, it's sunny out there.
It will be a relief sleeping
under our own leaky roof tonight.
Oh, let's get your
things. Vamos.
I won't be going home.
I got your message.
I'm always up for a road trip.
So where to? Slaughter
Beach? Death Valley?
We're headed north
to rescue Enid.
She's an Alpha.
Ooh, I hear those puppies got fangs
that can rip you apart like taffy,
and claws that can slice
you up like lunch meat.
What fun!
Go.
Another year at Nevermore
ends in carnage and chaos.
Unanswered questions
hover like vultures.
Why did I slice Tyler's bonds
rather than his jugular?
And will that impulsive act
of mercy become my undoing?
As for my parents, their
smiles don't erase their lies.
Was my mother's gift of
Ophelia's diary an act of trust,
or silent desperation?
First I must find Enid.
I gave her my word.
But who exactly will
return by my side?
My friend?
Or the beast that's
consumed her?
Aunt Ophelia.
Secrets are the bedrock
of the Addams family.
Toxic and festering
just below the surface.
Ophelia!
As I venture into the unknown,
I am determined to exhume
every lie and deception,
or die trying.
Sounds like a perfect
vacation to me.