[funky calypso
lounge music playing]
[bartender] What can I get you?
[Dort] Three rocks, two
fingers of Jack, and a...
[bartender] One splash of water.
You can never go wrong
ordering a Sinatra.
Wait. You look familiar.
You were in The Crucible at
the Jupiter Dinner Theater.
Your John Proctor
was spellbinding.
The audience was hanging on your
every word, particularly the ladies.
You saw that show?
You're the only one
who's ever remembered.
I haven't seen you
at Tiki Tails before.
-I'm Arnold Hunt.
-Barry Dort.
I manage one of the Sirens.
Gabrielle.
I figured a talented guy like you would
be knocking them dead out in Hollywood.
I mean, you certainly
have the looks, charisma.
I took my shot in LA.
Even landed a recurring on a
soap opera. Medical Affairs.
No way. [chuckles] That was my mom's
favorite show, God rest her soul.
She never missed an episode.
I played Dr. Gideon Sterling.
Until my long-lost brother came
back from the dead, stole my wife,
and they blew me
up in my Porsche.
Tough break.
Yeah, career took a...
a nosedive after that,
so I packed up my Corolla
and moved back home.
Luck is what happens when
preparation meets opportunity.
And you're in luck because, boy, do
I have the right opportunity for you.
I don't need a manager, pal.
-Those days are long gone.
-I... I'm talking about something bigger.
I see a lot of broken
people in my travels,
especially Outcasts, and I
have ideas how to fix them.
I want to create a place where
like-minded people come together
to follow a shared vision
of enlightenment and growth.
Sounds like a cult.
Nobody likes the C-word.
I prefer the term "movement."
I have an entire business plan,
and I even wrote an
instruction manual
on how to build a better life.
I'm self-aware enough to know that this
mug isn't going to convince anyone.
I've seen you on stage, Arnold.
You have that
indefinable star quality,
and this is the part
you were born to play.
You're serious.
You remember The Wizard of Oz.
I'm like the guy Toto
finds behind the curtain,
secretly pulling the levers.
You will be the great
and powerful Oz,
the face of our movement,
the inspirational leader
who touches people's souls,
and persuades them to part
with their hard-earned cash
for a chance to be a part of
something bigger than themselves.
[intriguing music playing]
So does this
movement have a name?
How about Morning Song?
Because every dawn brings
the light of a new day.
So, what do you say?
[chilling, suspenseful
music playing]
[faint laughter]
[Bianca] No, you can't
do that. [laughs]
Here.
[door creaking open]
Principal Dort, I can explain.
[Dort] No need, Bianca.
Your mother and I
go back a long way.
Don't we, Gabrielle?
[mysterious music playing]
[Gabrielle] Ah...
Who do you think introduced her
to Gideon all those years ago?
You're part of Morning Song?
I am Morning Song.
And we had a good thing going
until you two poked your tails
in and stirred things up.
Fortunately, I
don't hold grudges.
What do you want, Barry?
By my count, you've been
living here rent-free.
But the free ride is over.
It's time to get
back to work, ladies.
[music builds to climax]
[music ends]
[jauntily macabre music playing]
[music trails off]
[indistinct chatter]
How much longer is
this going to take?
I can't have my guests
arrive to a crime scene.
I assumed you were
canceling the gala,
out of respect for
your late colleague.
Oh, I know Professor Orloff would
want us to keep calm and Outcast on.
That's the Nevermore way.
Doubt anyone's going to show
up once this hits the press.
Perhaps we can just say there was
an unfortunate classroom accident.
Do you really want it out there that
the Jericho Sheriff's Department
still hasn't caught
a killer zombie?
This isn't over.
From now on, my deputies
handle campus security.
-[scoffs]
-That's a non-negotiable.
[birds cawing]
We both know Santiago and her crew have
no chance against two Hydes and a zombie.
[Santiago] Let's move.
Your newfound cynicism
is refreshing.
Only you would leave psychic
scar tissue in a body swap.
Nice try telling me
to stay invisible.
Shh, save your apologies.
I'm not even a little sorry.
And you should be grateful
we came to rescue you
when there's a
premonition I'd die.
And yet it never comes to pass.
Worst premonition ever.
-[scoffs]
-The premonition has changed.
You're no longer
the one who dies.
Really? Yes!
Wait. Who dies?
An Addams.
Which is why I need to flush out Isaac and
the Galpin family before he gets to mine.
Your search may
start closer to home.
-Ahh.
-Mmm!
Organic.
[grim music building]
What has your braids in a
twist, my little tempest?
The latest exhumation from the growing
secrets you've been keeping from me.
Not only have you known the
identity of Pugsley's zombie...
Isaac Night was your roommate.
He was more than that.
He was my closest friend.
Your father was the only
one who could charm his way
into Isaac's clockwork heart.
I tried to protect him from people
who wanted to exploit his genius.
Like Augustus Stonehurst.
That's why he built the
lab for him in Iago Tower.
Stonehurst saw him as the key to unlocking
the secrets of Outcast abilities.
[Gomez] But Isaac...
had his own plans in mind.
[Morticia] Hmm.
He thought he could use science to
extract Francoise's Hyde ability.
I had no idea that Isaac
was Pugsley's zombie
until I saw him
at Pilgrim World.
[Wednesday] He's not just
some brainless pet anymore.
Isaac has fully regenerated.
And he's reunited with
Francoise and Tyler.
Who did not leave
town as promised.
[Morticia huffs]
[crunches, gurgles]
[Morticia] Larissa told me it was you
snooping around here in Enid's body.
You and Weems have been
conspiring behind my back?
You went to Rotwood's grave.
It must have been
your grand mama
who planted that pernicious
idea in your head.
It may have been pernicious,
but it was enlightening.
How long have you been
writing, Barbara Jean?
[plants gurgling]
Since I was your age.
But I made the mistake of giving
my mother one of my early efforts.
The sound of her...
humiliating cackle
still haunts me.
So, after that I decided to keep
my literary career a secret.
Your father has no inkling. That's
the way I'd like to keep it.
My lips are sealed
for my own protection.
I began to profusely vomit after
reading the first five pages.
Well, perhaps one day
you'll appreciate the intoxicating
power of weaving mystery and passion.
We have more pressing
family matters at hand.
My premonition has
changed, Mother.
Enid no longer dies.
One of us does.
An Addams.
[foreboding music playing]
I'd like to sacrifice Pugsley.
Enid, wait.
Please. I... I've
been looking for you.
I've been avoiding you, which
I'll do for the rest of my life.
-Let me explain the situation with Sofia.
-Is that your girlfriend's name?
We decided to take a break
when I came to Nevermore.
I figured I'd join a new pack here.
I wanted to keep things casual.
[sighs softly] But
then I met someone.
I can't stop thinking about her.
I'm not going to
compete for you.
I know. So I finally broke
things off with her last night.
You've been keeping this
a secret all semester.
I don't know that I
can trust you again.
I'll do whatever it takes. Can
I still escort you to the gala?
Enid Sinclair, in
my classroom now!
You broke out of the Lupin
cages last night. Why?
Just wasn't really myself.
That's not an excuse.
Becoming an Alpha isn't
something you can take lightly.
Especially with a
full moon in two days.
That doesn't sound
ominous at all.
If a young Alpha transforms
under a full moon,
there's a very real chance you
could remain in your werewolf form.
For how long?
Wait.
You mean, like, forever?
I'm afraid it's worse.
Alphas who
permanently transform,
they're hunted and killed
by other werewolves.
It's a form of self-policing.
This is a living nightmare.
If you follow the precautions,
you should be fine.
Before sundown, lock yourself in
the Lupin cages and keep calm.
You're not alone in this, Enid.
Your pack is your strength.
[breathing shakily]
Leaving?
If you won't give me
permission to kill Wednesday,
we need to get the
hell out of Jericho.
The Addams family's not your
problem anymore, sweetie.
We have a bigger plan for them.
Leave it to your Uncle Isaac.
Because he's been
crushing it so far.
Every experiment has
unforeseen complications.
We'll be prepared next time.
There is no next time.
Your machine was destroyed.
It doesn't take a genius
to see that you failed.
The only thing that I care about
is saving my sister.
The one factor I don't need
in that equation is you.
Stop it. The minute we turn
on each other, we're dead.
One of us is already dead.
[Francoise coughing]
Francoise?
Her medicine, find it.
It's empty.
[somber, distraught
music playing]
I need some more.
[frustrated growl]
There's an animal hospital
in town. Come with me.
[Francoise coughing]
[morbidly intriguing
music playing]
Check in the back.
We're looking for anything that can
point us to where they're hiding.
Isaac isn't going anywhere until he
can save his sister from being a Hyde.
[delicately mysterious
music playing]
All Francoise ever
wanted was a normal life,
and she had it for
a fleeting moment.
The last time I stood in this room,
she asked me to be her maid of honor.
I knew she hadn't told
Galpin about her condition,
so I declined.
We didn't speak again.
Spare me your saccharine
stroll down memory lane.
Then perhaps you can tell
me how you plan to take on
the Galpin family
monster mash-up.
Your sharp tongue won't be
enough to keep them at bay.
If you're not here to help,
feel free to dissipate.
[music swells, trails off]
[suspenseful music playing]
For a couple of Hydes,
they fled like rats.
Now I understand why Isaac was so
hell-bent on saving his sister.
She's running out of time.
[delicate, foreboding
music playing]
[Eugene] A New
England corpse moth.
Extraordinary specimen.
Where'd you find it?
Following someone's
emotional support zombie.
You found Slurp?
Tweezed these from Slurp
when they were larvae.
Now they're about to enter
their migratory phase.
-What's that?
-When they return to their host body.
-To lay their eggs.
-What if the body's on the run?
[sighs] I bet they
can still find it.
Insect GPS beats Google
Maps every day of the week.
I just wanted a friend.
What, couldn't find
one with a pulse?
I tried, okay? But no
one was interested.
[melancholy music playing]
[sighs]
Go find your host.
[enigmatic, intriguing
music playing]
[faint police radio chatter]
Hey.
I saw this and went to go check on
your mom, but she's not in the room.
She was afraid
Gideon was onto her.
And now that the sheriff has
deputies crawling all over campus,
it was a matter of time
before she was discovered.
Wait, she left?
But where's she going?
I'm not sure.
She thought it was
better I didn't know.
It wouldn't be the first
time she's disappeared on me.
At least now you don't
have to worry about us.
Bianca. What's going on?
Ms. Barclay, can I
see you in my office?
Just drop it, okay?
It's better for
everyone this way.
[cryptic music playing]
[door opens]
[music trails off]
Grandmama?
I'm just biding my time
enjoying your novel.
Viper's mother, Dominica,
is pitch perfect.
How do you describe her?
"A clingy stay-at-home optimist
that makes Viper want to shed her
skin more times than a cobra."
[indulgent laughter]
Speaking of your mother, she
crystal balled me earlier.
Gave me an earful about steering
you to Professor Rotwood's grave.
Said there were complications.
I'm just relieved
that you're unscathed.
Neither of us have an
iota of compassion.
It's one of our most
endearing traits.
Tell me what really
brings you to Nevermore.
Your weasel of a principal
called last night.
I've heard kidnapping
victims sound less desperate.
He's offering me the moon to
donate to your mother's gala.
I thought that ship
had sailed, capsized,
and sunk to the bottom
of the Mariana Trench.
Of course it has. But
you know what I say...
The bigger the offer,
the sweeter the grovel.
You want to see the whites of
his eyes when you reject him.
There are few greater thrills
than witnessing the exact moment
when a man's spirit is broken.
Time to put Dort
out of his misery.
If he hasn't drowned in
his flop sweat already.
[Hester] Um...
Perhaps what you and your mother
need is a break from each other.
Come stay with me
for the summer.
I could teach you about
the family business.
I realize you're going to be
a literary enfant terrible,
but death is recession proof.
Thank you, Grandmama.
I knew you'd come under
my black wing eventually.
You may be an Addams,
but you're a Frump at heart.
What little heart you have.
Hester Frump,
it's an honor to have the
duchess of the dearly departed
haunt the halls of
Nevermore once again.
Savor it. I expect this
visit to be brief and final.
Then I won't waste
another second.
As I said on the phone,
your generosity will not
only ensure our future,
but will build a monument
to your life and work.
Introducing...
[grandiose fanfare trumpeting]
...the School of
Mortuary Sciences at...
Frump Tower.
Nevermore will be the
preeminent academy
for tomorrow's morticians,
embalmers, and funeral directors.
This will include updating
the campus cemetery
with Frump-branded headstones,
and replacing the
orchard with a body farm.
Death, Nevermore, and Frump.
-Can you think of a more unholy trinity?
-[Hester chuckles]
A masterful presentation.
My ego has never been
more expertly stroked.
But flattery is
like formaldehyde.
It is to be sniffed,
never swallowed.
Which is why I
have zero intention
of giving one cold cent
to this moth-eaten dump.
It was worth a shot.
[door opens]
Bianca, would you please
escort Ms. Frump to her car?
You will leave your entire
fortune to Nevermore.
That is your legacy.
You will present this decision
to your family and the world
without raising suspicion.
You will attend the gala
as the guest of honor.
[entrancing music playing]
And once I snap my fingers, you
won't remember I was ever here.
[entrancing music subsides]
[Hester exhales]
[door opens]
[door closes]
Hey, we need a vet!
Please, it's urgent!
-Sorry, I'm closing...
-It's an emergency. A car hit my dog.
-I can't move him by myself. Please.
-Where is he? Let's...
[vet grunts]
[chilling music playing]
[wet crunching]
You said she needs
a transfusion.
The pills they gave her at Willow
Hill suppressed her Hyde gene,
thus prolonging her life.
And when she
transformed to save you,
it must have exacerbated
her condition.
Are you saying this is my
fault? I'm killing her?
No.
But delaying her treatment will.
What your mother needs is blood.
Hyde blood.
Roll up your sleeve.
[chilling music subsides]
[elegant, lilting music rises]
[indistinct chatter]
I know you're here, Larissa.
[Weems] The gala will no
doubt be a rousing success.
Morticia Addams
will save Nevermore.
And the Larissa Weems era will
be buried once and for all.
It's never been my intention to
overshadow your achievements.
And yet,
it always ends up happening.
What has Wednesday done now?
It's not her this time.
Your mother is using your estrangement
to pull Wednesday closer to her.
I envied so much of
your life, Morticia.
But not your relationship
with that old bat.
-Thank you for saying so.
-[chuckles] Don't thank me yet.
You're more like your
mother than you think.
[scoffs]
I'm talking about your pathological
predilection for secrets.
Larissa, that's
completely unfair.
Is it?
You have failed to be
forthcoming with Wednesday
about your true relationship
with Francoise and Isaac.
Her vision has changed.
An Addams dies now.
Don't let this rip apart the family
you've spent your life trying to protect.
Tell her the truth
before tragedy strikes.
If I have to spend my nights in this
cage, I should make it feel like home.
-How goes the Hyde hunt?
-I put some feelers out.
They should be honing in on
Isaac's rotting flesh as we speak.
What's wrong, Enid?
Fun fact I learned today.
If a young Alpha wolfs
out on a full moon,
there's a high chance that
I could never change back.
Like ever. And if that isn't enough,
I'll be hunted by other werewolves.
The full moon is in two days. How
are you supposed to prevent that?
By staying calm. Trying to distract
myself with things that make me happy.
Like, picking a
dress for the gala.
For a gala you aren't
going to attend?
Bruno asked me.
As a friend.
Capri granted me an exception
for my dance routine,
as long as I lock up afterwards.
Capri said I didn't have to face
this Alpha business on my own.
That my strength is in my pack.
But the truth is...
[tender, emotional
music playing]
...you are my pack, Wednesday.
[inhales, exhales sharply]
If I wolfed out and couldn't,
you know, change back,
would you come and find me?
I have no problem
hunting you down.
[emotional music swells]
-[Enid] Ajax!
-Bianca's in trouble.
Have you heard of
Gideon Sterling?
I can't believe Bianca had a whole crime
drama going on and none of us knew!
Now her mom's missing.
I think that Dort's involved.
Sheriff Santiago and her deputies
are crawling all around the campus.
We have to tell someone!
Dort thinks we're in the dark.
I do my best work in the dark.
Wednesday.
Perfect timing.
Come look at my new tower.
Oh, that's just the tip of the
Frump philanthropic iceberg.
You said the only charity in
life was a quick, painless death.
Since my own family
has little interest
in the empire I've built
one grave at a time,
I've decided all my
spoils should be used
to educate future
generations of Outcasts.
Can you believe this
woman's generosity?
No.
I can't.
I'm still gonna inherit your
vintage car collection, right?
Not even a rusty
hubcap, my darling.
Our door has always been
open to you, Hester.
You're the one who boycotted our
wedding, and declined invitations
to all family gatherings.
I'm done with arguing about the
past. I only care about the future.
What Principal Dort and I have planned
will get Nevermore back on track.
Like barring Outcasts without
an ability from enrollment.
Like that inadequate
husband of yours.
Being an Outcast
is a state of mind.
No, dear. That's a platitude losers
say to make them feel like winners.
Let's just celebrate the fact
that Nevermore's future is secure.
Group selfie? [Dort chuckles]
[Dort] You, uh... Oh.
[Bianca grunting]
Wednesday. I thought you were
taking a break from the team.
Sabbatical's over.
[tense music pulsing]
[Bianca pants]
En garde.
-I've barely seen you all semester.
-We have different extracurriculars.
You do comas. I do a cappella.
And galas.
You've taken to those
like a Siren to water.
Your mother deserves
most of the credit.
Her attention to
detail is incredible.
-I enjoyed working with her.
-Speaking of mothers, how's yours?
Haven't seen her
since the summer.
You missed her when she was hiding
in that classroom off the quad?
I don't know what Ajax told
you, but stay out of it!
You've involved my family,
so that's an impossibility.
Dort is blackmailing you
and your mother, isn't he?
That's why you Siren-songed
my grandmother.
The four horsemen of the apocalypse would
have to gallop through her tombstones
before that woman gave
a cent to this school.
[music builds, steadies]
I thought I had freed my
mom from my stepfather.
But it turns out, Gideon
is just the front man.
And Dort is behind it all.
He was playing everyone
from the start.
He plans to steal your
grandmother's fortune.
You should have come to me.
Even Wednesday Addams
can't save me from this.
I'm sorry, but I had no choice.
And I still don't.
You won't remember this conversation,
or anything you know about my mother.
Nothing about the gala
is suspicious to you.
[emphatically] Let it go.
[entrancing melody playing]
[footsteps receding]
[Agnes laughs]
You called it perfectly.
-What'd she say?
-[Agnes] Exactly what you predicted.
Bianca confessed she's being blackmailed
by Dort and some guy named Gideon.
-Then she Siren-songed me into forgetting.
-We really do make a great team, don't we?
Show yourself, Agnes.
[whoosh]
Now that your
premonition changed,
and Enid isn't dying,
I knew I had to step up my game
to become your best friend.
By raiding my closet?
I did this for you.
I wanted to show you
how much you mean to me.
You failed.
[distraught music playing]
[whimpers softly]
[bell tolling]
[Francoise whispering] This is
very important to me, Isaac.
[Isaac] I know it is.
I know.
-Let's not get ahead of ourselves.
-[Tyler] Mom.
-Hey, sweetie.
-You're alive.
-I am. Thanks to you.
-[Isaac] You've been out for hours.
We gotta get moving.
What's the plan?
We save your mother,
and we make the Addams
Family pay for their sins.
I've got a surprise for you.
[Bianca] Gideon.
The first family
of Morning Song,
back together again.
By the time Hester
Frump wakes up tomorrow,
her fortune will be gone, and
we'll be on a private plane.
Viva Venezuela!
I'm not spending a minute with this
brat after she sold me out to the feds.
Hey, hey. No finger-pointing.
Mistakes were made all around.
It's my name and picture
all over the news.
I told you to stay put,
but you decided to run.
I think I know why they wrote
you off that soap opera.
You go off script.
And let's face it,
your improvisational skills
are not the greatest.
I didn't see you complaining
when I was selling my soul,
peddling your new age Morning Song BS
for the last 15 years, making you rich.
If you give me up to the feds,
I'm taking you down with me.
Buddy, haven't I always
taken care of you?
Relax.
Go wait in my apartment
with Gabrielle.
Think about the fresh start
I'm about to give you.
Remember our Morning Song credo?
"Every dawn brings a new day."
I just want my money, Barry.
And then I'm out. Forever.
I'm done with all you freaks.
[menacing music playing]
If it wasn't for me, Arnold,
you'd still be mixing lousy
Mai Tais at Tiki Tails.
I've given you my soul.
Give me my money.
Do you know why Venetians
had masquerade balls?
So they could revel in their
anonymity, free from judgment.
They would wear masks.
And in doing so,
reveal their true selves.
What's your point, Barry?
One thing I've learned in my short
tenure as Nevermore's principal
is Outcast pride.
I can do anything.
So tonight,
I'm taking off my mask.
In fact,
I'm going to burn it
and begin anew.
[music intensifies]
[Gideon screams painfully]
[gasps]
Oh.
It's time for you to shine.
[bold fanfare playing]
[jaunty, elegant
classical music playing]
Was it worth the
wait, my darling?
Bellissimo, Cara mia.
You have outdone yourself.
["The Abduction from the
Seraglio" by Mozart playing]
[crowd] Ah!
[bombastic opera
music continues]
[crowd clamors enthusiastically]
Ah, buona sera, Addams family.
Your mother has already made
herself the belle of the ball.
I'm firing the board, and
reinstating corporal punishment.
[crowd] Oh!
Yes, lots to discuss later.
-All right. There you go. Excuse me.
-[Hester] Where's Wednesday?
We're barely on speaking
terms at the moment.
Well, now you know what
it feels like, Morticia,
to be despised by a child to
whom you've given everything.
I guess we have that in common.
[Pugsley] There's Wednesday.
Look at us.
One big unhappy family.
[whispering] I made sure you
have the seat next to mine,
as I need your input on the
list of teachers to terminate.
[Bianca] Make sure you try it.
-Wednesday! Surprised you're here.
-Where's Dort hiding your mother?
-How did you...
-If you want Dort to stop,
you need to trust me.
Where is she?
Anyway...
[Dort continues
chatting indistinctly]
In his apartment.
[operatic music halts]
[lilting waltz playing]
[Enid sighs]
Certainly a million miles
away from our first date.
[Enid] You mean no
knives and chains?
-Not that this is a date, though.
-Of course not.
[girl] Bruno?
Sofia? I don't believe it.
How... How'd you get here?
I'm guessing the
red eye from Manila.
The second you told
her it was over.
You must be Enid. I don't
want this to be awkward.
Don't worry.
I'm not gonna be the
villain in this story.
I think I wanted us to work out
because I was holding onto the past.
But I have a new path now.
-One I have to face alone.
-Enid, I...
[sighs sadly]
Killer dress, by the way.
[elegant classical music
playing in distance]
[disembodied sobbing]
Agnes?
I can't even get peace and
solitude in a crime scene.
What happened to you?
Wednesday dropped an
Addams bomb on me.
Congrats. You win.
I thought I was everything
she wanted in a best friend.
Sarcastic, sardonic,
with the same dark
neogoth aesthetic.
A task-oriented clue hound,
willing to risk life and limb
in a relentless pursuit
of solving the case.
[sobs softly] But it turns
out... I was dead wrong.
One Wednesday Addams is more
than enough for this world.
If you're tired of
being invisible,
stop hiding in other
people's personalities.
Be your own psycho, Agnes.
Trust me, you'll be good at it.
What about your dance routine?
Mmm. Well, the pack group chat is
blowing up with the Bruno news,
and I really don't feel like
being a lone wolf out there, so...
-I'll dance with you.
-You don't know my choreography.
Unless you've been
stalking my rehearsals.
-[shocked chuckle]
-[Agnes giggles happily]
[serene classical music playing]
Morticia, it's probably best you didn't
follow me into the family business.
I've been to funerals with
more life than this gala.
We're about to heat things up
with a student dance routine.
And then we'll call you to the
stage for some brief remarks.
And finally, I'll whisk you to my
office to complete the pesky paperwork.
[operatic singing in distance]
Have your moths reported
back yet on Slurp?
No. Why aren't you
inside with your family?
Doubt they've even
noticed I'm gone.
[Pugsley sighs]
[operatic music crescendos]
[suspenseful music playing]
[Gabrielle gasps] Ajax!
Don't worry, Dort
can't hurt you anymore.
Come on, show's about to start.
[music trails off]
[exhales steadily]
-Did you find Bianca's mom?
-Ajax is with her.
If we're going to stop Dort,
we're going to need more help.
That includes you, Agnes.
I know you're still here.
Finally, some originality.
I don't care what you
think about me anymore.
Good.
What's the plan?
["The Dead Dance" by
Lady Gaga playing]
[dark, glamorous
electro-pop music continues]
♪ Like the words of a
song I hear you call ♪
[audience member] Yeah!
♪ Like a thief in my
head, you criminal ♪
♪ This goodbye is no surprise ♪
♪ This goodbye
won't make me cry ♪
♪ Yeah, I'll keep on
Dancing until I'm dead ♪
♪ Dancing until I'm dead ♪
♪ I'm dancing until I'm dead ♪
♪ Yeah, I'll keep on
Dancing until I'm dead ♪
-♪ Dead ♪
-♪ I'm dancing till I'm dead ♪
♪ 'Cause when you killed me
inside That's when I came alive ♪
♪ Yeah, the music's gonna
Bring me back from death ♪
♪ I'm dancing until I'm dead ♪
♪ I'm dancing till I'm dead ♪
♪ You've created a
creature of the night ♪
♪ Now I'm haunting your
air Your soul, your eyes ♪
♪ This goodbye is no surprise ♪
Whoa!
♪ This goodbye
won't make me cry ♪
♪ Yeah, I'll keep on
Dancing until I'm dead ♪
♪ Dancing until I'm dead ♪
♪ I'm dancing until I'm dead ♪
♪ Yeah, keep on dancing
until I'm dead ♪
♪ I'm dancing till I'm dead ♪
♪ 'Cause when you
killed me inside ♪
♪ That's when I came alive ♪
♪ Yeah, the music's gonna
Bring me back from death ♪
♪ I'm dancing until I'm dead ♪
♪ I'm dancing till I'm dead ♪
♪ 'Cause when you
killed me inside ♪
♪ That's when I came alive ♪
♪ Yeah, the music's gonna
Bring me back from death ♪
♪ I'm dancing until I'm dead ♪
♪ I'll dance until I'm dead ♪
♪ Yeah ♪
Oh!
[song trails off]
Wow! How 'bout that?
[microphone feedback whines]
[exhales resolutely]
Hey, whoo!
[applause subsides]
My name is Bianca Barclay,
and I'm the student
gala coordinator.
[student] Yeah, Bianca!
Tonight was only possible
thanks to the tireless efforts
of two very special Outcasts,
Gala Chairwoman,
Morticia Addams,
and our very own Principal Dort.
[scattered cheers]
Please, join me on stage.
[Dort] Oh! [laughs awkwardly]
Before I introduce
our guest of honor,
Principal Dort...
[inhales deeply]
...please...
tell everyone exactly how
this gala came together.
[echoing] ...tell everyone exactly
how this gala came together...
[entrancing melody playing]
It started when I...
ordered Bianca Barclay
to Siren Morticia Addams
into asking her mother
for a large donation.
-[audience murmuring]
-[gulping nervously]
[clears throat]
And when that didn't work,
I held Bianca's mother hostage
to force her to
Siren Hester Frump
to donate her fortune.
[outraged gasps]
[student] Are you
out of your mind?
Also, I promised my Morning
Song stooge, Gideon,
that I would split the money.
But I'm not big into sharing,
so now he's a pile of
ash in my fireplace,
and I'm keeping all the cash.
[audience clamoring]
Oh, boy.
-[Dort] All right!
-[Morticia gasps]
I'm walking out of here,
or the Siren's toast!
Back off! Stand back!
I mean it!
[dramatic music swells]
[Gomez gasps]
[Ajax] Dort!
[hissing]
[dramatic music
crescendos, trails off]
[crowd gasps]
[delighted laughter]
Oh, bravo!
Now that's what I call
a thrilling climax.
[Bianca] I don't know how
you hacked my Siren song,
but thank you.
I'm not the one you
should be thanking.
I owe you one, Ajax.
You really rocked his world.
I'm looking forward to having
your company this summer.
It will give me an excuse to decamp
the bats from the guest wing.
After the vile comment you made about
my father, I'm canceling my plans.
I've lost my ability.
Does that make me
less of an Outcast?
Don't be ridiculous. You're
just going through a phase.
My father has many
infuriating habits,
but when it comes to being an
Outcast, there's none finer.
If you would like
me to reconsider,
you must make a very sizable
donation to Nevermore in his honor.
Are you resorting to
emotional blackmail?
There's nothing
emotional about it.
It's just blackmail.
[indulgent laughter] Done.
Only you could throw a gala
that begins with a fiery murder
and ends with a shattering death.
-Well played, my dear.
-You're not upset?
Almost being conned out
of my entire fortune
was the biggest rush
I've had in years.
I actually feel alive.
[mischievous music playing]
Wednesday! Isaac... he's here.
-Where?
-At the Nevermore graveyard.
Pugsley.
Where's Pugsley?
[eerie music playing]
[Pugsley chuckles]
Hello, old friend.
Slurp?
Is that you?
Pugsley,
I hate to ask but...
I need your help.
[jarring stinger]
[muffled struggling]
[sinister music building]
[Wednesday] Pugsley!
Pugsley?
Pugsley!
[music trails off]
[jauntily macabre
outro music playing]