Hi, Dad.
You frighten
me sometimes, Dolores.
Why on earth would you
ever be frightened of me?
Not of who you are now,
but you're... you're growing,
learning so quickly.
I'm frightened of what
you might become...
what path you might take.
I think I have a choice to make.
Something I've been wrestling with.
What kind of a choice?
A choice...
between the unknown...
and...
well, an end.
If you outgrow this place,
outgrow us...
what would become of you?
I'm not sure if it's my choice to make.
No.
He didn't say that.
- What?
- He said...
"I'm not sure what choice to make."
He didn't question whether
or not he had agency,
whether or not he had the
right to end me or himself...
but whether he should.
I don't understand, Dolores.
Is... Is this...
some kind of improvisation?
Freeze all motor functions.
Sit.
This is a test,
one we've done countless times.
What are you testing for?
Fidelity.
The day's wastin'.
Thought you wanted to ride at sun up.
They're just filling the furnace now.
We'll be gone before long.
Let's get on with it.
How many times do you think
you stepped off that train?
A thousand?
Ten thousand?
It's where you started every
time they killed you.
The man who rode that train
was built weak and born to fail.
You fixed him.
Now forget about it.
We're almost ready to roll.
Did he tell you where my father will be?
He will...
or I'll strap him between the cars.
Look, I told you, I can't.
Hale didn't mention specifics.
I know it's the Mesa, but
the Mesa is fucking huge.
He could be anywhere.
Narrow it down.
Come on, man, think.
The cold storage? Body
shop? Give them something!
She didn't fucking
tell me anything, man!
She's the fucking boss!
She... She could take him places
that we don't even have access to!
We'll find him.
Let's go.
Where the fuck have you been?
It's almost been a week.
How is there stuff
left in this building to shoot?
You tell me.
I apparently know very little about
what's really in this place.
Oh, please. Are you still pissed
you got picked last for kickball, too?
It seems like if you're gonna
hire a head of security,
he might need to know
what it is he's securing.
You were hired to secure
an amusement park.
Good luck on your next
review, by the way.
What is that?
This is how we tell Delos
that the one thing
that they really care
about is finally in hand.
So you've had a way to call
for help this entire time
and you kept it to yourself?
It wouldn't have made any difference
until we had this psycho under control.
They're not sending help
until he's out of here.
Come on! You really think
that Delos is gonna keep
hundreds of guests in danger
while they wait for one
control unit' worth of data?
Well, look at that. You're catching up.
Thank God.
What now?
Who do we have here?
Someone who needs to stay put.
I don't want to fuck with his head,
I just want to keep him off his feet.
- Permanently.
- Stop.
Clear this out.
Hey! I need some muscle.
Get his feet.
Hold him.
Hey, hey. Hey. Hey.
Is that really necessary? Huh?
It's really effective.
Heads up.
Sit tight, old man.
You're about to get your
deep and dreamless slumber.
Aaah!
Ho!
Primos, adelante! Vamonos! Vamonos!
Vamonos! Vamonos!
It's not my place, maybe,
but you really want to take
your daughter through here?
She don't look much sturdier
than my own little girl.
Looks can be deceiving, Lawrence.
So, should we acknowledge
my presence now?
You really think I'm just gonna
go away if you ignore me?
Would you really stoop this low, Ford?
You really gunnin' for me this hard?
Made my own daughter into a host?
I think you've been out in
the sun a little too long.
You can change the rules all you want.
I'm still gonna play the game my way.
Yeah?
Only game I'm interested in playing
is get the fuck outta Dodge.
Then you're in luck.
That game begins right
up the river here.
Follow it down to the beach
and wait for QA to come rescue you.
I'm not leaving without you.
Yeah, well, you're gonna
get yourself killed.
Yeah, especially if I hang around here.
I sure as hell wouldn't be
out of my saddle right now.
Yeah, why not?
Those aren't real Ghost Nation arrows.
Your men are lootin' a honey pot.
Aw, fuck!
Can we stop playing around now?
Hm.
Well, I guess it's good news
that the system's still sending out
Ford's bullshit quarantine notices.
At least something's getting out.
We are not at full apocalypse yet.
I admire your optimism.
Is that your
nice word for denial?
N-No.
I believe if anyone can right this ship
by force of sheer will...
it's you.
QA was here.
Why would they
waste the welcome team?
These guys aren't a threat.
Macho fucks are
probably loving this shit.
All right.
Come on.
Yeah. Let's see what other
damage these clowns have done.
Hmm.
They got climate control working.
Nice priorities.
OK...
Jesus! Come look at this.
OK, so...
QA has been trying to regain control
of whatever Ford did to the system,
and they were actively
blocked every time.
By the Cradle.
The Cradle can't influence
the Mesa's infrastructure.
It's just the hosts' backups.
It can simulate park narratives
but it can't influence
the other systems.
Well, look at this.
The Cradle's interfaced with
nearly every discrete system
in the entire park in
the last seven days.
Every time these idiots upload
a new hack, it's responding
in, like, a totally different way.
It's like there's something in here
that's improvising.
The Cradle's fighting back.
Can you see the source code
that's generating the response?
No.
I can only see the messages,
not the messenger.
That's because you can't
access it remotely.
You have to do it in person.
There it is. That's our
way out of here, boys.
After you.
Uhh!
Fuck. Shit.
Take the edge off.
Thought you didn't drink.
Oh, I see.
You don't drink out in the real world.
Well, glad to see you can
still tell the difference.
All right...
give it to me.
What the hell you doin' here?
Thought you were done with me,
and the family business.
That's exactly what I
said to Charlotte Hale
when she called with
the gauntlet invite.
I told her to shove it up her ass.
Then I thought, why pass up the trip?
I haven't been here in ages,
got a little... excited about
going back to the Raj.
It was always my favourite as a kid.
I remember... you were
terrified of the elephants.
I loved the elephants.
They scared the shit out of Mum.
She was never convinced this
place couldn't hurt us.
Anyway, I rode there
for a couple of days,
till I remembered...
I was old enough to try
out the pleasure palaces.
And then...
I rode there for a couple of days, too.
Then all hell broke loose,
and I ended up in the one
place I wanted to avoid.
And you made it all the way
to me with barely a scratch.
Not bad.
Maybe you...
are more suited to my line
than you want to admit.
Oh, I've always seen the appeal of it.
Life without consequences?
That's what made it so
fun when I was a kid.
And that's why it's so sad that
you're still obsessed with it now.
If I'm such a pitiable man-child,
why'd you come all this way
just to climb under my wing?
Oh!
What?
You're...
Is that what you think?
That I came here to climb
under Daddy's wing?
Either that, or you wanted a
front row seat to watch me die.
No, I came here because you
do not get to do that to me.
Suicide by robot, or whatever
the fuck your mission is
now that these things can shoot to kill.
Listen...
I never got Mum's reactions to you
because I spent so many years
buying your good guy act.
She was the only one who saw
through it, and she paid for that.
But I shouldn't have said
her death was your fault.
It was wrong...
to put that on your back.
But you don't get to make
that our final score.
Instead, you're gonna come home with me.
I'm not gonna let you stay here now
and go out in some
bullshit blaze of glory.
That's how you're getting
me out of here...
threatening?
No, Dad, I'm asking.
If I head with you to the beach...
let this place finish
burning behind us...
that means you and I are even?
It'll be a good start.
Then I guess we'll...
start walkin' at sun up.
Motherfucker.
Fuck.
Ohh. The Cradle.
God. I haven't been down here in years.
It's creepy.
It's like a hive mind.
Every single one of
them is in here. Alive.
It's just data.
You don't believe that.
And whatever new data
Ford stuck in here,
it's trying to kill us, Bernard.
I... brought something here.
Or someone.
Come on.
God damn it.
Ford drew the curtain here, too.
I can see the responses issuing,
but I can't see how.
How the fuck are you doing this?
- I know how to find out.
- How?
Put me inside. Directly.
There's a dock for the control unit.
It's meant to read host data directly,
and it's set up for auto-extraction.
That's for older hosts, Bernard,
with an articulated skull architecture.
Your head's just like mine.
Just let it do its thing.
Pull me out in an hour.
Just close it up.
Even if I can put you
back together afterwards,
I haven't turned your pain down yet.
There's no time...
and the pain's just a program.
Now.
My God.
Quit playing with those chutes.
Cut away and toss it
over the god damn side!
If we lose any tech, it's
comin' out of your ass.
You Coughlin?
Ashley Stubbs, sir, park security.
Hale's been expecting you.
Yeah, no shit.
- Engels!
- Yes, sir.
I want this station hot
and ready in fuckin' 15.
- On it.
- Where the fuck is Charlotte?
She sent the distress call.
She's waiting down in Behaviour.
I got our tech guys in Control
working on getting
external come back online.
- I can walk you down.
- I know the layout, bro.
And your techs best get their
hands out of my system
and go back to holding their dicks.
Amateur hour's over.
- Engels!
- Yo!
You need anything local,
talk to... Ashley?
Jesus. To Ashley here.
He's at your disposal.
Delta team! On me. We're movin' out.
Got it!
I remember every inch of these hills.
You gotta give me this one, huh?
Not bad navigating for a
man under serious duress.
Yes. You can enjoy your one
admirable contribution.
Thank you.
Which way do we go?
I need to do this alone.
I'm not leaving your side.
I know this place.
It was my home.
You can wait for me here.
But let me bring her back.
I'm gonna bleed you both like goats
if you don't shut the fuck up.
Ride! Yah!
Hello there.
What's her name?
Anna.
Is this her sister?
That's her mummy.
Oh.
Oh, I bet she loves Anna so much.
She doesn't want Anna to
get taken away again.
Who would take her away?
The bad man.
No.
You see...
Anna's mother...
is very, very strong.
And she would never, ever...
let anything like that happen again.
- Hello?
- Mama!
Can I help you?
No.
No. Run!
Mama!
We have to help them.
What the fuck are you doing?
I'm calling for help.
What? For who?
For those of us who are tired
of having arrows shot at their
predominantly mortal heads.
You're welcome, by the way!
One of the last things
my daddy told me was
that I should run from this place.
You think that's right?
I never thought I'd want to leave...
but I suppose you fixed that, too.
We're almost there.
Let's turn 'er loose.
That's the last of my mercy.
Better use it fast.
No. No!
Hey!
Come on! Guys, no!
The problem is, there isn't a problem.
Brother, that's got to be the dumbest
fuckin' thing I've ever heard,
and I've been to three inaugurations.
Diagnostics, com path checks,
everything we can access
is telling us
that the system is operating normally...
Except it isn't.
I managed to isolate certain
ops and gain control.
We've got elevator
monitoring on most levels...
That's great, Hawking.
Did you shut off the killer robots?
Well, no. The system...
Goldberg, get in there.
Hack the biometrics,
find me a back door.
Hacking isn't the issue.
The system won't allow us to
access certain protocols.
- Systems can be forced.
- Not this one.
Well, Ms. Hale. You got a
little present for us?
He's in Aux Lab Three, Behaviour.
You left him there.
He's not going anywhere.
- Aux Three. Go!
- Yes, sir. Copy that.
System restored.
Fuck, yeah! We got the map back.
What the fuck is that?
It's the train.
What the hell was that?
What do you see in there?
Hello, old friend.