Déjà vu.
They say it's like a short circuit
in the brain.
Your sense of a moment
placed in your memory centre.
Makes you feel
like you've experienced all this before.
Do you know what I'm talking about?
That feeling.
Have we been here before?
Do we already know one another?
You don't know me.
I know that you feel out of place.
Detached.
Like your life isn't your own.
I know you wake every night
from a painful dream you never had.
Jesus Christ!
You scared me.
What are you doing down here?
Isaac?
Are you okay sweetheart?
Let's get you back to bed.
Go back to sleep.
And how often do these episodes occur?
About once or twice a month.
So, before the move?
That's right.
Well sleepwalking's really quite common
in children of Isaac's age.
No, sorry.
This isn't sleepwalking.
This is different.
And it's just the two of you at home?
Yes.
Does he still see his father?
Not anymore.
And how did he react when you told him
that you and your husband were separating?
He didn't.
Isaac, would you like
to come and sit by Mummy?
Thank you.
And how are you feeling today?
Isaac?
Dr Bennett asked you a question,
sweetheart.
Isaac, do you remember
waking up last night and going downstairs?
And do you remember why you did that?
Meredith was crying.
Sometimes Isaac imagines things.
People.
That's quite common, isn't it?
Imaginary friends.
Is that right, Isaac?
Is Meredith your friend?
She can't hear me.
She's been with us since the move.
She's not the first though, is she?
We've had, erm, Barney, Stephanie,
we even had an Alejandro once.
How's he at school?
Fine, I mean, I...
he does well.
No behavioural issues.
Is he always this placid?
He never cries.
He never laughs. He never gets mad.
He's just...
Did you say something, Isaac?
I'm not supposed to be here.
That's okay.
We're going to go to school just as soon
as we finished with Dr Bennett.
Oh, Ruby, please.
Ruby.
And there is an instance
of schizophrenia in the family?
Er, sorry?
Your mother.
Er, Dr Harper ruled out schizophrenia.
And what about your father?
Are there any issues
on that side of the family?
Not that I know of.
He died when I was young.
Brain aneurysm.
It's not schizophrenia.
It's not autism.
There is no easy answer here, believe me.
You're actually doctor number seven.
Lucky number seven, I hope.
I'll do what I can.
Luce?
No, I understand. Erm.
Thing is Karen,
we're overstretched as it is.
Yeah? What about Mark?
When's the last time he did a home visit?
Mark?
Mark doesn't use cash because he read
it's covered in vaginal bacteria.
He actually put that in writing.
I have got it in an email.
Bedwetting.
Yes.
The mum doesn't change her sheets,
so it's disgusting.
Was Rob with you?
No, of course not.
Rob should come with you next time.
Bedwetting could be a sign of abuse,
we need to rule that out.
No, Luce, it's not about
whether the kid's being abused...
Yes, it is.
No, what I mean is...
This is the job, Karen.
Yeah?
He's here.
Mr Fisher, my name is Lucy Stephens.
You've already met Rob.
Yeah.
Rob and I have both
been working on your case.
As you know, he's made several visits
to your family home.
No.
You weren't aware of that?
No. Don't know nothing about it.
With respect,
the situation's been made quite clear.
What's this about?
'Cause I've got stuff to do.
We have several police reports
of violent incidents of assault.
Some historic.
You're currently on bail
for the most recent charge.
Yeah.
Chloe tells us
that you physically assaulted her
and that you threatened
the safety of your daughter.
Nah. She says that, but it's not true.
I didn't do that.
- You didn't...
- I didn't threaten Tilly.
All right?
I wouldn't hurt her. That's bollocks.
She's making that up.
But there was an incident of assault...
Mr Fisher.
She pushed me, I pushed back.
Are you aware that you're not permitted
to have any contact with your family
at this time?
Three days ago, you approached Chloe
outside your daughter's school.
- She was carrying your son in a...
- He's not mine.
Look, she's not taking her
away from me, all right?
That's my daughter.
I love her,
I wouldn't do nothing to hurt her.
I want to be very clear with you,
Mr Fisher.
If there are any further incidents,
we're going to need to consider
child protection measures.
Do you understand?
Is that it?
This is very serious, Shane.
Yeah.
- If you approach your family...
- Yeah, I get it.
You all right, Luce?
Yeah.
It's always nice to meet new people.
Victim's a Mr Harold Slade.
Early fifties. Stabbed three times.
- Weapon?
- No, not yet.
Where is he?
Upstairs office.
Wife came home and found him around 4:00.
Home from where?
Book club, alibi's tight.
How's it looking up there?
Lot of spatter.
Let's get this over with.
♪ There's a world where I can go ♪
♪ And tell my secrets to ♪
♪ In my room ♪
♪ In this world I lock out ♪
♪ All my worries and my fears ♪
♪ In my room ♪
Say again?
I said, next door were out,
front door was unlocked.
Killer picked his moment.
Probably knew the victim.
Knew his schedule at least.
Wife said he was well liked.
Volunteered at St John's,
ran the local rowing club.
Pillar of the community.
Is that right?
Yeah, I know.
We found some magazines in the drawer too.
Nothing illegal.
Little bit of rough, you know,
bondage, S&M.
Do you want to step out?
No.
They're putting us up somewhere local.
Christ knows where.
Of course, we should be getting pissed
at the King's tonight.
Weird time of day for fireworks.
Are you alright, mate?
Sorry, I...
You know when you half remember something?
It's supposed to get easier.
You know, the blood.
Most people find it hard to start with,
but they get used to it.
I'm not criticising, I'm just saying,
you're the only DI I know
who still gets wobbly around the dead.
I'm not wobbly.
There's no shame in it.
Everybody's scared of something.
My Bella has an irrational fear of cheese,
believe it or not.
This isn't irrational.
Blood is death.
It's supposed to make us uncomfortable.
You could argue
it's irrational not to fear it.
You could do. It won't help you much.
Not when your job
involves staring at stab victims.
Are you gonna throw up?
I'm fine.
Why do this?
A grudge?
Bad debts?
- Botched burglary?
- No, no, no. I mean you.
Why do this job, given your disposition?
Someone has to.
What do you see when you look at me?
A murderer? A monster?
Why did you come here?
You said you wouldn't talk to anyone else.
And you came.
- You didn't have to.
- Well, they want answers.
No, they don't.
They want evidence, confessions,
close the file, forget all about it.
Do you think I don't want to forget this?
I know you do.
But you won't.
What time is it?
You still having the nightmares?
I told you not to sleep over.
You were talking in your sleep.
Said something about fireworks.
- Fireworks?
- Uh-hmm.
Can I get you something?
No.
Let's go to sleep.
Okay.
Mike?
Hmm?
Will you hold me?
Yeah.
I know it's weird,
but I actually quite miss this time.
I miss waking up
and hugging you back to sleep.
Look, I want you gone
by the time he wakes up.
I don't want him thinking
you're back if you're not back.
Yeah. Sure.
Unless you want to see him...
Mike?
Erm, I have a really early meeting.
You're making me too hot.
All right.
I'm changing my name back.
I thought it was about time.
Can we talk about that?
No.
Mum...
has Ellen been in today?
Who?
You know, Ellen.
Er, she gives you a hand
with things, doesn't she?
Has she been in?
She was in this morning.
Did she bring any teabags,
do you know?
Yes, yes, yes, yes.
Oh, she's hidden them well.
Hey.
Hey!
It's okay, it's okay.
It's okay.
Well, he'll eat the birds.
Fuck off!
There's nothing there.
Well, he comes and goes.
Nasty little bastard.
He's nasty.
Vicious cunt!
It's okay.
You're all right.
Ellen?
It's Lucy.
Lucy.
Well, I prefer Ellen.
Come on, I'll get you a nice cup of tea.
So just to be clear,
you're saying it was parked opposite
the victim's house.
Two weeks it sat there.
The council plastered it with tickets.
I told them, it's no good putting
the ticket on the thing,
we want it towed.
The other day,
I had to park in the crescent.
I told them I shouldn't have
to do that, not with my knee.
I'm sorry to hear that Mr Bell.
What sort of car was it?
Red. A Nissan thing-a-mee.
It was scuffed to fuck.
Dents all over it.
Nissan thing-a-mee?
You didn't get the model?
Joan took a picture of it. I'll ask her.
Joan?
She's fucking deaf.
Well, she's not proper deaf.
She needs a hearing aid
but of course she won't listen.
Well, she can't fucking listen,
can she?
Joan?
- I reckon she's outside.
- No, no, no, no.
You just stay there Mr Bell,
I'll go.
Vanette.
I'm sorry?
That's what it's called.
Nissan Vanette.
A red Nissan Vanette,
you're absolutely sure?
Yeah, it's a big chunky thing
with, er, bull bars.
Well, you don't see them
around much anymore, do you?
No, you don't.
Oi, mate,
out my way, you knobhead.
Well, none of us saw it happen.
He says it was an accident.
Then it was. He doesn't lie.
Isaac's not in trouble, Mrs Stephens.
Chambers. Stephens was my married name.
Chambers, sorry.
I'll get reception to update your details.
Well, I'll pay for the damage.
That's not really the issue here.
One of those bags belonged to a boy
who was picking on Isaac.
What boy?
He's been disciplined.
We take bullying very seriously,
even if it is just a bit of teasing.
Define teasing.
Name-calling. Silly things.
Still, he knows it was wrong
and he apologised.
Tell me his name.
Archie.
Archie?
What does Archie do to you?
Does he call you names?
Does it upset you?
Is that why you weed on his bag?
They moved the toilets.
No. No sweetheart, they didn't.
Isaac knows full well
where the toilets are,
don't you, Isaac?
Come on.
- Say sorry.
- Sorry.
We'll pay for the bags.
Isaac.
What are you doing?
Go back to bed.
Isaac!
Go to bed.
Shut your eyes.
Isaac?
Oh.
Fuck.
Isaac?
I'm sorry darling.
Mummy's sorry she yelled at you.
Come here and give me a cuddle.
Who's that man?
What's that darling?
What man?
What man, sweetheart?
He's gone now.
Mummy's going to make you better.
I promise.
Go to sleep.
Chloe Fisher?
Yeah.
My name's Lucy Chambers,
I'm from children's services.
Can I come in?
As you know,
we spoke to your husband,
just to get his side of the story.
Oh, thank you very much.
But just to be clear,
has there been any contact
since the incident at school?
He was here this morning.
What, here at the house?
He said he wanted to see Tilly.
Did you let him in?
No.
And what did he do then?
He got angry.
Shouting, swearing.
Saying he was...
he was gonna kill himself.
I told him, don't you say stuff
like that in front of Tilly,
I, I wasn't standing for it.
People was looking.
I said if he didn't go,
I'd call the police.
And did you?
Chloe?
Did you call the police?
Oh.
We made it very clear
that Shane was to have
no contact with you or with Tilly.
If he's not adhering to that,
we're going to need to consider
child protection measures.
Now if he turns up here again,
I want you to...
Look, I shoved him first.
Outside the school. I, I started it.
Don't let him into this house.
Chloe, I want you to promise me.
Okay, we can find you
somewhere safe to stay.
We're not leaving.
Erm...
I'm going to give you my mobile number.
So, if you are worried,
I want you to call me.
Day or night.
Doesn't matter.
I mean it, Chloe.
Day or night.
Yeah. Yeah.
Okay.
Bye Tilly.
Bye.
Hey...
Thanks.
Fuck's sake.
That's every Nissan Vanette
still registered in the county.
I wish we were back in the city.
Honestly, I don't know how
they cope round here.
Come on.
I thought you youngsters
were supposed to be good
with computers.
I'm 35.
Really? You've got a young face.
I like your screensaver
- Jonah Taylor's teddy bear.
- Yeah, I know.
We all remember little Horton.
The day they found him
was the beginning of the end.
Hobson.
Bear's name was Hobson.
Yeah. Hobson, right.
This is all a bit
before your time, isn't it?
I read her blog, Miranda Taylor.
She still updates it, even now.
Well, I never met her.
I know a lot of people who did though.
Not a very pleasant woman,
by all accounts.
She lost her son,
how pleasant would you be?
Yeah, but she didn't have
to blame us, did she?
All that rubbish about hiding
evidence from the press.
It was our fault we never found him.
- I mean, come on.
- Maybe it is.
Listen mate,
this case destroyed three careers.
Good people.
That kid was never gonna be found,
and that, that was a dead end.
Yes, it was. That's the point.
No through traffic. No access to town.
That road there led to five houses,
and this car didn't belong to any of them.
One hour later,
our mystery car shows up again,
just off the M3,
where they found the bear.
Now tell me Nick,
is that or is that not
a red Nissan Vanette?
Yeah, I'm sorry if we seem
to be going over old ground,
but, erm, I wanted to verify
some of Dr Harper's
observations for myself,
and to be honest with you,
these notes don't make
a great deal of sense to me.
Isaac doesn't make a great deal
of sense to anyone.
And the incident at school?
Oh, that's never happened before.
He is not vindictive, not like that.
Any other changes in behaviour?
Oh, how is, erm, the insomnia?
More frequent, I suppose.
He was walking around again last night.
And that was before
you, you went to bed?
No. I woke up.
I always wake up, never sleep through.
What sort of time was this?
3:33.
Always about that time?
- Half three?
- No.
It... sorry, no, it's not. It's...
I know it's strange, it's not half three.
It's 3:33.
No, it's the same every single night.
I wake up, I open my eyes,
I look at the time and it is 3:33 am.
Not 3:32. Not 3:34.
You must have
a very unique circadian rhythm.
Have you tried varying your bedtime?
Ooh... I've tried everything.
Trust me.
I've had this my whole life. Erm...
Is there a chance
that this could be genetic?
Have you ever suffered
from hallucinations
or mood swings?
I... I get déjà vu sometimes.
But it's not,
it's... it's not... it's not real.
I mean, it's not a memory.
It's like I'm misremembering.
Oh God, I sound crazy.
No, you don't, trust me. I've heard crazy.
Lucy, if you need to speak with someone...
No. No. I... no, sorry.
I shouldn't have said anything.
Erm, I'm fine. Just help Isaac.
Please, I'm not worried about myself.
Well, you don't seem worried Lucy.
You seem afraid.
I looked it up. 3:33.
Do you know what they call it?
What?
Isaac, it's time
to go home sweetheart.
Sorry.
Isaac?
Thank you so much
for coming in to see me today.
Will you come again?
I've got you in next Tuesday
at the same time.
Great. Come on.
Self-care isn't selfish, Lucy.
Remember that.
Say goodbye, Isaac.
Goodbye.
The devil's hour.
They call it the devil's hour.
Mummy needs to work when we get home,
so no dinner tonight.
You're okay with that, right?
Or, now promise me
you won't get too excited,
because I know what you're like,
but, um, how about...
♪ Fish and chips? ♪
♪ Oh yeah, fish and chips and mushy peas ♪
♪ Now we're talking ♪
♪ Mm-hm ♪
See, this is what I'm talking about,
you've gone and got yourself overexcited,
and you need to calm down.
Isaac, did you just...
did you just smile at me?
Look out, pumpkin.
Merry, go inside and help Mum.
She just ran in front of the car.
What?
Your daughter just ran into the road.
Oi, is that true?
Did you run in front of this lady's car?
What have I told you? Look at me.
What did we say about the road?
- It's not for playing.
There's cars going up and down.
What happens if you get hit by a car?
- I go splat.
- You go splat.
Now you need to apologise
to this lady, don't you?
- I'm sorry.
- Right, Meredith Warren, inside.
Meredith, in.
Meredith?
That's a nice name.
Mummy?
I had a bad dream.
Oh, so did I.
It's all right.
Mummy's here.
Mummy's here. Mummy's here.
Mummy's not going anywhere.
Bad dreams can't hurt us, Lucy.
Can't hurt us now.
There you go. Nice cup of tea.
I want sugar.
It is sugared, I put two sugars in there.
Ugh, can't taste it.
Um, would you like to play a game?
I could get the cards?
There's no cards.
She stole them. Thinks I don't know.
Well, maybe I should look for them.
I'm sure we'll find them.
Well, it's all in the wrong place.
Not supposed to be like this.
Hey!
It's...
It's supposed to be different.
It's okay Mum.
Look, how about a game of crib,
do you remember how to play?
We used to play this by candlelight
when there were power cuts,
do you remember?
Mum?
Maybe another time.
Lucy.
You came to see me again.
Of course, I did. I'm always here.
Oh.
I...
Are you real?
Yes. I'm real.
I can't get warm.
I'm cold.
Why is it always so cold?
Oh, shut up, shut up. Shut up!
Here.
Hold it.
Here you go.
Squeeze it.
It's real.
You're real.
There you go.
Lucy.
It's okay.
I'm not going anywhere.
It's going to be okay.
Not much traffic up here.
There's a farm up on the hill,
a couple of houses at the end of the lane.
One of them's empty.
Registration's a match.
Council confirmed it.
How far away is this farm?
- About a mile, mile and a half?
- Okay.
Find out what they know.
We already bagged some of it.
Old laptop, no hard drive,
mobile phone, no SIM,
long life UPS, and this.
Show the wonder kid.
Dhillon.
Dashboard cam.
Just had to park at the right angle,
he's got himself a 24-hour stream.
That's how he knew Slade's routine.
Without getting too close.
So, he's a clever bastard.
Maybe not.
Oh.
He's been driving on that for a while.
Could have gone looking for help.
Or another vehicle.
Not many options round here.
Guess we go knocking on some doors.
We can start
with whichever one this opens.
Find the cheapest hotel in the area.
I doubt he's fussy.
Do you think he'll go back there?
Not without the key,
but someone took his booking,
which means, someone's seen his face.
- Mike.
- All right?
I was just, uh, passing by.
Yeah, it's not a good time, I'm working.
What? It's 9:30.
And I'm working.
Okay.
- You okay?
- Mm-hm.
Just tired.
We could just talk?
I don't want to talk.
Okay.
I didn't say go.
That's it.
That's what?
Do we have sex because you love me,
or because you love sex?
Sorry.
Hello?
You said I could call any time.
Chloe?
Okay.
Have you phoned the police?
- Chloe, open this fucking door!
- No, I...
I don't want to get him in trouble.
Chloe, listen to me,
you need to call the police.
- It's not safe.
- He's been drinking.
Chloe, listen!
He's not normally this bad.
You are afraid of him,
you would not have called if you weren't.
Chloe?
I love you.
Open the door.
I'm being stupid.
- No, you're not, you're not, you're not.
- Sorry. I shouldn't have called.
Chloe, please.
Who was that?
Lucy?
Stay with Isaac.
What? Uh...
Hold on.
Just stay here.
He comes and goes.
Sometimes I don't see him for months.
- How long has he been staying here?
- He don't stay.
Not often.
He's had the lodge about nine, ten years.
That doesn't strike you as odd?
He pays cash.
A year in advance.
As far as I'm concerned,
he can stay as long as he wants.
Fair enough.
And I assume you asked for his name?
Asked for one, didn't get one.
Like I said, he pays cash.
Didn't look like he was
going to get a lot of post.
What did he look like?
Serious. Scruffy.
Maybe 50's, 60's.
But skinny, you know.
Grey hair.
Spoke with an accent.
- What sort of accent?
- Irish?
Scottish?
Same difference.
When was the last time you saw him?
Two, three months ago.
I'd had to check.
And, uh...
Nah, that tapes over itself.
Can you show us his lodge?
If you can show me a warrant.
Please Mrs Jones, this is very important.
My guests have the right to privacy.
Not that you'd know much about that,
filming us all the time,
tracking our phone calls,
watching what we do on the internet.
Do a lot of nasty stuff on the internet,
do you Mrs Jones?
I'd like you to leave.
Now.
What breed of dog is that?
Well, he's all right.
That's just Spud.
I didn't ask his name, I asked his breed.
- Looks like a pit bull terrier to me.
- So what?
It's a banned breed.
Sorry, I'm sure you know that.
As I'm sure you can provide us
a certificate of exemption.
Now, you can show us the room,
or we can sit and we can
talk about Spud a bit longer.
Maybe seize him under section 19
of the police and criminal evidence act?
Your choice.
You okay, Dhillon?
I'm fine.
Probably best if I go in first, eh?
Yeah.
Is there a key
for that padlock on here?
That's not supposed to be there.
Allow me.
You didn't know I could do that, did you?
Do you feel it now?
The dissonance.
Like something wasn't meant to be.
Something changed.
Changed from what?
This is today.
Dhillon.
Do you remember
this conversation?
How would I?
Well, maybe you dreamt it?
Maybe it's in there somewhere.
Back of your mind.
Ladies and gents,
can we keep back please? Back.
Will you answer a question for me?
It might sound strange.
What's the worst thing
you've ever experienced?
This.
All of this.
You.
I'm sorry Lucy.
I'm sorry but you've suffered
far worse than me.
You just don't know it yet.