Mummy went up to your bedroom,
but you were gone.
Do you remember what happened?
A man came.
There was a man in your bedroom?
He said it wasn't mine.
He wanted me to go.
Where did you go, Isaac?
To the woods.
And how did you get there?
In a car.
Do you remember what the car looked like?
Black.
Isaac, what happened
when you got to the woods?
They left me.
Who left you?
Just stay here.
I'll find someone
to take the kid back to the station.
He remembers what people say.
It's like a photographic memory
but with words.
Can you remember
what else they said, Isaac?
Keep the door locked.
It's okay, she's coming back.
You're okay.
How about we listen to some music?
Who wanted to listen to music?
The man in the black car?
Have you ever seen him before?
Could you tell us what he looks like?
Left these on the printer.
Thanks.
Not our case anymore.
MCIS know you're holding evidence?
It's just personal interest.
Don't worry about it.
I'm not worried.
Here, take a look at this
from my fly-tipping hotspot.
How did you get this?
Old colleague of mine
moved to MCIS a year ago.
He's my man on the inside.
What about the other cameras?
Nah, wrong angles, didn't catch anything.
Must have spotted this one though,
got spooked.
Drove off in a hurry.
Lost a hubcap.
Can we ID the vehicle?
We can narrow it down.
Rough shape, wheel size, tyre tread.
Might find something
we can work into your theory.
What about MCIS?
What's their theory?
Snuff films. Porn.
Whatever Slade had goin' on in
that basement, our suspect was in on it.
But they had a disagreement.
Our man killed Slade,
starts workin' alone.
Great.
Now work in Shane Fisher,
the dead dog, the watch...
The watch wasn't stolen,
the boy said he was wearin' it.
Isaac hadn't worn that watch for years
and our suspect had
a picture of it on his wall.
- Make sense of that.
- Don't have to.
It's not our case anymore.
How many times you watched that?
I'm just listening to music.
Right, silly me.
Could you tell us
what he looks like?
Have you always believed
in the supernatural?
Define "supernatural."
Clairvoyance, precognition,
you seem to have
a distorted relationship with time.
My perception of time
is better than anyone's.
You think you see the future.
I don't see it, I remember it.
And in this delusion of yours,
are you a time traveller
or a fortune teller?
Neither and both.
Do you know what I'm gonna say next?
"No more questions,
Mr Shepherd, you're free to go."
- That's funny.
Sorry, should have seen that coming.
What about those cuffs?
Did you see those coming?
Eventually.
I knew you wouldn't give up,
not after what happened
with Aiden Stenner.
But you probably
don't want to talk about that.
I don't know
what you want me to say.
You could start by telling us
where Aiden is.
When did you last see him?
Saturday. No, erm, Friday.
So why didn't you report him missing?
He's not missing,
he's just not here.
He does what he likes.
- He's 17, Kate.
- 18 in January.
But 17 now which means
it's still our job to look out for him
and we can't do that
unless you tell us where he is.
Fuck sake, he's just staying with mates.
Yeah, well what is he doing for money?
Kate, we need names and addresses.
You could try Mia Thomas.
Right. Who's that?
Used to live downstairs.
They had a thing.
- And where does she live now?
- I don't know. Ask her mum.
Number eight. I need a piss.
Oh.
Of course you do.
I mean, whose case was this?
It's Karen's.
Look it's not her fault.
These last two weeks have been a mess.
I'll have to tell my son
to stop getting kidnapped.
Could you?
- 'Cause I got no idea how to do your job.
- You did fine, Rob, honestly.
Thank you for stepping up, appreciate it.
If you need more time,
you know you should take it.
I guess she moonlights
as a birthday clown.
Mm.
Oh, nitrous oxide,
do you think she's got any more?
I could do with a laugh.
Oi, are you taking pictures?
Why are you taking pictures?
- I'm talkin' to you.
- Calm down.
Why are you taking pictures?
Why are you takin' pictures?
- Stop.
- Are you fuckin' deaf or something? Oi!
Are you gonna calm down?
- Are you gonna calm down?
- Yes.
Yes.
Fuckin' bitch.
I'm phoning the police.
Are you all right?
How did you do that?
I have no idea.
Could you do me a favour?
Could you stay perfectly still
just for one second?
Is it dying?
Just needs some food.
Bees are key to our survival.
Without bees, there's no crops.
No crops, no food.
No food, no us.
My sister's allergic to bee stings.
That flies off and sticks her,
it's on you.
It feels good.
It's only a small thing
but making one life a little better
without making something worse.
I ran over a dog two weeks ago on purpose.
Then I reversed over
its head just to make sure.
It belonged to a four-year-old girl.
Hey, you still there?
Yeah.
Sorry, I, I didn't hear
you say anything.
Well, I don't really know what to say.
It's a bit out of the blue.
We nearly lost him, Luce.
I nearly lost him.
Yeah, no, I know, I know.
Erm... And I get why
you've been ignoring my calls too.
And I fucked up.
But I just... I wanna try again, you know.
For him or for me?
Both.
I was thinking that, erm,
I was thinking we could all go
to your mum's old cottage,
just the three of us.
Uh, I've got people booked in.
Well, cancel 'em.
Say there's a, a damp problem
or something.
There is a damp problem.
Well, there you go.
You don't even need to lie.
Let me think about it.
Okay.
- Bye Mike.
- Bye.
- Hi.
- Sorry, I know it's late.
It's fine.
I thought you were back in the city?
I am.
I was. Erm, I wanted to give you this.
What is it?
Isaac's interview.
You said a psychiatrist
wanted to see the footage.
You said you couldn't give me this.
I can't.
So don't lose it.
And don't make copies.
Thanks. I won't.
And, erm, let me know
what she says, okay?
I will.
Do you wanna come in?
Actually I wanted to ask you something.
Oh, shit. Erm, uh, come in,
come in, come in, come in.
Fuck, fuck, fuck, fuck, ah.
Yup, that's, uh, broken.
Erm...
Oh, I mean...
This, erm,
this doesn't seem like a good time.
Well, it is not.
But you don't get to run away,
this is entirely your fault.
It was. I'm sorry.
You will be.
Now you have to make us dinner.
- Do I?
- Obviously.
- What would you like?
- I'm not fussy.
Isaac likes lobster.
What did you wanna ask me?
Slade's house.
You say you guessed the code to his safe.
Uh, classical music fan,
1812, I mean, it's not much of a stretch.
And the violin?
You asked me if Slade kept
a violin above his stairs.
I'm sorry, I know this is probably
the last thing
you want to think about right now.
I remembered it.
So you have been there before?
No.
But I remember it now
and it's like...
the memory already existed
before... somehow.
What else do you remember?
Uh, I remember the house,
that awful room in the basement.
Those two little girls
from the photographs,
dead, being pulled from the water.
That didn't happen.
Those girls are alive.
I spoke to them myself.
Yeah, sometimes I remember it wrong.
Hello, sweetheart.
You okay?
I'm cold.
You're cold?
Aw, come here.
Oh, you don't feel cold.
Isaac, do you remember Detective Dhillon?
Hello, Isaac.
Manly handshake?
Tap it.
Back, now three bumps.
One, two, three.
Explode it, hold it.
High five.
That is a very secret
policeman's handshake.
Don't tell anyone I showed you, okay?
- Okay.
You're my undercover officer now.
You need to keep an eye
on your mum for me.
Make sure she doesn't
do anything dangerous.
Like try to cook dinner.
I've heard the best way
to get warm is hot chocolate.
Lots and lots of hot chocolate.
Okay.
Well, I tell you what, you can have
a hot chocolate if you lay the table.
Mummy is gonna get a takeaway
because she's useless.
Would you like to stay for a Chinese?
Oh, uh, I shouldn't, but thanks.
Are you sure?
Yeah, things to do.
Early start tomorrow.
How far is home?
Back in the city.
Hour or so.
You came all this way?
It's good to see you again, Isaac.
Look at that, got it in one.
Great work.
Take care of your mum, okay?
Okay.
DI Dhillon?
- Ravi.
Oh, I know I shouldn't ask you this,
you can tell me to piss off if you want.
Piss off.
What is it?
I have this case at work, a kid...
well, he's 17.
Aiden Stenner,
his mum hasn't seen him for days,
sounds like drugs.
Right.
He has a friend, Mia, Mia Thomas.
Would you write it down?
And you've already reported this?
Yeah, I just don't know
how seriously they're taking it.
It's just a teenager shacked up
with his girlfriend.
So why are you so worried?
It's my job to worry.
I'll ask around,
see whose desk it landed on.
Maybe I can oil the wheels.
- Thank you.
- No problem.
I'm sorry about your dinner.
You should be.
Yeah, wait for your plate.
If you keep picking there'll be none left.
It's comin', it's comin'.
Hold on.
Just wait, just wait!
You need to hurry,
she is really nearly done.
All right, here it comes,
here it comes.
- Smells good.
- I know. Get out of it.
A little bit.
Beef, you're not coming for my beef.
All right, bye, bye.
More? You've had
about a thousand as it is.
How many, how many do you want?
- Oh, you bloody prick.
- What?
Now, I see why you wanted
to use my car.
- It's inconspicuous.
- Bollocks.
You just worried about someone
keying your paintwork.
It's not insured is it?
Because this isn't
official police business?
You see, I know what you're doin'.
Relax.
We'll be five minutes, tops.
That's the way it works now, is it?
She says, "jump," you say,
"how high?"
- Who?
- You know who.
Mystic Meg and the demon child.
- Your fancy woman.
- She's not my fancy woman.
Fuck off.
What?
Do you live here?
Maybe.
We're looking for Mia Thomas.
You seen her?
Mia!
What do you want?
Are you Mia?
We understand
you know Aiden Stenner.
Who are you?
He's not in trouble,
we just wanna make sure he's all right.
Are you police?
Like I said, he's not in trouble.
Just your name on the lease,
is that right?
Yeah.
Who's that lot then?
- Friends.
- A lot of friends.
Do they sleep over?
Are you all right with that?
Mia, shut the fucking door!
Aiden's not here.
Don't.
Walk away.
That's cuckooing.
I bet my life on it.
How many guys do you think
she's got squatting in there?
Too many.
I don't like your chances.
I don't like her chances,
cooped up with scum like that.
They'll do worse than scratch your car.
- Come on, be clever.
- You're the clever one.
- We're not even supposed to be here.
- So what?
- What? We just ignore it?
- No. But we do this properly.
I'll say we're following up
on an anonymous tip, okay.
I'll log it this afternoon.
Hey, what you doing tonight?
Chilli con Carne.
Sod it.
Never been a fan of Bella's chilli.
Don't tell her I said that.
This is a nice watch, isn't it?
Did Mummy get it for you?
- It's broken.
- Yeah, yeah,
I can see the strap's broken, isn't it?
Do you remember how that happened?
It got caught on the window.
Got caught.
Is that when you were
climbing into the house?
Mm.
Mummy says
you don't normally wear this.
Did someone tell you to put it on?
You just wanted to?
Mummy likes me to wear it.
Wanted to make mummy happy?
Isaac,
how did you find the house?
I walked.
Who was in the house, Isaac?
No one.
So, you slept there
for two nights all on your own?
Oh, where?
On the floor.
So you slept there and then you left.
Why did you leave?
I was cold.
He keeps saying he's cold.
He's never said that before.
I mean, he's been cold before,
I've heard his teeth chattering,
but he's never said it.
Like...
Like it upsets him,
like he wants it to stop.
Isaac, do you remember
when Mummy found you?
How did that make you feel?
I don't know.
You know sometimes
we cry when we're happy
as well as when we're sad.
Is that why you cried,
because you were happy?
And do you remember
why you were happy?
She knew me.
What's in the sandwich?
Fish paste.
Oh, it stinks.
- I've got extra.
- Oh.
Bella hates it, too.
Can't eat these at home.
Strictly a work meal.
What did she say about overtime?
What do you think?
Ah, I'll pick up some flowers
from the garage.
Get myself back in the good books.
Should I do the same?
Dragging you out here?
Well, you hardly had
to twist my arm, did you?
That's somebody's little girl in there.
She's 20.
Still a kid.
You never wanted any?
Kids, I mean.
We talked about it,
decided we had enough to worry about.
Happy just the two of us.
You?
Maybe. One day.
Need to find someone first.
Maybe stop spending
your evenings like this.
This is the job.
It's hardly
conducive to romance, is it?
Sitting in a car with some fat old duffer
eating fish paste sandwiches.
People probably think we're doggin'.
Oh, for fuck's sake.
Hey! What have I said?
Uh! Ah!
- Uh! Uh! Ow! Uh!
- Move!
I'll call it in.
Nick, wait!
This is Detective Ravi Dhillon,
we require immediate assistance
on Drakeford Lane, Matson Tower.
Hello?
Shit. Hello?
If anyone can hear me,
there is an assault in progress...
- Police!
- Oh, for fuck sake!
- What is up with this...
- Move, man, move, man.
- Ow!
- Mia!
What do you mean?
I haven't done anything.
Mia!
Oh, you fuckin...
Stay still, stay still!
Stay fuckin' still!
Still!
Stay still, stay still!
Get on your feet.
Get on your feet!
On your fuckin'...
So you like hitting little girls,
do you hey?
Huh?
Do you like hitting little girls,
you fuck?
Move. Move!
Ah, you fuck!
Fuck you, fuckin'!
C'mon, son!
Come on!
Let's see what you're made of, eh?
Fuck!
Do you know who the fuck we are?
- Get the fuck off me!
- You're under arrest.
- You're fucking dead!
- You don't have to say anything, but...
- Fuck off!
- Shut up!
- Shut the fuck up!
Hey stop it, stop, stop.
What's wrong?
Why were you doing that?
I don't know.
Were you having a bad dream?
What were you dreaming about?
He thinks this is his home.
Who?
I'm cold.
Oh, darling.
I'm sorry. I'll turn the heating up.
Oh.
We're not supposed to be here.
We returned to the property
at approximately 10:30 pm
hoping to speak to Ms Thomas again.
This was when we observed
a domestic disturbance outside.
Her attacker
grabbed her by the hair,
threw her against the wall,
dragged her inside.
No, I called it in.
DS Holness decided to...
investigate the disturbance.
In my professional opinion
there was an assault in progress.
An assault in progress.
That's my professional opinion,
at which point my partner acted without
any concern for his own well-being.
As we were the only two officers
on the scene, I made a call.
- He entered the property unarmed.
- Unarmed.
At which point he was met
with extreme resistance
from armed gang members.
They came at me with a knife,
- I picked up a crowbar.
- A crowbar.
No, it's not that unusual.
These people often
stash weapons on the premises
in case they're raided by rival gangs.
I got lucky.
As I said,
it was reasonable force.
He made the right call.
I shouldn't have hesitated.
Are we done?
Look, I know
she's been through a lot.
I just wanna ask some questions.
I won't be long.
Mia?
This lady's from social services.
Wants to talk to you.
You want a tea?
No, thank you,
I won't be a minute.
Hi, Mia.
How you feeling?
Must be nice to be back
with your mum.
I wanna talk to you about Aiden.
His mum said you were close.
I don't know where he is.
Don't bother asking.
You know what these people
are capable of.
He don't want your help.
Well...
neither did you.
Look, I'm giving you a chance
to do the right thing here.
But we are running out of time.
We need to find Aiden today
before the storm.
Erm...
Look, I know you're scared.
But you are safe now, Mia.
You can't promise that.
I can promise
that you are gonna regret
this tomorrow
when it's too late.
Okay.
Speed Kings.
There's an old go-kart track
on the Runford Estate.
If you're looking to score you go
and see the Speed Kings.
Pass me that brown one.
What's that supposed to be?
It's liquorice.
Liquorice?
Who wants a liquorice candle?
I'll tell you who wants
a liquorice candle!
Mary Dean of 43 Abbots Road.
Well, there you go Mary Dean.
How many more of these
have we gotta do?
Four more orders,
then we'll start on dinner.
We?
- I'm missin' half a hand here.
- Rubbish.
Stop feeling sorry for yourself.
Pass me a lemon one.
Careful, you clumsy sod!
Wounded in the line of duty
and this is the thanks I get?
I nearly died, you know.
Yeah, it does smell like lemon.
Bella?
I'm sorry.
You have to stop.
I know.
So, uh, what time you back?
Not late.
Uh, I'm not sure, sorry.
No, it's all right, I'm just...
I'm glad you came.
I brought this in case
you wanna read together
or just stick the telly on,
whatever you want.
No, this is... uh, this is great.
And I got you some ice cream
for after dinner.
- Oh.
- He only eats the strawberry.
- Don't ask me why.
- That's all right,
it means that Daddy can have
all the chocolate bit. Ah.
Mm, I ate the chocolate,
you can have the vanilla.
What?! Vanilla?
Boring.
He has been smiling on and off.
Tell him one of your shit jokes,
he'll like that.
Uh, mm,
I don't know any shit jokes.
I know lots of excellent jokes.
You laugh at daddy's jokes, okay?
Bye, sweetheart.
I'll see you later.
Mm. Uh, uh, just...
you like the new doctor don't you?
Dr Bennett?
Yeah, she's great.
Yeah, erm...
I was thinking maybe
I could come along, get involved?
Yeah. I'd like that.
Cool, okay.
- Bye.
So...
do you wanna cook or shall I?
Thought so.
Okay.
Two fish in a tank.
One says to the other,
"Do you know how to drive this thing?"
Do you know what a tank is?
You know with a big gun on the top?
You do, right. Okay.
Well maybe, maybe it's a bad joke,
but uh, you could at least smile.
Oh, okay.
Mummy says that when they found you,
you were crying.
Wanna talk about that?
I'm a good listener.
Got big ears.
See. Uhhh.
You really don't care
about anything do you?
I mean do you,
do you even get tired?
Do you... you know, do you even get hungry,
do you even get thirsty?
Would you even care
if I took that away from you?
How about now? Hm?
Do you want this back?
Do you want it?
No, thought not.
Yo, pack it in, man.
Supposed to be low key out here.
- Are you Aiden?
- Who are you?
Aiden Stenner?
Don't know him.
My name's Lucy.
I spoke with your mum.
She doesn't know where you are,
she's worried.
For real, what are you,
like social services?
Fuck.
You shouldn't sell here, not tonight.
Who says I'm selling?
I ain't selling nothing.
Okay, uh, look I will pay you.
I've got 200 in cash,
it's yours, no questions.
All you have to do is go home.
Just stay indoors.
Two bills, you know,
that's like pocket money.
- I'll go for 200.
- None of you should be here.
Ooh, be smart, yeah.
I am just trying to help you.
Why?
It's my job.
- Child protection.
- Shit, are you serious?
Do I look like
I need fucking protecting.
You don't need that.
Just go home. Please.
Why don't you just grab
the money? You've got the poker,
just fucking take if off her.
Yo, shut the fuck up, mate!
I don't think you're a bad person.
No? Is that what you do, is it?
You decide who's good and who's bad?
You are 17, Aiden,
you've got your whole life
to look forward to...
What is this?
This ain't no fuckin' drive-thru!
Stay where you are.
What the fuck was that?
Who you callin'?
Oi, I said, "Who you callin'?"
Fuck this.
Put the phone down now!
You don't wanna hurt me.
No? Why's that?
'Cause I think I just saved your life.
Run home Aiden. Don't stop.
This is DI Ravi Dhillon.
I'm sorry I can't take your call
at the moment.
For anything urgent, please contact
the Heart Valley Police Department
on 01632960555.
In 200 yards, turn left,
then you have reached your destination.
This is DI Ravi Dhillon requesting
a PNC vehicle check
on registration November, four, three,
six, whisky, November, tango.
Confirming.
November, four, three, six,
whisky, November, tango.
That's it.
It's not in the database.
It's all connected,
your dreams,
your memories,
everything that happens,
everything that doesn't,
everything that will.
You, me, him.
Isaac.
I don't know what happened to your son,
Lucy, but I can guess.
- So guess.
- You won't believe me. Not yet.
Not until you're as crazy as I am.
So that's what this is,
you're going for the insanity plea,
avoid a prison sentence.
I really don't care very much
what happens to me.
Sooner or later
I'll find a way to kill myself.
If that's what you want,
I... I'm not gonna stand in your way.
I think you would.
You're a good man,
that's why this job never suited you.
You're not at home in the dark.
You pretend that you're not scared
but most days you're terrified,
lost, lying to yourself,
trying to play the action hero
but that's not who you are,
is it, Dhillon?
He's just turned off junction six.
What road is that?
I don't know.
Southbound?
Look it up and call it in.
Are you sure
you wanna be doing this?
We can't lose him Nick.
What if he doesn't like being followed?
Nick?
I said,
what if he doesn't like being followed?
He won't see me.
Oh, shit.
You there?
Put your hands on the car!
You're not supposed to be here!
You don't wanna do this.
Back away, Dhillon.
I've never killed you before
and I'd rather keep it that way.
Little bit further. That's it.
This won't end well for you.
It won't end well for anyone.
Not with Stenner alive.
What do you know about Aiden Stenner?
I could have put him
out of his misery
if she hadn't been there.
If you hadn't followed me.
Now somebody else is gonna die.
No one has to die.
Just put the gun down, let's talk.
We are talking,
but you're not listening!
You never do.
What are you doing?
Waiting.
Waiting for what?
"I never killed you before,"
that's what you said to me,
that night in the lanes.
"I haven't killed you yet,"
that would make sense.
But you said,
"I haven't killed you before."
You should have listened.
I wish you'd listened.
I could have stopped the chaos,
but now you blame me.
You blame me because that's easier
than blaming yourself.
Blaming myself for what?
What happened after the storm.
That's all I got.
Mia's place.
They're looking for you right? Police?
I dunno.
You see that makes me nervous
'cause we got three of ours in jail
right now, bruv,
so who you been talkin' to?
Ain't a snitch.
Mia says you want off the line.
Is that right?
- Man, I paid. I paid what I owe...
- I tell you what you fuckin' owe me!
What's that?
Nothin'.
Show me.
You use this?
I could. Like, if I need to.
Look, you wanna come off the line,
- you gotta make it right with us, yeah?
- Yeah.
Can't fuckin' hear you!
Yeah, man.
I'll make it right.
Well, that's music to my fuckin' ears.
You got a burner?
It's Tyler that brought you in, right?
You know that pig that fucked up his leg,
them locking him up like that,
fucking police
brutality if you ask me.
Think they can do what they like,
no comebacks but...
he don't know we got his name.
He don't know we got his fuckin' house.
So you, you're gonna make this right.
Okay.
Here you go.
Is...
that better?
If you get cold, you tell me
and I can switch this on for you.
Oh, I hope you're not coming down
with something.
- Do you feel okay?
- I'm cold.
I know sweetheart, I'm gonna
get you some blankets, hold on.
Hey Rob, what's up?
Kate Stenner's issued
a formal complaint.
- Says you assaulted her.
- You're kidding?
I wish I was.
Look, obviously I've given them
my side of the story but...
but they're gonna suspend you.
Uh, pay you, I think,
just until they get it straightened out.
I saved her son's life
and she's got no idea.
What do you mean?
Nothing.
Doesn't matter anymore.
Erm, thanks for telling me, Rob,
I appreciate it.
Look we'll talk tomorrow.
Are you sure you're okay?
Yeah.
Uh, goodnight, Rob.
Okay, let's get you tucked up and warm...
Isaac, what you doing?
Don't do that, it's hot.
No, no, no, no, no, sweetheart!
- I'm cold.
- Oh, my God.
Why are you laughing?
It's not funny.
Isaac, why are you laughing?
Two fish in a tank,
one says to the other,
"Do you know how to drive this thing?"
That's hilarious.
I'm serious.
You, write a book?
Takes you about two days
to write a bloody e-mail.
I've got stories, you know.
You've got pub stories.
Sorry, but you'll have to do
better than that.
What about security?
Mm, they work nights
and it's dangerous.
Who knows.
Maybe I'll be a bloody taxidermist.
Mm, come here.
You know, you don't have to do anything.
I'm not old enough to retire.
And we'd have to take a hit
on the pension.
- Bella?
- Shh.
- What was that?
- What was what?
I don't know.
Did you lock the back door?
Probably.
Probably or definitely?
Yes. Now come on,
I'm tired, let's go to sleep.
I love you, Nick Holness.
I love you too.
Mm.