.
- Previously on
"Good Girls"...
- Guess we're
back in business.
Lemonade?
We have an employee, okay?
- Where did this guy
go to prison?
- He's gonna wash in ways
that we can't.
- So he just showed up
with all of it?
- Minus his cut, yeah.
- So your sister
was trying to protect you?
- Who's gonna protect her?
- You know what
they call this in the biz?
A breakthrough.
- Your principal says that you
and some girls shoplifted this.
- Like mother,
like daughter, I guess.
- We're not bad people.
- No, baby, we're good people
who do bad things.
- I gotta show you something.
- [screams]
- Lung...
[grunts]
Spleen.
Shoulder.
Yeah, we both know
how this ends.
- I'm pregnant.
- So you have
a nine-month solution
to a permanent problem.
- Three months.
Maybe four.
- Congratulations.
- Paternity test.
- Oh, you can do that
in about a month.
- Tried telling him to leave.
Says his boss needs him
to keep an eye on you.
Who's his boss?
- There's something
I have to tell you.
[Jazzboy's "Harlem"]
♪
- Are we going to school today?
- Uh--
- We're already late.
- ♪ Harlem
- Where's Kenny?
- Upstairs pooping.
- Go get him.
- ♪ Can't remember
of the season, season ♪
♪ Half past seven
♪ Oh, Harlem
- Good morning.
- I called the cops.
- [chuckles]
Okay.
- I have kids.
- I ain't got no issue
with them.
♪
You don't wanna do that.
- Oh, I think I do.
- [chuckles]
It's up to you.
- Fine.
Get arrested.
- Kay.
But you know what I gotta do
when I get out.
♪
- How we doing, folks?
Ma'am, got a call about
someone in the neighborhood?
- I-I called, yeah.
Um...
It's--everything's okay...
[laughs nervously] Officer.
Thank you.
Sorry.
- Y'all have a good day, then.
- Kay.
[Jazzboy's "Harlem" continues]
♪
- ♪ Harlem
- ♪ You got to me, I was 11
- ♪ 11
[vocalizing]
- Looking for some firepower?
- I'm looking for something.
[kids laugh]
- 'Cause it's not the gun
that does the damage.
It's the caliber of the bullet.
- Mm-hmm.
- So just depends
on your needs.
- I need to kill a man.
- Oh, oh, okay, uh...
[laughs nervously]
There are certain things
you can or can't say
when buying a gun.
- Mm, right.
- And, uh,
well, you just said
the only thing you can't say.
- What if I'm dealing
with a really aggressive moose.
- Oh, like an Alaska Yukon or--
- The kind that attacks you.
- That'd be the Shiras.
- Now, this moose--
he also has a thing
for my wife.
- Wait, what exactly
are we talking about here?
- We're talking about a moose,
Sean, who breaks into my house.
He threatens my kids,
has his way with my wife,
and I can't seem to ever
do anything about it.
- All right, well, that will...
[clears throat]
Narrow your selection
down to the Prairie Hawk,
the Liberty single-shot--
- Whichever's your favorite.
- Uh, just a few
easy questions for you,
like have you ever been
convicted of a violent crime?
- No.
- Ever get a not guilty verdict
by reason of insanity?
- No.
- Okay, well, just check "no"
for the rest of these,
and we'll get back to you
in a few days, maybe a week.
- Well, what if I need it
sooner?
- Well, with this type
of firearm,
they require us
to do a background check.
- What could I walk out
with today?
- He reads?
- Is that an "US Weekly"?
- "In Touch."
Mrs. Karpinski gave it to him
after he brought in
her recycling bins.
- [sighs]
- Jesus.
- How does he even
go to the bathroom?
- Mrs. Karpinski.
- That bitch.
- You guys,
I can't live like this.
- Okay.
Okay, here's what we do.
We go to Canada and get a baby.
- Get a baby?
- Well, she said
she's having his baby.
We're gonna need a baby.
- What are you gonna do?
pick one up with a cruller
from Tim Horton's?
- Oh, my God.
- That's where we got
that fake cash.
I mean, who knows what else
they're hiding up there?
Although we could just
pay for one.
I mean, the cash exchange rate
right now up there
is actually--
- You wanna buy a baby?
- I want my sister to not die.
- I wanna go to bed.
- Nuh-uh.
- What?
- You cannot be serious,
Mrs. Karpinski.
- Oh, dude.
- It's like she wants him
to use her bathroom.
- Oh, look at this.
She got snacks on snacks now.
- [sighs]
We'll figure
something out, okay?
[announcer talking
indistinctly on TV]
I'm sorry.
Am I in the wrong house?
[crowd ohhs on TV]
What is happening?
- Dad's mad.
- About what?
- I got fired from tutoring.
- Tell her why.
- They said
I took their stupid pen.
- We gave you a backpack
full of school supplies.
- Mm-mm.
It's not like that.
- Was it used to sign the
Declaration of Independence?
- Maybe.
- What?
- Yeah, they said it's some
platinum engraved fountain deal
that costs as much as a car.
- I didn't do it.
- Hm, where have we heard
that one before?
- How about their own daughter
who's always vaping
and skipping class?
- Okay, why don't you go
to your room
so I can talk to your daddy?
[door slams]
- You don't know she did it.
- And you don't know
she didn't.
- Okay, well,
what do we do from here?
- Oh, it's a "we"
situation now?
- And that means what?
- You're the resident
crime lord.
[pensive music]
♪
- [snoring]
[knocks]
- Can't sleep?
- Oh, God.
[dog barking]
Give me a ride.
[music escalates]
♪
- What's good?
- Can I get a shot of tequila?
- You might wanna
slow down, yeah?
- We never got to toast.
[drink pouring]
One for my baby daddy here too.
- What are you doing,
Elizabeth?
- I lost it.
[breathes deeply]
- When?
- Does it matter?
- All right, then.
[soft dramatic music]
♪
[exhales]
- So what comes next?
- Nothing good.
- How much would it cost?
- For what?
- My life.
- Ah, nah, too late for that.
- You haven't been in the game
for, what, two months?
- Don't worry about it.
- No pills, no cars, no cash?
It's gotta hurt.
- You don't know my interests.
- I know they need capital.
And your guy could chop me up
in a million pieces
whenever you want,
so what do you got to lose?
- [scoffs]
- How much am I worth?
- You couldn't afford it.
- What if I could?
.
- Okay, pros and cons.
- Pro.
You're not dead yet.
- How are we gonna get
100 grand?
- Another pro.
- How is that a pro?
- Well, he could have said,
like, 100 bucks,
which would have been
way easier,
but said a lot less
about you as a person.
- Do you know how many ones
we're gonna have to get
to print that much?
- Con.
- Thank you.
- It's a lot.
- Not to mention washing it.
- Con.
- Okay, there are gonna
be a lot more cons than pros.
- How firm was he
on this number?
[door clicks]
- Hey, ladies.
- What is going on?
- I got floss.
- Oh?
- We were out.
- What else did you get, Dean?
- Hm, got some razors,
deodorant.
I'm gonna try these
Breathe Right
nose strip thingies--
- Why is there a shotgun
on our bed?
- It's the only gun I can get
without a waiting period.
- What if the kids find it?
- I'll hide the ammo.
- And what if they find that?
- They won't.
- Kenny's found every one
of his Christmas gifts
for the past five years.
- That's 'cause you hide them.
- I know you're upset--
- No.
I'm terrified.
- And I get that.
But this isn't gonna
make him go away.
- Then tell me what will.
- I don't want a gun
in my house.
- And I don't want the tweaker
on the front lawn
reporting back to the guy who
emptied a clip in me, but hey,
that's the world
we're living in.
- Hmm, uh...
Time.
- 9 minutes, 38 seconds.
- Mm.
Not bad.
- Yeah, it's for preschoolers,
but congrats.
- What else you got
around here?
- We could talk about stuff.
- How do you talk
about something
that you can't talk about?
- Well, just start.
- I'm really worried
about my sister.
- Okay.
- She's dealing with something
that's very life-threatening.
- Well, they say
when someone gets sick,
it might as well be
the whole family.
- It's just that we thought
that it was gone,
and now it's back.
- The big C huh?
- Mmm.
- What kind?
- It's super rare.
- I lost my mum the same way.
- Oh, God.
- So I've been down the road.
- Yeah, it's just--it's not,
you know, one of the--
like a breast cancer
or a lung--
not one of
the super popular ones, so--
- Try me.
- [sighs]
I-I just--
I--
Eye...
ball...
cancer.
It's eyeball cancer.
Just the, uh--just the one.
Left one.
- Retinoblastoma?
- If I never hear
that word again...
- That's how my mum died.
- Oh, no.
- Has she--
has she lost her vision yet?
- Ish?
- Mum always wanted to see
the Grand Canyon.
I planned a whole thing.
We'd stay at the lodge
on the valley floor.
- It's supposed to be great.
- Yeah, but, um,
I got this cat 'cause I was
having a hard time dealing,
and it wouldn't sleep,
so I pushed the trip by a week.
She went completely blind
the night before our flight.
- Did you still go?
- I mean,
she said it smelled amazing.
[chuckles]
That's just who she was.
Um...
This made me
wanna be a therapist.
- "The Eye in Survivor."
- You're gonna make it whether
your sister does or not.
[gentle tender music]
♪
- Okay, I feel much better.
Thank you.
- Yeah.
- Same time,
same place next week.
I'm gonna grab Timmy.
Timmy!
Timothy, come on in.
[indistinct chatter]
- Add 350 to that.
- You know you don't have to
put the dot zero zero, right?
- I'm aware.
Thank you.
- Plus 200.
Stan's working a bachelor party.
- And I get time and a half
for nights,
so put half--like, another--
[patrons cheering loudly]
For, like, another hundred.
No dot zero zero.
- Okay, I like to see
the whole number, all right?
- Where we at?
- So that puts us at--
still way off.
- If we didn't hit
Fine and Frugal,
I had another plan.
Okay, this general attitude
is why I keep things to myself.
- What?
- You remember when
that Kardashian got, like,
a bazillion-carat
diamond necklace
stolen from her hotel room
in Paris?
- All right, I gotta pee.
[sighs]
- Do you still wanna hear it?
[knocking on door]
- Ooh.
[inhales deeply]
[winces]
[Delta 5's
"Mind Your Own Business"]
♪
- The hardest part is finding
the right width because
I think it has to be
of a certain quality that--
- Let's go.
We gotta go.
- Okay, you gotta
listen to this.
It's insane, but,
if we had explosives,
a hypnotist,
and a military helicopter,
we might be able
to pull this off.
- Hang on.
Did you--did you change?
- Yeah.
I got our money.
- What?
- It's Gordie Howe's.
- That means nothing to me.
- From the 1955 Stanley Cup.
- Even less.
- ♪ Can I have a taste
of your ice cream? ♪
♪ Can I lick the crumbs
from your table? ♪
- Oh, we gotta go.
- Let's go.
Let's go.
- ♪ Can I interfere
in your crisis? ♪
♪ No, mind your own business
[patrons cheer loudly]
- Oof!
[tray clatters]
♪
- Oh, my God.
I'm so sorry.
- It's okay.
It's old.
.
- I grabbed the only thing
I could think of.
- What was that?
- A toilet plunger.
- Smart.
- But I had to use
the wood part
to break the glass.
- Uh, but,
what'd you hold on to?
- Toothbrush.
- You didn't.
- I did.
- Vinegar, baking soda,
lemon juice.
- Did you at least wrap some
toilet paper around it?
- There was so much pressure
from the knocking.
- Plunger's seen some things.
- There's a volcano burger
on that menu.
- Double bison patty
smothered in habanero sauce.
- It comes with
bottomless chili fries.
- Oh.
- [sighing] Okay.
[mellow music]
- Now what?
- We wait.
- [whispers]
It's gonna be worth it.
- [inhales deeply]
- [sighs]
♪
- Hey.
How we doing tonight?
- How do you think we're doing?
- How do you even know
what this thing looks like?
- The guy sent me, like,
four different angles of it.
Hm?
Apparently, it belonged
to his grandfather.
- At what point
are we taking this too far?
- This is our job, Ruby.
- She's a straight A student.
- Yeah, smart like a fox.
- She tutors, volunteers--
- Good cover.
- The other day,
I watched her bring in
the Connor's trash cans
without even being asked.
- Casing the joint.
- She's a perfect kid.
- Yeah, and so were you.
[ambient electronic music]
♪
- [sighs]
- She's not me.
I need to get in there.
Please.
♪
[door clicks]
- Hey.
- What are you doing here?
- Um, uh,
I read it, so...
- Already?
- It's a--
it's a real page turner.
- Kay.
- Um, hey,
can I ask you something?
- Now?
- Yeah.
What's going on
with--with us?
- What do you mean?
- Well, you hugged me...
- Okay.
- With both arms.
- That's how I hug.
- It felt a little...
long.
- Ah, right, um,
maybe I overstepped.
- Maybe--
maybe I liked it.
- Um, I know
you're going through a lot.
- Oh, no.
No, no.
- There is still a line here.
- Oh, come on.
Grow a pair.
- We shouldn't cross it.
- And where is that line,
just so I'm aware?
- And to paraphrase Freud--
- Don't you need
a real degree to do that?
- Sometimes a hug is just a hug.
- Mm.
Okay.
Thank you so much, Dr. Cohen.
- I'm gonna go back
to the office and count to 50.
[MEMBA's "Schools Out"]
♪
- Little spot
of something red here.
- I think it's blood.
- Probably from that brawl
in the third period.
- Cool.
- So are we good?
- Let me run it past my guy.
[door creaks, clicks]
- [sighs]
- Late night?
- Couldn't sleep.
- Weren't you wearing
that yesterday?
- Okay,
I can see where this is going,
so just gonna cut it off
at the pass.
I tried to seduce
my therapist, okay?
Like, sexually.
Bone town.
He straight up rejected me,
so I went home alone,
drank a lethal amount
of Goldschlaeger,
and fell asleep in a pile
of my own Cheetos dust.
So if you wanna
rip me a new one
for being four minutes late,
you go right ahead,
but I'm not gonna feel
any worse than I already do.
- You're in therapy?
- Like, physical therapy?
- Why would I be
in physical therapy?
- I don't know.
'Cause of how you run?
- What's wrong with how I run?
- All right, ladies.
Where'd y'all say you got this?
- Oh, it's been in my family
for many generations.
- Yeah, our grandfather
taught him how to skate.
- Our great-great...
- Great-great-great...
- Grandfather.
- Hm.
Was he Chinese?
- Huh?
- 'Cause that's where
this jersey was made,
like, two years ago.
- Excuse me--
- Wait, it's a fake?
- How much for it?
- 20 bucks.
- 20 bucks?
- All right, 25.
- Excuse me.
Where did you get this?
- Limited edition.
Solid platinum barrel.
18 carat nib.
- Who brought it in?
- Some girl.
- Like, a little blonde
druggie type?
- What is going on?
- Okay, I'm not interested.
- Fine, we'll take the 20.
- I'd like you to leave.
- Was it her?
- You guys cops?
.
[door thuds]
- Guess what.
- [sighs]
Jesus.
- Language.
- You're home early.
- Got some good news.
- What's that?
- They found the pen.
- Wow.
- Yeah, so I made you these.
I know you've been worked up.
- How is it?
- Awesome.
- Jesus.
- What?
- How do you do that?
- Eat that like you deserve it.
Where's the money?
- Does Dad know?
- Where did you hide it?
- I don't have--
- Where?
- Same place you hide yours.
I don't know what you do,
but it doesn't come
from painting nails.
- [sighs]
- What do you talk about?
- Just stuff.
- Like what kind of stuff?
- More lo mein anyone?
Mmm, mm-hmm.
- Like me?
- I'm probably gonna stop going.
- Oh, my God.
It's 100% me.
- Okay, you know what?
Let's do fortunes.
- Well, mine doesn't have one,
so that's probably not good.
- Huh, let's see.
"You are smarter, prettier,
and much cooler
than your sibling."
Wow, hm.
- That's not what it says.
Show me.
- No, it does.
No, it does.
Says it right here.
- Give it to me.
- No!
That's like telling you
my birthday wish.
Fortune wants what it wants.
[knocking on door]
And now it shall
be written forever.
- You're the worst.
- Hey.
Thank you.
- Thank my derelict daughter.
- What are you gonna do to her?
- Um, I haven't devised it yet,
but it is definitely
gonna be illegal.
- Okay,
let's bring home some bacon.
[Sheena Easton's
"Morning Train"]
♪
- ♪ I wake up every morning
♪ I stumble out of bed
♪ Stretching and yawning
♪ Another day ahead
♪ It seems to last forever
♪ And time goes slowly by
♪ Till babe
and me's together ♪
♪ Then it starts to fly
♪ 'Cause the moment
that he's with me ♪
♪ Time can take a flight
♪ The moment
that he's with me ♪
♪ Everything's all right
♪ Night time
is the right time ♪
♪ We make love
♪ Then it's his and my time
♪ We take off
♪ My baby takes
the morning train ♪
♪ He works from
nine till five and then ♪
♪ He takes another
home again ♪
♪ To find me
waiting for him ♪
♪ My baby takes
the morning train ♪
♪ He works from
nine till five and then ♪
♪ He takes another
home again ♪
♪ To find me
waiting for him ♪
♪ All day I think of him
♪ Dreaming of him constantly
♪ I'm crazy mad for him
♪ And he's crazy mad for me
♪ When he steps
off that train ♪
♪ Amazingly full of fight
♪ Work all day
to earn his pay ♪
♪ So we can play
♪ All night
♪ My baby takes
the morning train ♪
♪ He works from
nine till five and then ♪
♪ He takes another
home again ♪
♪ To find me
waiting for him ♪
[music stops]
- [humming Sheena Easton's
"Morning Train"]
[muffled speech]
- Afraid we got a problem.
So here's the thing, man.
If you wanna move
your funny money
through my guys,
we gotta get some stuff
straight, yeah?
- Mm-hmm.
- Yeah?
- Mm-hmm!
- All right, for starters,
there is a licensing fee,
but, you know, if that's
gonna be an issue for you,
We can just--
- Mm-mm!
[muffled speech]
- No problem?
- Mm-hmm.
- Good.
Good, good, good,
good, good, man, good.
I was hoping you'd say that.
- Mm-hmm.
- Now, I need to know
who your employer is
'cause I don't know you.
[laughs]
And you don't know me.
I feel like
I should know everybody
that I work with, right?
- Mm-hmm.
- Yeah?
[muffled speech]
- What's that now?
I--
- [muffled speech continues]
[soft dramatic music]
♪
[muffled shouting]
- So who made your money?
.
- I'm home.
- Hey, babe.
I got your food
warming in the oven.
- Ah, okay.
You got a test tomorrow?
- Algebra.
- Hm.
So your mama told me
what happened.
[sighs]
So what now?
Stevensons gonna give her
that job back?
- Ooh.
It's up to her.
- I mean, either way,
they owe our family an apology.
All right,
gotta wash this day off first.
I love you.
- Why didn't you tell him?
- Because it would
break his heart.
- What if he runs into
Mr. Stevenson somewhere?
- Well,
that's the problem, isn't it?
You make up one story,
then you gotta make up
another to cover that story.
Before you know it,
you can't keep
any of them straight.
- Am I grounded?
- That's for kids.
You're big-time now.
You're a criminal.
- So what's that mean?
- You're gonna owe me.
[soft dramatic music]
♪
[door clicks]
- Hey, need a hand?
- Well, aren't you full service?
- You've missed two sessions.
- Stalking included.
- I got worried.
- Look, there's no point, okay?
I made it weird.
- We should talk about that.
- And make it weirder?
- It's called transference.
When people make progress
in therapy,
it's not uncommon to,
you know, develop, like, a crush
on the person helping them.
- Okay, well, this right now
is definitely not helping,
and I have stuff to do, so...
- All right.
See you.
- I'll, uh,
go back in my apartment,
count to 50.
- You know what I think?
You have a storied history
of pursuing inaccessible men,
which is a defense mechanism
to protect you from rejection.
In fact, you do that
with a lot in your life.
I mean, why pursue anything
that would make you happy
when there's a chance
you might not get it, right?
And you put all that
under a nice thick layer
of sex and sarcasm
that makes you bulletproof
to any real emotion.
But, uh, you know, hey.
What do I know?
I graduated
bottom of my class online.
- You can't charge me for that.
- If you don't come back,
I've gotta fill your spot.
- Hey, have you seen my purse?
- The, um--
the ammo's in the office.
The gun is in the garage
with the lawn stuff.
- How would you ever get to it?
- I just like knowing
it's there.
- Okay.
- We were so good
with him gone.
[pulsating electronic music]
♪
Purse is on the couch.
[door bell jingles]
[door creaks]
- I'll be right with you.
- Hey, now.
- I don't have it all
right now, okay?
- I'm not here for that.
I'm just here for some
custom printing.
Word is you do the best work.
I'd like to see how it's done.
- I don't know
what you're talking about.
- Oh, no?
'Cause your friend
says you do.
I wanna see.
- Well, he's got it wrong.
[gun clicks]
- Show me.
[Gabriel Bruce's "El Musgo"]
♪
- ♪ The trees dance
♪ They sway and bend
♪ To a song that
♪ Never ends
♪ The dragonflies
♪ Are making friends
♪ Unlike you and me
♪
♪ The sun paints patterns
♪ On your skin
♪ Through the lace that
♪ You dress in
♪ You walk on water
♪ But I would rather swim
♪ Whilst you look down on me
♪
♪ I hear your voice
♪ It's loud and clear
♪ I thought we were close
♪ But you were just near
♪
♪ When you talk
♪ It's not your voice
that I hear ♪
♪
♪ It's a symphony
- Pulp's gotta dry now.
- Okay.
- Takes a while.
- I got time.
- ♪ So I'll just watch you
♪ From afar
♪ I'll just hope
the weather is better ♪
♪ Where you are
♪ I'll wear this mark
like a medal ♪
♪ But it's a scar
♪ Where you took my heart
♪ From me
♪
- What do you think?
- I think I need you alive.
♪
chorus: ♪ Ooh