.
- Previously on
"Good Girls..."
- Did you remove a pen cap
from the evidence locker?
- I failed.
It's over.
- I tried to seduce
my therapist.
He straight-up rejected me.
- You've missed two sessions.
- There's no point, okay?
I made it weird.
- If you don't come back,
I've got to fill your spot.
- There's been a bit
of a snafu.
- You don't say.
- What if I made it up to you?
Not him but you.
- That'd be a huge order.
- You draw it?
- We make an engraver's plate
and print it all on site.
- Cool.
- You cannot
finish that plate.
- He said he'd let me go--
- He won't.
Wait, you need us.
You need all of us.
- Not all of you.
[tense music]
[gunshots]
- Have you heard from Lucy?
- I'm sure she's fine.
♪
[phone buzzes]
- ♪ Mm
♪ Mm
[dreamy music]
♪
- What is it?
- [sighs]
Her and the boyfriend.
♪
- So happy.
- ♪ Mm
- Little do they know.
♪
- We're just torturing
ourselves.
- Why did you take all this?
- I couldn't leave it there.
- Why not?
- Her phone was ringing.
Someone would notice
something horrible happened.
- Something horrible
did happen.
- And we just stood there
and watched.
♪
- I didn't watch.
- Honestly, neither did I.
- I did.
Saw the whole thing.
- Annie.
- It could've been us.
- She never even used this.
- What are we gonna do?
♪ To take the pain away,
Getting strong today ♪
- Print.
- Mommy, where are you?
- Here.
- Something happened
with Dorito!
- Oh, my God, what?
- He can sing!
- No way.
- Wow.
- Neato.
[bell jingles]
- Let me just drop my bag.
- Uh, Dorothy
wants to see you.
[bell jingles]
- Oh, Dorothy's here?
- In the back.
[ominous music]
♪
- Is everything okay?
- She's the one
who saw her last.
- I wouldn't say we're
best friends, exactly.
- Lucy would.
- Sisters more like.
- Mmm.
She's just the sweetest
little thing.
[sighs] I wish there was
something I could do.
- You could head
our media coverage.
- Consider it done.
- Like, start a hotline.
- I could print
beautiful posters.
Oh, do they still do those
adorable pictures
on milk cartons?
- Okay--
- Who will lead the air search,
Officer?
- Pump the brakes, folks.
We really can't do much
till it's been 72 hours.
Now where'd you last see her?
- We worked together
the other night.
- Anything unusual?
- No.
I left,
and she stayed and locked up.
- Well, no more of that.
- What do you mean?
- Well, I'm closing early
till we get some answers.
- Well, how will we
work nights?
- We're not, sweetie.
Mm.
- What about everything that
was in her fridge
or, like, her laundry
that was in the dryer.
I mean,
does someone fold that now,
or does it all just end up
in trash bag out on the curb?
- Well, how are you all
related again?
- She was someone
my sister worked with.
- I meant Gregg and Nancy.
- I wrecked their marriage.
- Ah, that's right.
- [sighs]
And what about, like,
her Instagram?
Or any of her social media?
Just frozen in time now
like those clocks at Chernobyl.
She had this lipstick.
She never even opened it.
Like, it was from France
or something.
I mean it must've cost her
like half her paycheck.
You know?
It's like a Cinderella level
lip scenario.
You can tell that she thought
she was really going somewhere
special with it,
but instead
she just went poof.
- Can I ask you something?
- Please.
- [inhales]
Are you wearing perfume?
- Excuse me?
- I'm smelling
something floral.
- Uh...
- From the moment
you sat down--
- I don't wear perfume.
- Body wash?
- Just plain soap.
- Hm.
- So I guess what
I really want to know is...
[sighs]
When do I stop seeing it
in my brain?
- Any lotions
or fabric softeners?
- Are you being serious?
- Sometimes the boxes
for scented and unscented
look the same.
- Someone died.
- I wanna help you.
- Thank you.
- For that to work, I need
complete and total honesty.
- Okay.
- Let's start over.
- Great.
- Are you wearing perfume?
- It's not fair!
- That's how you play.
- Last game.
Heads hit pillows in ten.
- Uno!
[humming]
- Uh, you got two cards.
- So?
- "Uno" means one, dummy.
- Remember when we thought
the age difference
would help them get along?
- My suspension
is up for review.
- How?
- Uh, maybe with Turner gone,
the D.A. doesn't have enough.
- So what's it mean?
- They might give me
my badge back.
- Do you want it back?
- You're gonna be a cop again,
Daddy?
- Well, they gotta talk to
Mommy and me about it first.
- Why do they wanna talk to me?
- Not about egg roll.
- Then what's it about?
- Mm-mm-mm.
Making me look good.
[kids mumbling]
All right, chop chop.
[melancholy music]
♪
- I don't have it.
- Really?
Again?
- I don't know what to say.
I don't have it.
[car engine stops]
[car door clicks open]
- [sighs]
- She was a good person.
- Seemed like
a really sweet girl.
- You didn't have to do it.
- Kinda did.
- She never would've
said anything.
- Rotten egg's a rotten egg.
It's just business, darling.
- Well, now you've screwed
your entire enterprise.
- Oh yeah?
How's that?
- Her boyfriend,
who is also a very good
person, by the way...
is beside himself
and has called the cops.
- Mmm.
[chuckles]
- Yeah.
And he's got the woman who
owns this place so freaked out
she's got it on lockdown, so...
great job, Mr. CFO!
- [sniffs]
So who's the boyfriend?
- Why?
- 'Cause he's gonna need
an address.
- No.
- We gotta get
back up and running.
I got my own debts to pay,
all right?
- No!
- Oh, you still think
you get a say in this, huh?
Nah, see that ship sailed when
you put three slugs in me.
- This is your fault!
- You, me, we?
It's just business.
♪
- I'll print.
- But what happened?
I thought you were on lockdown?
- I'll find a way.
- Gee, thanks.
That'll make it easier
on everybody.
[car door clicks shut,
engine revs]
[car door clicks open, shut]
.
- Are you sure this is hers?
- It was in her purse.
- One, two, three, four?
- Nope.
- What's her birthday?
- I have no idea.
- Four, three, two, one.
- What's Au Jus's birthday?
- Oh, like I'd know that.
- And I'm locked out again.
[sighs]
- What were you gonna text him
anyway?
- I don't know, like,
"I need space,
and so I left town."
- Oh, like a "Eat Pray Love"
situation?
- Ooh, that's good.
I'm mean, it's, like--
It's like he's been smothering
me and loving me too hard
and maybe I wanna buy
my own tampons for a change.
- Hey, hold up.
He's buying you tampons now?
- Not me.
Lucy.
- She's gonna dump his ass
so he calls off the cops
before they go all CSI.
- It's kinda harsh.
- Yeah, better than kinda dead.
- I'm sorry,
why did you think
we were trying
to break in to the phone?
- For everything
you guys just said,
just I thought we were gonna
slide into his DMs.
Oh, hello!
What's the
boyfriend's birthday?
- How would I know that?
- Don't you wanna ask the bird?
- Okay.
I'm just trying
to be a team player
and get in to that phone.
- Okay, well there's
a million possibilities,
and we're never
gonna guess it.
- [sighs]
- It's the new one.
- So?
- What?
- [whispers] There's another
way to get in.
[music playing faintly]
- [munching]
♪
Want some?
- I'm good.
- Mmm.
Can I get some more
bronco sauce?
- Yeah, one sec.
- [munching]
♪
- So...
- [smacking lips]
- Can you get it?
♪
- She's not in one piece.
- I don't need all of her.
♪
- What do you need?
- I just need her face.
- Bronco sauce.
♪
- You still owe me
for the last favor.
- I expected you would
bring that up,
so I thought I would triple
your invitation order.
- [laughs]
How you gonna do that?
You can't even make
your regular delivery.
- Exactly.
It's a vicious cycle,
don't you see?
I can't help you
if you don't help me.
- Or...
- Or?
- You can give me something
I know you got.
[smacking lips]
It's been on my mind
for a while now.
♪
- What's that?
- [laughs]
Your husband won't like it.
- I have herpes.
♪
- I want a hot tub.
- Oh.
- You say your prayers?
- In my head!
- That works.
[video game music]
What is that, sir?
- Nothing.
- That better not be my phone.
[music stops]
- I've been to hell and back
looking for that thing.
Give it to me.
- One more game!
- Better give me that phone
before I "one more game" you.
Go to sleep.
Good night.
- Mmm, how's this gonna work?
- How's what gonna work?
- How's Daddy supposed to be
a cop again?
- What do you mean?
- He'll have to arrest you.
I mean, right?
Like, at some point.
- Don't forget to floss.
[door slams]
- Hey, do you have a second?
- He won't eat.
- Since when?
- The kids said
he stopped singing.
Come on, Dorito.
Come on, lick it.
Come here, lick it.
Lick it for dada.
- How long does it take
to get a hot tub?
- Um, um, depends on the model
and the upgrades?
- Is there, like, a floor model
you could get right away?
- He's just not himself.
What if he is sick?
- I need your help.
- I can't watch
another thing die.
- Dean.
Neither can I.
- How many does this one hold?
- Um, that particular brand
has four
contoured lounge seats.
- But, how many people
can you fit?
- I guess that would depend
on you.
- Okay.
Yeah, I'm also gonna need
that laser filtration.
- Ooh, that's a much bigger
price point.
- Is that a problem?
- Welcome to
the Four Star family.
- Hmm.
Whoo!
All right.
Let's do this.
- Well, I--
I just have to transmit this.
It's gonna just take me a--
- [laughs]
Not this.
That.
- Now?
[upbeat jazzy music]
♪
- Uh-uh.
- What?
- Too dark, too quiet,
too perfect a place
to kill some suckers.
- Man, why you gotta
put that in my head?
- Because unfortunately,
I've been in way too many
of these situations,
and now I know
what to look for.
Following a murderer
two hours through cornfields
in the middle of the night?
- Cool it.
♪
- I'm sorry,
what more did you need to see?
♪
- Just that.
Drive.
- He's not gonna kill us.
He knows Dean's not putting in
the order till we get back.
♪
You should've seen his face.
He really wants a hot tub.
♪
Which one is it?
- I didn't bury her.
♪
.
- How many fresh ones left?
- Two more.
- [sighs]
- I can't do another one.
- This is the one.
I can feel it.
Hey.
We need the light.
- Sorry, we've got that
review thing tomorrow.
Stan doesn't know what to wear.
- What are you gonna say?
- I don't know.
Suit?
[phone chimes]
- I mean, do the police
review people or whatever?
- He's wanted to be a cop
since third grade.
He'd still be one
if it wasn't for me.
- So you go in there,
and you make it right.
- What happens the next time
he has to cover
for my criminal ass?
- It'll be more than probation.
- Well, maybe there won't be
a next time.
- We're digging up
the body of a girl
who would still be singing to
her bird if she hadn't met us.
- There'll be a next time.
[phone dings]
- [sighs]
He doesn't wanna wear a suit.
- You know he can't
be a cop again?
You know that, right?
- What am I gonna do?
- Yo.
Gimme some more light.
[heavy breathing]
- They're hers.
- [groaning]
Ugh.
[breathing heavily]
- We're gonna have to
uncover her face.
- [sighs]
- [heavy breathing]
[moody piano music]
♪
[sighs]
- Give me a wet wipe.
- [heavy breathing]
- [coughs]
Give me another one.
- [whimpering]
Give me her phone.
[clears throat]
[phone clicks]
We're in.
- Oh, God.
[both panting]
- I'm gonna tell Stan to wear
a sweater and khakis.
- Always classy.
- It's a tumor.
- What?
- Stage IV.
- What are you talking about?
- He's got a hard, hot lump
right where he poops.
You can feel it.
- I'm not doing that.
- Wing MD says it could be
a feather cyst,
but the Beak Brothers, they
have this YouTube channel--
- Why don't we make
an appointment with a vet
instead of YouTube?
- There's only, like, one
avian guy in all of Detroit.
- Make an appointment.
- Just gonna say chemo.
It's probably a lot more
expensive than human chemo.
[clicking tongue]
Little guy's a goner.
- What did you say?
- He's toast. Dunzo.
It's over.
- That's not gonna happen.
- It's like we're built
on an Indian burial ground
or something.
- Look at me.
- I'm officially cursed.
- Dean.
- What?
- I will get the money.
- [scoffs]
How?
- If I have to rob every bank
in the city, I will do it.
This bird is gonna make it.
- Oh--okay.
- Dorito can't die.
- I'll make an appointment.
- Thank you.
- It's okay.
- [crying]
It's gonna be okay.
- I read that the human body
starts decomposing
within a matter of minutes.
Like, one second your this
grape, all juicy and plump...
and the next you're just
a shriveled up raisin.
- Mm-hmm.
- I can't get away from it.
- Ever tried to talk to her?
- Who?
- The face you keep seeing.
- She's...
dead.
- She ever talk to you?
- Again--
- What other faces do you see?
- [groans]
This isn't like a, uh,
like "Sixth Sense" thing,
if that's what you're--
- I don't think you're talking
to dead people, Annie.
- Oh.
Good.
- Hallucinatory psychosis
can present for many reasons.
Let me ask you a question.
- Can't wait.
- Is the face in the room
with us right now?
- [sighs]
- What's the last thing
he texted?
- "Where are you?
Please call me.
I'm worried."
There's a whole lot of those.
- Before that.
- "I'm scared you're dead."
- "Toppings for taco night."
- What did they choose?
The usual:
cheese, lettuce, tomato.
- Hard or soft shell?
- No one chooses soft.
- Yeah, they do.
Flour or corn?
- They do not.
- They do bowls too,
with rice.
- Then it ain't really
taco night is it?
- And what would you call it?
- Mexican food.
- All right,
let's get this over with.
"I'm sorry it's taken so long
to get back to you...
but I needed some time--"
- No, you can't say that.
He's gonna think
she's coming back.
- Right.
"I'm not in a place...
to be in a relationship
right now."
- That's good.
That's good.
- Yeah, say the
"it's not you, it's me" thing.
- No one says that.
- Everyone says that.
- "It's not your fault..."
- AKA, it's not you, it's me.
- "And..."
- Just do it.
We're saving his life.
- Jugular.
- "I'm not in love with you
anymore."
- Shrug emoji.
- No.
- Broken heart emoji.
- Why do I need an emoji?
- It lessens the blow.
- Oh, to the moon
with a smiley face,
like "good night,
good-bye, it's over."
- Fine.
[phone chimes]
- Now what?
- We wait and see
if he buys it.
- [sighs]
- Bubbles.
- Wow, he really misses her.
- Oh, they went away.
- They're back.
- What's it say?
[phone chimes]
- "I think we should
have this conversation
face-to-face."
- Oh, no.
- Say she's out of town.
- Bubbles.
[phone chimes]
"Don't be mad."
Why would I be mad?
I mean, Lucy.
- Bubbles.
[phone chimes]
- "I used Find My Phone.
I know you're at
your friend's house."
.
- Turn it off.
- Now?
What does that do?
- Give me the SIM card.
- Why?
- So I can smash it.
- So this is
the last known location?
- Okay, so what are we gonna do
when he shows up here?
Tell him she's napping?
- It's not the worst idea
you've ever had.
- Yeah, it is.
- Might buy us a night.
- What are you doing?
- Beth.
[phone chimes]
- What'd you say?
- To come over.
- Why would you say that?
- Because at this point,
it is either him or the cops!
- I'm sorry, but this is
definitely the worst idea
any of us have ever had.
- What could we possibly
tell that child right now?
- That she's gone.
[indistinct chatter]
- Thank you, everyone.
I appreciate your time.
[sighs]
- How'd it go?
- We'll see.
You're up next, baby.
- I'm gonna be frank with you,
Mrs. Hill.
Although he was never
formally charged,
you can understand
we have a few reservations
about reinstating him.
- Right.
- The department
had reason to believe
that your husband
was compromised
by some kind of
outside influence.
- Can I get a glass of water?
Quick top off.
- We're ready when you are.
Has your family experienced
any kind of financial hardship
since Mr. Hill's probation?
- What does that
have to do with anything?
- Can be a risk factor.
- [sighs]
We've got it pretty bad.
- Do you feel your husband's
under a lot of pressure
because of it?
- I mean, I don't know if
you've ever been in a situation
where you can't pay your bills.
Add to that
two tiny mouths to feed.
It's a pressure
you can't imagine.
- How do you both
manage that stress?
- We...
dream about robbing banks.
- Excuse me?
- Yeah, plan the whole thing:
which banks, disguises,
hostage negotiations.
Stan being a cop,
he knows all the tricks.
And don't get me wrong,
it's not just banks--
jewelry stores, art galleries,
we wouldn't even rule out
a home invasion
if, you know,
it was the right zip code.
- What's kept you
from doing it?
- Nothing.
I'd do it in a heartbeat.
The problem is, um...
he would lock me up
and throw away the key.
Let me tell you something
about my husband.
This is a man
who let Richie Green
copy off his geometry test
in ninth grade
and is still sick about it.
It haunts him.
When they're giving out
free samples at Costco,
he takes one,
even if no one is looking.
He couldn't commit a crime
if his life depended on it.
And if you knew him,
you wouldn't question
his moral fitness.
Hell, you wouldn't have
suspended him
in the first place.
Because Stanley Lamont Hill
is a cop
whether you give him a badge
or not.
So...
if there's nothing else,
I have nails to paint.
- Thank you
for your candor.
[anxious piano music]
♪
[footsteps approaching]
[knock at door]
- Is she here?
I just wanna see Lucy--
Lucy!
Lulu!
- She's not here.
Why don't you sit?
- So where is she?
- I don't know.
- She just texted me
this morning.
- And then I drove her right to
the airport after that.
- She left?
Have you ever been dumped?
- I married
my first boyfriend.
- Then you don't know.
You want it?
- Sure.
- Arizona.
- Huh.
[somber music]
♪
[bells buzzing]
- ♪ Ooh
♪
♪ Ooh
.
- Why do all shrinks suck?
- Here's another five star.
"I found Dr. Sears
on Groupon..."
- Next.
- Kay.
This one has three stars.
First session is free.
- Hmm, me likey.
- Uh-oh.
- What?
- Someone says
his couch pulls out.
- [groans]
How far away, though?
- No!
- Fine.
Next.
- This guy seems cool.
- How many reviews?
- Pages.
- I'm listening.
- "Sense of humor..."
- Love.
- "Feel like he cares."
"Great with difficult
personalities."
- Okay.
Hit me.
- 2.2 miles away.
- Done and done.
- Dr. Josh Cohen.
♪
- No.
- [sighs]
You don't mind, right?
- Just, uh--
just a moment, Tim.
- [sighs]
I wanna come back.
- Window's closed.
But I've seen, like,
every therapist in Detroit.
- That can't be true.
- Fine.
Two.
- There are others.
I can refer you.
You can waste their time.
- What is wrong with you?
- You quit me.
- Yeah, and now
I'm trying to un-quit you.
- Already gave away
your session.
- You're the worst.
- Excuse me?
- How are you not
gonna help someone
who is standing in front of you
literally begging
for your help?
- Oh, now you want help?
- It's, like,
against your oath or whatever.
- You sit on that beanbag
making jokes
while real people
come in here...
- Children.
- And do the work
'cause they wanna get better.
- I want to get better.
- You hijack appointments,
and you get off
on making a scene.
You only want attention.
- I'm just scared.
- Of what?
- That if I died tomorrow
the only thing that people
would remember about me
is what was in my purse.
- What's in it?
- Some parking tickets...
an old cheese stick,
a single googly eye,
sunglasses case--
I lost the sunglasses.
- That's quite an obit.
- Right?
- Friday at 8:30.
- a.m. or p.m.?
- a.m.
- It's kind of early.
I'll make it work.
Why'd you change your mind?
- 'Cause that was so sad.
Pathetic, really.
- Okay.
- A real therapist would
probably have you committed.
- Well, guess I'm in luck then.
[door clicks shut]
- Better not get any of that
fruit gunk on Daddy's cap.
- He said I can keep it.
- [sighs]
- Well, what'd they say?
- They'd be honored
to have me back on the force.
- That's a good thing, right?
- Yeah.
Then I came home,
tried on my uniform...
Just didn't feel right.
- So I'll let the pants out.
I'll fit it.
- No, it made me--
it made me feel like a fraud,
Ruby.
Can't fix that.
[voices on TV
chatter indistinctly]
[languid organ music]
♪
- Dorito Boland?
- That's me.
I'm--I'm Dorito's dad.
- Soon to be grandpa.
- What?
- It's not a tumor.
She's laying an egg.
- Wait, what?
- Got caught in her oviduct.
That's the lump you felt.
Dr. Cromwell's gonna aspirate,
but she'll be fine.
- Dorito's a girl?
- ♪ Or two
♪ Oh, darling,
please see the time ♪
- Oh, thank you.
- Kay, have a good night.
- Okay, you too.
- ♪ Another one like you
[bell jingles, lock clicks]
♪
- Uh, I have
all this extra birdseed,
and I don't need it anymore.
Do you guys take donations?
- ♪ Wouldn't it be easy
♪ To find someone
♪ Who has the time?
♪
♪ Whoo-hoo, hoo, hoo
♪ And why?
♪
♪ Whoo-hoo, hoo, hoo
♪ And why?
♪
- Looks a little light.
- I couldn't make as much.
- Why's that?
- The price of ink went up.
- Gonna need to
see that invoice.
♪
- Thought you might.
- How's the boyfriend?
- He got over it.
- They always do.
[elevator dings]
♪
- Hi.
Cute.
- ♪ Whoo-hoo, hoo, hoo
- Hold the elevator!
- ♪ And why?
- Thanks.
♪
- ♪ Whoo-hoo, hoo, hoo
♪ And why?
♪
♪ Whoo-ooh, ooh-ooh
[elevator rumbling]
- Where'd you
get your bird?
- Oh, my wife rescued her.
- What's its name?
- Dorito.
- [whistles
"Frere Jacques"]
- [whistles "Frere Jacques"
refrain]
[elevator rumbling]
[elevator dings]
[Halleluwah's "Dior"]
- [vocalizing]
♪