.
- Previously
on "Good Girls"...
- We suck up to the gang leader
who we stole from
and convince him
to pay us a living wage.
- Which we then use
to pay someone else
to blow his brains out.
- I am here to see
a Mr. James Fitzpatrick.
- He left something for you.
- 11,000 in incidentals?
- How much cut
have you got now?
- I don't know.
- Where's it all going,
Elizabeth?
- I can't tell you.
- Then I can't cut you in
anymore.
- I quit my job today.
- Why?
- I kissed my boss.
- Hot tubs.
It's not regulated.
Any idiot can sell them.
- Welcome to Boland Bubbles.
- This is the crime jar.
Do something good
with the money.
- I figured out
who we should help.
I got their daughter's kidney.
- How about a car?
- Pardon?
- I had him recall
the nail polish.
Nail salon robbed.
Guess what they took?
[dramatic music]
[glass shatters]
♪
[The Unicorn's "Ooh Mother"]
[solemn ballad]
- ♪ Get smart
♪ Leave school
♪ Grow hard
- [sighs]
- ♪ Be cool
♪ Keep it in your head
♪
♪ Don't get in debt
♪ Don't fret or forget
♪ To wish your neighbor well
♪
♪ Ooh, mother
♪ It ain't like
the way you said ♪
♪ Ooh, sister
♪ Well, it seems
we've been misled ♪
♪ Ooh, baby
♪ Is it worth it?
♪ Is it hell?
♪ Old lady,
you could tell us ♪
♪ So tell us well
- [sighs]
[bell dings]
♪
How you doing today?
- Better than these guys.
- Then you came
to the right person.
- Let's hope so.
- ♪ Ooh, mother
♪ It ain't like
the way you said ♪
♪ Ooh, sister
♪ Well, it seems
we've been misled ♪
- Whoa.
- What do you think?
- Bold.
- Go Red or Go Home.
- Yeah, baby.
Go red!
[laughs awkwardly]
- That's just the name
of the polish.
- Oh.
- [laughs]
And go easy on the high-fives
till you're dry.
- Okay.
Oh, hey, oh.
Can I get some change?
- Oh, yeah.
- Thanks.
Geez, you gotta check tens now?
- You never know
what's out there.
- I wouldn't even know
what to look for.
- Oh, there's little tricks.
Obvious stuff.
Security strip, the ink.
But here's the real giveaway.
You see right below Hammy
there?
- Mm-hmm.
- Tiny microprint.
- Wow, you really know
your stuff.
- Ah.
You'll smudge.
- [laughs]
- I'll be right back.
- Thanks.
[indistinct chatter]
- So what can I do
for you guys?
- Well, I guess you could say
we're in the market.
- You came back
for a hot tub?
- We want all of 'em.
- [laughs nervously]
Excuse me?
- We would like to buy
your place, Gayle.
- [knocks] Yo, Pimp.
- Hey.
- How's the delivery biz
treating you?
- Really sucks, Eric.
- Word.
- I'm not following.
- So we took monthly sales
plus the equity left
in the franchise,
we netted out
the S, G, and A costs,
and projected a 5%
cash flow growth.
- And according to the National
Pool and Spa Association,
he's being very generous.
- That's how we got the number.
It's pretty fair.
- Why would I be looking
to sell?
- Because my husband's
looking to buy.
- Maybe he should look
somewhere else.
- Why's that?
You didn't.
Two ways we can handle this.
One: you bow out discreetly
and spend a little time
with your family.
- What's the other?
- Pretty much exactly the same,
only we would be less discreet
and your family
would just hate you
for the rest of your life.
- On page three, you'll see
we let you keep the awards.
- If I sold,
it would be for way more
than what you're offering.
- Try us.
- Where are we gonna get
that kind of money?
- I don't know.
- Like, a loan or--
I'll find it.
- No.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no.
- Why?
- If we're doing this,
it has to be legit.
- [sighs]
Okay.
- For real?
- I believe in you.
- How is that a win-win?
- He gets to feel like a man,
and we have a new way
to wash our cut.
- Have you guys seen my phone?
- Okay, but in what universe
are they gonna give
a business loan
to a Postmates driver?
- Whose last business
was raided by the FBI?
- Do you even have
a credit card right now?
- I have lots of them.
And they're all maxed out.
- How is it just gone?
- Look, he's gotta believe
this thing is his, okay?
- Again, so he can
"feel like a man."
- But eventually, he'll have
to come to me for the money.
- Which we don't have.
- Few more runs.
- Then we'll all be taking
steamy Bolands.
- I swear I had it
this morning.
- Well, did you check
your purse?
- Obviously.
- Car?
- I looked.
- Because your case
is the same color as your seat.
- Not in the car.
- Find My Phone?
- Don't get mad at us.
- Yeah.
We have our phones.
- Oh, my God.
- Oh!
Your pocket.
- My pocket.
You think I didn't check
my pocket?
[TV chatter]
- Where have you been?
- You likey?
- We're done.
- Too slutty?
Not slutty enough?
- He's pulling the plug.
- Why?
- 'Cause we don't have
anything.
- How about the third best
Pad Thai Detroit has to offer?
- That's not enough.
I'm just so much hotter here.
A D.C. six
is like a Detroit nine.
- How about this?
- Is that hers?
Cute kids.
- They're okay.
- I'll unpack.
- So how's your system going?
It's...good.
It's fine.
- Just fine?
- It's great.
We're almost up and running.
- So how's it work?
- What do you mean?
- Walk me through it.
- Hot tubs
are sorta like mattresses.
- That right?
- Brands aren't
apples to apples
so there's no way of knowing
what the real price is.
My books can say anything.
- Free delivery?
- Whatever the customer wants.
- Got my tub the same day.
- It's all profit.
You have my cut?
- Yeah, about that...
I'm thinking
it'd be better business
if you just wash everything
on your end.
And like you said,
car wash thing's bad news,
right?
- Yeah, IRS is all over that.
- And we don't wanna fight
with Uncle Sam, right?
- That guy'll mess you up good.
- [laughs]
- But my system is just for me.
- Oh, no.
No.
We're consolidating.
- So you want me to print
and wash.
- Mm.
There's a business term
for that.
What is it?
- Synergy.
- Synergy!
Synergy.
That's right.
[laughs]
So same time, yeah?
- For what?
- My cut.
[door closes]
- Please tell me
you've seen my phone.
- Nope.
- [sighs]
Been looking all day.
- Well, maybe
it's with all the money
that used to be in here.
Oh, you think
'cause you stashed it
in a Chico's bag
at the bottom of the bin,
I wouldn't see it?
- They needed a car.
- You know what I did
to fill this thing?
- She put me on the spot, Stan.
- All the shady hustles.
- Our child
wouldn't even be here.
- I left my soul in that jar.
- Okay.
It's my money too.
- Our money.
- It went to the right people.
- That's not the point.
- Okay.
What if you had said no?
- That's the point.
- What?
- You didn't give me
the chance.
- You didn't see her face.
- You know what?
You deal with the kids
in the morning.
- What do you want from me?
- I got a late shift.
- Stan.
- I want you to be the woman
that I married.
- I don't even know
what that means.
- You're paying me back.
- Are you serious?
- Yeah.
- Or what, Stan?
- There is no "or what."
- Excuse me?
- Do it.
.
- "Synergy"?
- What does that even mean?
- It means
it was never our system.
- Flipping his game.
Flipping it again and again.
- We've been building it
for him.
- I mean, it sounds more like
vertical integration.
Just if you wanted
to be technical.
- Why would you tell him
it's operational?
- I said almost.
And we needed the cut.
- That we didn't get anyway.
- Sorry, is something burning?
- Danny!
I said out in the driveway!
It's his science project.
- Where is the hit man
when you need him?
- Oh, lemme tell you.
Rasta Pasta
at the Rainforest Café,
oat milk lattes
at Great Lakes--
- He went bananas
at Home Depot.
- At least he put us
back on the schedule.
- When?
- Well, I don't know
because his appointment girl
won't call me back.
- How many people is he booked
to kill in a week?
- Okay, you know what?
Let's just not freak out.
'Cause all we have to do is--
if we take the--we can--
What do we do?
- We're gonna go old-school.
We're gonna wash it
little by little
till we can afford
to buy the place.
- Can't do that.
- Why?
- I need it sooner.
- Well, it's not like
that bitch
has any other offers coming in.
- It's for my marriage.
- I've got a bigger balance
on my Starbucks card.
- What's in her email?
- Nothing.
Only took me 22 hours
and a case of Red Bull
to break in.
- Texts?
- [sighs]
Husband, playdates,
carpool, church.
Emojis.
So many prayer hands.
- Those are actually two people
high-fiving.
- So when my friend Melissa
was at the vet
with her cat
who was hit by a car,
I high-fived her?
Like, "Yay, they got him good"?
- Unless she thought
they were prayer hands.
- How do I know?
- Well, what happened
to the cat?
- She never responded.
- You high-fived its death.
I mean, who hangs out
with friends this much?
- Where'd you eat lunch
in high school?
- In the bleachers.
Why?
- Say no more.
You know none of this
is admissible.
- Don't need it for court.
[distant bass-heavy music]
♪
- Something wrong
with the potato salad?
- Nope.
[distant crowd chatter]
- 'Cause it's
your mother's recipe.
- Already ate.
- You could've saved me
the trip.
- You could've asked me first.
Oh, right.
That's not your thing.
♪
- Hey, Ruthie!
- Hey.
- Ooh, is that Cherisse's
potato salad?
- Have mine.
- Oh, yum.
♪
- I have that same cream.
- It's yours.
- It's so dope
'cause when you have to pick up
all the money from the stage,
your hands get so dry.
Thank you.
- My pleasure.
- Super silky.
- Oh, I know it is.
- You know, it feels expensive.
- Very.
[car honks]
- Hey, would you tell Neal
I'll be out there in a second?
- You bet, Stanimal.
Bye.
[safe beeping]
- I know you're dying for me
to say "could've asked."
- What if you had said no?
- Perfect.
♪
I know how we're gonna wash
that money.
[light country pop]
- We do the traditional square,
but the pillow party box
is also very popular
I will be right over here
if you have any questions.
♪
- We're robbing Stan.
.
- Literally anything else
would be better.
- Okay.
Quick brainstorm sesh?
- What do you got?
[funky music]
♪
- ATM spree.
- Yes.
We hook a chain up
to the back of a car...
♪
- Then what?
- Okay.
What about something like the--
the pizza guy
with the bomb vest?
- Oh, yeah.
But that guy robbed a bank.
- Yeah.
Yeah, but, you know,
I saw a whole Netflix
documentary about it.
He was in on it
and he walked out
with a huge bag of cash.
- And then he got his head
blown off.
- Oh, I didn't know that part.
- Must've fallen asleep
by that point.
- Ugh.
I'm so mad at Stan.
This makes the most sense.
- What makes the most sense
is couples therapy.
Not grand larceny.
- You didn't see
the way he talked to me.
- Look, Stanimal aside,
I mean, that place
is pretty much a trash heap.
- The whole hellhole
should be burned to the ground.
- At this point,
I don't even know who we owe.
Is it a hit man, homeboy,
hot tub?
So whatever.
I'm down.
- I just don't get it.
- What's not to get?
It's an armored truck.
- Swap fake for real.
- But the fake cash
goes straight to the bank
and we go straight to jail.
- So there's a few kinks
to work out.
[upbeat jazz music]
♪
- [scatting]
[singing in French]
♪
- How's the Sisterhood
of the Traveling Pants?
- Always together.
- DL Dave's gonna want more
than their favorite tabes
at Cheesecake Factory.
- Here's what I know
about girls who are this tight.
- Literally nothing.
- But they know everything
about each other.
She's not in this alone.
- Get your own.
- What?
- Beth.
- Yeah?
- High risk.
- Uh, hello.
- That's what I heard all day.
- From who?
- Banks, credit unions,
those payday places,
even that D-bag
all over the bus stops.
You know how it says
"instant approval"
or "no credit score too low"?
Guess what.
They never met Dean Boland.
- So what are you gonna do?
- [sighs]
I don't know.
My mom's gonna give us
her ottoman.
- We don't have a couch
- I told her that.
- Good.
- The ottoman will be here
tomorrow.
- [sighs]
- I know.
I'm sorry.
I just don't want him
involved again.
- Okay.
- Now could you...
- Sorry.
[distant bass-heavy music]
♪
- What are you doing here?
- You still gotta eat.
- I'm fine.
- Cheetos aren't lunch.
♪
I'm gonna pay you back.
Every cent.
♪
- Is that pot roast?
- Ten hours in the slow cooker.
♪
- 'Scuse me, sir?
Sir?
Have you seen that man?
Did you see the man
go in there?
- I didn't see anyone.
[Flamingo Pier's
"Find Your Way"]
- Said he's here
for the Caesar salad.
Like that's why a man
spends all night in there.
For the tableside Caesar salad!
- I used this merlot marinade.
- Mm-hmm.
- It's literally going to melt
in your mouth.
[car honks]
- Oh.
Be right back.
- No, one bite, one bite.
- Do they even have
a Caesar salad?
I mean, do they have
- Maybe?
- Yeah.
Maybe.
Maybe it's a nasty-ass thing
they do on his face, huh?
- Yo, Neal.
- ♪ Find your way
- I got two for you today.
- Oh, my, that's good.
- ♪ Find your way now
- Now the potatoes.
- I gotta go.
- No, no.
Just one bite, one bite.
- Neal's waiting.
- ♪ Find your way
- Mmm.
- Who are you again?
- I'm from corporate.
You know, they send me down
when they're in a pickle.
[funky music]
- I'm sorry.
Excuse me, Neal.
I'm so sorry
to put you in this position
but I'm gonna need you
to go in there
and I'm gonna need you
to get him out for me, okay?
- Look, I'm just trying
to do my job, lady.
I gotta go.
♪
ATMs.
Making it rain.
- It is monsoon season,
am I right?
- ♪ Find your way now
- Tell Stan "feel better."
- Yeah, will do.
Hey, take her ease, Neal.
- ♪ Find your way
- You gotta try
the Brussels sprouts.
- No, the man's
got runs to make.
- ♪ Find your way
- Let me make my drop,
7and I'll be back
for the Brussels, okay?
- Wait.
You can't go out there.
- [sighs]
Hey.
- Hey, buddy.
Thought you were sick.
- Yeah, it was a stomach thing.
You all good?
- Yeah, I think so.
- Mind if I check?
- Your money.
- [sighs]
Let's see...
- Everything kosher?
- Yeah.
Just wanted to check
the deposit slips.
- Well, feel better.
Lot of bugs going around.
- Yeah.
[engine turns over]
[engine revving]
.
- Huh.
- Is there a problem?
- Just didn't know
you can get checks
with dolphins on 'em.
- The kids love 'em.
- Whatever works.
- So do we have a deal?
- [sighs]
That's up to you.
- What do you need,
a week or two?
I mean, ideally,
we would like to transition
as soon as possible.
- Can I ask you something?
- And we'll need a release
from the franchise agreement.
- Why would you do this
for him?
- Because he is my husband.
- That's enough?
- No.
I need you to initial here,
here, and here.
- I'm sorry.
You just take
"standing by your man"
to a whole new level.
- Well, you don't know him.
- I know if he told you
what really happened
between us,
you wouldn't waste
a cute dolphin check on him.
Oh, honey.
- What?
- I'm not the first, am I?
- We can finish this up later.
- Should I hold on to this?
- I'll take that.
- I think that's smart.
[door closes]
- Got a new phone.
- What'd you do
with the rest of it?
[sighs]
So what?
We just good now?
- You told me to pay you back.
I did it.
- So you steal from me
to pay back what you stole?
- It wasn't really from you.
- Yeah, it's from where I work.
- It's not a church, Stanley.
That place runs on sin.
- It's still my ass
on the line.
- It never made it to the bank.
- Oh, great.
- So you can say however much
you want was in those bags.
- Thanks for having my back.
- I'm just making my man happy.
You know, following orders.
- Come on.
- 'Cause you're the boss now,
right?
You run the house.
- I don't want that.
- That's what I heard.
- I want old you.
Okay?
The way you used to be before.
The whole point
of this stupid thing
was to make us better people,
babe,
and you stole from it.
- To pay for a car
for someone that needed it!
Which makes me a better person!
- It's ruining us.
- So what do you want?
You wanna go back?
- I don't know.
I don't know.
- You wanna go back
to the mall?
I go back to slinging donuts?
- I don't know.
- 'Cause I gotta tell you,
there's not enough donuts
in the world
that's gonna cover
our baby's meds.
But hey...
maybe Paul Blart
can save the day.
[somber music]
♪
- Oh, hey.
The kids' smoke detector
hasn't had a battery
in God knows how long.
[water running]
- Well, there's really nothing
left to lose.
- Right.
Only our whole family.
- Can I ask you something?
- Sure there was a spare 9-volt
in here somewhere.
- Would you have ever
slept with her?
- What?
- Like, before.
When we were really not
doing well.
- Um...
Found it.
- I mean, she's not...
not-pretty.
- Okay, you look amazing.
- That's not what I asked.
Would you have ever
slept with her?
- Uh...
[sighs]
She wears this...
perfume.
- Sexy.
- And she's got...
a really nice ass.
And...
perfectly sized...
boobs.
And she's kinda crazy,
which could go either way
in the sack, and--
and overall,
it seems...
you know, worth the gamble.
- So you would've.
- Probably.
- Thanks for being honest.
Where's the chief?
- Art class.
- Really?
- Yeah.
You know, pencils and chalk
and whatnot.
And then he's going
to aerobics.
Is that good enough for you?
Where the hell's his cut?
- It was my son's diaper bag.
Just bring it back next time.
Hey.
I need another favor.
- [laughs]
You serious?
- I'm obviously good for it.
- I'll have to add it
to your tab.
- Yeah, fine.
- What do you want?
- When you took my furniture...
- I didn't take nothing.
- How did you do it?
[mellow music]
♪
- They don't know who it was.
They completely took
everything.
♪
I'll call you back.
- Oh, my God.
What happened?
- What do you want?
- Well, I wanted
to buy a hot tub place, but...
this place doesn't have
any hot tubs.
So...
wow.
Not what I was expecting,
you know?
Uh...
I mean...
how's that?
- We already agreed
on a number.
- Well, yeah, but...
that doesn't seem fair.
I mean, why would I pay
that much
when it's just
an empty showroom?
♪
I mean,
if you're not interested...
- Sea lions, huh?
- Oh, yeah.
It's a whole marine life
series.
.
[laughter]
- Let's go!
- [laughing]
- Hey.
Those aren't church clothes.
- We're not going to church.
- You're not?
Says who, Jesus?
- Daddy.
- He says we're going
go-karting.
- Oh, yeah, they got so good
on your Jazzy,
I figured it was time
to take it up a notch.
Shoes.
[both giggling]
Shoes!
Put on your shoes!
[laughter]
- They have Sunday school.
- And the rest of their life
to be good.
- Where's all that going?
- I'm giving back.
- To who?
- The people who deserve it.
Last chance.
You were right.
- Oh, I know.
- I don't know
where we're going.
I just wanna go there together.
- Looks like a star.
[Goldberg's "Winter/Summer"]
♪
Jackets, bathroom, car!
Let's burn some rubber.
Hmm.
♪
You already tried to return it,
didn't you?
- Oh, yeah.
They were gonna hose me good.
[laughs]
♪
- Almost up and running, huh?
- We had an issue
with the previous owner.
- No, I love it.
- You do?
- Yeah.
Get away with anything you want
in a place like this.
- Well, it'll look even better
when I get the spas back in.
- Oh, yeah?
- And the barbecue accessories.
- Cool.
I'll take a dip.
- Okay.
- You wanna join me?
- I would be happy
to have a sales representative
walk you through
all the features.
- Nah.
Those things breed diseases.
- When does it get to be mine?
- When does what
get to be yours?
- ♪ It's time now
I think of it ♪
- I made all of this happen.
- ♪ You came from the circus
- Next time, empty the clip.
[laughs]
♪
I'll see you soon, yeah?
- ♪ You had a pocket full
of tricks ♪
♪ And six months to live
♪
♪ He's a gambling man
♪ Ah
♪
- That's classy.
- Always.
- ♪ Ah
- Hey, let your sister
have a turn.
♪
To being small business owners.
- Kinda.
- Very small.
- Like, micro.
- Okay.
To hit men.
- Wherever they may be.
- Good luck and Godspeed.
♪
- No way!
You did my nails.
- Huh?
- Go Red or Go Home, remember?
- Oh.
Hey.
- [laughs]
You guys probably know this,
but your girl here's
like Picasso.
My hands are a work of art.
- Oh, wow.
- Gorge.
- Yeah.
[breathing heavily]
So what are you guys
celebrating?
♪
- ♪ Ah
♪ He sings songs,
na na na na ♪
♪
♪ He sings songs,
na na na na ♪
♪
♪ He's a gambling man