♪ Stars shining bright above you ♪
♪ Night breezes seem to whisper
"I love you" ♪
♪ Birds singing in the sycamore tree ♪
♪ Dream a little dream of me ♪
♪ Say nighty-night and kiss me ♪
♪ Just hold me tight
And tell me you miss me ♪
♪ While I'm alone and blue as can be ♪
♪ Dream a little dream of me ♪
♪ Sweet dreams till sunbeams find you ♪
♪ Sweet dreams that leave
All worries behind you ♪
♪ But in your dreams whatever they be ♪
♪ Dream a little ♪
♪ Dream of me ♪
Hyatt Place Independence.
Jonathan Fraser, please.
- Hyatt Regency at The Arcade.
- Jonathan Fraser's room, please.
Hyatt Cleveland Legacy.
Can you put me through
to Jonathan Fraser's room, please?
This is Jonathan.
Jonathan Fraser?
Yes. Who is this?
I'm... I'm sorry, I, um...
Sorry.
Did you hear from Dad today at all?
Uh, not since this morning when he left.
You saw him before he left, at 5 a.m.?
Yeah. He came in to say goodbye.
Did he say anything else?
I think he just said, "Bye," and then...
And then he kissed me on the forehead...
and left, I was half asleep.
He didn't say anything else?
Probably that he loved me?
What's wrong?
Does he usually do that
before he leaves on a trip?
Say goodbye?
No, come into your room
while you're still asleep.
Doesn't he usually say goodbye
the night before?
Um...
Mom, you're acting strange.
Well, it's just, I haven't heard
from him all day.
I mean, I know
he has two presentations to give,
and he's probably busy, but I'm just...
Text him.
He left his phone.
He left his phone?
Mm-hm.
Do you know his code?
No.
How did he seem this morning?
He seemed like Dad.
He came into your room, he said goodbye,
maybe told you that he loved you,
and then he left?
What's going on?
No...
Nothing, honey. I'm just...
Um...
Nothing, it's nothing.
This guy shoots nothing
but three-pointers!
You never see the mid-range...
The community of the tony Upper East Side
Reardon Academy is in shock tonight
over the gruesome discovery
of a fourth-grade mother
found bludgeoned to death.
According to police,
Elena Alves never returned home
last night after
a school fundraiser.
It was her 10-year-old son
who found the victim
dead in her blood-strewn art studio
this morning.
Cause of death hasn't been confirmed,
but we're told
the victim was struck multiple times
with a blunt instrument,
suffering numerous abrasions
and lacerations to her skull.
One officer called it...
- Hey. Mm-hm.
- Are you seeing this?
It's all over.
Mentioning Reardon, it's just...
It's beyond awful.
I just can't stop thinking
about that woman.
I know.
And the children, my God.
You know what? I've got Amanda
on the other line. I'll call you back. Okay.
Mom.
Oh, God.
What?
You scared me.
- Don't do that.
- I said, "Mom."
What's wrong with you?
I don't know where your father is.
He's not returning calls,
he's not returning my e-mails, nothing.
And that doesn't make any sense.
Is it possible
that he just doesn't have Internet?
He's at a medical conference, Henry.
He has Internet.
All right. So, he's usually terrible
about checking in, right?
You guys fight about it all the time.
And he usually has those dinners
after the conference.
If he's at the dinner,
but if he doesn't have his phone,
then how is he gonna
communicate with you?
- Or maybe he's on the plane.
- Henry...
'Cause he did say
he might get back earlier, right?
- You're right.
- Yeah.
- So, don't worry.
- He's on the plane. He's flying back to us.
- Don't worry. It's fine.
- Exactly what you're doing...
Hello? Hello?
Jonathan?
Hello?
Hung up.
Somebody tried to call him,
heard your voice...
thought, "Wrong number,"
and hung up. Okay?
Sometimes I just,
I feel...
Overwhelmed.
And, um...
lost.
We are live in front of the Reardon School
where the son of victim...
Is this 'cause of the dead mom?
- Grace!
- We need to move quickly.
Grace!
- Oh, Sylvia!
- Hi.
- Hi! I know.
- Oh, my God, can you believe this?
Have you ever seen
such a clusterfuck? Sorry.
A caravan of concerned mothers.
God forbid they let the nanny
bring their child to school
on such a momentous occasion.
- Hi. Hi.
- Hi.
Alexis Young, Grace Fraser.
- She's a second-grade mom.
- Oh, hi.
- Hi. I've been told you're a therapist?
- Yes, I am.
I don't mean to be schnorring
free medical advice,
but my little Kimberly is already anxious
to begin with,
and this is our first school murder,
and I just was wondering if there were,
you know, any techniques
you could recommend.
- I'm gonna head in.
- Sure. I'll see you this afternoon.
Did you guys hear?
The husband suddenly
just turned himself in.
- What?
- Turns out that I actually met him once.
He gave me a bad feeling.
- You met him, when?
- Hello, Alexis, hi.
Well, I didn't realize
he was a parent at first.
I thought, you know,
he worked for the school.
- Excuse me, ma'am!
- I think I told him
we were out of paper towels
in the ladies' room.
I haven't heard anything
about him turning himself in.
I wonder if this is connected
to what happened at the benefit.
What? What happened at the benefit?
Oh, come on. She had
at least ten men inhaling her.
- Oh, please.
- I don't think that's insignificant.
It might help them figure out who did it.
What do you mean, "who did it"?
Of course, it was the husband.
First he vanishes,
and now he's turned himself in.
It's always the fucking husband.
Well, he didn't vanish. That was fake news.
I have to go,
so I'll see you this afternoon.
Hey.
- Did Jonathan call?
- No.
Would you give Stuart a call?
Dr. Rosenfeld at the hospital.
See if he's heard from him?
I think the secrecy was a part of it.
Maybe even a big part.
But I think I was trying
to break free of myself.
How so?
I've always been so righteous.
Living by my good values.
Oppressed by them.
I think what I did was more
about me rejecting myself than Michael.
I'm timid.
I'm safe.
Part of me wants to be dangerous.
Hello?
You've been chosen
for a trip to the Caribbean! Press five...
Stuart.
Grace!
Hi, um, did my assistant call you?
Ah, I'm not aware.
Um...
Have you heard from Jonathan?
I haven't.
He went to Cleveland
and he didn't take his phone, and I...
I haven't been able to reach him,
and I'm getting worried.
What's in Cleveland?
The conference.
The conference?
Pediatric oncology
at the Cleveland Clinic.
Ah, uh, I knew nothing about it.
- I really can't talk.
- The confer...
What do you mean, you can't talk?
Can't talk about what?
- I'm really late for a meeting.
- Stuart, please!
I cannot talk. I am constrained.
There are strict terms.
Strict terms? What strict terms?
- I'm sorry, I'm not at liberty.
- What?
- Please, it's me. It's Grace.
- I'm sorry. Grace, I'm sorry.
Oh, that's disgusting.
- Is he back yet? Dad. Is he back yet?
- What?
No.
- No.
- What?
Let's go. We're gonna be late for Grandpa.
Come on.
- Good evening, Mrs. Fraser.
- Good evening.
- Hey. Thank you.
- Thank you.
- Hi, Henry!
- Hi, Grandpa.
Grandma's made some penne marinara
especially for you.
So, that's all
Dr. Rosenfeld told you?
Yeah.
Hmph.
And you?
What are you telling yourself?
I don't know what to tell myself.
He didn't just leave his phone behind.
He arranged to be unreachable, Dad.
How have things been
between the two of you?
How have they been?
It's not a trick question, Grace.
We've never been better.
- Mmm.
- This doesn't make any sense.
I'm having a hard time
functioning right now.
But you have to.
You have a son to look after.
- Irma?
- Excuse me, Dr. Fraser.
- Yes?
- There are two police officers waiting
for you in the lobby.
I see. No, Dad. I will take care of it.
I need to take a walk anyway.
Thank you for coming down.
Can we have a word
in a more private environment?
Well, my family is upstairs.
Could we go down to the office, then?
To the police station?
Are you arresting me?
Why would we be arresting you?
We just wanna get
more information,
it's easier if we do it there.
All right.
Why would you go with them?
Because it's the straightest line
to what's going on.
You should have a lawyer.
I don't think that's the case,
but if... If it makes sense...
Oh, for God's sakes, child.
Thanks for watching Henry.
I'll call you when I know more.
Grace, this is a terrible idea.
I said I'll call you when I know more.
Everything okay?
I didn't really know Mrs. Alves.
We can talk when we get there.
Right this way, please.
This door here.
Hey! Hey!
Right in here.
Can I get you a coffee or something?
Um...
No.
No, thank you. I'm fine. This...
It looks a little...
Am I gonna need a lawyer?
I wouldn't have thought so.
We're just gonna talk.
All right.
Ahem.
Um...
All right. Ahem.
Dr. Fraser.
Where is your husband?
- I don't know.
- You don't know.
Is he in your apartment on East 63rd?
- No, of course not. He...
- Why "of course not"?
Because I told you. As far as I know,
he is at a medical conference,
and if he were here in the city,
he'd be at work, but he's not here.
- And work would be where?
- Um...
Price-Norbury Memorial Hospital.
Hm.
Dr. Fraser...
your husband has not worked
at Price-Norbury Memorial Hospital
for a long time.
You didn't know this?
What?
According to Dr. Sharp,
Dr. Jonathan Fraser's
employment was terminated
nearly three months ago.
You were not aware of this?
You're saying that
you were not aware of this
until this very moment?
I was... I was not aware.
I spoke to a doctor earlier today,
who wasn't forthcoming with information,
- but I was not aware...
- What doctor was that?
Um, Stuart. Stuart Rosenfeld.
Dr. Rosenfeld.
And did Dr. Rosenfeld tell you that
your husband's termination followed
three earlier disciplinary actions
at the hospital?
I want this to stop.
Are you hiding your husband?
No! I'm not hiding my husband.
I told you, I thought
he was at a medical conference.
He said to me that he was going
to a medical conference in Cleveland.
- Then he's not in your apartment.
- I told you.
He's not there.
His phone seems to be,
according to Verizon.
Yes. Yes, his... His phone is there.
- That's a detail you might've mentioned.
- You didn't ask me where his phone was.
You asked where he was.
- Right. Right.
- He forgot his phone at home.
I mean, it's not the first time
that he's done that.
And I found the phone last night,
and that's why it...
I don't know where he is
because he forgot his phone and I can't...
I can't call him.
- That makes sense to you, hm?
- No.
No, nothing about this entire day
makes any sense to me.
Dr. Fraser, do you know why
your husband was fired?
I suspect you figure that we do.
Are you not even curious?
Yesterday, we obtained the records
from Price-Norbury Memorial Hospital.
- You obtained confidential records?
- Yes, yes.
Yes, as a result of a court order
filed yesterday morning.
This is fucking bullshit.
This is bullshit. This is fucking...
This is bullshit.
In June of last year,
a full disciplinary hearing
alleged inappropriate contact...
with a family member of a patient.
I don't know what any of that means, but...
- I'm...
- But what?
It's cancer. It's children's cancer.
My husband's a warm, warm man.
He's not some asshole who walks
into a room and pronounces
that your child is gonna die
and then walks out the door.
He is a very caring man,
and maybe he has touched someone,
maybe he hugged someone
because he cares,
and that does not mean that he's some...
Okay.
I'm gonna tell you the name of the patient.
No. No, no, no.
- I can tell you the name of the patient.
- It's private.
I don't wanna know.
I don't wanna know the patient's name.
It's private information, it's confidential,
and I don't want to know.
- I don't want to know.
- You don't want to know...
or you already do know?
Your husband's patient...
was Miguel Alves.
Diagnosed with Wilms' tumor.
Miguel's mother...
Elena Alves.
So, you'll forgive me
for asking, Dr. Fraser,
but I'm going to be seriously pissed off
if you keep telling me your husband's
at a fucking medical conference,
in fucking Cleveland,
that he forgot his fucking phone!
Don't protect him.
Wherever Jonathan is,
we're going to find him.
So, if you know something,
this would be the right time
- to tell us what it is.
- This is what I know.
I'm sitting here in a room
with two detectives
who are treating me
very much like I'm a suspect,
trying to illicit
incriminating responses from me,
in a grossly custodial setting.
So, you either read me
my Miranda rights right now...
or tell me I'm free to go.
- Are you still with them?
- No.
- I just left.
- Are you all right?
Grace, what the devil's going on?
They were asking me a lot of questions,
aggressive questions.
I'm guessing there's still no word
from Jonathan?
No.
Guess it's safe to assume
he's not in Cleveland.
Now, you and Henry,
you stay here with me tonight.
Yes.
Grace, did you hear me?
Yes. I just need to go back
to the apartment.
I have to get some clothes,
some things for Henry.
I'll see you when you get here.
Yeah.
:::::: www.hiqve.com ::::::
Good morning, Mrs. Fraser.
Police are focusing
on events transpiring
at a Reardon School fundraiser
where the victim, Elena Alves,
was last seen alive.
- Several witnesses described Mrs. Alves...
- Morning, Henry.
- ...as visibly upset.
- Morning, Grandpa.
Though other partygoers dispute
that account.
Early suspicion was on
the victim's husband,
but we're now learning his whereabouts
have been accounted for.
Do the police think he killed her?
No.
They wanna talk to him.
As do I. As do you.
So...
Why did they take you
into the police station?
Because he knew her.
He was her child's doctor,
- and I knew her, and...
- It's not a crime to know somebody.
No. No, it's not.
- So, they think he killed her.
- No!
- Well, why else all of this, then?
- I don't know.
I don't know.
Excuse me! Excuse me, ma'am!
Wow, I can't believe she'd...
I see they're putting you to work, Jennifer.
- Hi, Mrs. Hartman.
- Go on in.
God, what was that?
I'll be right back.
- Morning, Henry. Morning, Grace.
- Morning, sir.
- God, this is...
- Indeed. It's quite something.
Henry, why don't you head up
to class? Huh?
- Yes, sir.
- Are you okay?
- Yeah. Mom, I'm fine.
- You sure?
Robert, what...? What's going on?
What is going on is, I am trying
to get us through a crisis.
- Grace...
- All right.
I don't think you should be here.
What?
I think, for the good of everyone,
you don't need to be here.
- What did they tell you?
- I want you to know...
this is a safe place for Henry.
- And if he needs to come to my office...
- What the...?
...at any time, he can come.
At recess or after school.
If anyone says anything to him,
- he should come see me right away.
- It's not true.
It's not true.
Whatever they said to you. Wha...?
- Listen to me.
- Robert, come on.
The teachers will be looking out for him.
I have spoken to all of them.
He's a Reardon student,
- and I take that very seriously.
- Really?
You're really doing this to me?
My advice to you...
is you send someone else
to pick him up this afternoon.
- Grace.
- Sylvia.
I have a cab. Come on.
- What...?
- Come on.
Ma'am!
Okay.
What are people saying?
I...
- Tell me.
- It's...
Just a water, please, and some privacy.
- Thank you.
- Tell me.
The word is that Elena's husband
evidently has an alibi.
The attention now seems
to be focused entirely on Jonathan.
So, he knew her? Elena?
Well, Miguel was his patient, so...
Well, it was her.
What?
He hired me. A few months ago.
Jonathan hired you?
As his lawyer.
I told him that employment law wasn't
my expertise, but he...
He insisted.
He signed a document hiring me
to formally represent him.
There was going to be
a disciplinary hearing at the hospital,
involved the mother of a patient.
He wanted my advice.
So, why didn't you tell me?
I didn't know, for sure,
whether you knew or not, and...
Grace, it was...
- It was privileged. It's still privileged.
- What happened?
I looked over the paperwork
that he brought me.
There was a lot there. A lot.
More than enough to fire him.
He insisted that he was innocent
of the charges.
That it was all being manufactured
by this crazy woman.
Really?
He called a week later to say
the accusations were dropped.
That the hospital found
the woman's claims were baseless.
He thanked me for my time.
And I just, I assumed that it went away.
But it didn't.
They fired him.
They kept it completely confidential.
I'm sorry, Grace.
I am. I'm really sorry.
My advice...
Not that you're asking.
...if you do learn where Jonathan is,
tell the police.
The sooner you make it clear
you're not involved,
the better you'll be treated by everybody,
police and media included.
Grace, you need to get out of here,
you and Henry.
Once they find Jonathan,
this story will explode.
You need to be somewhere else
when that happens.
So?
Nothing new.
You need to get protection
for yourself, Grace.
You think you can handle everything
on your own, alone.
This is bigger than you.
It's bigger than me, for chrissakes.
You should get out of town.
You should go to the beach house.
Look, I have patients.
Henry has school.
I'm gonna call Haley Fitzgerald.
You have to have a lawyer.
I don't want a lawyer.
Grace,
your husband is the lead suspect
in a murder investigation.
Excuse me.
- Excuse me, I live here. Yes, I do.
- You live here?
- Excus... I live here.
- Hey, hey, you can't come in here.
- You got some ID?
- Uh...
Come on. Let her through,
let her through. Come on.
What is going on?
Do you have paperwork for this?
Of course. Paul, the warrant.
Here you go.
So, you think
my husband killed this woman?
The search might take a bit.
You got somewhere else to go?
You don't need to worry
about me, detective.
Well, believe it or not,
it's kind of my nature.
To worry about people.
Where is his phone? We can't find it.
Thank you.
You guys need
a hand down here?
I really am sorry
about all this.
Why are you taking...?
Why are you taking his...? His hairbrush?
We're taking a number of things
that might help our investigation.
That's all.
I could be wrong,
but I think that you wanna help us.
I think that, at this point,
you're more angry at him than you are at us.
- And you're right to be.
- Please, don't fucking patronize me.
- No, that's not my intention to do that.
- I can't... Don't.
- I don't patronize people.
- Don't...
I've just seen this type
of situation one too many times.
Husbands who have kept their wives
in the dark about a lot of things.
And when I'm in the picture,
there's some fraud or a robbery.
Sometimes, a murder.
I'm sorry.
We need the hairbrush for DNA.
For a couple of reasons.
The crime scene...
and also...
Also what?
- What?
- Paternity.
They have a baby.
Mr. Alves is demanding a paternity test.
He insists he's not the father.
Please.
Oh! God.
Henry, you scared me.
Mom.
Mom, I don't wanna be here.
I know, but we're here.
- For how long?
- For as long as it takes.
That's not an answer.
When the police
and the media stop congregating
outside our apartment and your school,
that's when we'll go back.
- We'll go back when things...
- When they what?
- When they what? Go back to normal?
- Come on, Henry.
- Mom.
- Henry, come on.
I'm trying. I'm trying.
By running away.
That's bullshit, Mom.
There's no hiding.
Henry.
Come here.
Don't scream! Don't scream.
Don't scream, don't scream. It's me.
I didn't do it. I didn't kill her.
I did not kill her.
We were romantically involved,
but I didn't kill her.
I'm so sorry.
I'm so sorry, my Grace.
I'm gonna take my hand away,
and you're not gonna scream.
There.
I didn't do it.
I didn't kill her.
- I'm calling the police.
- Give me two minutes.
You're going to give me two minutes
before you do that.
- I gave you my whole life.
- Grace.
- No. Get your fucking hands off me!
- Grace!
- Or I will. I will scream.
- Grace. I didn't...
You can hate me as much as you want,
but Henry needs to know
his father's not a murderer.
He's gotta believe in me.
I will never, ever let him believe in you.
Look, here's what happened.
I had an affair.
She became obsessed.
With me, with my life, and then with you.
First it was all about getting
her boy into Reardon,
which I helped with 'cause I thought
it was about his education, but it wasn't.
It was about encroachment.
She was fucking possessed.
She was possessed.
When I heard she'd got herself
on your auction committee
and then joined your gym, I was scared.
I was scared for us as a family.
I was scared for you.
At the night of the fundraiser,
I went to confront her.
- I told her that had to stop...
- You snapped?
We argued.
We fought.
We had sex. I left. I walked the streets.
I went to a bar to collect myself, then I...
I went back to confront her again,
and she was fucking dead.
She was dead.
There was no sign of anyone.
I panicked. I totally fucking panicked.
I lost my head.
- Shock took hold of me...
- You came home.
You crawled into our bed,
and I held you.
I held you.
And I broke for you.
And we made love, Jonathan.
We made love.
And I thought you'd lost a patient.
How can I ever believe you?
Because you're a fucking liar.
You're a liar.
You've been pretending to have this job
- you didn't even have.
- No. That's all part of...
- What, are you...?
- It's part of the same big deception.
I lost my job 'cause of this woman.
I lost myself.
She got hold of me, Grace.
She got hold of every fucking part of me.
But I didn't kill her.
I did not...
Dad?
- Dad?
- Come here. Come here.
My name is Grace Fraser.
My husband has just broken in.
He's a fugitive. He's wanted for murder.
His name is Jonathan Fraser.
I'm at 361 Beachway...
Beachway Drive. And I'm fucking terrified.
I need you to get here quickly.
Please.
:::::: www.hiqve.com ::::::