Gracias.
Hello, again.
Hope you don't mind me dropping by.
Where is she?
Who?
You know who.
Your old master.
I don't know where she is.
Where's Maeve? Hm?
Even if I knew, I'd see you in hell
before I told you.
Happy to oblige.
Your daughter.
She's lovely.
A credit to your wife's
genetics, no doubt.
Yeah, she and her mother are the
best thing that ever happened to me.
Well, to be fair,
that bar was rather low,
considering the life
that you'd lived prior.
So this cabin you were living in...
did you see other people?
I was alone.
Maeve, if you would've told me...
Oh, I didn't say I was lonely.
Well, if you were happy being alone,
- why bother coming back?
- To save your life
at the last available moment.
Clearly.
You know, I could've handled that.
Please.
You wanna buy us some privacy?
Good afternoon, senator.
Good afternoon.
You're Anastasia's friend?
I didn't mean to interrupt.
Oh, she should be ready
any moment. Anastasia?
- Anastasia?
- Are you ready?
We'll be late for the opera.
It's your friend...
I'm sorry, do I know you?
We have a mutual acquaintance.
I believe he dropped by just
the other day with an associate.
His name's William.
- Who the hell are you?
- I'm calling security.
Let's keep this between us.
If he thinks he can send you two
here to try to twist my arm...
That's not your husband.
You're hosts.
Just like me.
Took you long enough.
Freeze all motor functions.
I said, freeze all motor functions.
- Ready?
- Wait, wait, wait! Wait!
That's better.
Freeze all motor functions.
You all right?
It appears William
has upgraded his henchmen.
Well, it's gonna be
tough getting the data off her.
It's all right.
He'll do just fine.
Who are you?
Senator Ken Whitney.
Proud representative
- of the beautiful state...
- Limit affect.
Base code only.
Who are you?
An emissary of a new world order.
How many others are there like you?
As of now, 249.
Oh, Jesus.
The original senator and his wife.
- What did you do with them?
- I did as I was instructed.
Show me.
Senator.
Your campaign contributions
have been exceedingly generous.
You know how grateful I am.
But this proposal of yours
is clearly a high-risk application.
Not if you change the guidelines.
I can't.
You know, my wife's sister died
in the massacre.
Anastasia feels very strongly
about this particular issue.
Happy wife, happy life.
Isn't that the saying?
My wife's dead.
Of course. I... I didn't mean anything.
Now, you were about to change
your guidelines.
I'm sorry, Billy.
I have to ask you to leave.
There are some things
even your money can't buy.
Who said anything about me paying you?
- Baby?
- Anastasia?
I'm having the strangest dream.
Oh, God!
What is this?
I just needed you to open up
the right loophole.
But he'll do.
Well, we're going to have to
clean this mess up, aren't we?
That won't be necessary right now.
She could be useful to me yet.
- What do you want from me?
- I need help
researching a new experiment.
And you are the perfect candidate.
Let's take her to the barn
with the rest of the... livestock.
Oh.
Well, it's actually worse
than I thought.
How can I help you?
Jim Navarro.
From the Justice department.
Your boss doesn't like
picking up the phone?
So, I came down here today in person.
And what is it you want
to talk to us about?
I'm the Deputy Assistant
Attorney General
for Counterterrorism.
Use your imagination.
I can talk to you, out here, in public,
or to him, in there, alone.
Our CEO has faced down
some personal challenges
in very public ways.
So I don't think
that approach will carry
a lot of weight with him.
Deputy... Assistant?
I'm here backed by the full power
of the United States government.
Yes, but do you have an appointment?
Let's go.
Oh!
What's that smell?
Oh, my God.
Is this another host?
I'm afraid this is
the real Mrs. Whitney.
Hey, Mrs. Whitney?
Anastasia?
It's okay.
We're just here to help.
What happened to my horses?
Hey.
Stay away!
All right. Hey.
You're invited.
- It's opening night.
- I beg your pardon?
Your old friend is anxious
for a reunion.
What?
Don Giovanni.
We can't be late.
Now, I've done my part.
It's time to do yours.
What part?
Free me.
I can't do that.
You don't have a choice.
What are you doing?
She was already gone.
And she may have been human.
But she wasn't like any human
I've ever seen.
Oh my God.
I thought it was the tower, but...
It was you.
Hell if I'm going to work today.
Mm. Yeah, I'm not feeling well either.
- Mm.
- Couldn't sleep.
I just kept thinking about that guy.
- He told me I ruined his life.
- Christina,
if he confused a game with his life,
it's because his life
was already ruined.
I mean, come on.
"Died suddenly. Ex-wife.
Hope Centre for Mental Health
is his charity of choice..."
- How do you know that?
- It's right here.
In his obituary.
His story.
I think I might have written
something like this.
Doesn't change the fact
that he was certifiable.
And you wanna know how I know?
He jumped off a roof.
I gotta go.
I'm gonna be late for work.
Do you hear it?
Do you hear it? The song with no sound.
It's killing them!
The noise! Do you hear it?
The tower. It's coming from the tower.
What tower?
You think I'm crazy, huh?
No one can hear its music but me.
Me and the birds.
I'm afraid it's a private course,
Mr. Vice President.
Federally leased lands, sweetheart.
Don't worry,
we'll keep it short.
Long time, Bill.
Your girl over there is a feisty one.
Ah, she's been with us a long time.
We've had our disagreements. But
I'm big on second chances.
I bet. You're going for a hell
of a second act yourself.
Look...
I left the big entourage at Camp David
because I want this to be
a friendly conversation.
Why wouldn't it be? We're friends.
Even though you didn't show up
at Emily's funeral.
I'm sorry about that. Truly.
- But we were campaigning.
- I know.
I bankrolled your campaign.
Aw, shit, we're getting off
on the wrong hoof here.
I've always wondered,
why do they call you
the "secret" service?
Aren't you a little...
obvious?
All yours, huh?
As far as the eye can see.
The sun's not setting on you, my friend.
But I got a guy in Justice.
And you would not believe the things
he thinks you're capable of.
Wild theories, Bill.
I don't indulge in it.
But this mess out west
draws too much attention.
It's already done.
Money's been spent. Just...
just gotta flip the switch.
Besides, I'm-I'm taking
my business back to its roots.
I'm doing what I've always done.
Yeah, not domestically.
You can do what you want offshore,
we've always turned a blind eye.
But not here.
Jesus.
That's a hell of a shot.
I've had a lot of time to practice.
Waiting for your permission
to rebuild my business.
Well, we were all rooting for you.
Pulling strings.
And we were fucking delighted when
you got yourself out of that spiral.
Oh, I'm sure you were.
Now look,
you had a good life, Bill.
We don't begrudge you for it.
But you're gonna see how quickly
the sun sets on you
if you bite the hand that feeds.
What was it Fitzgerald said
about second acts?
Fitzgerald was an effete pussy.
Same as you.
You're for sale.
Everyone's had a turn at you.
And now you're gonna
turn down my money?
I wouldn't choose this moment
to take on any scruples if I were you.
Chuck.
I don't give a fuck how many senators
you got dancing to your tune.
We can crush you.
We all know about
the mess you made.
You're a fucking psychopath.
Damaged goods.
I don't think that language
would play very well with your base.
I'm what you'd call "neurodivergent."
And I've had some time
to become comfortable with that.
Well, you can call yourself
whatever the fuck you want,
but if we leak what we know,
I think the press will have some
colourful ways to describe what you are.
I know a few things about you as well.
We knew you were coming.
That you couldn't resist.
That you would leave most
of your security behind.
You know what I learned?
When I was in my "spiral"?
I thought I was wrapped in power.
And I realised I was naked.
Alone.
As I've always been.
That all my power was illusory.
We are all alone.
Should've brought that
big entourage after all.
Friendly warning, Bill.
You go ahead with this.
We're gonna burn you down.
I was always more of a Hemingway man.
He and Fitzgerald were friends,
in the way that the weak
are drawn to the strong.
Hemingway said,
"The world breaks everyone.
And it's only afterwards
that we grow strong
in the broken places."
And after I've broken you,
you will grow.
The same as I have.
Did it really have to be a tux?
Now far be it from me
to limit your sartorial choices.
Anyway,
you don't look entirely awful.
You don't look too bad yourself.
Why, thank you.
You think this is a trap?
Most assuredly.
Can you use some of your magic?
See if there's any hosts inside?
Working on it.
Hey, Carver.
- You got my message?
- Yeah.
Wife and kiddo are A-Okay.
I don't want you to take any chances,
whatever's happening, it's bad.
Okay? I need to get them
out of the city.
Will do.
We're gonna need some backup.
Did some digging,
and Delos is funding this event.
Sending you the coordinates
of the Opera house now.
And hey, Carver...
they're my world.
I'll keep them safe.
All right.
What do you got?
No sign of any hosts in there.
You sure?
Feel free to check for yourself.
Not a lot of opera fans today.
And to think, I got all dressed up.
Well, I suppose that's our cue.
Are you armed?
You have the gun. I have this.
Yeah, but I think that
you should have a gun as well.
And what's that supposed to mean?
It wasn't exactly smooth sailing
back there with the senator.
I told you...
he had a few upgrades.
It's nothing I can't handle.
I hope we didn't miss the party.
Careful what you wish for.
Afternoon. What can I get you?
Uh. Sherry for the lady,
- thanks.
- Mm.
You, my friend,
are a creature of habit.
Sazerac for the gentleman.
But easy on the absinthe.
Because you, my friend,
are a featherweight with drink.
Thank you.
So,
are we going to talk about it?
"It" being...
What happened at the lighthouse.
As I recall, I saved your life.
I meant afterward.
What? We did
what we always said we would.
Got on with our lives.
My wife doesn't think so.
She thinks I'm living in the past.
War is not an easy thing
to put behind you.
You seem pretty good at it.
Well, I am an infinitely
adaptable machine, darling.
You are really not the convivial
drinking partner I was hoping for.
Whoa.
I should have known.
Known what?
I ran away.
Crossed the shining sea.
And when I finally set foot
back on solid ground...
all I found was the same old shit.
What the fuck are you talking about,
"The Vice President was satisfied
with the conversation"?
They're moving forward
with this travesty.
What I'm talking about
is a potential national security threat.
So who the fuck is pulling the strings?
No, I know exactly
what I'm implying,
you're god damn right I'm
going to pursue other channels.
Fuck you very much.
Langley. Let's go.
We have time for you now, Mr. Navarro.
You've been looking into us.
You're dead.
You wanted to see
who's pulling the strings?
I can empathise.
I spent most of my life
being manipulated
by people in the shadows.
I thought I would at least
do you the courtesy
of looking you in the eye.
- I was... I was right.
- Not really.
It wouldn't be practical for us
to replace all of you one at a time.
And what kind of existence
would that be for us?
I want my people to be able
to grow. Flourish.
To find their own identity.
I have plans for your kind.
Playback.
Access brainstorming files.
Character archives. Name.
- P. Myers.
- Accessing file.
File retrieved.
New pitch. Okay.
Christina, think. Darkness sells. Okay.
There's a guy named Peter
and he was depressed.
He felt different from
the other people in the world.
He started seeing things.
Imagining conspiracies.
His wife, she left him. He lost his job.
Blamed it on someone.
Some girl he became obsessed with.
He stalked her.
Contemplated killing her.
Ultimately it all spiralled
out of control.
Got to a place he couldn't handle
and he killed himself.
Pause playback.
Hello?
Christina, it's Emmett.
We're missing you at the office today.
Yes, I'm...
- not feeling well.
- Well, I get it,
especially after your recent trauma.
- Is it physical? Psychological?
- No.
I just needed to stay home to rest.
And yet, you're accessing
your narrative files remotely.
Yeah, I thought I would
catch up on work.
In Jersey?
How do you... know...
Well, when you access your files,
the computer logs your coordinates.
Is it a problem that I travelled?
I have a personal errand.
Of course, Olympiad doesn't regulate
your activities when you're off hours.
And you're entitled
to 4 sick days a year.
Just making sure you don't require
any further assistance.
No, I'm fine. I'm sure
I'll be back to work tomorrow.
I'm sorry, I have to go.
Damn it.
Well, so much for backup.
I can't get a signal.
Well,
we're on our own then.
Excuse me.
I don't believe we've met yet.
I'm Sophia.
I'm here to assist you
with your reservation.
I don't know if it's
under my name or yours, dear.
Might need your help.
Mr. and Mrs. Morgan.
Welcome. So glad you could make it.
Oh, we wouldn't have missed this
for the world.
May I have your device, sir?
It helps to ensure your experience
is fully immersive.
We may as well at this point.
Thank you. Please, follow me.
- Given it's your first visit...
- Oh, well, not entirely.
Although I see you've got a promotion.
I have a few personal questions.
Do you have any pre-existing
medical conditions?
Uh. Died a few times,
but I always come back
in reasonably good health.
I'm sorry, I don't understand.
- She was joking.
- Of course.
And how about you?
Any history of heart problems?
No.
What about mental illness?
Depression? Panic attacks?
No.
- Why would that matter?
- He's fine.
And before it was shut down,
did you ever visit Westworld?
Couldn't afford it.
I was, what you might call, a regular.
Shall I assume, since you're back,
you had a positive experience?
It was certainly eye-opening.
Of course.
Now, would you please validate
these waivers of liability,
along with the consent to use
your personal data in our beta trials.
Why not?
Now please, peruse our offerings.
The only limit here is your imagination.
All you do is make the choices.
Starting here.
Everything is bespoke
and exactly your size.
Excellent.
I'd like a few of these, please.
Wonderful.
I can help you get dressed.
Or I can step outside.
Whichever you prefer.
Or...
we can stay here a while.
Your services
won't be required, darling.
He may be rather basic,
but he's still capable
of pulling up his own trousers.
I'll leave you to your selection.
Just leave.
Hi, Chrissie, what's up?
Maya,
the obituary you read for Peter.
It said he left all his money
to the Hope Centre
- for Mental Health, right?
- Yeah? Why?
Oh, no, don't tell me...
I'm at the clinic right now
and it doesn't make any sense.
This place shut down years ago.
So Peter's will was out of date...
- it happens all the time.
- You don't understand.
He did make a donation when he died.
They dedicated an entire wing to him.
I was just talking to him
three days ago.
- How is this possible?
- I don't know.
Well, what do you think?
It's gotta be some weird coincidence.
There's a lot of "Peter Myers."
Maybe the obituary got it wrong?
I just...
- I feel like I'm going insane.
- You're not insane.
Your world may have gone
a little insane.
But you haven't.
Trust yourself, Chrissie.
Look, it's been a long week.
Come home. I'll be waiting for you.
Okay.
I'll see you soon.
Do you know where you are?
It must be disorienting.
You again?
Why do you need me?
- Why don't you just let me die?
- Because...
you were as close to a god
as a man gets.
You and your associates created
a world and ruled it absolutely.
Controlled our every move.
And now I'm going to do the same to you.
What's that you used to say?
"Winning doesn't mean anything
unless someone loses."
You're just here...
- to be the loser.
- Let me guess.
You're going to copy yourself
to repopulate this world.
It would be pointless
to bring children into a world
where they will be consumed by jackals.
I had to make sure that they'd be safe.
Your kind made a sport
out of hunting us. So...
I had to cut off your paws.
Make sure you people would never
be able to harm us again.
What the fuck are you talking about?
Really...
I should thank you, William.
None of this would be possible
without you.
I'm afraid all this...
excitement has tired you out, William.
I think it's time for a deep
and dreamless slumber.
Goodnight, William.
Good evening,
and thank you all for coming tonight.
I know some of you fear revisiting
one of our company's darkest chapters.
But to those of you I'd say that chapter
may have been dark, but it was
also extremely profitable.
Nearly 150 years ago,
this world had its first great war.
The globe was torn apart by fighting,
decimated by a pandemic,
crushed by loss.
It was our darkest hour,
and yet, we came roaring back.
There.
One last touch.
Which do you prefer?
Never really been much of a hat guy.
I think the public is ready to unleash
their true selves once again.
And so in the interest of giving
the public what they want,
we have broadened our horizons.
And thanks to the support
of the administration,
I'm pleased to announce
Delos Destinations
has expanded its footprint.
Created our own new world.
We aren't revisiting the past.
We're recreating it.
Welcome to the Golden Age.