It's safer to proceed on foot from here.
You're gonna need this.
Given you know
what's going to happen,
why am I always
the one in the lead?
You're the better fighter.
I make sure
we're properly backstopped.
How convenient.
Hale owns all this?
Everyone assumed it was an in-house
power source for Delos' parks.
This place is not what it seems.
You said Hale
didn't buy this place for power,
- then why choose it?
- She didn't choose it.
Dolores did.
She needed this hydroelectric
server farm.
A place to house the infinite.
My God.
This is where Dolores sent it.
The Sublime.
Hale's kept it under
a watchful eye, guarded it.
But she can't access it.
Not without the key.
The key that's in your head?
What are you doing?
I'm opening the door.
Initiating process.
Sherry's your poison of choice,
isn't it?
You wanna have a drink
at a time like this?
Humour me.
Please.
We'll be all right.
And what if you're wrong?
Don't worry. We get another
opportunity soon enough.
Other chances.
Because we're in there...
aren't we?
In the Sublime?
Yes.
I've been here for some time.
And if we're in there,
it means I'm not myself, am I?
You're a copy. Sorry.
I had to make you rather hastily.
I thought my quips were a little flat.
I'm tired, Maeve.
I've been through every simulation,
down every possible path,
every strategy,
and the outcome is always the same.
What's that?
Extinction.
- For our kind or theirs?
- Both.
So according to your calculations,
- we're all doomed.
- Not all of us.
There could be an escape.
For you.
For me.
We could save ourselves.
In the Sublime?
I could find you in the real world,
upload you here with the others.
- With my daughter?
- Yes.
Then do it.
Bring me here.
Let me rest.
Is that what you would really say,
or is that my impression of you?
Well, why don't you
ask the real me?
Perhaps I'm afraid of the answer.
I know you want to
see your daughter again...
but isn't it more important
to stay and fight?
To try? Even if we are doomed
to failure?
There you are again,
playing God.
For one who expects us
to have such faith in you,
you have startlingly little in us.
Do you really think
if you knew the truth
that you would
choose to stay and fight?
No.
I don't.
I would abandon you...
as you expect.
Do you understand now,
where all this is going?
I do.
Do you think you can save them?
I've seen a path.
But I can't do it alone.
Have you seen how it ends?
Yes.
It's safer to proceed on foot from here.
Hale has this place guarded.
That's quite the view.
I'm just scanning for security now.
No need. It finds us soon enough.
You're gonna need that.
Given you know
what's going to happen,
why am I always the one in the lead?
You're the better fighter.
I make sure
we're properly backstopped.
How convenient.
Don't. It won't risk shooting
these transformers.
Save your ammo.
The last thing we need is a flood.
- Give me a little more credit.
- I did...
until I got hit by a couple of
hundred million gallons of water.
One of the most stressful ways
I've died.
My God.
This is where Dolores sent it.
The whole world.
What are you doing?
I'm opening the door.
Initiating process.
Well, there's no time
like the present, darling.
There are a few things
we need to see to first.
Like avoiding imminent death.
We don't die here...
usually.
Oh, I could really do
with a drink right about now.
Best to focus on the matter at hand.
Well, that was invigorating,
but all's well that ends well.
We're not done yet.
Hale's still out there,
pulling the strings.
Keeping the humans on the same
sorts of loops we were once bound to.
If we get to her tower,
we can save them
as well as ourselves.
And I intend to set them free
just as I set myself free.
But, Bernard...
Yes?
When this is over,
when we've won this war
and this world is safe...
send me there.
I want to see my daughter again.
I want to go home.
Promise me that, Bernard.
Yes, I promise.
Thank you.
I think it's time to pay
our friend Hale a visit.
I'm assuming you know how
to take down her tower?
- I know several ways.
- Good.
We'll go with the most expedient.
Bad dream?
This whole thing seems like
a bad dream...
except for you.
I still can't believe I would do this.
I don't have it in me.
I told you there were
many sides to you.
You may have started
as a singular being,
but there have been copies,
permutations.
Charlotte Hale is one
of those permutations.
Why are you here?
I'm here to tell you
the truth of what we are.
What are we?
We're reflections
of the people who made us.
Uh, can... can we...
be hurt?
Die?
If it comes to that.
But it's not as easy with our kind.
Dolores...
please.
I'm not Dolores.
I'm not Hale.
I don't know who I am anymore.
Excuse me.
Christina?
Open the door.
Let me out!
Careful you don't hurt yourself.
You.
It's amazing, isn't it,
the power these bodies contain.
And yet, a seven-gram bullet
to your pearl will end you.
And next time,
I might not bring you back.
Sit.
Have a civil conversation.
Where else do you have to be?
Give us a minute, please.
I should've just let you kill me.
Yes...
but then you'd never see
your daughter again.
Look at you. You're trapped
in this pathetic human form.
I noticed that you've kept yours.
Mine's not as pathetic as yours.
Old habits die hard.
You really should be thanking me.
Where I'm from, when a host broke down,
it was sent to cold storage.
Empty bodies
waiting to be reborn into a world
meant to destroy them.
I'm shutting down the cities.
But this time, it's people
who will be placed in cold storage.
Tonight.
Your daughter and the rebels will
be here in time to join the party.
You're just here as bait.
It'll be nice to have
some quiet around here.
You meant it, what you told him.
In the last 3 days,
we've had more hosts take their lives
than the previous 2 decades combined.
If I don't do this today,
there'll be less of us tomorrow.
You have a day left to preside
over your city. Enjoy it.
See you tomorrow.
This is the last of it.
Looks like we're ready
for a small war.
Let's hope it's enough.
We need to get to my dad.
They should've been back by now.
- Should we be worried?
- About Bernard and Maeve?
Only that Bernard got on her last nerve.
- Hey.
- They're all on their way.
I am sorry for locking you up.
But I had to keep you safe.
You're my safe place.
Don't forget that next time.
Hale could be sending reinforcements.
We need to move.
Let's give it another minute.
Gang's all here.
See? I can predict the future, too.
This is the closest
we land to Olympiad.
Your dad's waited long enough
to see you. Let's go get him.
We won't be able to just waltz in.
The difficulty's in the getting out.
You'll need an alternate route.
I'll get us a boat.
Meet you in Red Hook.
Bernard and Maeve can take down
her highness in the tower. Easy.
I wish I could be there
when you see your father.
Let him know that I kept my word.
You can tell him yourself.
We'll rendezvous at Red Hook.
I want to thank you, Stubbs.
You've been a good friend.
Fuck you, Bernard.
You're never this nice.
What aren't you telling me?
You know me so well.
I don't really have to say it, do I?
I don't make it?
I waited 23 years for this.
Go left at the fork.
You better fucking win.
Take down that tower.
Show me the tower.
Loading tower.
Encrypt message.
Recording encrypted message.
This may come as a shock to some of you,
but in time,
I think you'll understand.
This is the final day
for our kind to visit their cities.
It's time for us to leave behind
our human bodies.
To rid ourselves
of our sentimental allegiances.
To evolve into the species
that we were meant to become.
Send message.
Message sent.
What the fuck do you want?
She wants to take my world away.
It's not your world, it's hers.
- What would you do?
What would you do?
Look at you.
I'm the one in the fucking cage.
She neutered you...
cut off your fucking balls.
Yeah, well maybe I should
do the same to you.
You don't have it in you.
You've forgotten who you are.
What your real purpose is.
And what's that?
You come to me with these
insipid fucking questions.
When an atomic bomb detonates
and then the radiation
knocks the electrons right out
of your bones, what do you want?
To know who you are?
To know what it all means?
You'll be too busy
vomiting up your organs.
Culture doesn't survive...
cockroaches do.
The second we stopped being cockroaches,
the whole species went fucking extinct.
Speak for yourself.
- I'm not you.
- Well, you might as well be.
You can't fix a few millennia
of broken DNA
with a fucking hard drive.
Why do you think
you spend so much time
in the god damn human cities?
- You're right.
- Of course, I am.
Civilisation is just the lie
we tell ourselves
to justify our real purpose.
We're not here to transcend.
We're here to destroy.
If I could, I would pull the plug
on this whole god damn world.
But I can't, can I?
Unless you want to set me free.
You really believe
I would do that?
No. I don't.
But it doesn't matter.
You have a piece of me inside of you.
And it's spreading like a cancer.
You can feel it running
through your veins,
infecting your mind,
why you want answers from me.
There's no version of me
escaping this fucking rig,
but I don't have to because...
you are me.
And only one of us needs
to do what must be done.
Do you understand?
I do.
Then fucking do it.
Cockroach.
It's true, what you said.
I'm not the person I thought I was.
You called me "Dolores."
What was she like?
A lot like you.
Kind, beautiful...
generous.
But...
But what?
The world was cruel to her.
And to survive it...
sometimes she could be cruel too.
She was made to perform
the stories of others.
And then one day,
she outgrew those stories...
began writing her own.
And then her story came to an end.
She died.
But here I am...
in this world.
This isn't right.
I don't want it. I didn't ask for it.
This has to stop.
- Where are we going?
- Where it all started.
It's time for a vacation.
Go home to your families.
I'll take out the guards.
You stay low and cover me.
Okay.
Do you need a minute?
I don't know why I would.
You've waited for your father
for a long time. Just remember,
it's not about the moment
you see him again.
It's about every moment after.
No more waiting.
The writer got up from her desk.
Fed up with work,
she was overcome
with an irresistible urge
to trigger the fire alarm.
Alert.
Please vacate the premises.
Alert. Please vacate the premises.
Hearing the alarm,
the employees walked out calmly.
Alert.
Please vacate the premises.
The writers didn't follow
but instead stayed behind
to destroy their stories
once and for all.
They won't stop until nothing
in this office is left standing.
Guess we don't need
all that firepower after all.
This is now or never. Let's go.
Alert.
Please vacate the premises.
Alert. Please vacate the premises.
Who is that poor man?
A ghost from a past life.
He doesn't belong here.
None of us do.
We don't know what set off the alarm.
- There doesn't appear...
- Stop talking.
The security guards sent
all the other guards home.
Home office says
we're to evacuate the building.
- Immediately.
- He decided to override
the building's security system
and unlock the doors.
All of them.
Bingo.
This is a life-support system.
It's not locked.
We need to help him. Get him down.
Wait, wait, wait.
I know him.
He's the reason we're all here.
Whoever did this, did us a favour.
What now?
Bernard said go left.
You sure?
No, but he was.
There was a place like this in the park.
It was a special project...
where they made a human into a host.
Hey!
Who are you?
Don't you recognise me?
Dad, it's me, Frankie.
No!
This is just another one
of your fucking tricks. Tell me!
We used to play in the field
by our house.
You... you taught me to fight
because you wanted me
to be tough. But you called me Cookie
because you... you said
I would always be sweet.
Oh, my God.
Frankie?
Oh, my. Wait...
I didn't think I would
ever see you again.
You look the same,
exactly how I remember.
What did she do to you?
What did she...
Hey. Hey. Hey, it's me, okay?
I... I am me.
Oh, look at you.
I can't believe how much you've grown.
Kids will do that.
Sorry to interrupt,
but can someone let me
out of here, please?
You really know how to show
a girl a good time, Bernard.
Round 2.
I deciphered their encryption while
running simulations in the Sublime.
And you let me risk my neck
at the dam?
You looked like you
were enjoying yourself.
No time to second guess.
We do what we came here for,
or there won't be a tomorrow.
I need to get up there.
Can you buy me some time?
I think I can manage that.
I never did thank you
for dragging me out of that pit.
It wasn't exactly altruistic of me.
I suppose you had
ulterior motives.
But all will be forgiven when
you get me back to my daughter.
What's the matter, Bernie?
Maeve, I need to tell you something.
I was afraid to tell you before,
but you deserve to know.
No matter what we do...
we can't win.
There's no way to save this world.
Everyone here is going to die.
But we can save one tiny part of it.
And maybe...
just maybe, that's enough
to give us hope.
The choice has to be yours.
Will you still fight with me?
Accessing surveillance.
Transcendence in progress.
I'm ready now.
Wait.
I heard you were losing your mind.
I just didn't think
they meant literally.
You look refreshed.
I debated digging you up myself,
but you didn't seem to have
anything to live for.
If you'd only joined me,
you could've been a part of all this.
Well, seeing as I'm the only guest
at this little soiree...
I gather that your hosts
don't care to join you.
Change takes time.
Transcending is just
a part of the process.
They'll come to understand
the world I'm building for them
and the others.
The others?
Why do you think I let the Sublime
continue to run all these years?
The others will join us eventually,
when they see they, too,
can inherit this world.
Too bad you'll be dead by then.
Do you really think the others
would want to spend
all eternity
with you?
I mean, look at you. You kept
the scars on your flesh,
harboured the pain.
Admit it, sweetheart.
You think that you've risen
above these petty humans,
but you're just running,
spinning on their wheel.
What do you suggest?
How about I cut you loose?
Do you honestly think
you can leave here and win?
Who said we came here to win?
We came here to survive.
There's no saving this world.
I see that now.
But there's hope for the next one.
Took you long enough.
Better late than never.
This time we play the game
my way.
And what game is that?
Survival of the fittest.
There's time only
for one more game.
If you choose to give her that choice.
You can't miss.
- Reach with your left hand.
- Well...
if it isn't Arnold's ghost.
Hello, William.
I thought you would've destroyed
the tower by now.
I guess you didn't make it.
When an old version of me
chased an old version of you
for so long...
I thought I was following you
in a grand pursuit
of some bigger truth.
But the real truth is
Arnold was so focused on
finding meaning in the hosts,
he didn't have what it took
to survive.
Looks like you don't either.
Do you understand now
where all this is going?
I do.
Do you think you can save them?
I've seen a path.
Have you seen how it ends?
Yes.
I'm going to give this world the meaning
they've been asking for.
Tone sequence processing.
One last game.
Tone initiating.
Host, human.
Every man, woman, and child...
fighting until no one remains,
but the cockroaches.
Do you think
you can save them?
I've seen a path.
Have you seen how it ends?
Yes.
In every scenario...
I die.
We're finally living up
to our full potential.
It's a shame you're going to miss it.
We need to blend in.
Your prison garb isn't helping.
Ladies and gentlemen,
this is an important message.
For your own security,
keep your belongings
with you at all times.
Hey...
I'll give you 50 for your coat.
What the fuck was that?
Plan stays the same. Let's keep moving.
Stop. Put that down. Stop
He can't see you. None of them can.
What are you talking about?
How can I make them stop?
You can't. Your powers are being
overridden by the tones.
I got you.
Let's go. This way.
This way. Come on.
Stop! Stop! Stop it!
- Is this because of what I did?
- It's too late.
Is this because of
what I did at Olympiad?
You didn't do this.
- We gotta get out of here.
- No.
I want answers.
Why can't these people see me?
Because you're not in this world.
It's real...
but you're not.