Déjà vu.
They say it's like
a short circuit in the brain.
Jesus Christ!
Your sense of a moment
plays through your memory centre,
makes you feel like
you've experienced all this before.
My name's Lucy Chambers. I'm from
Children's Services. Can I come in?
If you don't open this door,
I'll fucking break it down!
Don't let him into this house.
It's all connected.
Your dreams, your memories,
everything that happens,
everything that doesn't.
I'm not supposed to be here.
Neither am I.
What makes you special, Gideon?
I can remember the song,
and I can move the needle.
I've died more times than I can remember.
When I re-set,
all I have are my memories,
so I surround myself with every detail.
I learn the world's evils
like the lyrics of a song.
Whatever I do, wherever I go,
someone always finds me eventually,
and it's always the same detective.
I am not your mummy.
I am an officer of the law!
Are you deaf or what?
Are you gonna calm down?
- How did you do that?
- I have no idea.
You said my life was different.
Different to what?
I can help you remember.
I stayed alive for you,
incarcerated, alone,
waiting for you to come back.
You told me the worst thing
that ever happened to you.
Thirty years ago, I stopped it.
The last time we met,
you asked me to do this.
You didn't realise how different
your life was going to be.
You're not who you were.
Lucy!
Remember, Lucy, remember!
Mummy?
Lucy.
You know the score.
I can't help you if you won't talk to me.
You know, when you first came here,
you didn't speak for a month,
so we used to make paper flowers...
in silence.
But I think you're a bit old for that now.
Why did you run away this time?
Where did you go?
Mum's cottage.
Why did you go there?
We used to keep letters in the fruit bowl.
Bills, birthday cards,
suicide notes.
I didn't wanna open it, so I hid it
where no one would ever find it.
What do you want it to say?
She didn't love me.
She didn't care about me.
She didn't want to be my mum anymore.
Why do you want it to say that?
Because then I can hate her,
and I never have
to think about her again.
Okay.
Well, I think if we're gonna do this,
we need to take a breath.
We need...
Fuck!
Fuck.
It's okay. I've got you.
I've got you. You're okay.
You're okay.
- How old are you?
- Eighteen.
- Can I see some ID, please?
- No, I left it in the car.
Your date of birth?
5th December 19... 79.
Too slow, try again. How old are you?
Eighteen.
- Why haven't you got any tits, then?
- Fuck off, yeah?
Look,
you're not gonna get served!
Oh, and you think you can do better?
Watch and learn.
Right. Are you
ready to tell me your name?
Okay, I'll go first.
I'm PC Holness.
You can call me Nick.
Nice to meet you, Nick.
Very good.
What part of Wales are you from?
That was really stupid
what you did in there.
Stealing cheap booze like that.
I mean, if you're not gonna pay for it,
you might as well treat yourself
to something decent.
Look, we don't have to go to the station.
Just tell me your name,
I'll drive you home,
have a word with your parents,
and that'll be the end of it.
- My parents are dead.
- Aye, right!
You go to school?
Not often.
Yeah, I used to skip a lot.
Now come on, where's home?
- Alright, cop shop it is then.
- Percy Street.
Percy Street?
Very nice.
Yeah, well,
my foster parents are posh cunts, so...
Aye.
There's a lot of posh cunts
in Percy Street.
Are they gonna be pissed off?
They'll probably kick me out.
I'll go somewhere else,
turn 18 in three months, so...
Alright, what happens then?
You know, you can't get
a decent job with a record?
What, a decent job, bit like yours?
Well, it's better to be
a cop than a robber.
It has its perks.
Bella likes your uniform, does she?
How do you know my wife's name?
That's her in the photo with the candles.
I reckon that's her name on the box.
Right. Come on.
No more messing around.
What's your name?
It's Lucy.
Lucy what?
Lucy Chambers.
Well, you've got a good eye for detail.
You'd make a better detective
than me, Lucy Chambers.
We don't have a burglar alarm.
I told Mike I thought we should get one.
You know, I've got some jewellery upstairs
and it's, well, it's quite expensive.
But you say that's all accounted for?
Didn't touch any of it.
We... we don't even think
that he went upstairs.
Maybe something spooked him,
a neighbour or the postman.
Yeah, but...
Mike left his iPad on the coffee table.
I mean, if you're gonna take one thing,
you would take that, right?
I'd have thought so.
Yeah, so why take the microwave?
Will he come back?
No. Don't worry. We'll catch him.
Yeah, alright, thanks, mate.
Er, just spoke to Ian next door, erm...
He reckons he saw
an old van parked down the road,
red Nissan, he reckons,
but there's no sign of it now.
A red Nissan. What model?
No idea, mate.
Are you okay, Joshy?
Are you okay, mate? Oh...
He's a bit shaken up.
He's worried the burglar's
gonna come back,
but he won't, will he, mate, hey?
Not with Daddy around, hey?
Actually if someone botches a burglary,
they do tend to come back for another go.
I'd suggest you get an alarm,
double locks on the doors.
Okay, mate. It's alright.
Wow. I'm guessing
you haven't got kids, then?
Okay, mate. It's okay. You're safe now.
It's going to be okay.
Daddy's here, I'll protect you.
I mean, maybe don't say it
in front of the child.
Oh, God! I don't know why you
always get so soppy around kids.
- I don't get soppy.
- You do.
You'd be one of those
three-kids-and-a-mortgage people
with a dog and a ride-on mower
and a Citroën Berlingo.
And a wife, if I'm lucky.
Ugly wife. Short-sighted.
No sense of smell.
Oh! Bit out of my league.
I tell you what.
If we're both single
when we're 45, I'll marry you,
but we have to sleep in separate beds
and you will have to shave your beard.
Beards are sexy. This is a sexy beard.
No, it isn't, it's got crisps in it.
Did you ever hear about that weird case?
I think it was Dulworthy.
Someone broke in and didn't take
anything except a toy lion.
And the weirdest thing, a few months
later, they recalled those toys.
Loose eyes, choking hazard.
What the hell was that?
- Whoo!
- Weird time of day for fireworks.
So romantic, Ravi!
- Did you do all this for me?
- Oh, yeah.
I armed a bunch of farm kids
with some rockets, just for you.
What?
Nothing.
♪ I am the one and only! ♪
♪ Nobody I'd rather be! ♪
♪ You can't take that away from me! ♪
- There you go.
- No, no. On the house.
This woman saved my life. Seriously,
if it wasn't for her, I'd be homeless.
Yes, mate?
I arrested his landlord on drug charges.
Hard to chase up the rent
when you're in custody.
How do you drink this stuff?
Well, not like that.
Would you like some soda water?
Piss off.
Next round's my choice.
♪ Away from me! ♪
♪ Ooh! ♪
Oh!
There you go,
you're getting the hang of it.
No, I'm not.
This is gonna kill me tomorrow.
Hmm!
Mmm. Don't look.
- What?
- Don't look!
- Woman at the bar, sparkly top.
- What about her?
She's like totally checking you out.
No, she's not.
Buy her a drink.
What, and leave you on your own?
I'll hang out with Holness.
Bella's gonna kill him.
She will melt him down
and turn him into candles.
Lager-scented candles.
- You'll have to make the arrest.
- Bella Holness?
I think we'd need a SWAT team.
Ow!
What?
She's still looking.
Go on!
Fine.
♪ Hey, there you, with the sad face ♪
♪ Come up to my place and live it up ♪
♪ You, beside the dance floor ♪
♪ What do you cry for, let's live it up ♪
Fucking bastard!
Hey! Who fucking put that there?
Oh! There she is.
You know, your fancy man's
inside there talking to some bimbo.
He's not my fancy man.
He's my partner, Nick.
Is that why you're sulking out here?
I'm not sulking, I'm thinking.
Alright, suit yourself.
I'm gonna throw up and find myself a taxi.
Oh, give my love to Bella.
I will.
Don't know if she'll be
in a lovely mood, though.
Then again, you never know.
Goodnight, DI Chambers.
Goodnight, lover boy!
Who you calling lover boy?
What's her name?
Elena.
She's a school teacher.
Very wholesome.
What's on your mind, Chambers?
Toy lions and microwaves.
Somewhere in the noise,
there's always a pattern.
- What?
- Give yourself an evening off.
You let this stuff consume you.
This is the job, Ravi.
Amanda Milton and Margo Jackson
were last seen walking home from school
in the Tamford area at approximately
5:00 pm yesterday afternoon.
The nature of their disappearance
is not yet known,
but our response has been
swift and uncompromising.
We are coordinating with Hackridge Police
to ensure that no stone is left unturned,
and we are urging any members of
the public with relevant information
to come forward
and assist us in our enquiries.
Let's find these girls
and bring them home.
Oh, come on!
Argh! God!
- Argh! Oh!
- They don't have any Coke round here.
Oh...
What did you find?
Did you ever speak to Holness
about the Jonah Taylor case?
Tried to. He's not exactly forthcoming.
There was traffic cam footage
from the end of the Taylor's road.
Several houses on the route,
only one vehicle unaccounted for.
A red Nissan Vanette.
Yeah, I remember.
They never tracked it down.
No, they didn't.
But this...
this was taken three days before
Amanda and Margo went missing.
It's a doorbell cam three streets away.
They always take the same
route home from school.
Now tell me, Ravi,
is that or is that not
a red Nissan Vanette?
Might be coincidence.
That car's at least 20 years old.
It's not a fucking coincidence.
Have you got a cigarette?
- You're not supposed to smoke in here.
- I'll open a window.
DS Dhillon.
Say that again, please.
What is it?
Okay, tell them
we'll be there in ten minutes.
Have they found them?
It's something else.
- Stay outside.
- I can handle it.
It's a kid, Ravi.
I can't have you plugged in,
not in there.
Stay out here, find out what we know.
Ladies and gents,
step back, please. Back.
Husband had a record.
On probation for assault.
Neighbour said he was pounding
on the back door till she let him in.
- Where is he now?
- No clue.
We put out an APW.
Conscientious neighbours.
Anyone see him leave?
Shane.
It's Shane, isn't it?
Shane, I need you to put down the knife.
I have Fisher.
Upstairs bathroom.
Say again.
Fuck!
No!
- Stand still!
- Stop resisting!
Fuck!
Put them on!
Right, get in.
Head down.
Let me see.
No, you'll faint.
I'll be brave.
- Does it hurt?
- Ah!
Only when I laugh.
House hasn't fallen down yet,
so that's something.
- It's not a supporting wall.
- We'll see.
Nah, it looks great, babe.
Cheers.
- Start on the attic tomorrow.
- You're not serious?
What?
Can't you sit still for one minute?
What do you think I'm doing now?
What is it, love?
We don't have time for this.
It's someone's little boy.
I thought it might be nice
to find a kid for a change.
And no one's reported him missing?
Not yet.
Okay.
I still think you should have
gone for the gold one.
Here we go.
He's just up here.
Hello there.
My name's Ravi. What's yours?
Isaac.
Nice to meet you, Isaac.
This is my friend Lucy.
We're here to help you get home, okay?
He thinks this is his home.
Isaac.
- What's your mummy's name?
- Lucy.
Do you know her second name?
Chambers.
And do you know where Mummy is?
No, sweetheart.
I'm not your mummy.
No, I'm not, and we need to find her
'cause your mummy is gonna be
very worried about you.
You're my mummy.
No, I'm not Mummy.
Maybe... I look like Mummy.
Does she have hair like mine?
It's different.
Different how?
Oh... sweetheart.
Hey, don't get upset.
It's alright.
It's okay to cry if it hurts.
Sometimes crying makes it feel better.
What do we do?
- Er, I don't know.
- Well, someone must be missing him.
He can't just have
appeared out of thin air.
We'll call Children's Services, yeah?
Find him somewhere to stay.
No...
Isaac. You just...
You just need to stay here.
No, we're taking him back to the station.
Yeah, sounds good. How long?
Because we're not babysitters.
Sorry, what did you say your name was?
No, don't put me on hold.
Don't you...
Oh!
- Gotta love Children's Services.
- Helpful as ever?
Rob Shaw. Remember that name.
Prick.
Sorry.
I don't know what we do when we
get there. He's not gonna let me go.
- What do you think happened to him?
- I've no idea.
It's weird that no one's reported it.
Do you think someone abandoned him?
No.
- Who would do that?
- Someone who can't cope anymore.
Just leave him with another family.
It's possible.
You okay?
Yeah.
My arm's gone to sleep.
Come on, sweetheart. Let's swap.
Weird day.
Oh, you need to take the next left.
DI Chambers.
What?
What is it?
You need to turn around.
- What?
- Just turn around.
Stay here.
I'll find someone to take
the kid back to the station.
Do you think it's them?
Keep the door locked.
It's okay.
She's coming back. You'll be okay.
How about we listen to some music?
Would you like that?
She won't be long.
Looks like someone tried to weigh
them down, but the knot slipped.
There's a boat shop down the road.
Owner says he saw a van parked
out here the last few nights.
What sort of van?
Red. Doesn't know the make.
Might not be connected.
Everything's connected.
Isaac!
Isaac?
I took my eyes off him for one second.
- It's like he just disappeared.
- Kids don't just disappear, do they?
There's nowhere to hide.
I've searched everywhere.
What about in there?
It's locked.
So?
Can I help you?
Anything else you want to add?
It might help if you take us
through it again.
You know, get everything straight.
No.
Fine.
Interview with Harold Slade
terminated at 17:32.
- That make any sense to you?
- Only just got here, catch me up.
He didn't wanna hurt them.
He just wanted to...
keep them.
Sorry, Sam Boyd.
DC Boyd just transferred in from the Met.
What do you mean,
he wanted to keep them?
Well, he says it wasn't, erm, sexual.
Not sexual?
The key to that door was in his safe,
and we found
child pornography on his laptop.
What the fuck
did he do to them, Nick?
Nothing, according to him.
Then how did they die?
He's a big Tchaikovsky fan.
His wife surprised him
with a trip to Prague. Swan Lake.
Packed his case for him,
no time to double back for the kids.
Left them without food or water.
So, by the time they got back...
We're following up with the coroner,
but the theory is they died of...
thirst.
Oh, my...
He should have killed himself.
What made him turn himself in?
He was threatened.
Somebody saw him trying
to get rid of the bodies,
cornered him in the dark,
held a knife to his throat.
We're looking for a Caucasian male.
Tall, thin, Scottish accent, grey hair.
Cloven hooves, big old horns.
Slade said he was the devil
come to take him to hell.
This man said he could
see into the future.
Knew exactly when and where
those girls would be found.
- Right, so the devil made him do it?
- No, no, no.
- The devil made him confess.
- Sorry, erm...
You tied a red Vanette to the abduction?
Right, erm...
But it's...
it was just he was quite specific.
Specific doesn't mean
he's right in the head.
The guy's a fucking nut job.
No, no, I know but...
Well, it can't be a coincidence.
Guess what sort of car the devil drives?
Argh!
Name's Aiden Stenner.
Multiple stab wounds. Dead on arrival.
You see, they join these gangs and...
Well, it's just a matter of time.
You alright, mate?
Yeah, I'm fine.
- Do you wanna step outside for a minute?
- No.
It's not a gang attack.
How do you know?
Witnesses described
a thin man in his fifties or sixties,
white hair, Scottish accent.
They haven't seen him
around here before.
Get a statement from those kids.
I want an E-Fit for the suspect.
Put out an APW and check the CCTV
coverage on the buildings opposite
and every traffic cam
in a ten-mile radius.
We're not gonna
get a chance like this again.
Slade said he was the devil
come to take him to hell.
There was traffic cam footage
from the end of the Taylor's road.
Several houses on the route,
but only one vehicle unaccounted for.
A red Nissan Vanette.
Yeah, I remember.
They never tracked it down.
Everything's connected.
But it can't be a coincidence.
Is that or is that not
a red Nissan Vanette?
Cloven hooves, big old horns.
We're looking for
a Caucasian male,
tall, thin, Scottish accent, grey hair.
Guess what sort of car the devil drives?
We've found a link
between multiple cases
dating right back to the Jonah Taylor
abduction 12 years ago.
Sightings of a red Nissan Vanette,
which has, until now, never been traced.
We've cross-referenced past sightings
of the vehicle with recent ANPR hits.
Seems it always disappears
around the same black spot,
Thornham Green.
It's mostly farmland, single track lane.
Now, surveillance drones didn't
pick it up, but we did find this.
Used to be a holiday let.
The owner died some time ago.
No one claimed it.
It's supposed to be empty.
Thermal imaging tells a different story.
Working theory, this is
where our suspect is hiding.
Now, he is extremely resourceful
and quite possibly armed.
TFCs will brief firearms officers
on the finer details,
but we go in at night,
quiet, set up roadblocks.
Take him by surprise.
ETA to target, 30 seconds.
We believe suspect is still in situ.
Proceed as planned on arrival.
Clear!
Requesting medical support.
All clear! Suspect isn't here.
All units move in.
- Let's bring in aerial support.
- Copy that.
Sierra, Oscar, 43, control.
Any sign of the suspect?
This is DS Dhillon, request...
Stop there, please.
I said, stop there!
Is that you, Dhillon?
Are we really gonna do this again?
I would tell you to walk away
but I know that you won't.
Stop right there! Hands above your head!
You can't beat me.
I know every move you're gonna make.
Just let me pass.
I can't do that.
Alright.
Let's get it over with.
Don't come any closer.
I said stop!
Get a closer look at it.
Yeah, it's definitely it.
Get the plates as well.
He left on foot.
Tracks heed off in every direction.
This is petrol.
Ma'am?
Well, that thing runs on diesel.
So does the generator.
That means he's got another vehicle.
There's only one set of tyre tracks.
So he slips away on foot.
Keeps a back-up close to the main road.
Get me a map of the area.
- Go, go, go!
- Let's move!
- I said move.
Armed police!
DI Chambers, come in.
Go ahead.
We're a man down.
Can he hear me?
It's hard to say.
Sleep it off, yeah?
It's over now.
We got him.
We fucking got him.
They haven't fed me.
Good.
This is DI Lucy Chambers
of the Hart Valley Constabulary.
It is the 11th of November.
The time is 21:42.
Would you state your full name
for the benefit of the recording?
Gideon Shepherd.
Mr Shepherd, you've been arrested
for the murders of Aiden Stenner
and Connor Larson.
Is that it?
How many people have you
killed, Mr Shepherd?
More.
Do you know how many times we've
had this conversation, DI Chambers?
- What's that supposed to mean?
- Existence is a circle, recurring,
and in every recurrence,
you and I sit in this room.
You ask me your questions,
I tell you the truth,
and I warn you what's gonna
happen if you don't believe me.
What is going to happen, Mr Shepherd?
You've read my notes.
Tried to.
You need to work on your handwriting.
So you keep telling me, detective.
What is going to happen, Mr Shepherd?
Seventeen dead.
Eleven children.
I can't stop it now, but you can.
- What have you done?
- Not me.
I'm not what you think I am.
You look at me and you see
the devil incarnate.
The real devil's out there,
lurking in the shadows.
The blur on the edge of the picture.
I don't know his face, but I've seen
what he can do, and so will you.
Next year, 17 dead, 11 children.
Mr Shepherd, I'm going to...
...refer you
for psychological evaluation.
I go to prison. I kill myself.
We start over.
But we always end up here, every time.
I can't beat you, Lucy.
So I want you to join me.
Join you?
I'll live, just this once.
I'll stay alive.
I'll serve my time and wait.
When you're ready to talk,
you'll know where to find me.
Until then...
I've said all I have to say.
You know, silence won't help your defence.
No comment.
DI Chambers.
- Ma'am. It's DC Boyd.
- Go ahead, Boyd.
I'm just checking the CID logs.
A 999 call came through
about five minutes ago.
House fire at 7 Sycamore Drive.
- Why are you telling me this?
- It's just...
you've been there, ma'am, last month.
It's the house where
they found that boy, Isaac.
Detective Chambers.
Did we get everyone out?
Looks that way.
They're treating the mother for burns.
Is everything alright, ma'am?
It's nothing, just a feeling.
Déjà vu.
Isaac?
Isaac, are you in there?
It's Lucy.
Lucy Chambers. Will you come out, Isaac?
We're not supposed to be here.
Daddy made me cold.
There's nothing to be afraid of.
I couldn't stop it.
What couldn't you stop?
The fire.
Oh, sweetheart,
you don't have to stop the fire.
Everyone's okay.
The firemen are putting it out.
It followed me here.
What do you mean?
Isaac?
What time is it?
Late.
I'm surprised they let you in.
Perks of the job.
I said I had to speak to my partner,
urgent police business.
Oh, lucky me.
Yeah, I lied.
I just wanted to be with... someone.
Are you okay?
No.
No, I think I might be losing my mind.
Me too.
We can go crazy together.
I'd like that.
Does it hurt?
It's not so bad.
Good.
I know.
I'm insane for being here.
This might be my last chance.
I'm running out of time.
No, you're not.
You and I have all the time
in the world, detective.
You will return to this life
just as I will,
just as we always have.
Only next time,
we make sure it's different.
How much will it change?
I can't say for sure.
A butterfly flaps its wings
and greets a thunderstorm.
I can save your mother's life,
but after that, we surrender to the chaos
and the chaos will wake you up,
make you remember this conversation.
So if we do this,
if you stop my mother
from killing herself,
I lose everything.
You'll lose, you'll gain.
You'll walk a different path.
I'll forget him.
You were always going to,
but if you wake up,
we can save them all.
- I shouldn't be here.
- Yes, you should.
Lucy.
You know this case.
Every foul detail, it's etched
into your soul, I know it is.
Not just Rigby's, but the others.
The schools, the soft play.
Wrap it up.
We have to stop them, Lucy.
I need you on my side.
Okay.
Are you okay?
It's okay.
Someone help!
- What's wrong?
- Call an ambulance!
It's okay.
You're gonna be okay.
Ravi.
I'm here.
Can I get you anything?
Don't let go.
I only ever needed you.
You know that, don't you?
Come on, Chambers.
I think you're hamming this up a bit.
You made me so happy.
We'll see each other again.
I promise.
I will find you.
I love you, Lucy Chambers.
Ravi.
I'm here.
I can hear music.
So if we do this,
I lose everything.
You'll lose, you'll gain.
You'll walk a different path.
Our dreams can't hurt us, Lucy.
Can't hurt us now.
Still nothing.
He never cries,
never laughs, he never gets mad.
He's just...
Isaac!
Coming through.
- Don't try to speak.
- Isaac.
- He's okay.
- Where is he?
- He's okay. He's being looked after.
- Did he get out?
He got out.
Your neighbours found him.
Is Ravi here?
- Ravi?
- Ravi...
Ravi. Ravi Dhillon, my husband.
Lucy.
Do you remember what happened?
I remember.
I remember everything.