♪ I started a joke ♪
♪ Which started the whole world crying ♪
♪ But I couldn't see ♪
♪ That the joke was on me ♪
♪ Oh, no ♪
♪ I started to cry ♪
♪ Which started
the whole world laughing ♪
♪ Oh, if I'd only seen ♪
♪ That the joke was on me ♪
♪ I looked at the skies ♪
♪ Running my hands over my eyes ♪
♪ And I fell out of bed ♪
♪ Hurting my head
from things that I'd said ♪
♪ Till I finally died ♪
♪ Which started the whole world living ♪
♪ Oh, if I'd only seen ♪
♪ That the joke was on me ♪
Seventeen dead.
Eleven children.
The real devil's out there...
lurking in the shadows.
The blur on the edge of the picture.
I don't know his face, but I've seen
what he can do, and so will you.
Next year, seventeen dead.
Found these in the printer.
Thanks.
Have you been home?
Oh, didn't see the point. Ravi's
still in Leeds on this training thing.
Have you slept?
Not sure.
Well, we've accounted for all the victims.
None of them fit the profile,
the bomber got away.
We're still looking at CCTV.
- Any leads?
- No leads.
Just a reflection. Look here.
It's in the corner of the picture,
yellow hoodie.
But...
it never comes out clean.
Yeah, you plan something like this,
you know where the cameras are.
Yeah, well, you can't avoid them all.
We'll find him.
No. No, I don't think we will.
Yeah, that's the spirit.
Just sit there feeling sorry for yourself.
Shepherd was a fucking lunatic.
Same as whoever did this.
He knew something bad
was gonna happen,
just like I know
something bad's gonna happen,
'cause something bad
always fucking happens.
The world just keeps revolving from one...
fucked-up horror to the next.
And he got his numbers wrong.
He told me there'd be seventeen dead.
Last I checked there were sixteen.
What?
Kelly Watson, she was, er...
she was nine months pregnant.
Look, it's...
- No, it's got to be...
- Okay.
- Okay, Nick.
- It's a coincidence.
How many times have you
watched that, by the way?
I'm just listening to music.
Of course you are.
Silly me.
Existence is a circle, recurring.
And in every recurrence,
you and I sit in this room.
You ask me your questions,
I tell you the truth.
And I warn you what's going to happen
if you don't believe me.
It's been nearly a year,
and he's still dreaming about the fire.
I thought the nightmares would stop,
but they're getting worse.
Just wish there was a way
I could... make him forget.
I'm... I'm cautious with dreams.
They can be noisy and misleading.
There is a common theme, though.
When did Isaac last see his father?
Not since that night.
- Lucy, I think it might be...
- No.
He's never gonna see Mike again.
- With supervised visits...
- He left him.
He closed the door,
and he left him there to burn.
If I could prove it,
he would be in prison, but I can't.
- And you still don't believe me.
- It's a recurring nightmare.
- Based on a memory.
- A traumatic memory.
Muddled. Blended with imagination.
So what if he wasn't imagining it?
I mean, like, hypothetically.
What if he really experienced
all those impossible things?
How would you treat him?
Like, help him come to terms?
I... I'm not sure I follow.
Never mind.
I just don't want him
to be afraid anymore.
I wish I could... flick a switch.
Lucy, I wanted to ask if we could talk
about some one-to-one sessions.
Not all the time, just...
Mm, sometimes I feel like
he's picking up on your cues.
Lucy.
Yeah.
Sure. I mean,
I-I will think about it.
Thank you.
What do you think?
I can't see it.
Here.
Give it a squeeze.
Better?
Come on.
Got some bits for your room.
Five.
- Fifteen.
- Hmm!
It's all right.
It's just the house settling.
That's what happens with new houses.
They settle while we settle.
Isaac.
There are no ghosts here, I promise.
What is it?
Meredith said there's
no such thing as ghosts.
But there are.
There was one stood behind her
when she said it.
When was this?
When you went over to play?
Oh, sweetheart.
It's different here.
No one has ever lived in this house.
It's just for us.
Just for this lifetime, yeah?
This loop.
I'm not supposed to be here.
There's no such thing as "supposed to."
We're here because we choose to be.
Just like I chose to have you.
And I'm choosing to win this game!
Oi, mate!
Where you going?
- Walk away.
- What?
What's that, paedo?
- Why are you dressed like a paedo?
- Oi, catch!
Eh!
Give us your money or we'll report you
for being a fucking paedo.
I don't want to hurt you,
so just walk awa... Uhh!
Grab his phone! Quick, grab his phone!
Aargh!
Aaargh!
♪ I looked at you, baby,
and what did I see? ♪
♪ I saw love in your eyes ♪
♪ Made me feel so warm inside ♪
♪ Now look at me, baby ♪
♪ And what do you see? ♪
- ♪ You see love in my eyes ♪
- Dhillon, are you listening to me?
Dhillon!
Sorry.
Don't faint on me.
Mnh-mnh.
Jesus Christ!
Just tell me what I need to know.
Victim was struck three times.
Skull fractures here, here and here.
This blow ruptured a blood vessel.
Cause of death, it was an intercranial
hematoma. Not instant.
That's why he was still walking around?
- He bled out.
- No, bled in.
Bleed was between the brain and the skull.
Oh, for fuck's sake.
- Is there anything else?
- Nothing relevant.
Death from head trauma, open and shut.
You can charge your man.
- Right.
- Don't let him escape.
Hilarious. Get some
new material, Gibson.
DI Dhillon.
Ravi, it's Sam.
Sam Boyd.
Boyd?
Hi. Sorry, new phone.
- Haven't got your number saved.
- Yeah.
Sorry to call out of the blue but...
Not a problem. You after a reference?
A favour, a big one.
And you're gonna say no,
but I'm gonna keep on asking.
Of course you are.
Gideon Shepherd was sighted
in Hackridge Park last night.
Hatby wants a DI on the ground.
There are plenty of D.I.s where you are.
No, best one I know moved to Sheffield.
And he's an expert on the case.
The case that nearly got me fired.
Why do you think I moved here?
And we've already
cleared it with your DCI.
I'm not the one you want, Sam.
Why?
I mean, don't you wanna catch him?
Honestly?
I'm not sure I do.
Ravi.
He's out there.
He's close.
For all we know, he's planning something.
Yeah, of course he is.
So help me. Please?
Look, it has to be you.
No one knows him like you do.
That's not entirely true.
Members of the public are
warned not to approach the suspect,
but to notify police
of any possible contact.
This is the first confirmed sighting
of Gideon Shepherd
since he escaped from police custody
eleven months ago,
seriously wounding two police officers
in the process. Wanted...
Shit.
I told you not to come here.
You weren't answering your phone.
If someone followed you here...
I'm not the one
with my face in the paper.
You hurt people.
They didn't give me a choice.
- Kids.
- Barely.
I was outnumbered. I did what I had to.
Well, they're looking for you.
They've been looking for me
since I was 9 years old.
A thousand lives ago,
nothing changes.
Everything changes.
You don't know what happens next.
I have an idea.
There's something disgusting
walking around out there.
He could pass me in the street
and I wouldn't even know.
He could do anything to anyone.
But he won't.
We know what he does.
We know when he does it.
The monster just needs a face.
Don't smoke there,
you'll make the curtains smell.
You're gonna hate me
for saying this.
Mm, don't say it, then.
You need to take some time off.
Last year, with Shepherd and Slade,
and now this bombing.
I'm worried it'll break you.
I'm worried it'll...
What?
Even when you're here...
you're not here.
And I miss you.
I know that's selfish. I just...
Ugh! You know what?
- Ignore me.
- No, that's okay.
You're right.
I am?
You only get one life.
And I miss you too.
We should go away.
Somewhere hot and too expensive.
I don't wanna go away.
I wanna have a baby.
I'm not taking your fucking pills!
She's always here.
She just sits there on the end of the bed.
Don't look at me like that.
Don't look at me like that!
Don't look at me!
Dr Ellis saw her this morning.
Couldn't get her back into bed.
Mum?
She had a good day yesterday.
Not sure what's happened.
Mum, let's, um...
Let's sit you down. Come on, that's it.
All right.
A nice sit-down.
There.
Mum?
Look at me.
Er...
Where's Dr Ellis now?
He's with another patient.
Of course he is.
What's changed?
What are you giving her?
Same dosage.
She may have built up a tolerance.
We need to look into options.
Where's the picture?
Dr Ellis wanted to see if she was
staring at the photo or...
just staring.
Can you put it back, please?
Mum.
Talk to me.
Hey? What's happened?
What's wrong, hmm?
- Mum!
- Give her time.
I've given her time.
She just keeps getting worse.
It's this place.
- This is the best place for her.
- Is it?
She needs specialist care.
If-if you want to talk to Dr Ellis...
Dr Ellis doesn't know what's
wrong with her, none of you do.
And you don't listen to me.
Nobody listens!
I'm sorry. I just...
Can you leave us, please?
Where are you?
Where have you gone?
I'm not gonna let you leave me again,
do you understand?
You have to come back.
DI Dhillon.
DS Boyd.
Thanks for coming.
It's temporary.
Even so,
if I have to have a babysitter,
it's nice to have someone I can bully.
Should have just asked them
to promote you.
Well, you...
you can take that up with my wife.
And my 3-year-old. Plus, DI's
have to work on Sundays, so...
You still singing in the choir?
Badly but, you know, with feeling.
I've cleared a desk
for you upstairs, so...
I'll grab my pass,
we'll head straight out.
You don't wanna say some hellos?
They don't blame you, Ravi.
For Shepherd?
Or for Nick?
It's not a reunion, Sam.
Yeah. Just saying.
Thank you.
If it's all the same, I just wanna
get out there and put this right.
Yes. It's your call.
So, where do you wanna start?
Now, these cameras
belong to the school,
so you need to be very careful with them.
Jason Williams.
Are you listening?
No!
You're going to be taking
these home with you,
which means that you are responsible
for making sure they stay in one piece.
Martin, that goes for you too.
Er, no, Johnny, don't do that, please.
We're not taking pictures
of ourselves or each other.
Can we pay attention, please?
That goes for you too, Isaac Chambers.
Thank you.
I want you to take pictures of nature.
So... animals, trees, rivers, beaches.
But we're not just thinking about nature.
We're thinking about the effect
that people have on nature.
I thought you all
did brilliant work on these.
- What sort of effect does it...
- Lots of really nice ideas here.
- Or negative...
- Simon, please pay attention.
- I'm not gonna tell you again.
- Are we responsible or irresponsible?
I need to talk to a few of you
about your handwriting,
Okay. Pollution... Jason, put that down!
Isaac, what was I just saying?
What was I just saying?
Is that supposed to be funny?
What's wrong?
Are you feeling okay?
It's all right. It's not broken.
Quiet, please.
We don't wanna scare anyone.
This is all precautionary,
but we can't ignore coincidences.
Shepherd was a stone's throw away.
It's possible he's planning something.
Some of the kids come
to school through that park.
We need to make parents aware of
the risks but without causing a panic.
No, sure.
Sorry, Miss.
Sorry.
Sorry, I... I've forgotten your name.
DI Dhillon. Ravi.
All good?
Sorry. DS Boyd.
Er, Miss Rogers.
Elena. Isaac's teacher.
Great. Well...
if you see anything suspicious,
just give us a call.
Straight to mobile,
don't bother with the office.
Oh... er, thank you.
"This is for you," said the kind dog.
"Thank you," said Thomas,
"now I don't have to be sad anymore.
As long as I have this,
I will think of you,
and I will never be lonely again."
"Never be lonely again."
What are you doing here, Lucy?
Stocking up.
What are these?
Oh, pain au chocolat.
Don't tell me you've
never had pain au chocolat?
No.
Well, they're nice.
You have them for breakfast.
- Who has chocolate for breakfast?
- You only live once.
- No, you don't.
- Doesn't matter, they're not for you.
Who are they for?
Lucy?
Mum's in the car.
No. No, no, no, no. You can't do this.
She knows this house.
We made memories here,
it's the only place she'll find them.
You are not thinking clearly.
No. No, I'm not because if I don't do
something now, I will lose her forever.
There is no forever.
She will come back.
So will you, so will I,
and so will everyone else.
And round and round
it goes like a fucking pinwheel.
I tried to save her, I tried to
give her a life, but her body rejected it.
There's nothing you can do.
- You don't know that.
- I know everything.
My mind is thousands of years old.
You've got two lives in your head,
I've got hundreds.
I've burnt, I've drowned,
I've bled to death.
I've lived, I've loved.
- I can't help you.
- I'm not asking for your help.
I will come in every day.
I'll feed her, I'll bath her.
- No!
- You won't know she's here.
No, I told you.
You need to stay away from me.
You think you're safe?
You're not.
You think you know me? You don't.
I kill people.
You kill people who hurt others.
I kill people who get in my way.
She won't get in your way.
Excuse me.
Hello.
DI Dhillon.
I think we met last year.
Did we?
The Gideon Shepherd case.
Oh, right.
This is DS Boyd.
We'd like a word with the boss,
if that's alright?
Yeah, sure, wait there.
I'll see if he's free.
No, she's not worked here
for months.
- Are you still in touch?
- Off and on.
She handed her notice after...
- well, everything.
- Where's she working now?
Nowhere.
As far as we know.
What does she do for money?
Well, she had an insurance payout
when her house burnt down,
and she divorced her husband,
he had a bit of cash.
And she's been gambling.
I've seen her at the bookies
a couple of times.
Horse racing?
Wimbledon final. She won a stack of cash.
You don't get great odds on tennis,
so she must've staked quite a bit.
I guess everyone's luck turns eventually.
It's been very difficult
to predict this season, hasn't it?
Most games have been hard to call
so there's every chance
- Kevin will surprise you.
- You're right.
They've made a comeback after
a challenging start to the competition.
Last five weeks
seen a fair few near misses.
The last two games have surprised me.
They've taken on some tough opponents.
Their new coach has
really proved himself.
Ravi.
Hi.
- What are you...?
- I, um...
I'm back in town.
Thought we should catch up.
And I don't have your number, so...
How did you find us?
Well, I'm a detective.
- If it's a bad time, I could just...
- No, it's, er...
It's good to see you.
Hello, Isaac. Long time no see.
Hey. You remembered.
Um, Isaac, do you wanna
change out of your uniform, yeah?
Good boy.
It's a weird place to live, Chambers.
Yeah, well...
I haven't paid my TV license,
so hoping they don't find us out here.
Well, your secret's safe with me.
Do you wanna come in?
Do you want a beer? Or are you on duty?
Sort of.
Sort of?
You're back for him, aren't you?
I saw the news.
I thought it was over.
I thought...
all that stuff he said about
razor blades and resetting...
- maybe he just...
- Slashed his wrists?
Oh, sorry. Sorry.
How long are you back for?
As long as it takes.
I spoke to Isaac's teachers.
They're, er...
they're taking it seriously.
He's left us alone for a year.
He's a deranged monster,
and he's obsessed with you.
He was spotted in the park
behind Isaac's school.
Aren't you worried?
Mmm, should I be?
He's never hurt me,
he's never threatened me.
Yeah, well, he beat me
half to death, so...
I, um...
I keep a taser in the car now.
Is that allowed?
Not really.
I tried to visit you in hospital.
Tried?
The boss said it was a bad idea.
I was fighting to keep my job.
Oh.
I did call after,
but you changed your number.
Downgraded. Digital detox.
Smart.
Nope, that's the point.
You should stay for dinner.
Made a... a cassoulet.
Or casserole. What's the different?
What is the difference between
a cassoulet and a casserole?
I just... It's... It's a stew thing.
I don't want to intrude.
No, I've made loads.
Plus, you know,
if you're worried about us,
you probably should stick around a bit,
you know, keep us safe.
I don't think you need me
to keep you safe.
I do need you.
Besides, it's like you said,
there's a monster on the loose.
You don't have to eat it all.
I probably gave you too much.
Not possible. This is delicious.
Well, you're lucky
you're getting real food.
We usually rely on Captain Birdseye,
or Colonel Sanders,
if I'm feeling really stretched.
Clearly have a thing
about men with beards.
Isaac prefers fish fingers, don't you?
Not a big fan of Brussels sprouts, I see.
Top tip:
They're much nicer if you roast them.
If you boil them, they go a bit stodgy.
Um, well, you don't have
to eat my stodgy sprouts.
Oh, I didn't. I just put them in
my pocket when you weren't looking.
Unbelievable!
Just for that,
you can do all the washing up.
- I was gonna offer anyway.
- Were you?
- Yeah. Because I'm very polite.
- Yeah.
Right.
Oh. Thank you.
Ready to do this?
Okay, you warm enough?
Shall we have a few pages of Narnia?
I'm tired.
Well, look, I will put Metal Mickey here.
He'll scare away
your nightmares.
Okay.
Sleep well, darling.
You're happy.
Am I?
Why do you say that?
He makes you smile.
And you make him smile.
So you should kiss him.
You can't just go round
kissing whoever you like.
Look, I'll kiss you instead.
Come here. Mwah!
Ah! Night-night.
Night.
What are you doing?
Sorry, I wasn't, er...
- Yeah, that's private.
- I know, I shouldn't have opened it.
But I did.
- Lucy.
- What?
It's just a dream diary.
My therap... thera...
Isaac's therapist told me to keep one.
A dream diary?
Mm-hmm.
Okay.
Lucy, if there's any...
Sorry.
- Hey.
- Morning.
It's 8:30, yeah.
Sorry. I overslept.
Where?
Er...
You went...
You went to see Lucy Chambers?
It got late, I slept on the sofa.
I'll be five minutes.
I'm just gonna freshen up.
Ravi.
I've seen the tapes.
Gideon Shepherd.
He got to her.
- I know you don't see it.
- I see it.
I need you to look up a name.
Evelyn Wiseman.
See if there's a connection.
Did you get that from her?
I'll be five minutes.
♪ I started a joke ♪
♪ Which started
the whole world laughing ♪
♪ But I didn't see ♪
♪ That the joke was on me ♪
♪ I started to cry ♪
♪ Which started
the whole world laughing ♪
♪ But if I'd only seen ♪
♪ That the joke was on me ♪
♪ I looked at the skies ♪
♪ Running my hands ♪
♪ Over my eyes ♪
♪ And I fell out of bed ♪
♪ Hurting my head ♪
♪ Over things that I'd said ♪
♪ Till I finally died ♪
♪ Which started
the whole world living ♪
♪ Oh, if I'd only seen ♪
♪ That the joke was on me ♪
♪ I looked at the skies ♪
♪ Running my hands ♪
♪ Over my eyes ♪
♪ And I fell out of bed ♪
♪ Hurting my head ♪
♪ From things that I'd said ♪
♪ I finally died ♪