...UK's most haunted locations,
from a bridge in Kilmarnock
to a go-kart track in South Cannock.
But first we're kicking off
your Saturday morning mix
with the Hazy Eights, "Supposed To Be".
♪ Echoes of a memory... ♪
Su-pposed...
to...
be...
on the...
ra-di-o.
Five...
eggs.
♪ I'll disappear without a trace ♪
♪ Into a world ♪
♪ That you're not supposed to know ♪
♪ Take the road most travelled by ♪
♪ And spend a lifetime wondering why... ♪
Two cows...
on...
the moor.
♪ On the fate's mysterious fair ♪
♪ Like puppets on a carousel ♪
♪ Will you ever find your way to me? ♪
♪ Photographs ♪
♪ Of photographs ♪
♪ We find along familiar paths ♪
♪ To fade... ♪
Washing machine...
breaks.
Five eggs.
Cows...
on the moor.
Washing machine breaks.
Emergency services
were dispatched to Rigby's Toys
just after 11:00 am following reports
of a huge explosion.
Detective Inspector Lucy Chambers
is at the scene.
We're asking
all members of the public...
Oh!
...to avoid Hackridge High Street while
we ascertain the cause of the explosion
and secure the area.
Lucy.
Dunn came back.
What happened?
It's not him, it's a dead end.
- Gideon...
- It's alright.
Nothing's changed.
We still know when it's gonna happen.
I just need to get close.
Do you know how to defuse a bomb?
I have to see his face.
Once I know who he is, I can stop him.
Next time? You're talking about
next time, another life.
That's how it works.
If I can't change it, I'll learn, I reset.
I'm not resetting.
I'm... I'm phoning the shop, okay?
I... I... I will call in a bomb threat.
Then we lose.
Everything I've worked for.
He'll pick a new target.
I won't know where or when or how.
You make that call,
you're putting everyone at risk.
No one can know but us, do you understand?
Anything changes,
we lose him in the chaos.
Just go home, Lucy.
I don't think I can.
Dunn's dead. He came at me, I shot him.
Gideon?
Did you clean up?
I... I didn't have time.
- I had to get out of there.
- Did anyone see you go?
I don't know.
Come back here.
Clean up, burn your clothes.
If you lie low,
we might still have a chance.
What about Isaac?
You said he was with a friend.
Is he safe?
Lucy?
Yeah.
Are you with me?
Do I have a choice?
I'll see you soon.
Oh.
- Debbie?
- Lucy.
- Sorry, I've been trying to call you.
- Wait. What... what's happened?
It's Isaac. We've just got
back from the hospital.
He was attacked, bitten by a dog.
Er... He...
- He what?
- Are you far away?
No, no, no, I'm coming.
I'm coming right now. I'm coming.
Sorry. I don't know what ha...
He was right there
and then he wasn't.
Alright.
I took my eyes off him for a second.
A second.
This was tied to the wound
when we found him.
Erm, I'm gonna need to take him home.
Are you alright to walk, darling?
- Lucy...
- It's not your fault.
- Okay, it's just... It's not.
- No one saw a dog.
And whoever found him just left him there.
- Why would they leave him?
- I don't know!
- Debs...
- I'm sorry, I'm sorry!
Please stop saying sorry.
Okay? You've done nothing wrong.
Meredith was right next to him.
She says he vanished.
She says she saw him disappear.
It's just her mind playing tricks.
You know, it happens.
You weren't there.
No.
No, I wasn't.
♪ I'm a cork on the ocean ♪
♪ Floating over the raging sea ♪
♪ How deep is the ocean? ♪
♪ I lost my way ♪
♪ I'm a rock in a landslide ♪
♪ Rolling over the mountainside ♪
♪ How deep is the valley? ♪
♪ How deep is the... ♪
You doing okay?
I'm alright.
You didn't have to come out.
What are we looking at?
Or trying not to look at?
Shotgun blast.
Likely a sawn-off.
No sign of a break-in.
What, gang crime?
Possibly. Take a look.
Yeah, I... I will if...
if you have a look at these.
From Shrewsbury Museum, archive photos.
Look at number four.
Do you recognise it?
That's the house in Evelyn's painting.
How did you find this?
Look at the caption.
"Far Away Farm."
This could lead us to Shepherd.
And... if Lucy Chambers knew about it,
that's obstruction.
Okay, we still don't know
what we've found here.
We've found Evelyn Wiseman!
Maybe we've found Jonah Taylor.
That house is 40 miles west of Birmingham,
we could go there tomorrow.
We've got a fresh body, still warm.
It's not a good time to go chasing ghosts.
I'll go. You stay on the homicide.
If this is a dead end,
I'll take the flak.
- And Lucy Chambers?
- I'll call her in the morning.
Ask her to answer some questions.
On the record.
Okay.
Good. Thanks.
And I know what you're up to.
Going out there.
Taking the flak.
You just wanna get away from the blood.
I like your watch.
It's broken.
If it's broken, why not, erm...
throw it out?
It keeps the ghosts away.
Then it's not broken, it's doing
exactly what it's meant to do.
Have you ever seen
a dog barking at nothing?
See, they sense things.
Things most people can't see.
The changes.
The ripples.
The things that aren't
supposed to be here.
I killed a dog.
A year ago.
Because it was broken.
It was dangerous.
I think that the dog that bit you...
was the dog that lived.
It saw you...
through the veil.
Caught the scent of a threat.
Of another life.
Of a world in which it no longer existed.
Keep the watch, Isaac.
You're going to need it.
Time for bed, Isaac.
Go upstairs, brush your teeth,
I'll be up in a minute.
Is there anything to drink?
Is that a good idea?
Cupboard by the stove.
You shouldn't have brought him here.
He's not safe with anyone else.
He's not safe here.
I don't know what happens next.
We may need to run.
Then we take him with us.
It's no life for a child.
He's not your responsibility.
I'm the reason he exists.
Isaac.
Look what you're doing.
You're getting it all on the carpet.
Come on, off to bed.
Mum?
Night-night, darling.
Night-night.
- I have a plan.
- Go on.
Oh, it's stupid.
Tell me your stupid plan.
Whenever we come here,
we talk about the past and you...
you think about the things you've lost.
I think we should talk about the future.
And all the things... What?
You've got your serious face on!
Well, that's because I'm very serious.
Mm. Mm-hm. Yeah. Of course.
I have a very serious question to ask you.
Okay!
Oh, my God!
- Lucy Chambers...
- Er...
- You're shaking your head.
- No, I'm not, I'm not.
Open it.
- Lucy Chambers...
- Yes.
- Will you...
- You will?
- Yes, I will.
- Ask me properly!
- You keep interrupting me.
Mm.
Will you marry me?
Yeah, I guess.
Well, get up, you idiot!
Shit!
Those things will kill you.
Have you figured it out yet?
I can't show my face in that shop
until the last minute.
It doesn't give me much time.
I could go in.
I'd blend in, I could keep an eye out.
- It's Dhillon, again.
- Answer it.
Everything's fine.
You can't see him today, you're too busy.
I told you to stop calling this number.
Sorry, couldn't help myself.
You good?
Yeah, fine.
You?
Yeah.
You at home?
No. Er, I'm at the hospital
with Isaac.
He got bitten by a dog, believe it or not.
Believe it or not.
Sorry?
I want you to come into the station.
We'd like you to answer some questions.
What... Who's "we"?
What questions?
Ask for DS Boyd.
Where will you be?
- I'm taking a trip.
- Where?
Ravi, if you want to ask me
some questions, just ask me.
Okay.
Where did you hear
the name Evelyn Wiseman?
What? Who's Evelyn Wiseman?
- Just come into the station, Lucy.
- Er...
I have to go. My phone's
about to run out of battery.
No, it isn't.
I'm really sorry. I will talk to you
later though. Love you.
I love you.
Love you.
I love you. I love you. I love you.
Ravi?
Call him back.
What?
We need to know exactly what they know.
If they have Evelyn's name,
they can find out where she is.
He said he's taking a trip.
- Gideon?
- What did you tell him?
Nothing.
He must've seen the name in my notebook.
It's fine. You said they never find her.
They never found her before
but we've changed it.
Anything can happen now.
I have to get to her.
She's not the priority. If they
catch you, this is all for nothing!
She knows about Rigby's.
She remembers, Lucy.
Well, what does it matter?
She won't tell the police.
She will. She's unstable.
If she tells the police,
they close the shop.
They investigate, the bomb never goes off.
I never see his face and we're back
to where we started, or worse.
- What's worse?
- They take us alive, after all this.
And it's not prison,
it's drugs, it's therapy.
If they numb our minds,
they make us forget.
No more echoes.
No more memories.
Hard reset.
Doesn't sound so bad
when you put it like that.
Ignorance won't make it bearable,
not when it happens again and again.
You won't be able to stop him.
And I'll be dead
years before you were even born.
Keep Dhillon out of my way.
If you hurt him...
I will fucking kill you.
You won't be the first.
If anybody comes here,
anyone at all, you hide.
And you call me. Do you understand?
There's only one number on this phone.
Remember how I showed you?
Hold on to your watch.
Don't lose your balance.
Okay.
Good boy.
I love you.
But you have to leave me?
I'm not leaving you.
Here, look at me.
I'm never going to leave you.
Never.
Keep the door locked.
Lucy.
We need to talk.
- I have somewhere to be.
- So you found her, Evelyn.
- What do you know about Evelyn?
- Let's go inside.
Let's not.
- It's a dead end. She's not there anymore.
- How would you know that?
Because I've been there.
I'm looking for answers, same as you.
- Then why didn't you tell me?
- I don't know. I...
I am just trying to move past it, him!
Everything that happened.
Ravi, there...
There is nothing out there.
I think I'll see for myself, thanks.
I'm pregnant.
How sure are you?
Three tests, three positives.
Well, what do you want to do?
Would it scare you if I said
I wanted to be a family?
We hardly know each other.
Do you really believe that?
I've never read this.
Don't know why.
It was always your favourite.
You've just lost my place.
That's what it feels like sometimes.
Coming back to a book without a mark.
You can't remember where you got to
and you slowly realise
you've read these chapters already.
Have you ever told me about this?
The bookmark?
No, I haven't.
It was your eighth birthday.
You went for a walk in Housden Forest.
You, your mum, your dad.
Rhea ran on ahead
and she found this note on the ground.
Finders keepers.
You threw a strop because
you wanted it for yourself.
It was your birthday,
why should she get a present?
But your parents said it was hers
so she should keep it.
- How...
- You sulked for the rest of the day.
And that night you went into her room
and you stole the note
from her piggy bank.
And when she realised it was gone,
she was so upset
she cried herself to sleep.
Everyone knew you'd taken it.
But you denied it
and denied it and denied it.
And you denied it
because you hated yourself.
You knew you couldn't spend it
so you kept it.
Preserved it, laminated it.
It's the worst thing you ever did.
It's your sense of justice.
It's the reason you do what you do.
I've never told anyone that story.
I know you.
I've known you a million times.
I've loved you a million times.
I am the only person you've ever told.
I'm the only person you'll ever tell.
What do you wanna do?
I wanna go to that house.
- I told you, it...
- It's a dead end.
Fine.
If we find it empty, that means
you're telling me the truth.
But if we find Evelyn Wiseman,
I'm taking her in for questioning.
And I'm arresting you for obstruction.
I... I'm looking for a Jack Graham.
Drives a blue Subaru Impreza.
I'm told he works here.
Not today. He's in hospital.
Jumped off a wall round back.
Broke both his ankles.
Silly twat.
Was Steven Dunn involved?
No.
He just drinks here.
Drank.
Right.
Do you know who killed him?
No. I'm... That's what
we're trying to find out, so...
Sorry, erm...
Just...
DS Boyd.
Oh, hello.
It's Elena Rogers from Lyle Hill.
Miss Rogers, hi.
Erm... What can I do for you?
You said to call...
if there was anything suspicious.
Isaac Chambers is off today.
Apparently, he's been bitten.
Bitten?
- By a dog.
- What?
I know.
Mum's worried it might be infected
so she's taken him back to hospital.
Okay.
It's not the first time
that Isaac's been injured.
Well, last year, he burnt his hand.
They were cagey on the details.
And mentally, he's...
I'm worried about him.
I should have spoken
to Children's Services,
but she used to run that department.
They're all friends with her.
It wouldn't be handled well.
No.
I don't suppose it would.
There's something wrong with that family.
I don't know what they're hiding but
someone needs to start asking questions.
I was hoping that someone might be you.
Yeah.
I think it might be.
Well, look, thanks, Miss Rogers, erm...
I'll be in touch.
Hello, Grandma.
This is real.
Evelyn?
Hello, Evelyn.
You're not supposed to be here.
Pack everything that matters.
Anchors, keepsakes.
I don't think we'll be coming back.
Evelyn, do you hear me?
Evelyn?
There's a ghost in the mirror.
We need to get you out of here.
The police are coming.
They know where you are.
We have to tell Jonah.
Jonah is not the problem
right now, Evelyn.
Evelyn, Evelyn, stay with me. Evelyn.
I... I can't leave.
I have to fix
the washing machine tomorrow.
It's going to break.
You know what happens tomorrow.
It's going to happen again
unless I can stop it.
No, no, no. It's all wrong.
It doesn't happen like this.
You don't come here!
Evelyn, wait!
Evelyn, don't do this!
Please. I can't leave you here.
You understand me? I don't have a choice.
They're coming.
Thanks.
Is this your taser?
Put that back.
You ever used it?
I mean it.
Just put it...
back!
What the fuck are we doing?
You realise this is insane? We're driving
200 miles to look at an empty house.
So you keep saying.
Just turn around. I'll come
to the station, I'll go on record.
People lie on record.
You know me, Ravi.
Do I?
You've always known me.
We'll see.
I know this room.
This is my room.
Is it a dream?
It's all a blur.
Where's Lucy?
She's coming back.
She promised.
Isaac.
Your name is Isaac.
And you didn't cry when you were born.
But we...
we watched the birds together.
Oh, I've been...
I've been asleep for such a long time.
Thank you for waking me up.
I know this is hard.
I know...
But the police are coming.
If you don't leave with me now,
they're going to take you
and they won't understand.
They will make you tell them things,
things...
that will put a lot of people
in danger, a lot of people!
I can't leave you here.
Evelyn.
I can't trust you.
I'm sorry.
Do we have to start again?
No.
But you can't stay here.
Where are we going?
Somewhere safe.
- You have to pull over.
- No.
They can go back.
Ravi, no. No, no, no, no, no.
Get out of the car!
Drop the gun.
Now!
Stay back!
Last warning.
You shoot me with that thing,
every muscle in my body contracts,
including my trigger finger.
Put it down.
Get back in the car.
You do not understand what you're doing.
But she does.
Yes.
Gideon, drop the gun.
I can't do that.
We can explain.
He'll never believe you.
What won't I believe?
What the fuck is going on?
Ravi, you have to listen to him.
I would rather not hurt you.
The feeling isn't mutual.
Don't take another step.
No, no, no. Lucy?
- Is she okay?
- Lucy, can you hear me?
- Is she okay?!
- I don't know!
Lucy? Lucy?
Ravi.
Are you alright?
Yeah.
They knew we were coming for her.
You told him.
There's... There's no signal here.
Aah! Argh!
Let me help you.
You've done enough.
Oh, come on,
you've never been good at this.
Just stop talking!
You're under arrest.
I need you to get off your feet.
You look like you're gonna faint.
Ravi, I can... I can explain.
I can explain everything.
You're going to.
- Can I help?
- DS Boyd.
Hart Valley Police.
I'm looking for a patient, Jack Graham.
- Er, Jack Graham.
- Oh, found his car, did you?
We did.
- He knows it was missing?
- Someone was in yesterday.
Showed him pictures. One of your lot.
- A police officer?
- Erm...
Detective, I think.
Did you get a name?
Don't remember.
I need to check your CCTV.
Hollingbrook Ward?
What sort of time are we talking?
10:00 am, thereabouts.
Uh-huh.
Oh, hello.
- Stop, stop, stop, stop. Go back.
- No, no.
You think that's who you're looking for?
I know it is.
You're not taking me home, are you?
If you were, we'd have
taken a right back there.
I meant what I said.
You can't pretend you don't believe me.
I know part of you does.
I know.
I believe that you believe it.
So I'm crazy. I'm losing my mind.
We can go crazy together.
What?
Seventeen dead.
Eleven children.
But you can't tell me where or when.
- It's too dangerous.
- What does that mean?
We can stop it.
But we need him
to go through with the plan.
We need to see his face,
it's the only way.
Fuck. Fuck! Fuck!
I do love you.
I don't know why.
But I do.
And I'm worried about you, Lucy.
I think you're gonna get hurt or...
or worse.
That's why I have to
take you to the station.
- No, you can't, Ravi!
- It's for the best.
Please. Look, just... Urgh!
Just look at me, look at me.
You know me. I know that you...
Ah!
- What is it? What's wrong?
- Just give me a s...
Unfortunately, lots of women
do miscarry in their first trimester.
I'm very sorry.
We don't always know the reason why.
It isn't something that you did
and that's important to understand.
The ultrasound shows no uterine damage
so there's no ongoing cause for concern.
I do realise this is
quite difficult to process,
so if you have any questions
I'll try my best to answer them.
Miss Chambers?
Is that it?
Sorry?
You said that.
Can I go now?
Lucy.
Erm, there's no reason
for you to stay here,
but if you would like to
stay a while longer...
No.
Thank you.
Could we...
have a minute?
Yeah. Of course.
You two, take care.
Talk to me.
You know we did IVF.
We what?
We tried for years.
Never worked.
You used to talk about your weak swimmers.
It just wasn't meant to be.
Neither was this. How could it be?
What kind of life would it have?
So it's good.
It's good that it's gone.
It's good that it's gone...
Amir.
If we had a boy,
I would have called him Amir.
What else do you remember?
I don't know what's happening to me.
I do. I do.
And I can make it make sense.
But for now...
you have to let me go.
I can't.
Is there a vending machine?
I really, really need something to eat.
I'll see what I can find.
Thank you.
Yeah?
I've been calling. Where've you been?
Out of range.
We need to talk about Lucy Chambers.
She's more involved in this
than we thought.
What do you have?
It's circumstantial but I think
it's enough to want a DNA test.
We found hair and blood
at Dunn's place, not his.
Ravi?
Ravi, are you still there?
Ravi?!
Okay.
Do what you have to do.
Call me when you find something.
- I have to go.
- Ravi, wait.
Ravi?
Just here, please.
Here you go.
It's out of a can but it's hot.
Best I can offer.
Where's Ravi?
I left him at the hospital.
Are you okay?
No.
But we're safe for now.
Lucy.
Mum?
- I am so sorry.
- Mum!
I couldn't get back to you.
I just couldn't.
But I am here now.
And I see you.
I see you.
I made Grandma better.
Yes, you did.
Nobody move.
Stay where you are.
Sam, what are you doing?
I followed you.
I don't know what's going on here,
but I need everyone to put
their hands on the table and...
Your wife's name is Danielle.
What?
You have a son called George.
He wants to be
a firefighter when he grows up
but he's actually
gonna be a graphic designer.
What are you talking about?
I know this is hard to believe
but I need you to remember.
I need you to understand.
Understand what?
- Stop!
- Sam, don't!
- Get off!
- Mum!
- No, no. No, no, no.
- Don't move!
Aagh! Aagh!
Aargh!
Get off!
Do not move!
Sam, you don't know
what you're doing! Please, stop!
You're insane!
Stay still. Just stay still!
You do not have to say anything,
but it may harm your defence...
Tie her up.