- Ed. No.
- Peggy, come here.
This is... You're so
outta line, Sheriff!
Peggy, Peggy!
- You can't just ruin people's lives!
- Peggy, Peggy.
You come back inside. No!
Parade them around Main Street
for something they didn't do!
Falsely accused. No.
Peggy.
No! You're not gonna prove
my Ed did anything wrong.
It's unprovable!
Heard about the fire.
- You okay?
- You didn't have to come down.
Mrs. Solverson. Ed.
I'm worried about you.
Feels like the top might just spin
right off the globe these days
and take you along with it.
What's that for?
I'm just imagining you parachuting
into the Mekong Delta,
telling the black pajamas
to leave your husband alone.
Shoulda.
Coulda saved a lotta lives if wives
and mothers from both sides came
and dragged their fool
men home by the ear.
Anything I can do
to help this mess?
Yeah, you can take
Noreen home with you.
Her place burned
down with the shop
and we both know
she's just a kid,
emancipated or not.
Noreen.
Hey, Ed.
I told 'em what you said.
Quiet now. Both of you.
Come home soon.
We both know that's not likely.
Come on, dear.
Let's get you
home and in a bath.
I'll make us some cocoa.
All right?
She's a nice lady. Shut up.
Time for your phone call.
Five minutes.
I was thinking about
Elron the other day.
Before?
His face, you know,
trying to remember...
I was 10 when they came.
Soldiers in uniform
with that folded-up flag.
You were in Chicago, I think.
Mom says.
There's that picture in the hall,
with you and all the kids,
that winter in Bear Lake.
Everyone else in coats,
but Elron's in a T-shirt,
making muscles.
And what would he
do now, you know?
Now, with this.
'Cause he was the oldest, right?
Not Dodd.
What?
Uncle. Charlie's on the phone.
I get it.
You don't have
respect for anything.
But do you know
what a whore's life is?
Come on now.
I'm serious. This is me
looking out for you.
Some career advice.
A whore's life is
five good years,
five bad years,
and then some
half-dick sweat stain
grinds you out like a cigarette.
Like a goddamn spent cigarette.
My son? You sent my goddamn son?
Jesus! Will you cut it out!
C'mon, Bear! Will somebody get him off me?
You better stop now.
Okay.
You've been asking for it for
days now, and now it's time.
Tell your man, "Walk
away," and we'll see.
You're getting the belt, kid.
Strap or buckle?
You think you're... Belt was
dad's thing, and you're not...
The kid said he was ready.
Said it should be family that
pulls the trigger, which is true.
He's 17.
He's got a crippled arm.
Now see, I don't see that.
I see heart and will.
I see spirit.
I see Grandpa
after the war. Right, Pop?
Grandpa, who stows away
on a boat,
comes to America
and builds an empire.
Compared to that, what
have you ever done?
Or me?
Arm or no arm?
Now, you can have
the strap or the buckle.
'Cause I can't have you
knocking me around,
not in front of the men.
Give me the buckle,
you piece of shit.
That's my boy.
No!
None of your bullshit!
Not today.
You'll kill us all, you
split this family apart!
Now tell me what happened.
Bring back my grandson.
No excuses.
I'll call up to Winnipeg,
tell 'em he's coming.
He can stay there
till things cool down.
And you, while he's
seeing to the boy,
you take care of this butcher.
He doesn't live
through the night.
Already dead, believe me.
He just doesn't know it.
This better be
state-secret-level information.
They all left.
Who all?
Dodd and Bear,
and maybe half a dozen...
Going?
He called me a whore.
Well, darling, technically...
It's my body.
I got every right to...
Of course you do.
We're in full agreement, you and me.
A beautiful body and you can
do what you want with it.
But right now
I need you to tell me,
your dad and the others,
where are they headed?
They're going to
that town in Minnesota.
Where the judge... Luverne.
Yeah, Luverne.
And I want you to...
You're gonna...
Get the hell outta here.
Did I lose
you there, sweetheart?
You're gonna kill him for me.
Your dad? He's not...
Ozzie was a dad.
On the TV, shit, Mr.
French is more of a...
How long ago did they leave?
Just... Maybe half an hour ago.
Took a whole army, almost.
Okay, baby.
Any last message for
your dad when I see him?
Yeah.
Tell him, "Kiss my grits."
"'Twas brillig,
and the slithy toves
"Did gyre and gimble in the wabe
"All mimsy were the borogoves
"And the mome raths outgrabe
"'Beware the Jabberwock, my son!
"'Thejaws that bite The claws that catch!
"'Beware the Jubjub bird and shun
the frumious Bandersnatch!'
"And as if in
uffish thought he stood
"The Jabberwock,
with eyes of flame
"Came whiff ling through the tulgey
wood And burbled as it came!
"One, two! One, two!
And through and through
"The vorpal blade
did snicker-snack!
"He left it dead,
and with its head
"He went galumphing back"
I got coffee from this morning.
I could heat it up.
Please.
I'm gonna move these, okay?
No! Actually, no, those are my.
. . No, no, put them down!
No problem.
I just got that organized.
So, you collect these then?
The beauty and travel mags?
No. Not collect.
I gotta stay up with the latest
trends, you know, in my line of work.
Well, that explains
the beauty mags.
Well, there's more to life
than Minnesota, you know.
Do you think, uh...
I know there's
a lot of questions,
but I got this seminar tomorrow.
Lifespring?
And I gotta drive up to Sioux
Falls first thing. So...
Um...
Well, now, I got five
dead since Saturday,
including the one tonight in
the burned-down butcher shop.
And your husband is
currently in jail,
so, I wouldn't count on
getting there early.
No, I mean, that's terrible,
but what can Ed... I mean...
Attempted robbery and those
two men at the shop...
It wasn't a robbery, Peggy.
Those men came for your husband.
They came to kill him.
You don't know that
for sure, Sheriff.
You're just trying to be dramatic.
Trying to scare me.
I assure you, I am not.
And when I say five dead,
I'm only talking about
inside the city limits.
Reports are 15 more bodies,
15 more bodies, up in Fargo.
This is a turf war between
the Kansas City mob
and this Gerhardt family you've
gotten yourself mixed up with.
Stop saying that!
Me and Ed,
we're just bystanders.
Not even. Disconnected.
Him with the shop, and me, just
trying to actualize fully, you know?
Be the best me I can be,
because these are
modern times, you know?
And a woman, well, she
just doesn't have to be
a wife and a mother no more.
She can be... There's
nothing she can't be.
You're a little touched,
aren't you?
What?
It's not that there's
anything wrong with that.
Don't get me wrong.
It's just the time and place
in which you're...
Well, you know, if you mean
I got dreams, then, yeah.
And maybe I don't see it all like
everybody else, but I got plans.
We got plans and you can't just
come in here and derail...
Yeah, Peggy.
They tried to kill your husband.
I mean, they burned
down his shop.
You think that's the end of it?
Well, I mean, look, right?
Ed, he really...
He loved that place.
But life's a journey, you know?
That's what
John Hanley Sr. says.
He's the founder of Lifespring.
Life's a journey, and the one
thing you don't do on a journey
is stay in one place, right?
So, maybe we'll, I don't
know, go to California or...
California... someplace.
Now that the shop's gone...
Peggy,
before you, uh, before you start
making plans, you should know
I got a forensic
team coming down
from the Twin Cities
in the morning.
And I know it's been repaired,
but we're gonna check
your car for blood.
Microscopically, I mean.
Which you'd be amazed
at what we can find
on the atomic level these days.
No. I mean, you can't
do that, of course,
without permission
from the owner.
You know? So... Oh, we got
permission about an hour ago.
You sold the car to Sonny
Greer, didn't you?
Earlier? At the body shop?
And Sonny now is
the owner on record.
And he was more than happy to.
. . No.
No, you can't. That's...
Hold on... Peggy. Peggy.
I'm serious now.
Better you tell me before I
get a fistful of evidence.
What happened that night when you
hit Rye Gerhardt with your car?
I'm the victim here.
Lou... Ed.
I mean, 'cause...
I sat in your living room last
night and gave you the chance,
you and Peggy both,
I gave you the chance to...
I know, but you
gotta understand.
We're just trying to... No, me.
I'm just trying to
protect my family.
There was a cleaver
in the man's head, son,
which Noreen said was you.
Not to mention
there's a war going on
up in Fargo that
you may have started
when you ran over that
Gerhardt boy in Peggy's car!
You or Peggy, or both!
This is all just so crazy.
And I can't stop thinking about
that book, Noreen's book.
It's, like, stuck in my head.
What?
What book?
It's about this
guy who, every day,
he pushes this
rock up this hill.
Like a boulder.
And then every night,
it just rolls back down.
But he doesn't stop, you know?
He just... He keeps going.
And he wakes up every day
and he starts pushing.
By which, I guess I'm saying,
it doesn't matter
what they throw at me,
I'm gonna take care
of what's mine. And...
These boys aren't gonna rest
until you're dead, son.
Possibly Peggy, too.
I want a lawyer.
Lou, I need one.
I'm asking you for one.
Ed, that's not... No,
I've seen the shows on TV.
No, you don't...
Ironside and...
This is all too important
to make mistakes here.
So, get me a lawyer, a good one,
and if he says, then I'll talk.
No, Sonny, they just called
themselves plumbers,
but what it was was a
special investigative unit
inside the White House...
Hey, Karl.
Percy. Got a customer for you.
A client, I guess you...
Over at the station.
Ed Blumquist?
Butcher's assistant?
I guess he's mixed up
in all the craziness.
You hear that, Sonny?
There's a crisis at the highest
level, so who do they call?
The best lawyer in town.
Aren't you the only
lawyer in town, Karl?
Yes, but that's because I scared
away all my...
Great Caesar's ghost.
It would appear I'm
a little unstable...
You okay there, Karl?
Want me to tell Lou
you need a few hours?
Fermez ton bouche, son.
I am sound in mind and body,
and ready to run circles
around the inferior minds
of the Rock County
Sheriff's Department.
Lou is a state cop, Karl.
Shut up, Sonny.
I will need you
to drive, however.
My question for you is,
how come after
you hit that fella
you didn't just
drive to the hospital?
Or wave down a passing motorist
and ask him to call the cops?
You say it like these
things happen in a vacuum.
Like it's a test. Check A or B.
But it's like decisions you
make in a dream, you know?
I'll tell you what, if it
was me and we had to run,
I wouldn't look back.
- For what? The dazzle?
- This house?
This is Ed's house.
He grew up here,
his mom washing his undies.
His father taking his paper
to the commode.
You ask me how come
I buy all these magazines?
I'm living in
a museum of the past.
Okay.
You stay here.
Sheriff? Go inside now, Peggy.
If you got a hiding place in the
basement or the attic, go to that.
What about you? Go, now.
And don't come out,
no matter what you hear.
Hi.
Hello.
Help you fellas with something?
Hope so.
Ed home?
Ed who?
Oh.
Ed. Yeah.
Yeah.
Yeah, you just missed him.
A whole squad took him to the
station about an hour ago.
And that's the well-guarded
and impenetrable police
station on Hazel Lane
which, don't let the name
fool you, is a fortress.
Or maybe he's inside
and you think I'm stupid.
Son,
I could fill a steamer trunk with the
amount of stupid I think you are.
But, no, that's where he went.
Yeah, that's what I thought.
Here we go.
No, Peggy, hey, hey...
Said the butcher's
down at the precinct.
Could be bullshit,
take Polk and Carter.
I'll clean up here.
All clear upstairs!
Here, kitty, kitty.
Come on, kitty.
Kitty.
Here, kitty, kitty.
Shut up.
Shut up, you fool.
Shit.
When I find you, darling,
I'm gonna make you bleed.
Bitch!
Hon.
Yeah? Don't leave.
Wanna talk to you
about something.
Are you with us?
When you say "us..."
I mean the family. All of it.
You don't get to
pick and choose.
Sure, Grandma.
We all got a role to play.
You need to take my example.
Be a leader.
This is our time.
No such thing as men's work,
women's work anymore.
We got just as much right to...
Keep it running, Sonny.
I'll be back before
the beer goes warm.
Greetings and salutations.
I have made the pilgrimage
from the Hall of Veterans,
as George Washington
once forded the Delaware,
steely in my resolve,
prepared to battle
unto my dying breath
for the rights...
Lawyer's here. Hey, Denise.
For the rights of free men!
Hey, Karl, Ed's in back.
Rights that were squeezed
from British oppression
like water from a stone!
That all men are created equal,
free from the jackboot tyranny
and gulag magic tricks
of nameless,
faceless committees.
Hey, hope they didn't wake you.
Out of my way,
tool of the state.
For I have come to comfort
and counsel my client
even as you seek to prison him!
Yeah, whatever you're gonna
do, you got 30 minutes.
Don't dictate terms
to me, you rogue.
For the law is
a light on a hill,
calling to its breast all
those in search of justice.
To wit, this poor, mottled
wretch in front of me.
Hey, Karl.
Edward.
What a sad and fortuitous day.
You chained to
that table and me...
No, I'm not in cuffs.
Chained in thought
if not action.
At the mercy of
a cold and venal...
I didn't do this thing...
No, no, don't tell me.
The establishment has ears
everywhere, even here.
Ears?
Instead I shall
simply ask, "G or NG,"
and you, my client,
will shake your head
in the affirmative
for the letter or letters that
best describes your status.
So, I shake my head "yes"?
Let's say, for the purposes of the
cameras that are no doubt watching,
that a negative shake,
side to side,
shall in this case be
a positive affirmation.
Remember, only shake once.
G?
Or NG?
Well, son, rest assured,
whatever your status, I shall
defend you till your last breath.
I mean, my last breath.
Excuse the obvious
death penalty snafu.
I'm slightly inebriated.
Still got 26 minutes.
And that, by no
strange coincidence,
is the amount of
time it'll take me
to rouse Judge
Peabody from his bed
and have him dismiss
these unfounded charges.
No charges as of yet.
Held without charges!
Even better.
Then I shall have to tell His Honor
to boost my client from these
baseless restraints you've
shackled him under! Whoa!
Hey, you're not driving,
are you?
My choices outside this
building are none of your...
But, no, Sonny valeted
me here tonight.
But now,
now I must bid you all adieu
and admonish you to watch
your proverbial butts,
for I shall be back with the
sledgehammer of justice,
prepared to lay Joseph waste
to these four walls,
if you so much as
touch a hair on my client's...
Karl?
The jackboots are upon us.
Deputy Bluth, I need you
to lock the back door.
Do it now.
Garfield, kill the
lights in back.
Denise, get on the horn to HQ.
Tell 'em we need every man
available yesterday.
There's a lynching
party outside.
Shouldn't call
the sheriff first?
Well, you can try, but somehow
I don't think he'll answer.
If he does, tell him not
to do anything heroic
until reinforcements arrive.
You okay there, counselor?
It's possible I soiled myself.
Here for my boy.
Doesn't have to get any
more complicated than that.
Met you before. At the compound.
So you know.
Already called for
backup on the radio.
Nobody's coming.
No, they'll come.
State police up in Marshall or sheriff
out of Nobles, 30, 40 minutes.
Maybe we got a trap set.
That's possible.
Just gonna keep coming, though.
After Wounded Knee?
Hell, the governor may send
in the National Guard.
Now, we got your son
on attempted murder.
Took a shot at the local butcher.
The place burned down.
Where's that butcher now?
No.
I know you got designs on him.
He inside?
He's safe, guarded by armed men.
No.
No, he's not.
This kinda thing
didn't work in Westerns
and it's not gonna work tonight.
We got enough men and guns
to hold you off till morning.
Maybe I got a trunk
full of dynamite,
blow my way in.
Either way, you got less than five
minutes to send my Charlie out.
Who's this Charlie now?
Karl, I'm serious, I need
you to sit over there
and stay out of the way.
Deputy, how we doing securing
the back of the building?
Well, I mean, I locked the door.
Well, let's barricade
that, yeah?
Shades down on all the windows.
We got any light bulbs?
Light bulbs?
I want you to take
all the light bulbs we got,
smash 'em up by the
back doors and windows.
That way we can hear 'em
if they try to sneak in.
Oh. That's good thinking.
Need your help here.
I thought you had backup coming.
Closest men are outside
Nobles, an hour away.
Plus, you're talking
about farm boys
who've never been face-to-face
with a serious man before.
Whereas I stared
down Chiang Kai-shek.
That, and I need someone who can
talk some sense into the father.
Who better than
his son's lawyer?
Don't represent the son, though.
You do now, Karl.
Lou?
I'm walking you out of here.
Am I released then?
Well, let's call it
that for simplicity.
Truth is, there's a
lynch mob outside
wanting to string you up.
What are you...
Come on.
Stay close and be ready to run.
Sheriff, come in.
Sheriff?
Come in. Sheriff?
Sheriff, there's a calamity up here.
If you're there, pick up.
Yeah, Denise. I'm here.
Oh, Sheriff, thank God! There's
an army of men outside.
They want Ed Blumquist
and that kid from the fire.
Lou's got this plan to...
Told me to tell you not to
come till reinforcements arrive,
which, sheriff's
deputies are on their way
from Nobles,
so maybe 45 minutes, sir.
Yeah, okay. Uh...
Tell Lou to sit tight.
Can't have him getting
killed without me.
Never hear the end
of it at dinner.
Maybe they forgot we're here.
Yeah.
Gear up. We're going in.
Hold on now. We're allies.
Like Ho Chi Minh
and the Red Chinese.
Arms in the air.
Karl Weathers.
That's my name.
I'm your son's attorney.
Don't need a lawyer.
He's going home tonight.
Send him out. I'm done playing.
Yes, sir.
That's in the works as we...
You mind if I...
As your son's man,
I spoke with the constabulary
at the highest level,
and they're prepared to
meet your demands.
Send the boy out.
Processing him now.
But as his lawyer...
Don't need no lawyer,
I told you.
As his lawyer, I gotta advise you
of something, which is this.
You're making it worse.
He's a minor, see? Only 17.
So, reduced sentencing applies.
Shh.
And, yes, witness
puts a gun in his hand
with a shot fired,
but it's a miss.
You understand?
A miss, so even if they convict
him, it's attempted at best.
The maximum is 10 years, he's
out in five for good behavior.
Done.
But this,
you take him outta here now and
he's running the rest of his life.
A wanted fugitive,
shoot on sight.
But there's a way out.
Leave now,
take your men, and none
of this falls on the kid.
This is the deal I made.
He stays clean.
But you gotta go. Now.
Maybe we leave Charlie,
just take the butcher.
Well, now, that's a problem.
See, any movement there
and they loop the kid in,
make him an accomplice.
Kidnapping, conspiracy
to commit murder,
assaulting a police officer,
or worse.
So, we're back to
the best thing for the kid
being a fast
retreat on your part.
That's the clearest path
of victory for you.
Think about it.
He's only 17.
Let's go.
I need to find Peggy.
Can't do that, Ed.
Not right now.
You're still in my custody.
Yeah, but what if
they came to the house?
I mean, they went
to the station,
what if they came to the.
. . Shh.
Come on.
Christ, man.
You look worse than me.
Smell better maybe.
No, don't tire yourself.
We know where he's headed.
Maybe you drive.
I'm seeing double.
I am a man of constant sorrow
I've seen trouble all my days
I'm talking about
the camaraderie of men, kid.
That hard-to-define male bond,
born in the age of the Neanderthal
when men still hunted mastodon
with flint and spears.
The place where he
was born and raised
For six long years, oh,
I've been in trouble
I'm saying you find that in
wartime, that foxhole brotherhood.
Then when you come back,
well, there's no civilian
equivalent, not in peacetime.
...to help me now
He has no friends
to help him now
So it's fare thee well to you,
my old true lover
I never expect to see you again
You sure know
a lot of words, Karl.
I'm an esquire, kid.
A barrister.
Defender of the common man,
the misaccused.