Where were you?
I'm drowning out here.
Sorry.
Two short stacks.
Let me get you guys
some more syrup.
- Enjoying the show?
- Best seat in the house.
What are you doing?
I'll catch you later.
Hey.
So when are we gonna stop
driving separate cars to work?
As soon as we stop living
at separate addresses.
- I mean...
- Right.
I'm not pushing for that.
No.
It's okay.
You can push a little.
- Oh, really?
- Yeah, just a little.
Can I help you?
My name is Kurt Bunker, sir.
I'm here to apply for
the open deputy position.
Seriously?
I understand that my physical
appearance may be unsettling,
but I can assure you my ties to the
movement were severed long ago.
Unfortunately,
the removal of my tattoos
has taken longer
than anticipated.
Dade County
Sheriff's Department.
- You're a long way from Florida.
- I was born in Banshee.
Just became prudent for me
to distance myself
from former associates.
Then why are you back?
It was time to come home, ma'am.
What do your former
associates think about that?
What they think
is none of my concern.
Sorry, Bunker.
Position's filled.
You can hold onto that.
I appreciate your time.
Was that for real?
I kind of liked him.
- Mr. Cage.
- Mr. Proctor.
- How are you, Kai?
- Good. Thanks for coming.
I couldn't turn down an
invitation from an old friend.
Who is this pretty young thing?
Oh, that's Rebecca
Bowman, my niece.
I'm introducing her
to the family business.
Proctor pulled the kid out of high
school for a little show-and-tell.
Martin, watch your mouth.
Show a little respect.
Sorry, Kai.
So what was it you wanted
to see me about?
Well, old friend, we need
to clarify our arrangement.
What arrangement is that?
While my factory
was down for three weeks,
you began supplying
my Philadelphia customers.
I understand the impulse.
You saw an opportunity.
But I'm up
and running again now,
so we got to go back to
things as they were before.
I stay out of Ohio and you
stay out of Pennsylvania.
You couldn't supply them,
they came to me.
Plain and simple.
Just business.
You fucked up, Proctor. You
don't get to take that back.
What did you just say?
Your uncle may be
a big deal here in Banshee,
but in the rest of the world,
he's just a country inbreed
with an inflated ego.
- Martin, shut your mouth.
- I got it, Dad.
Yeah, I heard you were
a scary dude back in the day,
but he doesn't look
so scary now, does he?
Martin, shut...
Rebecca, no!
Ah!
Finish what you started.
No. No.
Just got off the phone
with Sperling.
Proctor will plead to a single
misdemeanor weapons charge
in exchange for time served.
- I told him to go to hell.
- Yeah, we'll make the deal.
What?
Call Sperling back
and tell him that we'll...
I heard what you said.
Then why are
we still talking about it?
We've got a shot at putting
Proctor away
and you just want to roll over
and play dead.
No, I'm done fighting
battles I won't win.
Are you still on the pills?
No, I'm clean.
So, I...
I get to experience every single
moment with total clarity.
Look, if you'll excuse
me, I need to...
I need to get back
to being the mayor.
What does that entail, exactly?
I'll let you know
when I figure it out.
Thanks.
Bad enough you got us
robbing a military base,
now we got to worry about all these
motherfucking Rambos
killing our asses.
You know, the colonel's got the
Marines guarding the money.
What the hell does
he need the mercs for?
'Cause it ain't Uncle Sam's
cash they're protecting.
Turns out not everything is
kosher at Boy Scout camp.
The official log accounts for
nine million in that safe.
What about the unofficial log?
That's saying closer to 15.
Someone's cooking the books.
Not just someone.
Colonel Douglas Stowe.
Naval Academy grad,
first in his class.
Tours in Beirut,
Panama, and then Haiti.
After that, he took a little
walk on the wild side.
We're talking about a
string of nasty black ops
in Iraq and Afghanistan.
This ain't just another
bad motherfucker,
this the guy they send in to clean
out all the other bad motherfuckers.
On the other hand,
you steal from a thief...
no one calls the cops.
The cops won't come after us with
hit teams and Apache helicopters.
You are not welcome here.
Kai.
I have to speak with my mother.
You did not have to come.
You have a fever.
It's just a touch of the flu.
Here, drink some water.
How can you allow this to go on?
The doctor was here.
He gave her medicine.
She doesn't need a house call.
She needs a hospital.
He will be here again tomorrow.
We will ask him.
But that's not good enough.
- Leave her!
- Oh, Kai.
Get out of my way.
We can take care of her here.
Your mother is suffering from
advanced pancreatic cancer.
How much time, Doctor?
A month, maybe less.
I'm going to put
you down, Mother.
- Can you stand?
- Yeah.
Your mother is dying,
Mr. Proctor.
You should start thinking about how
you can make her most comfortable.
- Hey.
- Hey. You okay?
Before you answer that...
Don't.
Stop.
Stop!
I can't do this anymore.
Do I get an explanation?
Does it really matter?
- Your husband?
- No.
- Somebody else?
- There's no time for anyone else.
There isn't even time for this.
Then what's the problem?
My kids.
They need their mother at home,
not sneaking out at night
for booty calls.
This isn't about your kids.
It's about you.
Don't do that.
This is a bubble.
This isn't anything.
What we had was great,
but I've got to get back
to the real world.
Take care of yourself, okay?
All right.
You really like...
...your military men.
What are you doing here?
I was gonna ask you
the same thing.
Who I fuck is none
of your business.
It is when it affects the job.
And how about you getting involved
with your deputy sheriff?
How does that affect the job?
We can't do the heist if you're
involved with the target.
I already broke it off.
Are we done?
Should I be worried?
I told you I'd be ready.
I'm not talking about the job.
I gotta get home.
Hold your fire!
Adolf Hitler's favorite game
was cowboys and Indians.
He called the Russians redskins
and found inspiration
in the white man's
ethnic cleansing
of our Navajo kin.
Now, Proctor has
slaughtered our chief
and continues to take
what is rightfully ours.
Viho, Songaa.
Go get Proctor and the girl.
Bring them back here.
Hey.
I should be the one
getting Proctor.
Not now.
I've got other plans for you.
Chayton.
Everyone here thinks I get a free
ride 'cause I'm your brother.
I need to show them.
You need to be patient.
Alison.
I need your signature
on the plea deal
before I can file.
Come in.
I included
a future crime clause.
If Proctor gets so much
as a speeding ticket,
we can revoke the plea deal
and reopen the case.
Can I pour you a drink?
- I'm fine.
- All right.
Suit yourself.
I like the new apartment.
Yeah, you know, for a lawyer,
you're a pretty shitty liar.
Well, you have to at least
put in some effort.
Set up the kids' rooms.
Hang pictures.
Start cooking in the kitchen
so it smells like home.
Yeah. You cook?
I dabble.
Why don't you stick
around and teach me?
Gordon, I know you've
been through the wringer,
but you've got
to get it together.
- That was out of line.
- You think?
Alison, look,
you don't have to go.
I respect you too much to watch
you embarrass yourself like this.
Nola?
You know, I thought
you'd gone native, but this...
this is a whole new level.
- I'm glad you like it.
- I'm glad you think I like it.
I wondered if you'd come back.
I wondered the same thing.
Every time I think I'm rid
of this goddamn place...
- This place is your home.
- It's your home!
It's not mine.
You are a Kinaho woman.
Fat lot of good that did me
growing up here.
I know you suffered
greatly back then.
You think you know.
- Nola.
- What?
Let me die.
We already had this
conversation in New Orleans.
Can we not do it again?
You're already dead.
I'm very sorry
about your brother.
- You despised Alex.
- I pitied him.
He forgot who he was,
but his murder
was a tragedy
and we will avenge it.
By sending a couple of
gangbangers to Proctor's house?
They can handle it.
Alex is dead because
he underestimated Proctor.
With all clue respect,
I am not Alex.
No.
No, you're not.
Alex never liked you. He thought
you were bad for the tribe.
I am the tribe.
Yeah, I really don't care.
Nola.
Don't get in my way.
He was my brother, Chayton.
And you will have your blood.
- When you say?
- Yes.
No.
There's an old steam tunnel
buried underneath the base.
It's like our own
personal VIP entrance.
We're in.
Okay, now y'all
be careful down there.
You know, snakes and whatnot.
After you.
Just like old times.
So how we doing
with the vault?
Based on your description,
it has to be a JT-3000
custom-built in Virginia.
- How many locks?
- Two.
One mechanical,
the other digital.
If we get past the
rolling encryption code,
I'll have to drill through six
inches of reinforced steel
to disable the tumbler system.
Job can handle
the encryption code.
- It changes every 12 minutes.
- We'll have to work fast, then.
- And by we, you mean me.
- Yep.
- You wanted to see me, sir?
- Sit.
My unit was point for
black ops in Afghanistan.
Asset recovery, bag grabs,
the dirty stuff.
One night we came under fire.
Not just a couple of
insurgents with small arms,
dozens of them
all armed to the teeth.
Someone had tipped them off.
I called for air support,
but it never came.
President's troop reductions
meant less support
for soldiers
still on the ground.
Murphy and I were the
only ones to make it out.
The powers that be
let seven good men,
patriots, die for politics.
That's why I only trust
my people.
This was found beneath a
floorboard under your bunk.
It's not mine.
You're an idiot, Haddock.
I could have made you rich,
and you blew it, for what?
- Thirty grand?
- Sir, I swear...
Did I tell you to stand?
Lock him in the brig.
Seems too easy.
Maybe Stowe doesn't
know about the tunnel.
He knows.
We got a solid steel
door blocking us.
How thick?
About 12 inches.
- Shape charges?
- Now you're talking my language.
Now, hold on. If those walls
are not properly reinforced,
your language will bring down
the whole damn tunnel.
What do you suggest?
Look, I'll pull the door
off the hinges
the old-fashioned way.
Like you got any other
motherfucking way.
Checking in.
All rooms secure.
Go find Proctor.
I'm starving.
There's some shepherd's pie
in the fridge.
Ooh, beef or turkey?
I stopped eating red meat.
You should, too.
Yeah, that's not gonna happen.
You know what?
I'll make us something to eat.
I'll make us some sandwiches.
You got some lunch meat?
Some cold cuts?
Brock, what's
your current location? Over.
Don't. She'll find somebody else.
I'm still on duty.
Give it to me.
- Just let it...
- Come on, give it to me.
- I'm not messing around, Em.
- Come on.
Damn it!
Uh...
Yeah, this is Brock.
Go ahead, Alma.
We got a call of a disturbance
at the Proctor place.
Casualties reported.
Copy that.
I'm on my way.
Job still comes first, huh?
- Come on.
- Just like the old days.
Em.
What do you want from me?
I want you to leave.
You know what?
You're in luck.
I need pictures of everything.
Tell her to keep it
in focus this time.
I can hear you, Job.
Oh, I know.
Hold on one second.
- Hood.
- Hey, it's Brock.
Look, we got a DOA
in Proctor's pool.
Redbone. Looks like he and his buddy
roughed up the niece pretty bad.
I'm on my way.
I gotta go.
Fuck, you mean
you gotta go?
I'm still on duty.
Ana will finish up down here.
Baby, this whole
fake sheriff bullshit
is getting in the way
of your real job.
- You hear me?
- Hard not to.
You all right?
Hey, Brock.
Give us a minute.
Sheriff.
You started this war when
you took out Longshadow.
Yeah, well, you would know
about starting wars, Sheriff.
Chayton's not gonna
stop coming for you.
That's unfortunate for Chayton
and anyone else
- who comes after what's mine.
- Okay, let me be clear.
You and the Redbones
can tear each other apart.
I don't give a shit.
Just hurry the fuck up.
My house was violated
by these lowlifes.
You do your job, Sheriff.
Hey, Raven.
Come here.
You know the reservation.
Where do we start?
We can't just go
to the reservation.
Yeah, we can.
I do it all the time.
This is it?
Yep, Dog Iron.
A lot of Redbones hang out here.
Drinks are cheap
and nobody bothers them.
Hmm. Well, let's see
what we can do about that.
Can we get a couple of drinks?
Sure, three miles down the road.
Hey, Sue.
Billy, you know better than to
show up here in that uniform.
Then just tell me
if you've seen Chayton.
- Get the hell out of here.
- People are getting hurt.
Our people.
All I know is that they're
deep in the woods.
Whereabouts in the woods?
- You gotta go.
- Yo, Raven.
Thanks for your time.
What do you think
your old man would say
if he knew you were taking
orders from the white man?
- Move, Spatch.
- Or what?
You sure that's how
you want to play this?
Your, uh, badge...
...don't mean shit
around here.
Well, the badge is the last
thing you should worry about.
How's that?
Sit the fuck down.
How about we all
put our dicks away?
It's good to see
you, too, Aimee.
What the hell, Billy?
The hospice nurse is here.
- Mr. Proctor.
- Ms. Lotus.
Thank you for coming
on such short notice.
You came highly
recommended, you know.
Please, call me Emily.
All right, Emily.
Why don't you make
yourself at home here?
And anything you need, just ask.
Why don't you start by
introducing me to your mother?
This is Leah, my mother,
and Rebecca, my niece.
It's a pleasure
to meet you both.
Emily will be staying
with us, Mother,
to help care for you.
What happened to you?
I had an accident.
Well, have you put
anything on those cuts?
No.
Here. It'll help keep you
from scarring.
- You've got great skin.
- Thank you.
Let me show you to your room.
Notie and Spatch
were looking for a fight.
You were looking for a fight.
What are you thinking going to
the Dog Iron in a BSD uniform?
- He was following me.
- I wasn't talking to you.
We're looking for
Chayton Littlestone.
- You know him?
- Is he serious?
- We're on the same side here.
- Get off the res, Billy.
If Yaz finds out
that you're out here...
Whoa, whoa, whoa.
Who's Yaz?
Karl Yazzie.
Chief of the Kinaho PD.
Sounds like someone
I should meet.
Let's go. I'll take you.
No, you should probably
get in your car
and drive away if you know
what's good for you.
Do I look like someone who
knows what's good for him?
Chief.
You must have made
a wrong turn, boy.
This is the Kinaho
Police Department.
- And who do we have here?
- Sheriff Lucas Hood.
You busted that fat bastard
that killed the Cleary girl.
I'm surprised
you know about that,
seeing as you didn't
lift a finger to help.
Happened on your beat, not mine.
I stay on my side of the line.
Okay, well, Chayton
and the Redbones,
they hijacked a truck
from Camp Genoa.
Stole about a dozen crates
of AKs and M4s.
- What? When?
- Sounds like a military issue.
Not if the guns end up in Banshee.
Sorry, I can't tell you where
the man is if I don't know.
But we'll keep an eye out for him.
You'll keep an eye out?
None of your business, huh?
- Let's go.
- Oh, one other thing, Sheriff.
- Yeah?
- I call you sheriff as a courtesy,
even though out here
you've got no standing.
The next time you pull
some shit like you did today,
I'm gonna have BIA
crawling all over your ass.
You mind your own backyard
and we'll mind ours.
Billy.
That goes for you, too.
So Yaz is dirty?
No.
That would actually
require ambition.
Yazzie gave up on that
a long time ago.
Between the tribal council
and the Redbones,
he's everyone's bitch.
- What about the girl?
- Aimee? She's the real deal.
She just wants to make a difference.
She doesn't like you much.
Yeah, she feels I abandoned her.
She's not wrong.
But I had to get my family out.
You got kids?
Yeah, two little girls.
Rachel and Kim.
You?
No. No kids.
Jenny.
Mr. Mayor.
Living room or bedroom?
I think I'm gonna...
I'm really tired. I...
I bet I can wake you up.
No, Jenny.
Look, I shouldn't have called you.
For your trouble.
Try again tomorrow?
No, I think this is the
end of the road for us.
Well, if you change your mind,
you know where you can find me.
Kitchen's closed, men.
That's all right.
We already ate.
I would think after a guy like you
got his ass kicked by a woman,
the last thing he'd want to do
is bring his friends over
to watch it happen again.
You got a smart mouth
on you, bitch.
So I hear.
I'm gonna shut it for you
tonight permanently.
Listen,
it's been a long day
and I'm all out of repartee.
So if you came here
to fight, quit whining
like a little girl
and get right down to it.
- What's going on here?
- Get lost, Pocahontas.
- Ain't none of your business.
- Normally, I'd agree.
But if you're messing
with the only person
who can serve me
some of that apple pie,
then I'm afraid it is my concern.
I'll give you three seconds to
walk your pretty little ass
out that door before I...
Don't talk about my ass.
So, how about that pie?
You got it.
- You're Alex Longshadow's sister.
- Nola.
And you're the New York
mobster's daughter.
Carrie.
Sorry about your brother.
Sorry about your life.
Those are nice.
What are they, Glocks?
Modified 17Cs.
Cycle at 1,200 rounds
per minute.
Mm.
More of a Springfield girl myself.
Different strokes.
That's a great pie.
They bake it here?
I should know
the answer to that.
I don't.
I do know where
they keep the Scotch.
Sins of the fathers.
Amen.
Hey.
Hi.
I, um, thought we could hang out.
You shouldn't really be here.
Don't you have school?
- Yeah.
Okay, so then after school?
- I can come by the Cadi.
- No, Deva...
- Don't you want to get to know me?
- Yes.
Then why won't you?
Look, I know this
is confusing for you,
but Gordon raised you,
he loves you,
he's your father.
And what about you?
You told me you stayed
in Banshee because of me.
I had to make sure
you were okay.
I'm not.
Fuck!
Get down!