What are you thinking about?
I was thinking about something
someone said to me the other day.
I mean, you get used to
a certain way of being.
And...
...you think we are who we are
or you think we can change?
What, you mean people like you?
Well, me, you, people in general.
I don't know if anyone
ever changes really...
...but we can evolve, right?
I mean, that's what
we're trying to do, isn't it?
Just become...
better versions of ourselves.
Get down!
Hood!
Shh.
Medicine will help with the pain.
Kai.
Forgive me, Kai.
If I had only been stronger...
...I could have saved you.
Could have saved us both.
Kai, where are you?
It's Emily.
You need to come home now.
Stay down.
- Where are you going?
- Can't let them get inside.
- Alma, you good?
- I think so.
All right, stay down.
Alma, get on the radio.
- Radio's fried.
- Try the landline.
The phones are dead.
And they're jamming cells, too.
Keep trying.
Hood! Hood!
- Hey, you okay?
- Yeah, yeah, I'm fine.
- Raven?
- All good.
- Good.
- Everyone else okay?
- Yeah.
- Okay?
- Siobhan, you okay?
- I'm okay.
No blood. No blood.
You okay?
I... understand that my physical
appearance may be unsettling, but...
...never mind.
Who the hell was that?
I thought he was with you.
- Sheriff, get me out.
- Shut the fuck up.
Lock and load. Regroup.
Next one, move!
Gather the weapons.
- Brock.
- See if we can get you some water.
Yeah?
Get me out
of this goddamn cage right now!
Shut up, Proctor.
If you haven't noticed,
we got a bit of a situation.
I have no cover in here!
You've got
the same cover we all have.
If I wanted to get in here,
those gates wouldn't stop me.
Well, it's a good thing
you're already in here.
Hey, it's the Redbones.
They're spread out in the parking lot
and across the street.
We just need to hold them off
till the state police get here.
No, they're not coming.
Phones are down.
- Cells, too?
- Yeah.
Oh, shit.
All right...
so we're basically on our own
against a homicidal maniac
and a dozen thugs armed
like a platoon.
- That about sums it up.
- What the fuck do they want?
I don't know, but whatever it is,
we're not gonna like it.
They want me.
I killed Tommy.
I don't give a fuck what
Chayton wants. He's not getting it.
Raven, Siobhan, get these civilians
down to the basement.
Okay, folks. Come with us.
We're gonna take you
someplace safe.
You all right?
Yeah, I'm fine.
What the hell's
going on out there?
I'm guessing
these gates threw 'em
and they're regrouping,
figuring out their next move.
What's our next move?
I don't know how long
those gates are gonna last.
We need more firepower.
Go down to the armory,
get everything you can.
Is this enough?
I hope you don't mind, Sheriff,
I took some initiative.
Figured there was
no time to waste.
You're the guy who gave me
your resume, right?
Dade County
Sheriff's Department.
Yes, sir. Kurt Bunker.
How the hell did you get
into our gun locker, Bunker?
I smashed the lock.
- You're hired.
- What?
- Thank you, sir.
- Get those guns handed out.
- Serious... Hood.
- What?
- What about Mr. Proctor?
- What about him?
Keeping him in that cell is
a violation of his civil liberties.
Couldn't happen to a nicer guy.
Sheriff, are you gonna
let him out or not?
- Not.
- Okay, so the sheriff is willfully
endangering the life of my client.
You're an officer of the court.
Do something.
This is a war zone, Counselor.
Due process just got blown up.
Hey, Sperling, I got an idea.
Why don't you go down
to the basement?
I'm not fucking going anywhere
without Mr. Proctor.
Okay, Bunker, give him a gun.
What? Why?
Time to make yourself useful.
I don't know how to shoot that thing.
Well, neither do I,
but it's not gonna stop me.
Ma'am, that gun
packs a powerful kick.
Are you gonna stand there like
a total misogynist and patronize me,
or are you gonna show me
how to shoot the damn thing?
Thank you. I just felt married again.
All right, here we go.
Magazine goes
right in here, all right?
Make sure the safety is off.
One in the chamber.
And just point, squeeze.
Repeat as necessary.
Hood, the basement.
What about it?
The exterior doors
don't have gates on them.
Bunker, through the range
down the stairs.
I'm on it. Sir.
Alison, you go with him.
I'm not going anywhere
with that guy.
With all due respect, ma'am,
I understand my physical appearance
may be alarming...
Save it. I've known men like you.
- I know everything about you.
- Hey, you wanted to help people.
There's people down there
who need your help.
Then let the Nazi calm them down.
I'm asking you.
Fine.
But keep your distance.
And I am new with this thing,
so it might just accidently go off.
- Fair enough?
- Yes, sir.
Citizens are secured
in the basement.
What do we do now?
All right, spread out, settle in.
You shoot anything
that comes through those gates.
Hood!
I'm listening.
You've got Billy Raven
and Proctor in there.
Send them both out
with Nas and Tate,
and we'll spare the rest of you.
- Let me think about it.
- You got two minutes.
Sheriff, you are not
seriously considering
handing Mr. Proctor over
to that psychopath?
Relax, Jackson.
I'm sure the sheriff hasn't forgotten
a night much like this one
where he would have died
if not for my intervention.
Huh, Sheriff?
Hey, Chayton.
- Can't do it.
- You won't get another chance.
Is that right?
Tell you what.
You leave now, I let you live.
We are coming in there, cop.
Maybe, but if you do,
more Redbones are gonna die.
Wasn't your little brother enough?
Shut your mouth, white boy.
You know, you really
should have protected him more.
I'm gonna make you suffer.
Hey, Chayton.
Fuck off.
If those gates come down,
we won't last long.
How much ammo we got left?
Not enough.
Sheriff, let me talk to Chayton.
He doesn't want
to talk to you, Billy.
- He wants to kill you.
- I could end this.
What, by sacrificing yourself?
- It's tribal justice.
- No, bullshit is what it is.
We go down, we go down together.
Well, this sucks.
- Who needs a light? Siobhan?
- I got one in my drawer.
- Billy? You got it?
- Got it.
- Hey, Brock!
- Here, take it. Go.
Where's the emergency lights?
- We don't have emergency lights.
- Perfect.
- Fuck. Stay down.
- Shit.
You're wasting your time.
At some point
Chayton is gonna wise up
and he's gonna pull
those gates off the hinges.
And then he's gonna
eat you alive.
I could always send you
out there as an appetizer.
Yeah.
Well, I'd rather fight
for my life out there
than wait in the dark
to die like the rest of you.
He's got a point.
- Hood, listen.
- Yeah?
There's a backup
generator in the basement.
Won't power everything,
but it'll buy us some light.
- I'll go.
- Okay.
- Who's there?
- Siobhan.
They took out the lights.
They're trying to mess
with our heads.
Well, it's working.
All right, listen.
Someone heard that gunfire.
Okay? So the state police,
they're on the way.
Till they get here, I need you
to hang tight. Can you do that?
Good.
Siobhan, take care
of that generator.
- All quiet?
- So far, sir.
You always so polite?
Only when I'm nervous.
- Hang in there, Bunker.
- Yes, sir.
- Oh, shit.
- Out of gas?
Almost. Here, hold this.
God damn it.
- Here, let me try.
- No, I got it.
- Come on.
- I said I got it!
This fucking day
just keeps getting worse.
How do you think I feel?
I was about to retire.
You're an asshole.
Yeah.
You don't even know
what you're doing here.
You're not even a cop.
No, I'm not.
Then why the fuck
are we all listening to you?
You know what?
You're right.
But I've been
in tighter spots than this...
...and I'm still here.
So I need you to trust me.
Ha! Do you have any idea
how ridiculous that sounds?
Yes.
I don't want to die tonight.
You're not going to.
We're all walking
out of this together.
Let's try it again.
Oh, thank God.
This isn't the first time
this has happened, you know?
I mean, one army of guys with
machine guns would be bad enough.
But two?
I mean, that's just...
Bad luck?
No, it's something else.
- Jesus. Hey.
- Hey.
- Here.
- Thank you.
Thanks.
It's so quiet in here.
You think they left?
Chayton's not going anywhere.
- Not till he gets what he wants.
- No, they'll make a move soon.
Wish I had...
Sperling!
What the hell are you doing?
I'm getting my client
out of harm's way.
Give me the keys, Jackson.
- Blow me.
- Get down!
- Shit!
- Give me the fucking keys, Jackson.
- Fuck off, Alison.
- Give me the fucking keys!
Al! Al!
Hey, hey.
Come on. Come on.
Where's Raven?
- Brock, where's Raven?
- In there.
- Raven!
- Yeah?
Cover me!
- Down! Down!
- Come on, move! Take cover!
Let's get this hole covered up.
Where's Proctor?
Apparently his lawyer
got him an early release.
- What?
- Help me. Help me.
Come on.
Those aren't gonna
hold them off for long.
No, but it's better than nothing.
- What is that?
- I don't know. Stay here.
Hook it up.
Let's do it.
We gonna have a problem?
No, not tonight.
As we forgive those
who trespass against us.
And lead us not into temptation.
But deliver us from evil.
Thine is the kingdom.
The power and the glory.
Forever and ever.
Amen.
Go! Go!
- Stand clear!
- Move! Move!
Put it out!
I can feel you looking at me.
- Are you okay?
- I'm fine. Don't worry about it.
I'm not who you think I am.
Oh, really? Right.
- I guess you've changed.
- Yes.
People don't change.
When I was 16, I watched
my father beaten into a coma
by two men who looked
just like you.
Do you have any idea
what that feels like?
To watch your father
helpless and bleeding,
begging two thugs to spare
his only daughter.
They didn't.
You know, spare me.
So tell me, Bunker,
what fills a man
with so much hate
that he has to permanently
paint it all over his body?
Announce to the world
that he hates something that much?
My father was
the biggest man I ever knew.
He beat me a lot
when I was a kid,
so I stayed away from home
as much as possible.
I had a stutter,
a really bad one,
so I didn't talk much either.
There was this guy
in our neighborhood, Tank.
Big and badass
and covered in tattoos.
And every time he saw me,
he would sit me down
and buy me a soda.
Tell me that I had the power
to change things.
Introduced me to his buddies.
They were the only people that...
made me feel like I mattered.
One day, my father
gave me a black eye.
I don't remember why,
but Tank saw it.
He marched me home,
he grabbed my father
by the throat,
made him apologize.
Made him promise
he would never do it again.
He said, "Your boy...
...is one of us now."
My father never laid
a hand on me again.
For the first time in my life,
I had power.
And before I knew it...
...I had become one of them.
That is no goddamn excuse.
I know that.
Drop it, Proctor!
- No, Brock, it's okay.
- The hell it is.
Now drop your weapon.
Drop it!
- Get that fucking gun outta my face.
- I said drop it!
- I'm on your side!
- Hey, hey! The fight's out there.
An hour ago, I stopped you from
braining this asshole
with a fucking hammer.
Now you're letting him do
whatever the hell he wants?
- No. No, not in my house.
- It's not your house.
- It is my fucking house!
- Don't you fucking touch me.
Hey.
You gave Proctor a goddamn gun.
Are you kidding me?
He had the gun.
- I gave him some ammo.
- Why?
Because we need
all the help we can get.
No, no, no.
I don't want his help.
I don't need his help. I want
that murderer locked up in a cell.
- That's what I need.
- It was my call and I made it.
Yeah, of course
it was your call.
You know,
forget the law, forget the rules.
Just make it up as you go, huh?
- Hey, just calm down.
- No, fuck that!
People are dying
and any one of us could be next.
- Listen to me.
- No, you know what?
The fact is you go off
half-cocked whenever it suits you
and the rest of us
just have to fight your battles.
Well, I'm done. I've had it.
I'm not listening to you anymore.
All right, fine.
Give me your fuckin' badge.
My badge?
You know, before you got here,
I did this job by the book.
I put in my time,
I sacrificed my marriage for this job
because I'm good at it.
I'm good at being a cop.
Being good at killing people
doesn't make you right for this job.
Is that right?
'Cause you're pretty
fucking good at doing that, too.
Yeah. Yeah.
I did. I tried.
I tried, Hood.
I tried doing things your way.
I convinced myself
it was for the best,
but everything you touch
turns to blood.
Get everyone
in the other room now!
Go, go! Get out!
Other room, go!
Go, go, go!
Fuck.
Hey.
Hey, you all right?
Yeah, don't worry about me.
Just cover the door.
People are dying.
Everything you touch
turns to blood.
You don't even know
what you're doing here.
You're not even a cop.
- I'm going out there.
- What are you talking about?
Someone's gotta make
sure help is on the way.
- Hood, it's suicide.
- He's right, you'll die out there.
You can barely even stand.
We can't hold them off forever.
Find another way.
I'll go.
Once we're clear,
I'll call for help.
You won't get clear.
You'll be dead inside of 30 seconds.
Well, either way you win, Deputy.
You know what?
You're under arrest, Proctor.
You don't get to just
walk out this door.
Desperate times.
Right, Sheriff?
Godspeed.
If I don't make it outta here,
you stay the fuck
away from Rebecca.
Okay.
If I do make it,
you and I have
unfinished business.
Yeah, I know.
Don't forget to make that call.
Come on. Let's go.
Let's block up this door.
It's not too late, Rebecca.
Leave this house.
Find your own way.
Raven's covering the bullpen.
Brock's downstairs
watching the door with Bunker.
Okay.
You think Proctor made it?
I do.
What we had...
...was any of it real?
All of it.
Are you sure?
How long were you locked up?
Fifteen years.
Oh, my God.
And then you come here
and Carrie's got Gordon and the kids.
That's right.
And now?
Would you really
just have walked away?
If that's what you want.
What if it isn't?
Then we leave together.
Do I know everything about you?
Not yet.
But if you want to...
...you will.
Okay.
Start by telling me
your real name.
Billy.
What the hell are you doing?
- I'm ending this.
- Get away from there!
I have to do this.
It's the only way.
- Chayton.
- Raven.
- This has to end.
- You know what it'll take.
- Blood for blood.
- I'll give myself up.
You call off your men.
You leave these people alone.
The time for negotiating has passed.
They'll all pay now.
For Christ's sakes.
Haven't you killed
enough people already?
Come on.
Come on, Billy,
we gotta get you outta here.
Come on.
Here, hold on.
- How bad?
- Just have to stop the bleeding.
Can he stand?
Yeah. Yeah.
Get him up.
Gotta go to the basement.
Fuck.
Come on, come on, come on.
No, just go.
Just go, we'll be right behind you.
- No, come on.
- Just go.
Go. We'll be okay.
Okay.
- I can't control my legs.
- You're going into shock.
- You need to get downstairs.
- I'm not leaving you here.
Siobhan.
Come here.
I killed Tommy.
- It's blood for blood.
- Billy, look at me. Listen.
You saved my life at the Savoy.
You're not gonna die for that.
I have no ammo.
Here.
In case I don't get a chance,
- I just want to say...
- Don't do that.
- Do what?
- What you're about to do.
I was just gonna say,
I still think I would have been
a better sheriff than you.
Yeah, you're probably right.
Should we go after them?
Help yourself.
Let her go, Chayton.
I said, let her go.
God damn it, you let her go
or I'll blow your fucking head off!
No. No.
No, no, no, Chayton. Chayton.
Just stop, okay?
This has got
nothing to do with her.
All right?
Please.
It's between you and me.
Just let her go.
Shh.
- No.
- Please.
Shh.
Please. Please.
Mutter.
God, our Father...
Your power brings us to birth.
Your providence guides our lives.
And by Your command,
we return to dust.
Lord, those who die
still live in Your presence.
Their lives change,
but do not end.
I pray and hope for my family,
relatives, and friends,
and for all the dead
known to You alone.
In company with Christ,
who died and now lives...
Siobhan?
...may they all rejoice
in His kingdom,
where all our tears
are wiped away.
Siobhan?
Unite us together again
in one family...
Hey!
...to sing His praise
forever and ever.
Amen.
Oh, my. Oh, my. Oh, my.