Who the hell are you?
- Siobhan.
- Stay the fuck away from me.
You played us.
Me, Brock, Emmett.
Everything about you is a lie.
Siobhan, listen to me.
Don't.
Okay. Okay.
Okay.
Put the gun down.
It's me, Siobhan.
No.
You hear me?
Hey, it's me.
Come on.
It's just me.
There is no you.
I need time to think.
Just get out.
We should talk about this.
Get the fuck out!
Now!
- Hey, good evening.
- Where's Mario and Frank?
Oh, they had to do
a double at Raymor Plaza.
Some kind of plumbing leak.
They're up to their eyeballs
in shit, literally.
- Yeah.
- Give me your badges.
We already scanned them.
And I'm gonna scan them again.
Excuse my friend.
He's a little slow
since the accident.
What?
Something wrong?
Why'd you cut your hair, man?
What?
The 'fro.
You know, just hanging
around guys like this,
it just felt too much
like showing off.
Thanks.
Have a good night.
Yeah, thank you.
You, too.
Okay.
Big Brother's in the house.
You seeing what I'm seeing?
Shit, they're watching
them monitors like hawks.
Then let's change the view.
All right.
Okay, you're clear.
Go get that formula.
- It's an algorithm.
- Yeah, you say tomato.
Hey, one of the
guards is on the move.
- You better step on it.
- You need to step off it.
I ain't watching fucking
YouTube videos up in here.
Damn, he's getting
on the elevator.
Sh...
- Hey.
- Where's your partner?
- Oh, he went to take a leak.
You know?
Look, you better
step on it, man.
Gonna get real crowded
in there real soon.
Got you.
Job.
- Sorry I'm late.
- 45 minutes, Carrie.
Her teacher couldn't wait.
What did she say?
Well, Deva's missing assignments,
she's disruptive in class,
and basically
her attitude sucks.
And apparently the school
feels that our daughter
is lacking any kind of
discipline or structure at home.
- And that's my fault?
- I'm not pointing fingers.
Well, you just did and this
from a mayor who bangs hookers.
Yeah, and like abandoning your
family to go off to hunt down
your gangster father
is a lesson in family values?
Fuck you, Gordon.
Carrie, can you stop, please?
Look, we need to do better.
I realize that I have been
blaming everybody else
for my inability to handle
everything that's happened.
I just...
It's our family.
But you know that I have never
been a victim in my life
and I'm done with that.
I want to figure this out
for all of us.
Where I come from,
it's customary
- to drink to a job well...
- Done.
Ha!
Done?
That algorithm was just the
tip of this cluster fuck.
No, it's the small victories
that keep you in the fight.
I know you are the Dalai Lama
of Mayberry and all that shit,
but that don't mean everything
coming out your mouth is wisdom.
It is far from party time.
Fine.
Cheers.
Who'd you piss off this time?
We may have to bail.
What, on the job?
On everything.
Everything everything?
How bad is it?
- Siobhan has the police file on me.
- Oh, fuck.
So why aren't we already doing
95 out of this shithole?
Could be she won't turn me in.
Let me explain something to you.
There are fake cops, that's you,
and there are real cops,
that's her.
Difference being real cops
will turn your ass in.
Maybe not.
Would you please tell this man
it is way past time
to cut and fuckin' run?
You two both do
what you gotta do.
But I'm going to work, Job.
Baby, I want you
to try real hard
to remember what happened the last
time you rolled the dice on a woman.
Fuck this.
I'm packing.
- When were you gonna tell me?
- Brock.
You're working
for Proctor now, Emily?
Have you lost it?
How could you
possibly know that?
- I called your agency.
- You did what?
- I didn't hear from you.
- Jesus Christ, Brock.
- I was worried about you.
- You're spying on me.
- I'm not spying on you.
- You're unbelievable.
Do you have any idea
how dangerous Proctor is?
The kind of people
that he deals with?
And now you're living
in the goddamn house?
His mother is dying.
Yeah, well, apparently
she's not the only one.
I was there the other day fishing
a dead gangbanger out of his pool.
Em, bad things happen there.
I care for the dying.
That's what I do.
That's what I'm gonna
keep on doing.
Listen.
Em, I'm begging you.
Get as far away from
that man as possible.
The only one I need
to get away from is you.
Emily.
That's very interesting.
Just call me
if anything changes.
Tommy Littlestone's body
has been cleared for release.
I'm pretty sure his brother's eager
to get him back to the reservation.
I want to go, too.
All right.
Thank you, Uncle.
My mother is driving me crazy.
She's got a problem
with everything I do.
Any time you want to trade moms,
just say the word.
Sorry.
Yeah, didn't think so.
How is Max doing?
Fine, I guess.
Max has been wanting
that game for months.
$75 for a video game?
What the hell?
It's crazy.
How's she doing?
Resting comfortably.
The new meds are doing
a better job with the pain.
That's good.
Thank you for taking
such good care of her.
Well, it's what she deserves.
It's what we all deserve.
Yeah.
How are you holding up, Mr. Proctor?
Me?
Well, I'm not the one who's dying.
But you are suffering
and you don't get any meds.
The downside to being
strong for everyone else
is that you never get
a moment for yourself.
If you ever want to talk or...
I've got nowhere else to be.
Do you want to sit down?
Apple on three.
Table six is ready to order.
Table nine needs silverware.
And the campers on 12 are asking
for a third refill on coffee.
A little help here.
12 is still asking
for that refill.
Carrie.
- What now?
- We wait.
Stay here.
Get in.
I've been practicing
with my uncle.
You're not
an experienced driver.
Well, then let's go
get me some experience.
What the hell?
You called.
What's going on?
I'm withdrawing
Proctor's plea bargain.
I don't understand.
We'll file the motion
first thing in the morning.
Sperling is gonna
go apeshit on us.
Well, that's just the gravy.
By the way, I'm sorry I was a jerk.
You weren't a jerk.
You were an asshole.
I should probably go.
Let you get settled.
You've got secrets, boss.
Don't we all?
If they ever get to be too
much or if you want to talk...
- I'll see you tomorrow.
- Yeah.
Hi, you've reached Siobhan Kelly.
Please leave a message.
- Hood.
- Yeah?
I just got a call
from fire and rescue.
There's a wreck
out on Highway 6.
- You handle it.
- Two DOAs, both Redbones.
They were transporting
Tommy Littlestone's body.
Great, let's go.
Tequila.
Whatever you got.
She'll have the Anejo, chilled.
A real woman like you, I think
that she deserves the best.
You buying?
Yes, ma'am.
Make it a double.
And keep 'em coming.
I thought I was
having a bad day.
What do we got?
Driver is Hakan Evans.
He signed for the body
at the morgue.
We'll need dental records
to identify the other.
- Any witnesses?
- Not out here.
A second set of skid marks confirms
another vehicle was involved.
- Could have been an accident.
- Yeah.
You know this wasn't
an accident.
No?
Chayton is gonna see this
as a declaration of war.
Yeah, well, that's
Proctor's problem.
Well, what are we
gonna do about it?
- Nothing.
- What?
We stay the fuck out of it.
Ah, it burns so good.
You have a real pretty smile.
- Yeah, I still got it.
- Yes, ma'am.
That's good.
Is that your bike
parked outside?
- Sexy beast, isn't she?
- Mmm.
I used to dream about
owning a machine like that.
What do you mean used to?
Another life.
Well, that is
a terribly sad story.
But don't you worry 'cause
your new buddy Scuyver,
well, he's all about
the happy endings.
Is that right?
That is right.
I think that...
...maybe you and me should go
somewhere more private.
That sounds great, but, no.
I gotta go.
- Maybe next time.
- What?
Hey, hey, hey.
Hey. Hey.
I got six drinks
invested in this little party.
So you ain't going nowhere...
...till you show me...
...a little gratitude.
When I say no, I mean it.
Hi, you've reached
Siobhan Kelly.
Please leave a message.
Where are you?
You should be asking
where I'm not.
Because in 20 minutes,
the answer's gonna be
Banshee,
Pennsyl-fucking-vania.
Give me until the end of the day
and I'll come with you.
Just gotta tie up
a few loose ends.
Well, then you tie
them up quick, baby,
and let's get
the fuck out of here.
Hey.
- Hey, Deva.
- What?
- You aren't in school.
- I'm just running a little late.
Maybe that's 'cause
you're going the wrong way.
- Like you never ditched.
- I never got caught.
Hey, Deva,
I'm sorry about the other day.
I'm over it, seriously.
Look, I didn't mean
to blow you off.
Okay? I...
You caught me off guard
and everything came out wrong
and I'm sorry.
Well, it won't
happen again, okay?
From now on, you're just the
asshole who knocked up my mom.
Okay, fine, I'm the asshole.
I mean, I've caused you nothing
but problems since I got here,
so I get it.
Pretty much.
Fuck.
- Why do you even care?
- I just do.
Why?
Look, my old man never
gave a shit about me.
All right?
I mean...
I guess you could
call him honest.
But I fucking hated him for it.
I still do. I wish I didn't,
but I do.
I don't want you
to hate me, Deva.
But I can't make you do
anything; no one can.
That's a choice you
gotta make on your own.
You're leaving, aren't you?
I have to.
Does it matter
that I want you to stay?
Yes.
It matters.
Okay?
But I made a huge
fucking mess, kid.
I have to go.
Yeah.
I don't hate you.
Well, maybe a little bit.
I can live with that.
What the fuck are you doing?
Hi, Jackson.
We have an appointment?
We had a goddamn deal.
Yeah, well, our position
has changed.
You can't do this.
It's already done.
Proctor will have
his day in court.
You're making
a big mistake, Gordon.
Careful, Jackson, that almost
sounded like a threat.
It's a warning.
I'm gonna come at you
with everything I've got.
Yeah, and what you've got
is a guilty client.
You should talk some sense
into your boss.
Your ass is on
the line here, too.
I appreciate your concern.
Shit.
So you want to talk about it?
I was stupid.
I just got carried away is all.
I feel trapped.
I keep waking up from a dream
to realize that it's real life
that's become the nightmare.
Then I do these stupid,
dangerous things.
I know that.
It's just...
I need to breathe.
Well, I know how that feels.
It's good to have you around.
Yeah.
- About that.
- What?
What?
I know I'm being selfish,
but I don't want you to go.
Not now.
Well, there's really no
choice anymore, is there?
Do you really think
she'd arrest you?
It doesn't really matter, does it?
She knows.
Where are you gonna go?
I don't know.
Anywhere.
Right.
Deva.
She'll be okay.
She's strong.
Like her mom.
And what about you?
Are you gonna be okay?
Of course.
Yeah?
- Hey.
You look upset.
Everything okay?
It'll be all right.
You know we have
to talk about school.
Yeah.
Not tonight, though.
Get some sleep.
Okay.
Good night.
You can get undressed now.
Are you leaving?
You wanna take on the Redbones,
go right ahead.
I'm too old and too tired
to be sticking my nose
where it don't belong.
We're the goddamn police, Karl.
I'm going home.
Don't call me unless
the building's on fire.
I still don't think
you're much of a cop,
but I think you're serious
about getting Proctor.
This town's been waiting for somebody
to do that for a long, long time.
Sheriff, do you know
why they're afraid of me?
Why is that?
Because they should be.
And maybe you should be, too.
You have no evidence, no body,
not even a name you say.
Would you put him away?
Could you even put him away?
A guilty verdict could mean
five years in prison.
Not acceptable.
I will file every motion I can
to slow the process down,
but barring a miracle, your case
is gonna be decided by a jury.
Then a miracle is exactly
what you're gonna get me.
You get it?
- Yeah?
- Kai, it's Emily.
Your mother's taken a turn.
You should come home now.
She doesn't have much time.
Thank you, Emily.
I'm on my way.
You fucking fix this.
We're closed.
Leave.
- Get out.
- What the hell are you doing?
You need to leave now.
Whatever it is, Sheriff,
it has to wait.
No!
Jesus.
Call the police.
Uh, he is the police.
God damn it.
Hood!
Come on.
Get up.
You okay?
Kai Proctor, you're under arrest
for assaulting an officer.
Whoa, whoa. It was self-defense.
Hood attacked him first.
Back up or I'll cuff
your ass, too.
Go to your grandmother.
She needs you.
Yeah, let's go.
Sorry for the wait.
You can all head back now.
The sheriff will need
just a few minutes.
Go.
May I help you?
I would like to speak
to the sheriff, please.
Is he expecting you?
- No, ma'am.
- Take a seat.
On second thought,
go wait back there.
Yes, ma'am.
This is beyond harassment.
I've got a dozen witnesses
who will testify
that you started the fight.
- Why don't you shut the fuck up?
- What the hell happened?
- He tried to murder my client.
- I wasn't asking you.
Do you have any idea
how bad this looks?
Ask me if I care.
- Hood.
- Stay!
What's up, farm boy?
You three play nice.
Hey, Hood.
Yeah, don't worry.
I got this.
I'm not gonna turn you in.
Not because I don't want to,
but because the truth would
annihilate this department.
It would wipe away all the good work
real cops have done around here.
You know I tried to do good
with that badge.
That badge was never
yours to wear.
Rabbit was your boss?
You stole for him?
Yes.
And Carrie Hopewell,
the two of you were...
- Yes.
- Jesus.
Why me?
Siobhan, no matter
what you think,
you and me was not a lie.
Siobhan, I swear to God.
The only time I ever felt safe
was with you.
I trusted you.
I let you in.
- I know.
- You endangered
my life, my career,
and I let you.
- Siobhan.
- No.
Don't fuckin' touch me.
This is what you're gonna do.
You're gonna go
out there right now,
you're gonna finish
booking Proctor,
and then you're gonna
quietly resign.
Then what?
And then you're gonna walk away.
Get down!