Please.
No.
Go, Charlie!
Hit him!
Kick his ass, man!
- Watch your back!
- I can't watch this.
- Yeah!
- Deva, I'm gonna go home.
Deva.
Beaty, do whatever the hell
you want. I'm staying.
Fine.
I'm out of here.
- Do it!
- Hey, that's my boy right there!
Fuck this shit!
Let's get real.
Round two!
Oh, Light him up!
Yeah!
Oh, ho! That's it!
Yeah! Again!
What the fuck
are you doing here?
I know a Cl that can
help find Chayton.
A former Redbone.
Price tag's gonna be steep.
Whatever it costs,
I'll get the money.
Call your informant.
Hood.
Should have pulled the trigger
when I had a chance.
It's hard to shake all that
history in one moment.
Trust me, I know.
Colonel Douglas Sto...
Fuck!
Wouldn't it be easier to just use
a recording of Stowe's voice?
No, it would not.
Stowe's voice recognition system can
identify most digital forgeries.
Colonel Douglas Stowe.
But not mine.
- All right. Then we good to go.
- We ain't even close.
That base looks
the same as it did
the last three
times you checked it.
No, something ain't right.
- That would be your nerves.
- Please! I do not do nerves.
Do you want to know
what I think?
You do know my answer to that
question never changes, right?
There's only one way to
lay those doubts to rest.
And it ain't sitting around
here driving yourself crazy.
That's all.
What?
Scream and I'll kill you.
Is there anyone else in the house?
Let's go.
Oh...
I will lift up mine eyes
unto the hills
from whence cometh my help.
My help cometh from the Lord,
which made heaven and Earth.
He will not suffer
thy foot to be moved.
He will keepeth thee
and will not slumber.
Behold, He that keepeth Israel
shall neither slumber nor sleep.
Brothers, if anyone is
caught in any transgression,
you who are spiritual
should restore him
in a spirit of gentleness.
Welcome, Kai.
Keep watch on yourself
lest you, too, be tempted.
If anyone thinks they are
something when they are not,
they deceive themselves.
Each one should test
their own actions.
Then they can take pride
in themselves alone
without comparing themselves
to someone else.
For each should carry
their own load.
Look, the man is 6'4"
and covered in tribal tats.
I can't believe
no one has seen him.
No, I...
I understand.
Okay. But, look, if you hear
anything, you know where to find me.
Thank you.
Any calls?
No, sir.
Slow day.
Hi, you've reached Emily Lotus.
Please leave a message.
Hi. It's me.
Again.
Haven't heard from you, so...
Look, I know I'm not your most
favorite person right now, but...
you know, I was just thinking
about us and I... Thanks.
Yeah. Please return my call
at your earliest convenience.
Our friend from Philadelphia
tells me you're a little confused
about the offer he
delivered from Mr. Frazier.
They were buying
from our competition
and you want to reward that
with a discount?
I already agreed
to Frazier's terms.
Stop all sales to the
Salvadorans immediately.
Is that understood?
Please be reasonable.
Is that understood, Rebecca?
Does your uncle
know you're here?
- That's not your concern.
- Everything is my concern.
So tell me,
why am I having a conversation
with the niece of the man
who cut me off?
I'm here to correct that
temporary error in judgment.
What makes you think
I'd ever buy from you?
Because you'd be a fool not to.
Word on the street is that Frazier
is trying to put you out of business.
You've lost control
of your street corners,
your raves.
In a couple of weeks,
you'll be shut down completely.
I can get you back in the game.
Can you?
We'll start slow.
- Two kilos per week at $7,000 per.
- Four thousand per key.
Six thousand.
Or maybe you can convince
Frazier to throw you a bone.
You guys go way back, don't you?
I like you, chica.
I really do.
But if you fuck me,
your uncle will be scooping
you up in tiny little pieces.
I look forward to a long and
fruitful relationship, Mr. Morales.
Hector.
Just so you know, I have been
monitoring the FBI's progress.
Chayton is still off the grid.
Sheriff Hood, however, is not.
Captain Ferillo has filed
a formal complaint.
Have you been
watching Camp Genoa?
- Did you hear what I just said?
- I did. Fuck Ferillo.
Is there anything
I should worry about?
With all clue respect,
we should all be a little worried.
I want to delay the job.
That base will be shut down
by the end of the week.
It's now or never, Job.
Well, then I guess it's never.
What?
Baby, I have seen
every side of you there is.
Reckless, dumb,
and especially stubborn.
But I ain't never seen this.
You in the deep end.
If you don't keep
your head above water,
you're going to drag the rest
of us down there with you.
We're doing the fucking job.
We're doing it tonight.
Well, good luck with that.
Job.
You asked me what I needed.
Right now, this is it.
Fine.
I'll go get cleaned up.
Might as well look pretty
for my mug shot.
Hold it.
Okay.
You're not afraid of me?
No.
You should be.
I buried a husband and a child.
There are days I don't think I have
anything left to live for anyway.
Whew! Well, she ain't gonna
win no beauty contests.
Thank you.
So how is he?
Same as ever. Well, don't worry,
we can count on him.
Has the waitress checked in?
Carrie hasn't checked in yet,
but she will.
She best be on her game.
You'd think we were knocking
over a motherfucking 7-Eleven
- the way these two are acting.
- You know what, Job?
You worry too much.
Well, somebody's got to.
Let's see what we got.
Ooh.
That's good.
Hey, Beaty.
What's up?
What?
Where is she?
- You sure this is the place?
- Yes.
Any chance I can convince
you to stay out here?
All right, then.
Deva!
- What the fuck?
- We're going home now.
What the hell
are you guys doing here?
- I'm not gonna tell you again.
- She's not going anywhere.
- Okay, you need to shut your mouth.
- I don't believe this.
You guys can't just decide
when to give a shit.
- Deva!
- No, I'm staying.
You heard her,
she's not going anywhere, man.
- Get out of my way.
- You're on my property, old man.
And you need to fuck off now.
Okay.
Let's just all take a deep
breath and think about this.
- Oh!
- You shouldn't have done that.
Come on, man. Come on!
- Gordon!
- Charlie, no! Please!
- Please, don't.
- Deva, shut the fuck up!
You man enough to pull
that trigger, son?
I'll kill you.
Dad.
Then stop talking and do it.
I swear,
I'll shoot you, motherfucker.
Pull it.
Put the gun down.
Deva, come here!
Holy fuck.
That's the mayor.
You okay?
I don't eat out much.
To be honest,
it's been a while for me, too.
Forgotten what medieval
torture high heels can be.
You look beautiful, Emily.
It's also been some time
since I've heard that.
Thank you.
Well, here is to getting
outside of our comfort zones.
You have a nice smile.
I bet not many people
get to see that.
No. No, I guess not.
Yeah, I know what
it's like to put up walls.
Your niece, Rebecca...
How long has she been
living with you?
Not long.
She was in trouble.
She needed guidance.
And the time is coming
for her to be on her own.
It's probably for the best.
So do you think that's what other
family interventions are like?
I hope so.
I mean, why should we be the
only ones having all the fun?
You want a small pour or big?
Neither.
We did good out there.
Yeah, we did.
Where were you?
I went for a little ride.
Hope you don't mind.
It would be unwise to test me.
I wouldn't dream of it.
You're out of gas.
So...
See you around?
Yeah.
Okay.
Good night, Gordon.
Good night.
You can take my husband's truck.
I haven't driven it
since he passed.
You can't hide from the dead.
Isn't that what you're doing?
Lisa, you in there?
- You lied to me.
- No, he is just a neighbor who...
He just comes to check
on me now and then.
Get rid of him.
- There you are, sunshine.
- Hey.
Margaret's fixing dinner.
She's got the table set for three.
Thanks, Vince.
No, thanks.
Come on, she's making her
world-famous chicken and biscuits.
I said no.
- Is everything all right?
- No, I'm fine. I just...
I just needed a little
time alone, that's all.
Sorry.
- Okay.
- Thanks.
No, no, no!
Oh, my...
Let's go to work.
Sugar.
Wake up.
Run through it again.
We've already done it six times.
And we are going
to do it a seventh time.
If you can count that high.
Hood.
You.
Carrie.
Satisfied?
No, show me the security
cam from Genoa.
Real time.
Now, show me the loop.
Okay. Anything else?
- Yeah.
- What?
I'm going to be leaving
these cover cams
at our entry and exit routes.
Like I don't have
enough to watch.
I ain't taking no chances.
If you see anybody or anything
that don't belong there,
you open that big-ass mouth
of yours and make some noise.
Yeah.
Three, two, one.
Okay.
Everybody ready?
Yeah.
- Yeah.
- Let's do it.
Time for some peace
and quiet.
Explosives up.
All right.
It's all yours, Sugar.
Bringing it UP-
It ain't gonna
fucking give.
God damn!
Motherfuck!
Okay, all quiet
on the western front.
That was the easy part.
We're in.
Okay.
I'm on my way down.
On me.
Let's do it.
Okay.
All right. All right.
Looking good.
Colonel Douglas Stowe.
Clear.
You got three minutes to set up.
- Don't keep me waiting.
- I got it.
Okay, the hallway to the
computer room is wide open.
Just keep moving.
Once I initiate the algorithm,
you're gonna have 12 minutes.
Ready when you are.
Get ready.
Three, two, one, move.
Please.
Please, don't.
What the...?
Please.
Shit! Job needs help
in the computer room now.
Anybody hearing me?
Anybody hear me?
I can't.
I'm running out of time.
What the fuck is he doing?
Where the fuck were you?
Echo-one-nine,
what's your 20?
Aw, Fuck.
You got two minutes.
Wake your ass up, old man.
We flying to you.
Oh, Shit.
Now, that can't be good.
All right, listen up, people.
The big boss man has
just arrived on base.
Colonel Douglas Stowe.
Fitzpatrick,
my ID isn't working.
I can't get into my office.
I have you swiped
into the armory.
Send a team to the armory now.
- How many?
- All of them.
Come on, baby.
Keep it moving, people.
It's about to get
real crowded down there.
Baby, we got to move!
Shit.
I don't fucking believe it.
Someone reset the codes.
Open the fucking door!
Got it.
Go!
Shit!
Colonel Douglas Stowe.
Oh, shit.
Try again.
Colonel Douglas Stowe.
What's wrong?
How the fuck should I know?
Colonel Douglas Stowe.
- Job, move!
- Find them.
No, no, don't, don't.
They're gonna hear us!
- Fuck!
- Move!
Come on, come on, come on.
Let's go, go, go!
Go, go, go, go!
Come on, come on, come on.
Go!
Fuck!
Come on, baby.
Come on, now.
What did you do here?
You sly little cunt.
Take the bags!
Go!
Job!
- Sugar!
- Got it. Ah!
All right, come on, bring it.
Got it.
Come on, baby.
Blow it now!
There's something wrong.
Something's wrong.
Check the detonator.
- Blow it!
- Just do it.
- Do it!
Damn.
- All right.
- Where is he?
If he was down there
when it blew,
he didn't have time
to clear the blast.
We got to move.
Wait!
Oh, my God.
Shit!
Come on, baby,
we going!
Everybody still
breathing back there?
Yeah.
- Hello, Brock.
- Oh, Emily.
I didn't think you'd pick up.
Neighbors told me the police
were at the house.
Well, yeah. I hadn't heard from you.
I was worried.
God, Emily, please.
Anybody but him.
- Brock.
- No.
Look, this isn't about
you and me anymore.
- This is about your safety.
- I'm fine.
Yeah, maybe now.
But, I mean,
you're tempting fate.
Listen to me. You have got to get as
far away from that man as possible.
You don't understand.
We have a connection.
Connection? No, no.
You know what it is?
You think you can fix him the
same way you tried to fix me.
- Good-bye, Brock.
- Hello? Em...?
Hello? Emily?
God!
Where's Hood?
You guys do know this
is a celebration, right?
I got to get home.
You did great, Sugar.
I know.
Look, I don't know what's
going on between you two,
- but whatever it is...
- I got distracted.
You put us all
at motherfucking risk.
- You left me hanging...
- Job!
Don't.
It...
L'chaim.
Keep it.
I convinced my Cl it was
time to grow a conscience.
Where's Chayton?
Headed to Louisiana.
There's a group of tribal outcasts
based in New Orleans.
They call themselves
the 18th Ward.
You're going
down there?
Yes.
What are you gonna do
when you find him?
What you couldn't.
- Look, I know this is hard for you.
- No. The boy I knew is dead.
That day in the woods,
I looked into his eyes
and he would have killed me
without a second thought.
Whoever he once was,
he's a stone-cold killer now
and he needs to be put down.
I just can't be there
to watch it happen.
Take care of yourself, Sheriff.
- Hey, Brock.
- Hmm?
Cover for me.
Sorry, can't do it.
What?
Because I'm going
with you to New Orleans.
I'll drive.
It's not my fault.
It's your fucking fault.
Precautions were taken.
Blame them.
It's your fucking fault.
This isn't possible.
I did not...