Previously on Hannibal...
Do not discuss me with Hannibal Lecter.
I brought Gideon back
because I thought he may be useful
in Will Graham's therapy.
I'm going to give you a chance
to save Will from himself.
Who does he want to kill, Doctor?
I want you to kill Hannibal Lecter.
Will Graham is not a murderer.
He asked you to do this?
Get an ambulance!
You're moving smoothly and slowly, Jack.
Carrying your concentration
like a brimming cup.
Hannibal Lecter was almost murdered
by an employee of this hospital.
An attendant
who we believe is the person that
killed the bailiff and the judge
at your murder trial.
He killed the bailiff, he didn't kill the judge.
- That was the Chesapeake Ripper.
- You know this?
He told me.
Then you told him to kill Hannibal.
Nothing I said made that happen, Jack.
It just happened.
"It just happened."
You don't seem to be too broken up about it.
There's a common emotion we all recognize
and have not yet named.
The happy anticipation
of being able to feel contempt.
You feel contempt for Hannibal?
Well, I have contempt for the Ripper.
I have contempt for what he does.
- And what does he do?
- What does he do?
What is the first
and principal thing he does?
What need does he serve by killing?
He harvests organs.
No, that's only the action of what
he does. Why does he need to do it?
The Ripper kills in sounders
of three or four in quick order.
Do you know why?
I know why.
Then tell me.
Because if he waits too long,
then the meat spoils.
He's eating them?
Hannibal is like Garret Jacob Hobbs?
A cannibal?
No, not like Garret Jacob Hobbs.
Hobbs ate his victims to honor them.
The Ripper eats his victims because
they're no better to him than pigs.
With the exception of Beverly Katz,
there is no connection between Hannibal
and any Ripper victims.
No immediate connection.
Hannibal Lecter is not
the Chesapeake Ripper.
If the Ripper's killing,
you can bet Hannibal Lecter's
planning a dinner party.
You and I probably sipped wine
while swallowing the people
to whom we were trying
to give justice, Jack.
Who does he have to kill
before you open your eyes?
A remarkably lean organ, the heart,
yet such a potent symbol of life
and the things that make us human.
Good and bad,
love and ache.
All of them skewered.
It's a thematic dish.
My heart certainly feels skewered.
You have the scars to prove it.
It feels as if that noose
is still around my neck.
Strange having nightmares. I never used to.
Don't make the same mistake I've made.
Being your own psychiatrist.
I'm always assessing my feelings
instead of acting on them.
It's the safest course.
You have to find a way
to deal with what happened to you.
I'm metabolizing the experience
by composing a new piece of music.
Harpsichord or Theremin?
Harpsichord.
Stravinsky said a true composer
thinks about his unfinished work
the whole time.
He's not always conscious of this,
but he's aware of it
when he suddenly knows what to do.
And do you know what to do?
I need to get my appetite back.
What do we got?
He's literally grafted in place.
These are living roots.
He's got varicose vines.
Threaded through, from his heels,
under his legs, his back,
through his torso, out his fingertips.
Followed some pretty tricky
endoscopic surgical paths.
Chesapeake Ripper
usually cherry-picks his organs.
He took almost all of them.
Everything but the lungs.
The time that he devotes to his work...
He really takes pride.
Belladonna for the heart.
Chain of white oleander for the intestines.
Ragwort for the liver.
These flowers are all poisonous.
Yes. This is judgment.
The Ripper believes
that his victim was toxic somehow.
A poisonous man.
He's so damn certain, he makes me sick.
There is a pattern taking shape.
I just have to convince my eyes to see it.
I've convinced myself of something
I had refused to see for a long time.
And it only took Will Graham
trying to kill you to see it?
Yes.
I can't help Will.
I can't trust him.
He's in a dark place
where the shadows move,
and it's not safe to stand with him anymore.
I feel the same way.
We found another Ripper victim...
I'm sorry, Jack. I can't.
Not only do I have to let Will go,
I have to let this all go.
I nearly died.
I would have if it weren't for you.
I'm sorry. I can't dwell on death anymore.
I don't blame you.
We both have to transform
our misfortunes into life enhancing events.
Well, when you figure out
how to do that, do let me know.
I'm going to start by hosting a dinner party.
And please tell me you'll come.
I wouldn't miss it.
You should've let him die.
Shoulda, coulda, woulda.
He's gonna kill you, you know.
Can't get me in here.
No, here is exactly where he'll get you, Abel.
The moment I convinced the chief of staff
to put you in a cell next to me,
you were stamped with an expiration date.
Anyone who gets too close gets got.
He's the devil, remember? Smoke.
I'd be very nervous if I was Dr. Chilton.
He's getting close, too.
The only way you and Frederick
are gonna get out of this alive
is if the Chesapeake Ripper is stopped.
Hannibal Lecter deserves to die.
You didn't bring me here
to help you kill Hannibal Lecter.
No, I didn't,
I brought you here to bear witness.
To tell Jack Crawford that I sat
in Hannibal Lecter's cobalt blue
dining room,
an ostentatious herb garden
with Leda and the swan over the fireplace
and you having a fit in the corner.
That's where I asked him
if he was the Chesapeake Ripper,
and he avoided the question
and suggested I kill Alana Bloom.
Yes.
Tell Jack that.
I'll tell Jack Crawford everything
if you tell me why Hannibal did it.
Because he wanted to see
what would happen.
That's where I asked him
if he was the Chesapeake Ripper
and he avoided the question
and suggested I kill Alana Bloom.
Abel Gideon is a lunatic.
He is psychotic, not psychic.
We know that Gideon has a history
of being susceptible to suggestion.
The simplest explanation as to why
he can describe Hannibal Lecter's home
is that he was in Hannibal Lecter's home.
Will Graham could've given him the details.
No such details were given.
There has not been a word exchanged
between those two men
in my hospital that I have not heard.
Then you're aware
what Will is accusing Hannibal Lecter of?
Yes. I am aware.
And I am grateful that
I have trouble digesting animal proteins,
as the last meals I have shared
with Hannibal Lecter have all been salads.
Do you believe him?
Hannibal once served me tongue
and then made a joke about eating mine.
It would be narrow
to not at least consider it.
Will is delusional.
He would like to reinforce his delusion
with you, with me, with Abel Gideon.
That doesn't mean he is not right.
No, it doesn't.
The Chesapeake Ripper is killing again.
And Hannibal Lecter
is throwing a dinner party.
Jack, he fits the profile.
He is attracted to medical
and psychological fields
because they offer power over man.
Cannibalism...
Cannibalism is an act of dominance.
His name's Sheldon Isley!
A Baltimore city councilman!
Ripper's a politician now!
At least a conservationist.
Five, six years ago, Isley brokered
a woodlands development deal
despite the disapproval of the EPA.
So the councilman paved paradise
and put up a parking lot, huh?
Well, what he paved was
an important nesting habitat
for endangered songbirds.
The son of a bitch.
He was wearing this as a crown.
Autopsy report gave us what you'd expect
from the Chesapeake Ripper.
Pre-mortem surgical dissection,
latex glove impressions.
Body was posed before rigor set in.
- What did the lungs cough up?
- Water.
The councilman was drowned.
Lungs filled with aspirated water.
He was standing in water up to his thighs
for 48 to 72 hours before he died.
- To feed the tree.
- Possibly.
Now, here's the exciting part.
Tree man actually bears fruit.
Diatoms, unicellular colonies.
Good as fingerprints.
No two water sources have
the same diatom population.
Water in the lungs gives us
location of death. Show me.
Here, in a 50 mile radius.
My head is filled with conspiracies.
Too many versions of events.
He said she said. He said she said she said.
It's just maddening.
In my experience, that means
a lot of people are lying
about a lot of different things.
Well, the one thing I have clarity on
is Will Graham tried to kill Hannibal.
And thinks it was a righteous act.
Well, that says more about Will
than it does about Hannibal.
Hannibal's been a teacher,
a mentor, and a friend.
I've known him before
you, or Will, or any of this.
I don't claim to know anyone.
I look at these dogs,
I see the best part of Will.
But he's lying. He's manipulating.
He's playing a game
and he's not scared, not anymore.
That's what's making him dangerous.
Hello, Dr. Lecter.
I feel like I've been watching
our friendship on a split screen.
The friendship I perceived on one side
and the truth on the other.
It's a terrible feeling, isn't it?
You've been lying to me, Will.
Well, I don't have a gauge for reality
that works well enough
to know if I've been lying.
But you understand the reality
of Beverly Katz's death.
You understand your role in that.
What was my role?
Beverly died at your behest.
You are as angry with yourself
as you are with whoever murdered her.
Actually,
I am singularly angry
with whoever murdered her.
You tried to kill me, Will.
It's hard not to take that personally.
However, if I were Beverly's murderer,
I'd applaud your effort.
I'm no more guilty
of what you've accused me of
than you are of what I've accused you of.
I don't expect you to feel self-loathing,
or regret, or shame.
You knew what you were doing,
and you made your own decisions,
decisions that were under your control.
You think I'm in control?
I think you are more in control now
than you have ever been.
You found a way to hurt me.
I wonder how many more people are
going to get hurt by what you do.
I'll give Alana Bloom your best.
Goodbye, Will.
So, it seems all the king's horses
and all the king's men
could indeed put Humpty together again.
Is everything back where I found it?
With one or two exceptions.
I know people who consider me autocratic.
I'm not the most loved of administrators,
but that nurse you murdered,
she was well liked
and so were the attendants you killed.
There is nothing like grief and trauma
to pull people together.
Jack Crawford would like
to have a word with you.
I trust you will behave yourself, Abel.
I'm sure you and Frederick
have had many a conversation
about my bad behavior, Jack.
How does he describe me?
A pure sociopath, by the book.
- Is that by your book, Frederick?
- Yes.
I would just like to point out
that the word "sociopath" has not been used
by any respected psychiatrist since 1968.
Dr. Gideon, do you have any information
about the Chesapeake Ripper, or not?
Down to brass tacks.
You told Will Graham
that you were in Dr. Lecter's home.
Why were you there?
I have never set foot in Dr. Lecter's home.
I only met the man a week ago.
However, Dr. Chilton was kind enough
to share the details of his dining room.
Why would he do that?
Yes, why would he do that?
Will Graham is very keen to believe that
Hannibal Lecter is the Chesapeake Ripper.
Dr. Chilton did very little
to disavow him of that notion
and encouraged me to do the same.
I apologize, Agent Crawford,
for wasting your time.
It's not your actions and betrayal
that I resent, Dr. Chilton.
It's just the lies.
- I'll walk you out.
- Thank you.
Dr. Chilton hired a nurse
who's had experience in mental hospitals,
but not as an employee.
That nurse attempted
to murder Hannibal Lecter,
and you blame Will Graham.
You got the right box there, Jack,
but you're looking in the wrong corner.
All the coiled resentment in this place,
it's gotta be bad for the digestion.
You know that poor Nurse Shell
that I murdered?
I know she's seen
as some kind of beloved sister,
but wasn't she also kind of a good-time girl
with a beer or two inside her?
I asked her if she had eyes for me,
she said no.
So I had to take 'em.
Prosciutto roses.
Heart tartare.
Beef roulade.
Whatever this is.
Needless to say,
I will not be eating the food.
Nice to see you again, Dr. Chilton.
Hannibal the cannibal.
That is what they'll call him, you know.
Not according to Abel Gideon.
Gideon has given me
enough trouble for one day.
The fact that he lied to you
makes me even more certain
he was telling Will Graham the truth.
Why did you come here tonight
if you're so convinced?
Darwinism.
I do not want him
to think I suspect anything.
I really shouldn't be seen speaking to you.
I don't want to be perceived as a threat.
Jack.
I'm so happy you're here.
After all, you are the guest of honor.
You saved my life.
Unfortunately, my friend, I can't stay.
I would love to take some food to go,
if that's all right.
Of course. I'll get one of the staff
to get you something from the kitchen.
No, no. That's all right.
Just bring me a container
and I'll serve myself from here.
With your permission, of course, Dr. Lecter.
Hello, Jack.
Hello, Alana.
I do have your permission, Dr. Lecter?
- Help yourself.
- Thank you.
Eat it soon or it'll spoil.
Thank you.
- Good evening.
Z.
Test this.
Well, the ending to my composition
has been eluding me,
but you may just have solved that problem
with chopsticks.
If only every problem
could be solved with a simple waltz.
Jack's treating you like a suspect.
Pointing fingers in the dark.
I've walked away from Will,
but I'm still trailing his accusations.
I walked away, too.
I can't forgive Will for what he did to you.
I just want to walk away from all of it.
What does walking away leave us?
Each other.
Hello, Dr. Gideon.
Put the heart monitor on the guard
so no one knew Gideon was missing,
at least as long as it took
for the guard to die, which wasn't long.
It was long enough.
He was strung up with fish hooks.
Hand-tied flies,
just like Will Graham used to make.
This one has a human hair in it, and a tooth.
Jack, there is no way Gideon
could've done any of this
with the injuries he had,
much less get out of bed.
Well, the last time Gideon escaped custody,
he went looking for the Chesapeake Ripper.
He found him, all right.
Last night the Ripper found Gideon.
You're awake.
So are you.
I was thinking about funerals,
how often they make us want sex.
It's one in the eye for death.
Not that...
- This wasn't funeral sex or...
- Of course it was.
We both just buried a friend.
We buried Will.
There's something liberating
about finally letting him go.
Yes. There is.
We have a lot of reasons to do this,
not just funeral reasons.
Last time someone rang
my doorbell this early,
it was a census taker.
I'll see who it is.
- Jack.
- Hannibal.
- What can I do for you?
- We need to talk.
Abel Gideon fell down a stairwell last night.
He was hospitalized.
The security guard standing
watch has been killed
in what appears to be another
Chesapeake Ripper murder.
Gideon is nowhere to be found.
He escaped?
We know he didn't
leave the hospital on his own.
His back was broken.
He was taken by someone.
Someone who knew him.
Where were you last night?
I was here.
All night?
Yes.
Anyone other than yourself
that can verify that?
I can.
I was with Hannibal all night, Jack.
What are you accusing him of?
I'm not accusing him of anything,
only asking his whereabouts.
That's not all you're asking.
Rôti de cuisse.
Clay-roasted thigh
and canoe-cut marrow bone.
I love cooking with clay.
It creates a more succulent dish
and adds a little theatricality to dinner.
We come from clay, return to clay.
Shall I carve?
I think you already have.
Your legs are no good to you anymore.
You've got a T4 fracture of the vertebra.
This is a far more practical use
for those limbs.
Hard to have anything, isn't it, Dr. Lecter?
Rare to get it, hard to keep it.
A damn slippery life.
You were determined to know
the Chesapeake Ripper, Dr. Gideon.
Now is your opportunity.
You intend me to be my own last supper?
Yes.
How does one politely refuse a dish
in circumstances such as these?
One doesn't.
The tragedy is not to die, Abel,
but to be wasted.
My compliments to the chef.
- Goose, pig, cow.
- Not just cow, Wagyu beef.
There's about $100 worth right there.
How do you know it's not Kobe?
Well, all Kobe is Wagyu,
- not all Wagyu is Kobe.
- Okay.
Well, at least we know
Dr. Lecter wasn't serving up people.
You want people?
The Chesapeake Ripper
has been tying flies with them,
just like Will Graham allegedly did.
Hair woven into
the mono filament is Beverly's,
bone fragments of Miriam Lass.
Veining from Sheldon Isley,
optical nerve and arteries
from Judge Davies,
and a toenail from James Gray, our muralist.
All victims of the Chesapeake Ripper.
These four lures are almost identical
to what we found in Will's house,
made with material from
the exact same human remains.
Abigail Hobbs, Donald Sutcliffe,
Marissa Schurr, Georgia Madchen.
Will didn't kill any of these people.
There was no copycat, never was.
It was always the Ripper.
Finally taking credit for all of his murders.
Maybe too much credit.
Found something else in the lures.
Madrona bark.
A tree almost non-existent on the east coast,
but this bark was peeled recently.
There's a small stand
of madrona bark in Virginia.
Inside your diatom search area?
Yep.
Here.
Miriam.