Previously on Hannibal...
I want you to admit what you are.
You still refuse to see
the monster growing inside you.
I want exclusive rights to your story.
It's all yours, Freddie.
What is the heir to the Verger Meat Packing
dynasty doing at my door?
We have some very similar issues.
I tried to kill my brother.
I assume he had it coming.
They are looking for you.
It's important you do exactly what I say.
I'd say this makes us even.
I sent someone to kill you...
You sent someone to kill me.
Even Steven.
Consider it an act of reciprocity.
Polite society normally places
such a taboo on taking a life.
Without death, we'd be at a loss.
It's the prospect of death
that drives us to greatness.
Did you kill him with your hands?
It was...
Intimate.
It deserves intimacy.
You were Randall Tier's final enemy.
Don't go inside, Will.
You'll want to retreat.
You'll want it
as the glint of the rail tempts us
when we hear the approaching train.
Stay with me.
Where else would I go?
You have everywhere to go.
You should be quite pleased.
I am.
Of course you are.
When you killed Randall,
did you fantasize you were killing me?
Most of what we do,
most of what we believe,
is motivated by death.
I've never felt as alive
as I did when I was killing him.
Then you owe Randall Tier a debt.
How will you repay him?
The killer chose not to dispose of the body,
but to display it.
A jarring reminder
of the informality of death.
Randall Tier was denied the respectful end
that he himself denied others.
This is a humiliation, a final indignity.
He isn't mocking him.
This isn't disdain.
He's... Commemorating him.
This killer has no fear
for the consequences of what he's done.
No guilt.
Hello again.
Come closer.
I want to see you.
Can you see you?
Clearer and clearer.
You forced me to kill you.
I didn't force you to enjoy it.
You made me a monument.
You're welcome.
The monument is not to me, it's to you.
I gave you what you want.
This is who you are.
What you feel finally matches
the reality of what I see.
This is my becoming.
And it's yours.
This is my design.
He knew his killer.
There's a... Familiarity here.
Someone who met him, understood him.
Someone like him.
Different pathology, same instinct.
His killer empathized with him?
Don't mistake understanding
for empathy, Jack.
No, if there's anything, it's...
It's envy.
Envy?
Randall Tier came into his own
much easier than whoever killed him.
This was a fledgling killer.
He's never killed before,
not like this.
Not like this, no.
This is the nightmare that
followed him out of his dreams.
I've upped the ante on my publishing deal.
There's been movie interest.
Hollywood is a fine place
for the obnoxious and wealthy.
You're not wealthy, Freddie.
I will be.
Though I am a pariah among journalists
because I took a different faith,
but I am putting that faith in you.
Let's talk about the Chesapeake Ripper.
Frederick Chilton. Who knew?
Who knew?
No one did. No one would, not even you.
You were so certain the Chesapeake Ripper
was Hannibal Lecter, you tried to kill him.
You neglected to say "allegedly."
No, I didn't.
Hannibal Lecter is your psychiatrist again.
What's up with that?
I was wrong about him,
that's what's up with that.
Maybe you were.
Maybe you weren't.
Dr. Chilton was the Chesapeake Ripper.
The Chesapeake Ripper had surgical skills,
Dr. Chilton did not.
- They had the same profile.
- Dr. Chilton was
a woeful surgeon, dangerous, even.
I've been chatting with some
of his old medical school chums.
They say he fled to psychiatry
to avoid embarrassment.
My story with the Chesapeake Ripper
already has an ending, Freddie.
Mine doesn't.
Do you really think Dr. Chilton
killed Abigail Hobbs?
I don't.
Even if I let this story go,
I will never let that go.
Trust me, Freddie...
Neither will I.
You know you will have to kill him, Margot.
You've known it for years.
I may have missed my opportunity.
Do you know why you failed
to murder him, Margot?
Poor planning.
You failed to murder your brother
because you still love him.
In love, you take leave of your senses,
but in hatred, you must be present
to calculate your actions.
Allow yourself to hate him.
Do you think Mason will just
give you what you want?
You'll be begging him
for the rest of your life.
Did begging help when he tore you?
Same thing as taking his chocolate
and letting him have his way.
I'm lucky I didn't kill him.
Papa's will was very clear.
Upon the passing of his beloved son Mason,
in the absence of a legitimate male heir,
the sole beneficiary shall be
the Southern Baptist Convention.
Even in death, Mason would
take everything from you.
One of the most powerful forces
that shapes us as human beings
is the desire to leave a legacy.
What legacy would you leave behind?
I don't get a legacy.
Unless you make one.
Have a good ride?
Here, put him away.
What do you want?
What do I want? What do I want?
I want to...
Share something with you.
This is Pavlov. Say hello, Pavlov.
Say hello.
Margot, say hello to Pavlov.
Hi, buddy.
After Papa died, I had a Christmas epiphany.
I've seen exotic pigs from all over the world.
What would happen if I brought together
the best of all that I had seen?
You built a maze.
I shudder to think.
I feel like Stradivarius.
Our father was a pioneer
in livestock production. I think he'd be...
He'd be proud of my efforts.
A pig is not like other animals.
There is a spark of intelligence,
a terrible practicality in pigs.
Well, you do have an unparalleled
understanding of piggishness.
Your mouth gets rough
when you're scared, Margot.
Tough as a livery pony
who is resentful of the bit.
The structure is designed
to excite and antagonize the pigs.
It's taken a while to find the perfect mix.
Any pig will eat a dead man,
but to get him to eat a live one...
Some education is required.
Carlo is experienced in this field.
He actually fed a man to pigs
in Tuscany. 20 years ago?
That's one of my suits.
I'll buy you a new one.
We stuff the clothes with meat,
scent it with human smells, and play
the screams every time they are fed.
Come the real thing,
we won't need the recording.
It's not just about making Papa proud,
it's about us.
It's about family.
I want you to be proud of me too, Margot.
You're all I have.
And I'm all you have.
And this little piggy went,
"Whee!" all the way home.
- It sounds like I'm killing it.
- You are killing it.
Don't kill it.
A theremin is an instrument
that can create exquisite music
without ever needing to be touched, but...
It requires the rare gift
of perfect pitch to play properly.
I've come to replenish your stores.
Feel the vibration moving through you.
Feel it here.
And here.
It's like composing in thin air.
Thin air is a musician's canvas.
What happened to your window?
A stag got lost in the storm,
came through there.
Got a few scratches getting him out.
Are you scarred?
Probably more than I know.
I'll show you mine if you show me yours.
I don't have the right parts
for your proclivities, Margot.
It's a very psychological instrument.
Yes, we work with people the same way.
Never touching...
- Yeah.
- ... but guiding them from
dissonance toward composition.
But people are not instruments.
Whatever it is you're playing, Hannibal,
you have to listen very carefully
to what you're creating.
I'm listening.
I'm listening to you.
You and I went so long in our friendship
without ever touching,
yet I always felt attuned to you.
Who did this to you?
My brother.
Who shot you?
A friend.
I've always admired teachers,
molding impressionable young minds.
But you can only learn so much and live.
No one likes a know-it-all, Freddie.
Hannibal Lecter taught you when you
were an impressionable young mind.
Your book's about Will Graham,
it's not about me.
Were you sleeping with Hannibal Lecter
when you were his student,
or is that a recent development?
You are sleeping with him.
I was just guessing.
Figured you had to be sleeping
with one of them.
Maybe that's why you can't see it.
See what?
Will Graham was right
about Hannibal Lecter...
And I was right about Will Graham.
I'm not having this
or any other conversation with you, Freddie.
Hannibal Lecter had four patients die
while under his care.
Three former patients die after his care,
and then there's Will Graham.
All that fuss about Dr. Lecter.
Will even tried to kill him.
And now they're back in therapy together
and another former patient is dead.
Will understands that
Hannibal Lecter can help him.
Maybe what Will understands is,
if you can't beat Hannibal Lecter,
join him.
Dr. Lecter.
Mason Verger.
So very nice to meet you.
Thank you for accepting my invitation.
I'm prone to Old World politeness.
Would have seemed rude to say no.
Since I'm paying for Margot's therapy,
I thought I should at the very least
meet her psychiatrist.
I enjoy putting a face to the name.
Your swine are exceptional.
Never seen pigs like these.
They're a special breed.
Product of many years, many litters.
What's your ground note?
We started with giant forest pigs,
6 teats, 38 chromosomes,
a resourceful feeder,
and an opportunistic omnivore.
Just like man.
You must know pigs
as well as you know people.
- I do know pigs.
- Papa would've loved you.
He could feel the face of a hog and tell
by the bone structure its genetic makeup.
Breeding was very important to my father.
Margot really pissed him off with all her...
Button stitching.
No breeding there.
Do you have a sister, Dr. Lecter?
I had a sister.
Then you understand my need
to protect Margot, mostly from herself.
She's pathological.
I'm sure she's told you
horrible things that I've done.
I can't tell you
what Margot's confessed to me.
Fortunately for you, I can't tell anyone.
Got me.
Even the worst of us need
someone to talk to, Mason.
Have you ever considered
therapy for yourself?
Maybe I should.
Can I have Carlo slaughter you a hog?
A token of my appreciation
for all that you do for Margot.
Please.
But I must insist on selecting my own pig.
Always do.
Brined and roasted
whole suckling pig.
A gift from a friend.
A friend of yours, not a friend of the pig's.
There are those who raise livestock
and have a genuine affection for them.
The farmer who hand rears
lambs loves them
and sends them to slaughter.
They love and kill what they love.
And eat what they love.
It's a paradox.
Freddie Lounds thinks
the two of you are a paradox.
She sees something no one else sees.
What's that?
That neither of you is the killer
she's writing about,
but together, you might be.
Freddie Lounds must consider
you a bland interview subject
if she's already resorted to fiction.
She won't be fenced in by
something as malleable as the truth.
Freddie has no boundaries.
Someone with no boundaries
is a psychopath...
Or a journalist.
Freddie isn't the only one
without boundaries.
Your relationship doesn't
seem to know many.
Patient and therapist,
friend and enemy.
Crossing boundaries is
different than violating them.
Boundaries will always be
subject to negotiation.
It's just hard to know
where you are with each other.
We know where we are with each other.
Shouldn't that be enough?
Better the devil you know.
There really is a very good
explanation for all this.
I don't want to hear it.
Not just a little bit curious?
Get away from the door.
I can't let you go, Freddie.
Not till you've heard what I have to say.
I know you're scared.
You only have to be scared
a moment longer.
Give me the gun.
No!
Freddie Lounds left me
that message three hours ago.
Her cell signal is dead now.
Last call was traced
to the nearest phone tower in,
Wolf Trap, Virginia.
We have her on security cameras
at a gas station, filling up her car...
Six miles from your farm.
Freddie was supposed to interview me.
She never showed up.
Why are you granting interviews
to Freddie Lounds?
I owed her one.
Surely, Freddie Lounds
has more enemies than Will.
Not in Wolf Trap, Virginia.
I live in the middle of nowhere, Jack,
if someone wanted to take her, it's...
Not a bad place to do it.
And I provide the ingredients.
You tell me what we should do with them.
What's the meat?
What do you think?
Veal?
Pork, perhaps?
She was a slim and delicate pig.
I'll make you lomo saltado.
We will make it together.
You slice the ginger.
The meat has an interesting flavor.
Its braising...
Notes of citrus.
My palate isn't as refined as yours.
Apart from humane considerations,
it's more flavorful for animals
to be stress-free prior to slaughter.
This animal tastes frightened.
What does "frightened" taste like?
It's acidic.
The meat is bitter
about being dead.
This meat is not pork.
It's long pig.
You can't reduce me to...
A set of influences.
I'm not the product of anything.
I've given up good and evil for behaviorism.
Then you can't say that I'm evil.
You're destructive.
Same thing.
Evil is just destructive?
Storms are evil, if it's that simple.
And we have fire, and then there's hail.
Underwriters lump it all
under "Acts of God."
Is this meal an act of God, Will?