Previously on Hannibal...
We're just alike.
This gives you the capacity to deceive me
and be deceived by me.
Have you been firing a gun?
I told you, I was feeling paranoid.
All I want to do is catch him.
He's given me nothing.
I know what to expect from lung cancer.
And there will be a time
when there is nothing you can do.
No.
What are you up to?
I want you to come with me.
Alana Bloom isn't harboring any doubts.
She's convinced
that he murdered Freddie Lounds.
How was my funeral?
We're going to get caught.
Jack already suspects
you killed Freddie Lounds.
That means he suspects you.
I know.
You should give him what he wants.
Give him the Chesapeake Ripper?
Dr. Hannibal Lecter, requests the pleasure
of my company for dinner.
You sit in that chair, Will,
as you have so many times before.
It holds among its molecules
the vibrations of
all our conversations
ever held in its presence.
All the exchanges,
the petty irritations,
deadly revelations,
flat announcements of disaster.
The grunts and poetry of life.
Everything we've ever said.
Listen.
What do you hear?
A melody.
We're orchestrations of carbon.
You and me.
And Jack.
All our destinies flying and swimming
in blood and emptiness.
Everybody's settling in for dinner.
I'm wearing a wire.
I have sharp shooters on the roofs
of neighboring houses
with lines of sight to all the windows.
He'll try to kill you in the kitchen,
for convenience.
Make it easier to prepare the tartar.
Jack won't be easy to kill.
He'll be armed.
He's strong, well-trained.
We can't hesitate.
Hannibal thinks you are his man
in the room.
I think you're mine.
When the fox hears the rabbit scream,
he comes running.
But not to help.
When you hear Jack scream,
why will you come running?
When the moment comes...
...will you do what needs to be done?
Oh, yes.
See?
Forgiveness is such a profound,
conscious and unconscious state of affairs.
You can't actually choose to do it.
It simply happens to you.
Does forgiveness happen to you?
I died.
I'm between deaths.
The punctuation at the end of a sentence
gives meaning to every word.
Every space that preceded it.
You moved my punctuation mark, Dr. Lecter.
You moved my meaning.
I'm not here because I want to be.
You saw to that.
I'm here
because I can't abandon Jack.
Not again.
Love and death are the great hinges
on which all human sympathies turn.
What we do for ourselves dies with us.
What we do for others, that's beyond us.
You saved me for Jack.
Will you save him, for me,
when I'm gone?
I'm going to enjoy my resurrection.
Nothing sells better than a survival story.
I wouldn't count us as survivors
just yet, Freddie.
I'm counting me as a survivor.
I started as a cancer editor
at a supermarket tabloid.
Cancer is very lucrative media.
Ain't that the truth?
"New Cures for Cancer"
"Cancer Miracle Cure."
We're all desperate for a little hope.
I want to ask you
to do something for me, Freddie.
Or rather, don't.
Don't write about Abigail.
You can write about me.
You can write about Hannibal.
But leave Abigail alone.
You really don't know
if you're going to survive him, do you?
Just let her rest in peace.
These are your notes on me.
So they are.
Won't your patients need these
after you're gone?
The FBI will pore over my notes
if I left them intact.
I will spare my patients the scrutiny.
I'm dismantling who I was
and moving it brick by brick.
When we have gone from this life,
Jack Crawford and the FBI behind us,
I will always have this place.
In your memory palace?
My palace is vast,
even by medieval standards.
The foyer is the Norman Chapel in Palermo.
Severe, beautiful and timeless,
with a single reminder of mortality.
A skull, graven in the floor.
All I need is a stream.
In those moments when
you can't overcome your surroundings,
you can make it all go away.
Put my head back,
close my eyes,
wade into the quiet of the stream.
If I'm ever apprehended,
my memory palace will serve
as more than a mnemonic system.
I will live there.
Could you be happy there?
All the palace chambers are not lovely,
light and bright.
In the vaults of our hearts and brains,
danger waits.
There are holes in the floor of the mind.
In the few jerky seconds of sleep I do get,
all I see is dark,
swarming behind my eyelids.
I dream darkness comes into me.
It comes and it's insidious.
Up my nose, into my ears.
I feel poisoned.
We've all been poisoned.
You saw what no one else could.
All it took was the traumatic.
We're still in the thick of it.
We're getting through the worst of it.
You've set some sort of trap
and you're goading Hannibal into it.
How can you be sure he's not goading you?
I can't.
Do you know what an imago is, Will?
It's a flying insect.
It's the last stage of a transformation.
When you become who you will be?
It's also a term from the
dead religion of psychoanalysis.
An imago is an image of a loved one,
buried in the unconscious,
carried with us all our lives.
An ideal.
The concept of an ideal.
I have a concept of you,
just as you have a concept of me.
Neither of us ideal.
Both of us are too curious
about too many things for any ideals.
Is it ideal that Jack die?
It's necessary.
What happens to Jack
has been preordained.
We could disappear now.
Tonight.
Feed your dogs,
leave a note for Alana
and never see her or Jack again.
Almost polite.
Then this would be our last supper.
Of this life.
I served lamb.
Sacrificial.
I don't need a sacrifice.
Do you?
I need him to know.
If I confess to Jack Crawford right now...
I would forgive you.
If Jack were to tell you all is forgiven,
would you accept his forgiveness?
Jack isn't offering forgiveness.
He wants justice.
He wants to see you.
See who you are.
See what I've become.
He wants the truth.
To the truth, then.
And all its consequences.
This is entrapment, Jack.
You can't entrap someone
into committing premeditated murder.
Yes, you can. You're doing it.
You conspired to violate
Dr. Lecter's property and personal rights.
And for the record,
the only one involved in this investigation
we can confirm actually having
killed someone is Will Graham.
It was self-defense.
Hannibal Lecter is being induced
to commit murder
by an undercover FBI informant.
This is outrageous government conduct.
You would never get a conviction.
You're not thinking clearly, Jack.
We are as close as we are ever going to get
to catching this man.
I understand that your wife is very ill.
You're distracted.
After an inquiry, I'm putting you
on forced compassionate leave.
This is just staggering.
What are you going to do
about Hannibal Lecter?
What Jack should have done.
We've frozen his passport
and we're getting a search warrant.
Hannibal already opened his doors
to the FBI.
There won't be physical evidence.
The only way to catch him is in the act.
Are you saying we should have
just let Jack hang himself?
And everyone else in his department?
No. But Will and Jack are still
your best chance to catch Hannibal.
This man that Will Graham
killed in self-defense,
he was mutilated.
At a certain point, self-defense stops.
Will Graham didn't stop.
Jack Crawford sanctioned this
and then he hid it from us.
I have to believe that Will was trying
to maintain his cover identity.
Reality doesn't go away
because you stop believing in it.
It's stubborn like that.
The reality of this situation
is Jack Crawford misused
the power of his office.
Miss. Prurnell, they are desperate.
They are breaking the law.
I'm bringing these men up on charges.
They're not going to stop.
That's why they're being
brought into custody.
Jack knows what you'll find.
He knows what you have to do.
That won't stop him
from doing what he has to do.
- Hello?
- It's Alana. Is Jack with you?
No.
Why?
They've issued a warrant
for your arrest, Will.
For acting as an accessory to entrapment.
And for the murder of Randall Tier.
They're going to arrest Jack as well.
Will?
Goodbye, Alana.
Hello?
They know.
Hello, Jack.
You're early.
I couldn't wait to get here.
Would you care to sous-chef?
I want to thank you
for your friendship, Hannibal.
The most beautiful quality
of a true friendship is to understand
and be understood with absolute clarity.
Then this is
the clearest moment of our friendship.
I'd like to report gunshots.
Hannibal.
Hannibal!
Where's Jack?
In the pantry.
I was hoping you and I
wouldn't have to say goodbye.
Nothing seen nor said.
You may have found that rude.
Stop!
I was so blind.
In your defense,
I worked very hard to blind you.
You can stay blind.
You can hide from this.
Walk away.
I'll make no plans to call on you.
But if you stay,
I will kill you.
Be blind, Alana. Don't be brave.
I took your bullets.
I found more bullets!
Abigail?
I'm so sorry.
This is Will Graham.
I need ERT at 5 Chandel Square.
Jack is inside.
Go.
Abigail?
I didn't know what else to do,
so I just did what he told me.
Where is he?
You were supposed to leave.
We couldn't leave without you.
Time did reverse.
The teacup that I shattered
did come together.
The place was made for Abigail
in your world.
Do you understand?
That place was made for all of us, together.
I wanted to surprise you.
And you,
you wanted to surprise me.
I let you know me.
See me.
I gave you a rare gift.
- But you didn't want it.
- Didn't I?
You would deny me my life.
No. No. Not your life, no.
My freedom then.
You would take that from me.
Confine me to a prison cell.
Do you believe you could change me,
the way I've changed you?
I already did.
Fate and circumstance
have returned us to this moment
when the teacup shatters.
I forgive you, Will.
Will you forgive me?
Don't.
Abigail, come to me.
No, no, no!
You can make it all go away.
Put your head back.
Close your eyes.
Wade into the quiet of the stream.
Hello? Jack.