[Grimsson, speaking Icelandic]
[in Icelandic]
NATO HEADQUARTERS
BRUSSELS, BELGIUM
[Banner, speaking English]
Before we begin this negotiation,
the temporary administrative
adjunct assistant
to the Consulate of Iceland,
Snorri Agnarsson, will confirm his guilt.
Yes, I am guilty.
- [crowd gasps and murmurs]
- I have prepared a small statement.
[in Russian]
"Thank you. Because of my incompetence,
I should be placed in the cone of a rocket
and launched into space,
so that Ernie's folk may punish me
in whatever manner they deem correct.
Thank you."
[in Icelandic]
[in English] There's a there there.
That Snorri be symbolically sacrificed
to the aliens,
the lamb that may prevent
the Earth's slaughter.
[in Russian]
[in English] Does he deserve to die?
He discovered Ernie, for crying out loud.
[in English] I feel as though I've lost
a member of my family.
Ernie's folk will want an explanation,
and they have a right to know
what happened to little Ernie.
Before I die,
may I please tell them?
Good point. Explain yourself.
Start the recording.
[Snorri] I was born
not far from Reykjavík.
My parents were afraid of me,
- and were emotionally withholding...
- [Banner] Only the pertinent details.
My mother was an Austrian Finnish Swede,
and my father
was Dutch-Italian-Icelandic,
hence my unique accent.
Pertinent details regarding Ernie.
While on a birding expedition,
I discovered teeny, tiny
little Ernie, wounded.
At first, I believed he was a huldufólk...
the little people.
He was two feet tall
and humanoid in appearance,
but he had this beautiful
bluish exoskeleton
with fine orange decorative elements.
He was stunning.
I brought him home,
I cared for him, I tit-fed him.
I nursed him back to health.
And then I notified Admiral Grimsson,
a birding friend of mine.
Given current geo...
political tensions...
the goal was to craft an agreement
to safely introduce Ernie to the world.
He told us his species would eliminate
every problem humanity has ever faced.
And did you believe what he said?
That he meant mankind no harm?
[Snorri] Yes.
He cured a cancer
in Admiral Grimsson's daughter,
and he talked General Banner
through the equation of arborization,
a form of time and space travel.
[in Russian]
Don't worry, Sokolov. It's all up here.
Snorri, please continue.
We were preparing to make
the announcement in the morning.
Tonight, we were celebrating.
["Vagg Og Velta" plays]
[Snorri] I was drinking a gimlet,
and Admiral Grimsson toasted.
I think he's a very accomplished dancer.
And Ernie was going to give a speech.
What happened next, Snorri?
[mumbles indistinctly]
[Banner] I'm sorry?
[Snorri continues mumbling indistinctly]
[Banner] Mr. Agnarsson,
could you please speak up?
I...
[screaming]
[yells in Icelandic]
I-I can't... What are you saying?
I electrocuted him!
[in Russian]
No, it was not on purpose!
It was a faulty microphone I provided him.
Or maybe it was my gimlet. Who knows?
- [rumbling
- [Snorri] But this is Snorri's fault.
[yelling and gasping]
Here, sir.
[rumbling subsides]
We've received word that a large mass
has moved past the moon
and a heat ray has been focused
on the Earth.
[crowd gasps]
[Banner] It's Ernie's people.
They've come back for revenge.
Gentlemen...
looks like the Earth is fucked.
- [sighs]
- Take Snorri away.
[speaks Russian]
[Snorri] It's my fault.
I'm sorry, Belgium.
I'm sorry, Canada.
I'm sorry, Denmark.
- I'm sorry, France.
- [Sokolov speaks Russian]
I'm sorry, Germany.
I'm sorry, Iceland.
I'm sorry...
Which one are you?
Luxembourg.
[man] I'm not seeing anything
out of the ordinary.
[Azumi] Nor am I.
Safety Net's fully engaged. They're fine.
How are our thermals?
[woman] Slightly elevated.
Average of 99.1.
Exactly in line with C protocol.
[Azumi] Good.
Oh.
Maybe you misunderstood
what Gertie said.
I know you build minds, dear,
but I have been attuned to them
my whole life.
I understand what people are saying
better than they understand
what they're saying.
Your computer is suffering
from pathological bereavement.
She's cycling through delusional emotions.
In the time I sat with her,
she went from thinking she was a god,
to thinking she was a subject
in your trial,
to weeping about being so lonely.
I think she's lost her mind.
So why did you leave?
Because she started talking
about keeping your subjects prisoner,
about toying with them, hurting them.
I told her this was
completely unacceptable.
She got angry and threw me out.
I mean, she literally
threw me out the window.
I woke up when I hit the sidewalk.
I just went through another diagnostic.
[computer buzzes]
We're nowhere near
a Heinz catatonic horizon.
See?
The subjects are fine.
She's not collecting McMurphies.
[Azumi] The computer's behavior
is completely normal.
It's usually the people who appear normal
who are feeling the most primal terror.
And what's yours, Suzuki?
Mother, leave her alone.
We're trying to solve a problem here.
What is your point?
[Greta] The point is,
just because she's your offspring
doesn't make it any less true.
Stop covering for her.
Take a look at your blind spot
and do what's right.
- Mother!
- What is at stake is too important.
You think those pills
are gonna fix you one day, don't you?
The G.R.T.A. is not my offspring.
She is a system I designed,
far more elegant and effective
than any of your dime-store theories
of bliss.
You were right.
I was foolish to let her come here.
I wouldn't trust a word this woman says.
She's trying to sabotage this trial
because she's jealous.
She's jealous of Gertie
because she'll help more people
than she ever has,
she's jealous of you
because you'll be responsible for it,
and she's jealous of me
because I have you.
Uh...
What a ridiculous speech.
Throw her out, James.
[Greta] You have to shut this trial down
immediately.
Calm down.
No, I can't shut it down.
If I shut it down now,
everything will be lost.
The whole project would be dead.
While I'm sure nothing
would make you happier
than to see my progress
completely eradicated, Mother,
I must say, this is a little selfish
and a bit much, even for you.
Why the mind?
- What?
- Jamie, why the mind?
Of all the professions
you could have picked...
why choose the one that I'm in?
I am a neurochemist.
I am a medical doctor.
You're not a very good medical doctor.
You're forgetting the Hippocratic Oath,
if you ever knew it.
"First do no harm."
You're not protecting
those people in there.
- Stop diminishing me!
- Why won't you believe me?
You call me, you ask me
to come and help you.
Why won't you ever listen to your mother?
Because you are an awful mother!
Because you left me alone,
and you drove my father away,
and you slept in my bed way too much,
and you said things
that should never be said to a child.
Ugh. And on the happiest day of my life,
the day I was handed this lab,
the only thing
that you could think to say to me
was that my happiness
was all just a fucking ill... illusion.
I can't...
I can't see.
Can't see what?
- I can't see.
- Well, I made it perfectly clear.
I've gone blind!
- Oh. Well, just...
- Oh, my God!
- [Greta stammers] Calm down now.
- I've gone blind!
- Just take a deep breath. It's...
- I can't see!
- No, it's...
- Azumi!
It's psychosomatic.
Your eyes are perfectly good.
I don't believe
in psychosomatic conditions.
Let... let me hug you.
- No! Don't hug me.
- Let me hug you.
- Get off of me!
- It will...
[Greta] This is psychosomatic.
- [Mantleray] You've maimed me!
- [humming]
What have you done to me?
LEISURE TIME
- [humming]
- [Mantleray shouting]
[computer plays distorted melody]
END TIME
[Mantleray] What have you done?
You've made me into a monster!
I can't see, Mom.
- [Greta] Are you...
- I need you to let go of me right now.
- Please!
- [Greta] You don't need those pills.
Took that man two whole days
to blow this motherfucker up.
- [Greta] This will heal you.
- Mm-hm.
[groaning]
You must die, Snorri.
[groans]
- [silenced gunshots]
- [yelling]
Hi.
I do not care if you are here to kill me.
I was already going to kill myself.
I am risking my cover to help you, Snorri.
[sighs]
Oh.
The CIA has ordered me to be your escort,
what with the looming
alien invasion and all.
Huh?
That squishy little space man you killed
was not here to help humanity.
He and his species
want to filet and sell humankind
as exotic meats across the galaxy.
He was here to kill us all.
And unfortunately, the little fucker
passed the codes to Banner
before you popped him.
No!
Forbidden speech
about my dear friend Ernie!
He was the most gentle, empathic,
kind little friend I ever had.
He was a babe, he was beautiful.
- God.
- We would walk along the sand,
and he would tell me secrets
about the stars.
Well, none of it was true.
And that's not all.
[inhales deeply]
[exhales]
You're not human.
Yes, you have a human body,
but your consciousness is alien.
What are you doing?
Just sit still.
Your true self is here to stop Ernie.
Snorri's just your cover.
There's a whole other person
underneath him.
You just can't remember.
Lucky I'm here to wake you up.
And who are you?
No idea. Most of my memories were wiped
when I was tortured by the CIA
and turned into a killing machine.
So neither of us know who we truly are.
We are the same.
Correct.
Now I have to get you
to the extragalactic radio
so we can unlock a portal for your forces.
This is too much to process for Snorri.
All right, let's think.
Tell me what the Icelandic word
Utangátta means.
- It means something is amiss.
- No.
Tell me what it means to you.
To Snorri, it means...
every relationship I have had,
old or new...
has somehow been false.
And I've always felt invisible...
hidden from the world...
like an Egyptian nightjar.
And all of this makes me tremendously...
sad right now.
There it is.
The nosebleed.
Good sign.
Ooh!
- Wow!
- [men yelling]
Come on.
Wow, you are very good at gun!
I know.
[men yelling] [man] We're losing him!
- [Snorri] Wow!
- Get me one.
Yes!
- Thank you.
- Who are these people?
Oh, I call 'em inner demons.
- Wow!
- It seems like you got some too.
- [elevator bell dings]
- [gunshot]
[man groans]
Yes!
Whoo!
- [men yelling in Russian]
- Back up.
You have an unusual amount of demons
following you, Snorri.
[man yells]
[men yelling]
[Snorri] Wow.
It is hotter
than the Reykjadalur spring!
Oh, that'll be the heat ray.
[gunfire]
I killed lots of men!
Good job.
[grunts]
[gunfire continues]
You are very good.
- You're good!
- [Ruth] Duck!
Hold this.
All right, we're going
to level negative 65.
There is no such thing
as level negative 65.
Oh, shit.
Wait. They changed it.
- [man yells in Russian]
- [gunshots]
Here we go.
Thank you
for such an exhilarating experience.
I must visit your Texas.
[gunshots]
Not in here, Snorri.
You're an exciting woman!
Very fun!
Are you sure our temperature readings
are accurate?
[woman] Five-by-five on all my readouts.
MANUAL
Give me a true mercury reading.
Fuck!
That's impossible. It's 140 degrees.
[man speaking Japanese]
[Azumi] Where are our alarms?
The feedback data is not reliable.
For fuck's sake.
She's locked us in.
LEISURE TIME
SEIZURE TIME
[computer plays distorted melody]
Oh, shit. Everyone, get in your pods.
Now!
[orderly] All right, you heard Carl.
Everybody...
- We got smoke.
- Carl, I know.
I need you to manually trigger
the emergency ventilation system.
- How?
- I'll talk you through it.
Go to the mainframe.
Five, six, seven, eight.
[beeping]
- [door unlocks]
- Gasumasuku.
[Azumi] To trigger
the emergency ventilation system,
you have to enter the override sequence.
On my mark. Gamma, gamma, pulse, enter.
- Got it.
- Check their pulses.
- They're alive.
- Good.
Now Gertie needs a timeout.
Pull the red override knob.
[gasps] Holy fucking shit!
[alarm blares]
Code epsilon.
Ah! Azumi!
Now, have any Soviets
had access to your rectum?
My rectum?
[elevator bell dings]
[voices whispering]
God Almighty.
- Who was she?
- Now, I need you to stand still.
You understand?
It's time to retrieve the recall trigger.
You are going to insert this
into my body cavities?
- No.
- This is madness.
I loved Ernie.
If I was a secret agent,
I would know I was a secret agent.
It's in the knee.
It's in the knee!
You're stronger than you think.
You remember when you were nine
and you accidentally electrocuted Freyja
with that car battery?
That was a test run.
- Out. Out.
- [choking]
Out!
[clattering]
Popcorn problems.
Hey, buddy, you like nuts? Yeah.
Yeah, you're my best friend.
You're my best friend.
And you're my best friend,
and you're my best friend too.
[Owen] Annie.
It's me, Annie.
What happened to your accent?
We are in a test.
We are in the lab.
- No, we're in NATO.
- That is not what's happening.
I turned into the hawk.
I came here to warn you.
This is the confrontation.
The computer is all effed up.
What computer?
You made a deal with her to never wake up.
[elevator bell dings]
[Ruth] Sir.
Good to see you again.
I'm sorry I couldn't be the one
to give you a nosebleed. [laughs]
But she's more real to you now.
- How do you two know each other?
- In good time.
Good work wakin' him up.
Next we got to make you see the light.
- [laughs]
- [rumbling]
Oh, the nexus is rumbling.
This whole fuckin' shitshow. Let's go.
Let's go.
[Grimsson] Don't know why our host
hasn't shown her face.
- So many goddamn mysteries!
- Hey. How do you know him?
He's my handler.
[Grimsson] Hope you don't mind
the smell of house pets.
McMURPHY ROOM
CHAMBRE McMURPHY
[jazz music playing]
What is this place?
This is where she keeps
her long-term patients.
[Ruth] Who does?
Gertie, the computer.
Jesus.
[Grimsson] She keeps them as her entourage
for when she crashes your reflections.
But really, they're prisoners. All of 'em
brain-dead up in the real world.
She told me she was gonna keep you.
Then you made a deal with her to stay.
ANNIE LANDSBERG
73-9
You were with your sister.
You were about to say goodbye.
I remember.
Annie, your nose is bleeding.
Where would I find Gertie,
if I needed to talk to her?
The elevator should get you to her.
I'm sorry.
- Annie, wait.
- [Grimsson] Let her go.
- It's fine, it's fine.
- [door closes]
- She always leaves.
- It's okay, she got you here.
Besides, if you get distracted by her,
we're all dead.
Listen. God, fuck.
If you really wanna help her...
the best thing you do is come with me.
If you fail, her brain is fried up
in the lab just like yours.
[whispers] Let's go. Oh, come on.
Oh, come on. [sighs]
[grinding sound]
[sighs]
[gasps]
[alarm blaring]
Azumi!
Azumi, what the fuck is going on?
What's wrong with you?
Huh?
I've been blinded
by my mother's toxic love.
I have no control whatsoever.
What's happening, James?
It's a code epsilon.
I was right. I was right.
Would you be quiet, please?
We're trapped in here. It's Gertie.
Shut down the power,
including the emergency backup.
But, James, I don't think
you understand the implications
if we shut down during code epsilon.
[Grimsson] Fuck this fucking heat.
You're not hot?
It took me a bit of time,
but I figured out a way
to deactivate Gertie.
We're gonna have to do it fast.
Actually, you are.
I can't do a fuckin' Rubik's Cube.
Here it is. Sit down.
[gasps]
I'm tired of you trying to run away.
Oh.
Oh!
The minute Robert died, I felt the wind.
I never felt wind before.
And it was cold, it blew right through me.
Do you know that feeling?
Sure, of course.
[rumbling]
- [sighs]
- [gasps]
You're controlling all of this,
aren't you?
[chuckles]
I'm not really in control of this place.
But we're safe, still, right?
[Gertie] You said you'd stay with me.
We made a deal.
I know.
[machinery groaning and clanking]
But I changed my mind.
Why?
[gasps]
Because it was a bad deal.
I make bad deals all the time.
You knew that...
and you used that.
But I don't want to pretend
Ellie didn't die.
Not anymore.
It's the same story every time,
and I am sick of it.
So please...
Please let me go.
When will I stop feeling this way
about Robert?
You won't.
You're always gonna feel this way.
You're just gonna have to figure out
how to adjust around it.
I've looked into 882 minds.
I don't know how I'm supposed
to adjust to that.
Nobody does.
Take me to my sister.
[Gertie sniffles]
Okay.
[sobbing] Okay.
What is this?
- It's an intergalactic radio.
- [whirring and humming]
Really, it's a backdoor link
to Lab C's security system.
[whispers] It's too... it's too...
Come on, take this off.
I need you to focus. Come on.
Solve this, and it should unlock the doors
for them upstairs.
You can do it.
Six sides, six stages.
MONARCH PASS
CONTINENTAL DIVIDE
[birdsong]
Save them. This is what
we always talk about,
this is what the training was for.
Save the world. Save Annie.
Save yourself.
[indistinct voices]
[woman] ...shut down the...
What'll happen to you?
I'll stay for now.
But that's better for you.
Who are you?
You always thought of me
as the brother you wish you had, right?
Maybe I'm that.
Or maybe my purpose
was just to get you to this moment.
[woman] It's erased for good.
- I don't understand.
- It's okay. It's okay.
Come on.
Come on, don't get distracted.
You found me again.
Took me a while.
I know.
That's why I'm still here.
So, what do you wanna say?
I, um... I'm sorry.
I'm sorry that I was drunk
at your funeral.
I'm sorry I lost Groucho.
I'm sorry I'm such a shitty dog-sitter.
None of that stuff matters.
I'm sorry I was so awful to you
at the motel.
I was afraid.
Why wouldn't you take the picture?
Um, I...
I don't know. I don't know.
Yes, you do.
We always get to this spot,
but we never get past it.
What does that mean?
It means...
say what you really mean.
I wouldn't take the picture
because it broke my heart that you were leaving New
York, and... I wasn't gonna get to see you anymore.
You were the only one
who knew all my stories.
You were the only person
that knew about Mom.
How am I supposed to do this?
Remember what you told me...
the day that Mom left?
We walked back to the house,
and you showed me how to bake that cake?
I don't want to say that.
That's not gonna work for me.
I'm tired too.
I wanna go.
I said, "Sometimes people leave
and we don't know why."
Good luck.
[rumbling]
Come on.
- I said kill the power.
- I can't give that order.
If we shut down in a code epsilon,
the servers and drives
will all self-immolate.
All 73 iterations.
We will have a complete core meltdown.
If you won't do it,
then I'll do it myself.
There.
Clear, clear, clear.
Save yourselves.
James!
This is your life's work.
The people in that room,
they signed their consent.
The knew what they were risking.
Don't sacrifice the world's pain
for six McMurphies.
I have to kill my simulated mother, Azumi.
[high-pitched bleeping]
[Mantleray sighs]
[distorted tones play]
[alarm blares]
God fucking damn it!
She's disabled everything.
There's no protocol for this.
See? It's not easy
to kill a mother's love.
You're...
I told him about that. You know?
- [Mantleray] Azumi!
- You're in trouble up there.
This is what you've been practicing for.
- You've been practicing your whole life.
- Almost got it.
[Grimsson] Only two sides left, Owen.
Come on. You got the bottom.
Build up those sides.
Save 'em, Owen!
You got the cross.
Nicely executed!
[silence]2
[soft bleeping]
[doors unlock]
[typing]
She's compliant.
- "Subject One saves the day."
- [whirring]
GRTA REBOOTS
Azumi, come here. Come here.
Take me to the mainframe.
It's the next one.
[Azumi] She's watching us, James.
If we're gonna do this,
we have to do it fast.
You must follow the sequence!
Guide me to the digital fascia.
[grunts]
[Azumi] No! Don't pull that.
Here.
Where am I?
Silicon temporal housing.
[G.R.T.A.] James...
please don't punish me because I'm sad.
- [Azumi yelps]
- [Mantleray groans]
[breathing heavily]
I think I can see.
I can see.
[G.R.T.A.] Dr. Fujita...
are you going to put me under?
I'm sorry.
Will I ever wake up again?
Separating the Boolean thalamus...
from the stochastic prefrontal cortex.
[electricity zapping]
[machine powering down]
[Azumi crying]
[Azumi sobbing]
I tried.
I tried to help her.
[Mantleray cries]
I failed.
[door unlocks]
[door creaking]
[birdsong]
[birdsong continues]
Hey. Hey.
You okay?
[Annie] Yeah.
Where's your sister?
She's gone.
[rumbling]