I brought you here tonight
to sign a petition
so we can try to bring
an end to this nightmare.
I think a lot
about being a doctor again.
A way to make
amends for the pain
that we have caused others
is to give back.
You need to get
to a hospital immediately.
Fuck off.
Come to New Orleans.
I'll be the regional manager.
We'll make a fortune there.
A black box label
indicates the drug is
much more dangerous.
Absolutely not.
I don't believe
you will find support
at Main Justice
for felony charges
against these individuals.
Excuse me,
ladies and gentlemen.
After careful consideration,
I have decided to indict
Michael Friedman,
Paul Goldenheim,
and Howard Udell
on felony charges.
I'm starting
Suboxone tomorrow.
Give me one hell of a send-off.
Got it.
Beth is in heaven now.
Shame on Sackler!
Take down their name!
No longer!
No longer.
400,000 dead, 400,000 dead,
400,000...
Sacklers lie, people die!
Shame on Sackler!
Your record since
the plea deal continues
to be clean, which is good.
You also continue to pass
your drug tests, also good.
You're on path
to complete your probation
in three months' time.
Have you thought
about what you'll do then?
Well, I really want
to get my medical license back,
but I can't do that
as long as I'm on Suboxone.
How long do you think
you'll be on the MAT for?
I don't know.
Um...
I'm afraid I'll relapse
if I stop.
If you choose
to stay on the MAT,
you need to consider
a profession
that doesn't require
a medical license.
Yeah, okay.
Hey, Elizabeth Ann.
How you doing?
What--
what are you doing here?
Same as you, Doc.
You had enough to eat,
enough sleep?
You don't--
Can you just leave me alone?
Hey, you.
What if I wait outside for you?
When you're done in here,
I'll take you to lunch.
We'll visit a little bit
and catch up.
You know,
I'll buy you anything you want.
If you don't eat it,
you can take it home.
How was your meeting?
Not great.
I got two years left,
and she keeps telling me
I'll probably end up
back in jail.
Yeah, they all think
we're just a bunch of,
you know, worthless junkies.
They don't get it.
They don't know that
if we don't have this stuff,
it feels like we can't breathe.
If I stop, I'll die.
And if I don't stop, I'll die.
So I guess I'm gonna die.
So that's kind of why
I wanted to talk to you.
Okay?
I'm seeing this doctor.
And I'm on this new medication,
and it's really helped me.
I haven't relapsed in a year,
and my mind is coming back
like it used to be
before all this.
Really?
Yeah, really.
Hey.
Elizabeth Ann, you're young.
You got an entire future
that you could do anything.
You could go to college
if you wanted to go to college.
You could if you wanted to.
You could.
Listen to me.
I will personally drive you
to this doctor
I've been seeing.
I'll drive you there,
and I'll you drive back.
And I'll take you
to therapy twice a week,
and I'll pay for all of it.
What's in it for you?
I delivered you, girl.
Ain't no one thing
in this world
I wouldn't do
to help you get better
when you're sick, nothing.
I'll try it.
But no promises
I'll keep going.
Okay, okay, fair enough.
Today, we are here
to celebrate the promotion
of Amber Collins.
Look, all I have to say is,
New Orleans better watch out
because they got a bitch tiger
coming their way!
Cheers!
Sayonara, you motherfuckers.
Hi.
Hey.
Someone hasn't put in
their transfer to Nola yet.
I was giving it
some space between you leaving,
so they're not suspicious.
Are you not coming?
Of course I'm still coming.
'Cause I'm a big girl.
If you changed your mind,
you can tell me.
I haven't changed my mind.
Good, I wanna make this work.
Me too.
You better.
Hey, Billy.
Um, I gotta run
a few things past you.
Can you swing by my office
in say, ten?
Sure.
Okay.
Shut the door for me, Billy.
Sure.
Have a seat.
Yeah.
How's it going?
These are two lawyers
from headquarters.
I have some concern
over three training tapes
that went missing
from my office.
And you were
in here alone last week.
Right.
Um...
I didn't take--if that's...
I don't know anything
about any missing tapes.
If Purdue property were
to show up in the media
or in the hands
of law enforcement,
and those tapes were
traced back to you,
we would sue you
for stolen property,
breach of contract,
and misappropriation
of trade secrets.
We'll bankrupt you
with litigation
for the rest of your life.
But I didn't--I didn't--
I didn't take 'em.
I didn't take the tapes.
Several people,
including myself,
have noticed
a very negative attitude
towards your work of late.
We think it's best
to terminate your contract.
Um...
Okay.
This is
a nondisclosure agreement.
If you sign it,
you'll get a severance package
of $75,000.
I would need to show this
to my lawyer first, but I--
No, you need to sign it
right now, right here.
If you don't, you get nothing,
and you make
yourself vulnerable
to future litigation.
Billy, come on.
This doesn't have to get ugly.
If you did take the tapes,
this will smooth it all out,
as long as you destroy
those tapes right away.
You are not gonna get
a better deal than this.
And the flip side,
flip side could get really bad.
Do what you do best,
and take the money.
Clear the way, Clear the way!
Are you friends with him?
No.
I always thought
he was kind of a tool.
All right?
I remember you were
one of my smartest.
You were probably
the smartest patient I had.
Always reading a book,
you know.
I'm looking for something new.
You got any favorites?
How'd it go?
She did very well.
She took her first dose,
and she needs to wait here
an hour to make sure
she doesn't have an adverse
reaction to the medication.
All right, okay.
Well then, we'll just
stay put for a minute.
I'll see you in a week,
young lady.
Thanks, Doc.
He's a good guy.
You okay?
Vanity Fair.
What?
You should read Vanity Fair
by William
Makepeace Thackeray.
It's one of my favorites.
People think
it's a girls' book,
but it's really
more than that.
What's it about?
It's about this poor girl,
Becky,
who's smart, and cunning,
and determined
to make her way
into London society.
But, of course,
it's not easy,
'cause all those snobs care
about is status and class.
Sounds about right.
Neither Purdue, nor the FDA,
nor the DEA,
nor the medical community
anticipated the extent
of this problem.
Purdue's marketing practices
have not played a role
in the criminal activities
of doctors
who illegally prescribe
OxyContin for cash
and have not
encouraged robberies
from pharmacies or patients.
From Dr. Goldenheim's
personal emails,
we can prove that he knew
his testimony
before Congress was false.
He was aware the reports
of patient abuse are not rare,
as they were described
in countless
newspaper articles,
some of which were emailed
directly to Dr. Goldenheim.
This testimony was taken
in D.C.,
so it's not admissible
in the state of Virginia case.
Well, the state
of Virginia is a Commonwealth,
and we thought
you might bring that up.
We uncovered that transcripts
from Goldenheim's, Udell's,
and Friedman's false
Congressional testimony
were faxed to sales reps
all over the country
to show them top executives,
quote, "had their backs."
And one of the places
that it was faxed to
was here in Virginia,
which makes it not
only admissible,
but we'll now also be charging
wire fraud and conspiracy
to commit wire fraud
based on the use of wires
to transmit
this false testimony.
You really think
a judge will go for that?
You really think they won't?
My client will not
move forward
with any settlement
that involves felony charges
against individual executives.
However, I am authorized
to offer a financial settlement
to resolve this matter.
How much?
$10 million.
The Commonwealth
of Virginia counters
at 1.6 billion.
Is that a joke?
No, and since we have
Michael Friedman, Howard Udell,
and Paul Goldenheim
all dead to rights
on lying to Congress
and conspiracy to defraud,
there will be no deal
until they plead guilty
to felony charges as well.
Thank you, gentlemen.
Thank you for coming by.
These assholes
really do think
they're just gonna barrel
right over us.
I mean, 10 million?
Fuck those guys.
How long before
they find out Main Justice
doesn't want to pursue felony
charges against individuals?
Well, they probably
already know through Giuliani,
but it doesn't really make
a difference.
We're just gonna keep moving
ahead like it's happening.
We don't indict,
we lose any shot
of getting 'em to flip
on the Sacklers.
Yeah, I get that, but look.
If we're gonna move
Main Justice on indictments,
it's going
to take something significant
to change their mind.
I mean, it's gonna take
something emotional.
It's gonna take something
egregious that might
publicly blow up in their face
if they don't indict.
Of course.
We'll keep looking.
Thank you, sir.
Anything with
breakthrough pain?
Covered it.
Maybe new way
into blood charts?
Maybe a direct link
to Richard Sackler
ordering
the graph manipulation?
If it was there,
we'd have it.
We never did
anything substantial
with Toppers Contest.
You think
a drug-selling competition
with a powerful narcotic
might move Main Justice?
Hey, Jerry.
You mind if I come in?
Sure.
Diane.
I haven't really
been able to sleep
since I heard about Betsy.
And...
I'm sorry I didn't come
to the funeral.
We didn't want you there.
Well, that's why
I didn't come.
If I could change places
with her,
I would.
I heard you got off that stuff.
Is that true?
You know, one day at a time.
Good for you.
Hey, man.
I sure am sorry, Jerry.
Look,
ain't nothing either one of us
can say gonna
change anything.
Or make us feel
any different, really.
So just go on
and live your life, Doc.
Yeah.
Well...
All right.
You take care.
You too now.
"I never wanted
to tell anyone
"my dream was to be a famous
writer living in Paris
"'cause I knew
they'd all laugh at me.
"But I wrote almost every day
till the drugs took over.
"I liked how they made the fear
"I had of not
being successful go away.
But the shame I feel
outweighs any of that."
Hey, wait, I'm stopping you.
I don't want to hear
about shame.
I want to hear about Paris.
That was great, wasn't it, Doc?
Heck yeah, it was,
really great, really great.
You know what I want
you guys to do?
Write about your
favorite memory, all right?
Write something
about your favorite memory,
and you can make it fun.
It's okay to have fun with it.
Hey, Doc.
I mean, Sam.
It's real nice of you
to keep driving us like this,
but you live an hour east,
and this takes up a whole day.
Why don't you move back
to Finch Creek?
No, no, no, no, no.
No, don't think that's
a good idea.
I don't think--
I don't think anybody
wants me back in Finch Creek.
So?
Nobody wants me there.
You should come back.
Nah.
No, I don't think
I could ever go back.
Purdue Pharma.
Ever since I left that place,
I've been trying
to put it out of my mind.
So what are you guys
looking for?
We'd like to discuss
a sales competition
known as Toppers Contest.
Right.
Was it effective?
Yeah, yeah, it was,
like gangbusters.
You've got every rep
in the country
selling as hard
as they can for,
you know, a free trip
to Bermuda or Palm Springs.
You ever seen
any other pharma company
do something like that before?
You guys mind taking a walk?
All right, look,
to answer your question, no.
The bonus structure
was unbelievable.
The more milligrams you sold,
the more money you made.
No one else does that.
Did it bother you
that sales reps
were financially motivated
to sell higher doses?
Not at first.
I mean, look,
they tricked the managers
the same way
they played the reps.
They would give us all
this data from pain societies
that made everything
seem so legit.
So why'd you finally leave?
Yeah, so hold on.
So I kept having
to appear in court
for all these lawsuits
that were coming in.
I show up one day
to a deposition,
and Purdue doesn't have
a lawyer for me.
They left me on my own,
and I knew right then
I have got to get out,
or I'm gonna end up
in some serious shit.
So why didn't they have
a lawyer for you?
They were pissed.
One of my sales reps stole
some training session tapes
out of my office,
and they were scared
that they were gonna leak them
to the press.
Well, Billy, thanks for
seeing us on such short notice.
Sure grateful to you.
That's--
that's all right.
I kind of knew
this day was coming.
I figured I'd have to account
for my sins eventually.
So, what would you like me
to do, testify or...
You didn't sign an NDA?
No, um, I couldn't.
I just couldn't keep
taking their money anymore,
so I didn't sign.
I can tell you
whatever you want to know.
What we want are
those videotapes.
Tapes?
I...
I don't have any tapes.
We think you do.
I'm sorry.
I don't.
Listen.
You know,
we all done things in our lives
that we aren't proud of.
But we make amends by trying
by trying to make the future
a better place for others.
And, hey,
you have
a real opportunity here.
You could help millions
of people
avoid the pain
brought to so many.
I did not take those tapes.
And if I did,
they were destroyed
a long time ago.
Unless you have a subpoena,
this interview's over.
And if you do,
we won't continue
without an attorney present.
This is my wife,
Kaitlyn.
We're at law school together.
Is it a boy or girl?
Boy.
Okay.
Well, good luck in law school.
What--what field
are you thinking of?
Consumer protection.
That's perfect.
You can protect the public
from people like yourself.
Y'all have a nice day.
We'll let ourselves out.
Sir.
Dr. Richard,
th-there's a petition
going around Virginia.
I thought
it was West Virginia.
No, it was Virginia.
Like there's a difference.
Exactly.
So I guess a nun
and a country doctor
formed a community coalition.
I'm sorry, a--a nun
and a country doc...
did they walk into a bar?
Richard, they collected
10,000 signatures
on a petition to recall OC,
pull it from the market,
and reformulate it
to make it safer.
And sent the petition
to the FDA,
where it has
not gone unnoticed.
Okay.
Go to West Virginia
and resolve the situation.
Um, how would you
like it resolved?
What did we spend in Florida?
A little over two million.
No, just take care of this.
Yes, sir.
Dr. Van Zee, Sister Beth.
How're you doing?
Howard Udell, Purdue Pharma.
Nice to meet you.
A real pleasure.
This is my wife, Sue Ella.
Thank you for meeting us.
It was a real surprise
to hear from you.
Of course,
we were very concerned
when we saw your petition.
Sister Beth, I've actually
known quite a few nuns.
I'm still good friends
with a Sister Julie, so...
That's wonderful
that you know other nuns.
It makes me feel
a closeness to you
I have never
before experienced.
Before we discuss
our petition,
we wanted you to hear
a personal story
from a parent who lost
their child to addiction,
so you could get
an understanding
of how your drug
has affected the community.
Hello.
My daughter Betsy was
a quiet, hardworking girl.
After she hurt
her back on her job,
she started taking OxyContin,
and within a year,
she was a liar, a thief,
and a heroin addict.
No matter what she did,
she couldn't stop.
And she tried.
When she died from an overdose,
there was a part of me
that was relieved
that she was finally
out of her pain.
But that pain lives in me now
and in her father.
OxyContin destroyed our family
like it has so many others.
And we hope you can find
a way to make it safer.
Thank you.
That's Betsy.
Yeah.
Thank you for this story.
And, um, we're so sorry
for your loss.
Our coalition
has gathered a petition
with 10,000 signatures
requesting you
reformulate OxyContin.
We know this is possible
because in 1983,
Sterling-Winthrop pulled
their painkiller Talwin
and added a narcotic blocker,
which immediately
reduced abuse.
Thank you, Dr. Van Zee.
We have carefully looked
into this,
and one of the reasons
we came down here was
to pay you the respect
of giving you a preview
of an open letter
to your community
that we are going to publish.
And I'd like to read it
for you now, if I may.
"Dear Lee County,
at Purdue Pharma,
"we are aware there has been
an issue in your community
"with drug diversion involving
our painkiller OxyContin.
"We take very seriously
these issues,
"and we want you to know
we have heard you.
"We understand
there is a request
"to reformulate the drug,
"but unfortunately,
at this time,
"it is not easy to do,
"and we do not plan
on taking that action.
Our main issue--"
You don't care.
You don't care
that it's killing people.
You know it's dangerous.
You just wanna make
as much money as possible.
That is absolutely untrue,
ma'am.
You've done more to hurt
the people of Appalachia
than the coal industry
ever thought about doing.
Yeah, ma'am,
I resent that accusation.
My family goes back here
for generations.
This whole meeting is
a setup, it's a setup!
Let's all calm down please.
Ma'am, I'm sorry to interrupt.
It is not a setup.
The main reason
we came here was
to make a donation
to your coalition,
which we know is
doing tremendous work.
What kind of donation?
Howard...
Purdue Pharma just wants
to help.
So in that spirit,
we'd like to donate $100,000
to your group as a gesture
of goodwill
to help the community.
That's--that's very generous.
We'll need to discuss it.
Of course.
The number of new patients
I could give free care
to would be significant.
That money would make
a huge difference around here.
If we can get something
out of these people,
I think we should.
One bad month, and you
could be shut down for good.
What do you think, Diane?
Well, I don't know much
about these matters,
but if it would
help people down here,
then I think it might be
a good idea to take it.
You might be right.
Sister Beth?
Well...
You know, I'm not
from this region originally,
but I have been living here
for over 30 years,
and I've seen
a lot of things.
I've seen coal executives
fly in for generations
and use their money
to shut down unions
and manipulate this region
into lower labor costs.
That's just what
wealthy people do.
They take advantage
of the folks
that don't have money
to fight back.
That's what Purdue is doing
in this very moment.
So you wanna take their payoff
to shut us all up,
you go ahead.
But if you do that,
I will quit this coalition
right here and now because
I would rather burn in hell
than take a penny
of their blood money.
Hey, Karen?
You know what this is?
There's no return address.
No, but it was marked urgent,
so I just left it on your desk.
Do you think it's dangerous?
I don't hear ticking.
Stop it.
What's going on?
Somebody sent Rick a bomb.
Well, we only got a thousand
potential suspects, so...
What is it?
Purdue Pharma training tapes.
I'll be.
Looks like
Billy found his soul.
Emphasize
the time release coding.
It makes our drug
less addictive,
less prone to abuse.
It makes it almost impossible
to extract oxycodone
from the drug
in order to snort or inject.
If the--
There's hours
of tape just like this
showing Purdue sales reps being
trained to lie, manipulate,
and aggressively sell
addictive narcotics
as nonaddictive.
It is absolutely outrageous.
And we now have an open-
and-shut case of misbranding,
mail fraud, wire fraud,
and because the company
profited from illegal activity,
we've got money laundering
as well.
We need to discuss this
with our client.
Of course.
I think we can get at least
100 million out of 'em.
I think so, too.
What does Main Justice say?
Any new indications
on individual indictments?
No, not yet.
But, you know,
the quiet tells me
that we've got 'em thinking.
Now you really gotta hit 'em
in the gut
with your prosecution memo.
Lay it all out for Main Justice
so that when they read it,
they know they've got no choice
but to indict these guys.
Yes, sir.
Proposed indictment
of Purdue Pharma,
Michael Friedman,
Howard R. Udell,
and Paul D. Goldenheim.
Perhaps no case
in our history rivals
the burden placed
on public health and safety
as that in the Western
District of Virginia.
It is our recommendation
to charge the defendants
with conspiracy,
mail fraud, wire fraud,
interstate distribution
of misbranded drug
with intent to defraud,
conspiracy to commit
money laundering,
and money laundering.
OxyContin abuse has
significantly impacted
the lives of millions
of Americans.
And the fraudulent scheme
and conduct articulated
in this matter has
a direct correlation
to the health of this region
and to the entire nation
as a whole.
Hello, Father.
Well, I see you've decided
to ruin
a perfectly good evening.
Good to see you too, Richard.
Let me guess.
Mortimer's kids
want more disbursements?
I've asked Stephen to join us
because we have
a very serious issue.
This is John Brownlee,
U.S. Attorney for the Western
District of Virginia.
I've taken care
of West Virginia.
Brownlee is the U.S. attorney
that covers Appalachia.
That's the region
where that nun
and that country doctor
rejected your offer.
I said, it's taken care of.
The FDA isn't going to respond
to their petition.
But this problem goes deeper
than a petition.
John Brownlee is former army,
spent four years
in the infantry,
left the military
to go to law school
with the intention
to be a prosecutor.
His father is currently
the secretary of the army.
Now, I'm telling you this
because he has opened
a secret grand jury
into Purdue Pharma.
Since when?
We think maybe four
or five months ago,
but we're not exactly sure.
Call the governor
or a senator.
They have no authority
over a U.S. attorney.
Now, these are
the assistant U.S. attorneys
running the case,
Rick Mountcastle
and Randy Ramseyer.
Both men are top prosecutors
and are driven
by a strong sense of justice.
Ramseyer--he referees
local high school sports
and has a deep connection
to the region.
Mountcastle used
to prosecute mobsters
and converted to Christianity
at the age of 40.
Why are you
telling me all this?
So that you understand
they cannot be bought.
They cannot be
pushed off the case.
They will not be seeking
our employment
when they leave office like
the U.S. attorney in Maine.
And it is very likely
that they will soon subpoena
Purdue's internal documents
to make a major case
against us.
The damage
a U.S. attorney can do
for a company like us
is staggering.
They can fine us to death.
And they can bring
criminal charges
against individuals.
You think that's possible?
It's not possible.
It's likely.
These people
in Appalachia are very angry,
and now their U.S. attorney
is coming for us.
We're gonna hire
Rudy Giuliani,
and he'll be able
to lobby high up
in the chain
of the Justice Department
and the White House,
but eventually there will
be a price to pay.
From this point on,
you need
to do everything you can
to reduce personal liability.
It's very possible
people are going to prison,
and I don't want that
to be you.
Elizabeth Ann?
Hello?
This is Sally Washington
from the Virginia
Health Department
returning for Samuel Finnix.
Yeah, yeah.
Thanks for calling me.
Listen, I will--I--
Fuck off, I know
you fucking took it from me!
Excuse me?
What was that?
Sorry, I was calling
about the, MAT clinics
in Virginia.
What about them?
Well, I've seen people have
really good results
with Suboxone and methadone,
and seems to me the problem is
that there are so few clinics
that people just can't
get access to the drugs.
I understand the problem,
but people don't want
treatments centers
in their community.
It's just
a political nonstarter,
I'm sorry to say.
Yeah, I understand.
Well, okay.
Well, thanks for your time.
Hey, Elizabeth Ann!
Hey, wake up!
Hey!
What are you doing?
I brought you coffee.
Thanks.
Come on.
I gotta get you
out of this place.
Did you work in the mines?
Yes, I did.
I was in that protest.
You are doing very well.
No relapses or craving
for opiates.
If you want, we can try
and taper you down.
You think one day I can
just be completely off it?
Like I said, it can be hard
to get off the medication
permanently,
but some do.
We won't know until we try.
So what do you think, Sam?
I just really wanna be
a doctor again.
What's up?
No good.
Fraud unit agreed
with your prosecution memo,
but unfortunately, it didn't
sway the criminal division.
Shit.
Look,
the career guys are with you,
but I think you'll
ultimately get blocked
by the political appointees.
This is so fucked.
I know, but there
may be a compromise here.
Purdue's hinting
they'd go for misdemeanors
against the execs.
Misdemeanors.
And the company
will plead guilty to felonies
and pay a substantial fine.
You'd end up with a big win.
Those executives belong
in jail.
But what happens if
you indict and lose in court?
I get nothing.
There's a lot
of risk with indicting.
Personally, I think you should
take the misdemeanors
before Main Justice
shuts it all down.
Randy.
Sir.
We would have been happy
to have come out to Roanoke.
It's a hell of a case.
A couple of AUSAs
in a strip mall
taking on one of the wealthiest
families in the country.
Did the memo get Main Justice
over the finish line
on felony charges?
I don't think it did.
But there's also a chance we go
to court and lose everything.
That's why I made a deal.
It's finished then.
It is.
All right, have a seat.
So the three executives
will plead to misdemeanors.
Significant consequences, and
there's three years' probation.
It's 400 hours of community
service, and their careers
in pharmaceuticals
are effectively over.
Misdemeanors.
But without felonies,
we got no shot
at any of them ever flipping
on the Sacklers.
Yeah,
but at the end of the day,
we're not sure
they would have.
Right.
And look,
I'll be honest with you guys.
I...
I think that this is about
as far as Main Justice
was going to let us go.
I'm sorry, sir.
I tried to build the case
in a way that Main Justice
couldn't just brush it
under the rug.
No, don't apologize.
You did an incredible job.
All right,
we got a hell of a lot here,
but the company is going to
plead guilty to misbranding.
We're also gonna have
a public sentencing
of the executives,
so we can shame the ever-living
shit out of them,
create a lot of negative media
attention around OxyContin.
Now, on the financial
settlement with Purdue,
they came at me again
with 10 million,
and I countered
with 600 million
and told them
I wouldn't budge.
So where'd you land?
600 million.
Congratulations, guys.
It's--
it's one of the highest
settlements ever paid
by a pharmaceutical company
in the history of the country.
Look, it's not everything
we wanted, but it's a big win.
Congratulations, sir.
Well done.
Randy, congrats.
Have a seat.
I know that sometimes
I have a bad habit
of ignoring people's feelings.
I've always been an outsider
in this family.
And my...
my personal life
took a--a path
I--I didn't expect.
I held a great deal
of resentment
that I unfairly took out
on the people around me,
pressures
of launching the drug.
But now that
it's doing so well,
it's time I--I focus
on my family
and--and mend
some of those fences.
I, think that's
a great idea.
I do as well.
So I'm going to step down
as president,
and I couldn't think
of a better person
to take over than you.
Are you serious, sir?
Very serious.
As you know, what's
most important to the board
is your loyalty to the family.
Of course, of course.
And, um,
you shall have it, sir.
Congratulations.
You're the new president
of Purdue Pharma.
Thank you, sir.
Hey, whoa!
No splashing.
Yeah?
I have the chief of staff
to the deputy
attorney general.
Okay.
Hey, John.
Sorry to call so late.
No, that's fine, Mr. Elston.
Mike, call me Mike.
Okay, Mike.
Look, I know
you're supposed to sign
the deal tomorrow with Purdue,
but Mary Jo White called.
Howard Udell's attorney.
Correct,
and she'd like to delay
finalizing the plea agreement.
She wants more time
to discuss it.
No, no, no, no, I'm sorry.
The time
for discussion is over.
I have a deal.
It's not signed yet.
No reason why you can't keep
talking with her.
Sorry,
is this request from you
or from the deputy
attorney general?
It's not coming from
the deputy attorney general.
Then you can go
fuck yourself.
Purdue signs tomorrow,
or we go to court.
I've been getting a lot
of tips on other pharma cases.
I'm thinking maybe we ought
to find another Purdue
to go after.
What's the point?
To get the bad guys again.
Did we get 'em?
Purdue's just gonna
keep on selling.
The field's just so compromised
with the government.
Well, gentlemen,
here you have it,
a signed guilty plea deal
from your friends and neighbors
at Purdue Pharma.
What were they like
when they signed?
Quiet, solemn.
How brave.
I still can't believe
Main Justice tried
to shut it down
the last second.
I can.
Thank you for pushing back.
I mean, I had to.
Needed to stop, or who knows
what could've happened?
Um, sir, can I speak to you?
There's an urgent issue.
Go ahead.
You can tell me
in front of these guys.
Okay.
A memo leaked from
the attorney general's office
of a list of U.S. attorneys
to be fired.
There's gonna be a wave
of firings.
Am I on the list?
I'm afraid so, sir, yes.
I'm sorry, sir.
Reject the plea!
We are live
at the Abingdon courthouse
for the sentencing hearing
of three Purdue pharma
executives for their role
in criminally misbranding
their drug OxyContin.
Now, there are a number
of protesters here
who want the plea deal
rejected,
enraged none of the executives
would go to prison.
Reject the plea!
Do you feel your
placement on the U.S. Attorney
firing list is because of
your involvement on this case?
You know, I don't know.
I don't know why
I was on the list.
Do you feel vindicated
since you weren't
ultimately fired?
Well, today--
today is not about me.
It's about the people here
and having their voices
be heard.
My grandson Brian is here
in the courtroom
with me today.
He lost his mother
to your horrible drug
when he was only six years old.
And I wanted him here
so he could see
that bad things do happen
to bad people.
You are sheer evil.
The first time that
I heard the word OxyContin,
my 18-year-old honor student
son was dead from it
after taking it at a party.
You are nothing more
than corporate drug lords.
You have killed
and continue to kill
our future of tomorrow.
And you killed my son
and so many others.
I know you don't care
about what happened
to our children.
But what if it was your son
or daughter
you saw in the morgue?
Would you care then?
On May 1st,
the year 2003,
my husband and I
lost our only son,
an 18-year-old son
named Randall,
to an accidental overdose
of OxyContin.
Right before this happened,
he was getting ready
to go to college.
We ended up using
his prepaid college
to pay for his funeral.
These are his ashes.
This is from your drug.
This is what you did to him.
Now he's here in the courtroom.
Reject the plea deal!
Money means nothing to them!
Let the punishment
fit the crime.
Reject the plea.
Reject the plea!
Order,
order in the court!
Order, order!
The lack of incarceration
in this case, to me,
is the most difficult aspect
of the plea agreements.
And I must confess
it bothers me.
And I have studied this case
for many months.
However, I have concluded
that the plea agreements
should be accepted.
While I understand this may
not be a popular decision,
it is my job to follow the law.
We're adjourned.
The first thing
you tell your doctors
is that the settlement
was grossly unfair.
These execs didn't have
anything to do
with what they were
charged with.
It was a few bad apples
we fired years ago.
What's most important is,
you keep selling aggressively
as possible.
This isn't a time for caution.
I'm going to fly
down there next week.
I will personally visit
doctors with you.
You need to push higher doses
for longer periods of time.
You have to get these doctors
to keep prescribing.
Sell, sell, sell.
Well, thank you very much.
We're going to look into that.
I appreciate it, buh-bye.
Hey, so...
You okay, boss?
What's up?
Well, I know you're not
gonna be over the Moon
at the prospect
of another pharma case,
but I just got some interesting
intel on Abbott Labs.
They got a drug
called Depakote.
It's an antiepileptic
medication,
and supposedly they have been
targeting nursing homes.
Why don't you give it
to the Eastern District?
We don't need to go down
that rabbit hole again.
You think maybe you ought
to take a couple of weeks off?
You know, recharge a bit.
Randy, I'm okay.
You guys have a visitor.
I brought sparkling cider.
I remembered you guys were
a couple pussies
that don't drink.
I know you were hoping
to never see me again,
but I really wanted
to toast to you guys
for staying the course.
Nothing's gonna change.
They'll just keep selling
as hard as they can.
Yes,
but you dealt the first blow,
and now there's convictions
and a legal record
of their crimes.
It's an important achievement
that people will be able to use
to build future cases on.
I worked in D.C. for years,
and I always knew
it could go down this way,
but given the facts--
I don't know, I had to try.
Cheers to that.
Here's to the ones
who fight the battles,
even if they don't win the war.
Okay.
Hear, hear.
So what are you guys
up to next?
We have another pharma case
we're looking into.
I... I really can't
thank you enough
for bringing this case.
I mean it.
I don't know
if I'd ever sleep
if the Sacklers
hadn't been publicly exposed.
And they will someday go down.
I know this in my heart.
I don't know.
400,000 deaths!
Under pressure from protests
led by artist Nan Goldin,
major museums are refusing
to accept future donations
from the Sackler family.
Louvre Museum in Paris
has become
the first major institution
to remove the Sackler
family name from plaques.
I lost my sister
in this epidemic, and--
so this is like
a really great win for us.
Members
of the Sackler family
are moving out
of New York City
after being publicly shamed
as a family that originated
the opioid crisis.
This morning,
my office filed a lawsuit
in Massachusetts State Court
against Purdue Pharma...
For fueling
the nation's opioid epidemic...
By knowingly deceiving
doctors and the public.
Attorney generals
in over 25 states
have brought class action
suits against Purdue Pharma.
David Sackler
and Dr. Kathe Sackler
recently went public to
defend the family's actions,
testifying remotely
at a Congressional hearing.
You knew
that it was too potent,
and you did nothing
about it as a family.
You have created
a nationwide epidemic.
You and your family are
addicted to money.
I'm not sure that
I'm aware of any family
in America
that's more evil than yours.
There is nothing
that I can find
that I would have
done differently.
Late today,
a federal bankruptcy judge
gave conditional approval
to a multi-billion dollar plan
to settle lawsuits
against Purdue Pharma.
The Sackler family
will forfeit ownership
of Purdue Pharma,
turn over 30 million
documents,
and pay $4.5 billion.
In return,
the Sacklers cannot be sued.
This process was stacked
from beginning.
They knew that
the Sacklers were betting
on a broken bankruptcy system
that would allow them
to use the bankruptcy
of the company
of Purdue Pharma
to shield themselves.
Let's be clear,
the Sacklers are not bankrupt.
As far as I can tell,
no Sackler will have
to sell a boat,
or a house, or a piece of art.
Dr. Finnix.
Yeah.
I need you
to sign these prescriptions
for Suboxone.
Yes, ma'am.
And you've got group
in ten minutes.
All right.
After group,
you've got individual patients
until 6:00 p.m.,
and then you have to attend
that fundraiser at 8:00 p.m.
I hate those.
I hate asking people
for money.
You want to keep
the lights on, don't you?
Yeah, you're right.
You're always right.
You know, what's so important
about these group sessions is
the chance to connect.
Addiction does
the exact opposite
of what connection does, right?
Addiction tears apart.
It tears apart friendships.
It tears apart marriages.
It'll tear apart a family,
tear apart a whole community.
Part of the reason
we relapse is
because of pain.
There's some kind of pain
that's in a lot of us,
or all of us,
we just don't want
to feel anymore.
And further we fall
into addiction,
pain says to us, hell,
we'd better off
just feeling nothing at all.
So we go numb.
And our souls go numb.
Now we've got a real problem.
You know, pain is just pain.
Not good, not bad,
just part
of being a human being.
And sometimes,
good can come out of it.
And if we're brave enough
and willing
to go a little deeper,
work our way through it,
and try to overcome it,
well,
we just might
find our better selves.