♪ ♪
The time has come
to redefine the nature of pain.
For too long,
the American medical community
has been ignoring chronic pain.
And this has created
an epidemic of suffering.
When we live with pain,
we are not living
our true selves.
We are not living
our best selves.
We're not even living at all,
because the pain overtakes
our ability to think, feel.
Even to love.
As you all know,
when our patent
for MS Contin expires,
it will deliver a significant
blow to the company,
because it comprises
25% of our sales.
However, I have a solution.
I propose we take
the extended time-release
of the Contin system
and create a new opioid
specifically designed
to treat moderate pain
for long-term use.
I don't see doctors
prescribing an opioid
for long-term pain.
- You don't chase a market.
- You create it.
Please, Richard...
tell me more.
Thank you, Uncle Arthur.
Dr. Peterson,
please tell the grand jury,
when did you first hear
about OxyContin?
Um, it was around
the summer of 1996.
A sales rep from Purdue Pharma
told me
that they had a new drug
that was very effective
in combating pain.
"Pain" was becoming
a big buzzword at the time.
There was a nationwide movement
to rethink
the treatment of pain.
Did Purdue Pharma
spearhead this campaign?
I believe they did.
I don't know if it was them
in particular,
but their sales reps
brought it up repeatedly.
The sales rep said
the drug was different
because it was basically
nonaddictive.
Had you ever heard
of a nonaddictive opioid?
No, sir, I had not.
And did he tell you
what percentage
of patients became addicted?
That was the key
to the whole sales pitch.
He said less than 1%
became addicted.
Less than 1% would
become addicted to OxyContin.
He said less than 1%.
He called it a miracle drug.
Dr. Finnix, did more than 1%
of your patients
become addicted to OxyContin?
♪ ♪
Dr. Finnix.
I can't believe how many
of them are dead now.
♪ ♪
♪ I'm just a poor ♪
♪ Wayfaring stranger ♪
♪ Traveling through ♪
♪ This world below ♪
♪ There is no sickness ♪
♪ No toil, nor danger ♪
♪ In that bright land ♪
Hey.
Doing good, Bets?
Fine, Dad.
♪ ♪
♪ I'm going there ♪
♪ To see my Father ♪
♪ And all my loved ones ♪
♪ Who've gone on ♪
♪ I'm just going ♪
♪ Over Jordan ♪
I put this rooster tail on,
or, as I call it,
my lucky rooster tail.
I've been working this pool
for at least an hour.
Not even a nibble,
and I'm starting to think,
"Well, my lucky rooster tail
probably isn't so lucky."
Jack, this is from
when you fell, right?
Yeah.
And all of a sudden,
this thing falls
down to the bottom,
and I feel this tug.
And I'm pulling,
and I'm pulling,
and I'm pulling on this thing.
Lift your--lift your arms up
for a minute.
I'm just gonna
give you Tylenol.
Take two
three times a day.
It's healing nicely.
So how am I
gonna pick my nose now?
Use that hand.
Now, this fish was this big.
Duane's a bullshitter.
It's not unusual
that it hasn't happened yet.
You're 14.
Don't worry about it.
For some girls,
it can happen when they're 11.
Others, 17.
It's just embarrassing.
There's nothing
to be embarrassed about.
Easy for me to say.
♪ ♪
I never thought that poor
girl was gonna stop crying.
Did you tell her it's gonna
mess up a few days a month
for the next 40 years?
Heh, I figured I'd
let her discover that herself.
You got plans
Friday night?
We're having a potluck
at my Aunt Clara's.
Be the best soul food
you ever ate.
Oh, that's sweet.
Thanks.
I got plans, though, honey.
No, you don't.
Hey.
I'm telling you,
I didn't forget.
- I belie--
- I just want to check.
Ugh, I--you come to my house
every night,
and I take my pills
all the time.
I don't know why you bother me.
I don't know
why you come every night.
- Ah, yeah, see?
- Looks like you forgot some.
- I did?
- Yeah, you left a few.
- Really? Oh.
- Yeah.
- Let me get you some water.
- Well, I--
It's all right.
That's all right.
I thought sure
I took them this morning.
I mean, I take them every day.
Hey, everybody forgets
sometimes.
- Yeah.
- There you go.
All right, well, you don't
have to bother me tomorrow.
I'll remember.
- Okay, okay.
- I won't bother you.
I just want to make sure
you're gonna take them now.
- Uh--
- Okay, okay. All right.
I'm not gonna bother you
anymore.
- Okay.
- All right, honey.
- See you.
- Bye.
♪ ♪
♪ I'm just going ♪
♪ Over Jordan ♪
♪ Over home ♪
♪ ♪
- Heya, Deskin.
- How's your back?
Same.
- You gotta try acupuncture.
- Really works.
That some sort
of lesbo voodoo?
Yeah.
After your first session,
you'll finally get
to eat some pussy.
Grace, please refrain
from that kind of language
around my daughter.
- Sorry, Jer.
- Next time, I'll say "vagina."
Dear Lord, please, uh,
we give thanks
for this good food
that You've provided us.
Please, uh, protect
my beautiful wife,
precious daughter,
and, of course,
our beloved neighbor
Mrs. Blevins from harm.
And, uh, please keep
the mine open
so we can continue
to enjoy this good food.
In Jesus' name, we pray.
Amen.
- Amen.
You gonna finish your quilt
this weekend?
Yeah, I only have
a few more squares left.
This one's really nice.
Thanks. I like it.
And I heard you got
a little wound up
by that lesbian girl today.
It's still illegal to swear
in public in the commonwealth,
last I heard.
I work with a lesbian
at the textile mill.
Mrs. Blevins,
the textile mill
closed down ten years ago.
Oh. That's right.
Wait a minute.
Patricia Bellinger
was a lesbian?
Dear, everyone knew that.
I knew she was
when I was ten.
Oh.
She's a tough broad.
I need to have
a catch-up whiskey with her.
Well, Patricia passed the--
To--yeah, she's tough,
all right.
Sure is.
She sounds a lot like Grace.
She's tougher
than any guy at the mine.
So are you.
You're the smallest one there
and probably the strongest.
Well,
bless their hearts.
I'm gonna pray
for both of them tonight.
Bets.
I wouldn't get too friendly
with that Grace girl.
Management doesn't
care much for her.
Yeah, okay. I'll definitely
steer clear of her.
♪ ♪
Coming up next, uh,
Mr. Chris Madison,
who's running for Congress
in this district.
Uh, come on up here, Chris.
I would be honored
to represent this district
in Congress.
Now, I know the jobs haven't
come back like we'd hoped,
but I will do everything I can
to make sure the mines
stay open and jobs come back.
Aren't you
that miner girl?
Yeah.
I heard you're tough.
Are you tough?
- Maybe.
- Maybe?
- Depends.
- Depends? On what?
- I don't know.
- You don't know?
Well.
Now, we all know you're trying
to steal a husband
in that mine.
Don't ever forget,
we got our eyes on you.
- Yes, ma'am.
- I-I won't forget.
Mm-hmm.
♪ ♪
I got some good news
for you.
My mama said
she was gonna pray for you.
Well, bless her heart.
♪ ♪
♪ I wanna take
the breath that's true ♪
♪ ♪
♪ I look to you and I see ♪
All right.
Cable's good, Eddie.
All right, Bets.
♪ ♪
♪ I look to you
to see the truth ♪
Hold on!
♪ ♪
All right, let's all--
My back! My back!
Be okay.
- Ah, it's my back!
- Get up!
Betsy?
- Try to get her up.
- Betsy?
♪ ♪
Well,
before you fly back,
you have to see Master Class.
It's fabulous.
- I don't know.
- I hated McNally's last play.
- Really? It won the Tony.
- Yes.
Gay men running around naked
onstage for three hours.
How could it not?
Hello, Uncle Mortimer.
I didn't know
you were flying in.
Well, I had to, didn't I?
♪ ♪
Richie, can I talk to you
for a second?
Do you find it odd
your stepmother
is a year younger than you?
She's not as bad
as the last two.
So I wanted to tell you
that, um,
I'm gonna have
to speak up tonight,
and I didn't want
to blindside you.
Okay.
I'll see you in there.
♪ ♪
Please tell
Dr. Raymond Sackler
that the holders of "A shares"
are greatly concerned
with the significant
overspending by his son
in the development
of this new product.
Dr. Sackler,
there's great concern
that your son, Richard,
has spent more than $40 million
in the development
of this new--
Ten times more than
what we've spent on anything.
Ever.
As stated by Mortimer's son,
Mortimer D. A.,
there is great concern
among "A shareholders" --
You have literally placed
this entire company
in jeopardy.
Please tell
Dr. Mortimer Sackler
that "B shares,"
who, last I checked,
have the same voting power
as "A shares,"
are honored he flew in
from his self-imposed exile
in Switzerland
and we hope
his unpatriotic tax-dodging
continues to be successful.
It has!
Now, I understand
his confusion
about the development process,
since he has never built
a single thing in his life,
but advise him that
once the drug is launched,
it will make his children,
who cash checks
generated by "B shares,"
significantly wealthier
than they are now.
Uncle Raymond,
I resent the implication
that we're all dilettantes.
My apologies, Kathe.
We all know you're an
invaluable part of the company.
Thank you.
But "A shares" are
rightfully concerned
that if OxyContin doesn't sell
or if it runs afoul of the FDA
or if insurance companies
stop covering it
for whatever reason,
it could literally sink
this entire company.
Richard, I respect
how hard you work.
I really do, but this family
has had a successful company
for 40 years,
and now it's at risk.
You vastly overspent,
and it's not unreasonable that
we would be upset and anxious.
It'll work.
I promise you.
Thank you.
Tell my nephew...
it fucking better.
♪ ♪
Samuel,
I see you're
making the rounds today.
They're trying to make
the good pastor fat
with all this delicious
desserts out here today.
And a little too much sugar
there for you.
- Hey, Doc.
- Hey.
I want you to cut back
on that Tylenol PM.
Just a few days a week.
Hey, Bets.
Heard you took a pretty good
lick the other day.
Your back.
Why didn't you come see me?
I keep telling her to.
Why don't you show him
your back?
- No, no. It's--it's nothing.
- I'm fine.
- Hey, Doc.
- Give her some Vicodin.
Maybe a couple for me too.
Shut the hell up!
What do you think
caused so many deaths
over such a short
period of time?
- You too, young lady.
- You take it easy, all right?
I know, Doc.
♪ ♪
Dr. Finnix.
OxyContin.
So just to be clear,
you're blaming numerous deaths
in your town
on just one medication.
Yes, sir.
I am.
And are you the individual
that prescribed
this medication?
Yes, sir.
I did.
Mr. Brownlee,
you're early.
I'm always early.
- Great to meet ya.
- Hey.
- Randy Ramseyer.
- John Brownlee.
Rick Mountcastle.
Well, hey, uh, congrats
on your new appointment, sir.
You know, we would have been
happy to drive up to Roanoke.
Ah, that's okay.
I wanted to see
the branch office.
Yeah, well,
it's, uh--
It sure is impressive,
isn't it?
You know, we even
churn our own butter.
So how'd you end up
in Abingdon?
- Well, I got a, uh--
- A clerkship with a judge
at the state courthouse
just down the block,
and this job came open.
He--he, uh--he tried
to talk me out of it.
Told me I'd be broke
my whole life,
but I thought, "What the hell?"
And, you know, honestly, it's
the best decision I ever made,
'cause I love working all
the different kinds of cases
and learning new things.
It's, uh--it's what
makes life interesting.
- What about you, Rick?
- How'd you end up here?
I just came here
to serve justice, sir.
We got multiple
bank fraud cases,
illegal arms, racketeering,
federal health care kickback.
Okay, yeah,
that all sounds good.
Look, here's...
what I drove two hours
to say to you face-to-face:
I'm not afraid of risk,
not afraid to rattle the cages,
I'm not afraid to lose
if we're on the side
of the righteous.
And I want you not to be afraid
to think big.
Took this job
to get things done.
And when I leave here,
I'm gonna hit the road,
I'm gonna tell
every sheriff that I meet
that if they've got someone
in their community
that is violent,
that's a predator,
for whatever reason,
the state won't get it done,
bring it to us, and we'll throw
that son of a bitch in jail,
'cause we sure as hell
are gonna get it done.
- Yes, sir.
- All right.
You guys holding out on me?
Um...
Well, it's still very early,
but we've begun looking
at something that could be big.
Mm, what are we
talking about?
OxyContin.
Specifically Purdue Pharma.
That's the company
that makes it.
They've been marketing the drug
and pushing it on doctors
as something
that's nonaddictive,
when it clearly is.
Has any other
U. S. attorney pursued?
No, sir.
Civil litigation?
What is it, 65 cases?
And how many has Purdue won?
- 65.
- Yeah.
Well, going after
a publicly traded company
is a pretty steep hill
to climb.
They're not publicly traded;
it's privately owned
by a single family,
the Sackler family.
Sacklers.
They're big philanthropists,
right?
Oh, yeah.
Yeah, they give lots of money
to museums and schools.
- Rich-person stuff.
- Very rich.
So what do you guys got
that no other U. S. attorney
in the country is onto?
Well, about four months ago,
I was reviewing our caseload
when I noticed
an unusual pattern.
Almost every case
over the last three years,
uh, was related to OxyContin.
Nearly every one.
Illegal drug sales, theft,
armed robbery, job abandonment.
I mean,
it has transformed
the entire district.
Jails are suddenly full.
Violent crime
is running rampant.
Uh, you know,
for the last 200 years,
folks around here
didn't even lock their doors.
Didn't even think about it.
Now, starting
three years ago...
Everyone locks their doors.
It's the single
highest source of crime
in the entire region.
Well, look,
if you guys want
to go after
a billion-dollar company
from a strip mall,
you're gonna need more evidence
than you can fit
in this entire building.
No other U. S. attorney
wants to touch this thing.
That means it's gonna take
something significant
to make it work.
You have to prove
the heads of this company
know that they're lying
about the dangers of the drug
and that
they're selling it anyway.
Well, we believe
that very well may be the case.
Since I've been
on this new medication,
I haven't missed
one day of work.
This frees me up.
And it helps with my anxiety.
You can just
take the medicine and go.
I can
take walks with my husband.
And I can go swimming.
All because
of the pain medicine.
Rick? Rick!
Would you get up here?
Uh-huh. Yeah.
Thank You, Lord, for this meal,
and allowing us
to enjoy it together. Amen.
- Amen.
You working
on that pharma thing?
Yeah. Napkin in your lap.
But it's tricky.
Uh, we'll be outspent
by millions.
And, uh, I'm looking at it,
you know,
and there's just--
There is something there.
It's just, uh, I can't quite
find a way to get at it.
I don't even know
what to charge them with.
- Hmm.
- Digging through
a mountain down there,
and I just can't find--
Can't find a way at it.
Well, what does the new,
handsome boss think?
He's ambitious,
so he likes it,
if we can find something
to get it going.
Aren't all U. S. attorneys
ambitious?
Wow.
She must really think
he's handsome.
Maybe this is
the perfect opportunity
for you to take on
something big that...
might scare off someone
who isn't as ambitious.
Well...
The DEA was actively
investigating Purdue last year.
What's the status
of the investigation?
About six months ago,
the DEA basically ended it.
No fines, no charges.
From what I can tell,
very few actions taken at all.
And she's Diversion?
Yeah.
This is Bridget Meyer.
She's the deputy director
of the Diversion Division.
Mm-hmm.
Try and say that
three times fast.
You think she's
gonna tell us what happened?
No.
You know, I had
to call her four times
just to get this meeting.
She, uh--she's got an edge.
All right, guys,
I don't have a lot of time,
so what do you want?
Well, we know about
your investigation into Purdue,
and we were hoping to find out
what you uncovered,
why it abruptly ended.
Did you find evidence
that they were illegally
promoting the drug?
Is there a reason you're
not answering the question?
Anything with the DOJ
is a waste of time.
So is that it? 'Cause
like I said, I'm really busy.
Right. I know. I know.
How can a couple hicks
from rural Virginia
take on a massive company
like Purdue Pharma?
You know, Rick here
is former army,
so he's been
all over the place,
seen lots
of different countries.
Been to France?
- Argentina.
- South Korea.
- See?
And I even wore
my fancy no-lace shoes.
It'd sure be nice
if you could just have
a reasonable conversation
with us.
"Delayed absorption, as
provided by OxyContin tablets,
is believed to reduce
the abuse liability of a drug."
Barely makes sense.
That fucking label
caused everything.
How so?
It was the first time
the FDA labeled
a Class II narcotic
as less addictive.
Now, how does that
even happen?
That's a great
fucking question.
Well, did you investigate the
approval process for the label?
See, that seems
like a yes to me.
Yeah, it definitely
seems like a yes.
- Mm-hmm.
- I couldn't charge anything.
It's a challenge
in this case.
Purdue has so many levels
of deniability:
patient abuse,
doctor malpractice.
Did the heads of the company
know it was false
when they marketed the drug
as being nonaddictive?
Thanks for coming in, guys.
Um, I've got a call
with my divorce lawyer,
and I always need to calm down
before I talk to her.
- I understand.
- Mm-hmm.
Thank you for your time.
You know, a few months ago,
we caught a doctor
selling pills out of his car
to an 11-year-old girl.
And when we arrested him,
he thanked us.
He told us he couldn't
have stopped on his own.
And at that moment, we knew
that what we got going on
in coal country
is similar to San Francisco at
the start of the AIDS crisis,
that our community
is ground zero
for a growing
national catastrophe.
We're gonna do
everything we can
to hold someone accountable.
It might just end this thing.
So if you change your mind,
we'd love to talk to you.
♪ ♪
I found my life again,
and it's worth living now.
I'm so grateful.
Since I have been
on this pain medication,
I have not missed
one day of work.
I-I can't say
enough good things
about this pain medication
that, uh, allows me
to get work done,
and that's--that's something
I didn't think
I would ever be able
to do again.
It's just changed my life
for the better.
Since I've been taking
this new pain medication,
I've not missed a day of work.
And it takes the anxiety away.
You can just
take the medicine and go.
Because
of this pain medication,
I enjoy my life again,
'cause there was so much
that was just missing from it.
I got my life back.
Seems like
a typical promotional video,
with patient testimonials
extolling the virtues
of the drug.
There's just one
very unusual thing here
is that they almost never
mention OxyContin by name.
They say "pain medicine"
or "drug therapy"
or, uh, "time-release pill."
But you got all these people
twisting themselves into knots
not to say "OxyContin"
in a video promoting OxyContin.
Just doesn't
make much sense to me.
Do you think
they weren't really on it?
I don't know.
I'd like to found out.
Well, if they weren't,
then Purdue
deliberately sent
a promotional video
to 15,000 doctors
stating these patients
were on a drug that
they weren't actually taking.
That's right.
And this video
is the first major introduction
of OxyContin.
♪ ♪
Hey, Jennifer.
I think your husband here
needs some new glasses.
He's the worst referee
in the entire state.
You lost by 20, Marge.
It's not my husband's fault
your team sucks balls.
- Oh, baby.
- I'm sorry about that.
Mm.
You know, you don't have
to come to these things
if you don't want to.
What? Watching you
get screamed at by everyone
is the highlight of my week.
♪ ♪
Hey, babe.
You hang on one second?
I'll be right back.
♪ ♪
$50 for a blow job.
$100 if you want to fuck me.
You need to get
to a hospital immediately.
Fuck off.
You need to make sure you--
♪ ♪
I have some concerns
about the sales force.
I think it's too small.
If we're gonna launch
in a big way,
we need to double it.
The board is very concerned
about how much
we've already spent.
And the board
doesn't seem to understand
I'm trying to make this
a blockbuster drug,
which I can't do
without more sales reps.
Uh, Dr. Richard,
with all these new sales reps,
we won't even have enough
doctors for them to target.
IMS is about to release
a 3.0 version
that tracks daily prescriptions
instead of quarterly.
So if we double
our sales force,
we can use this data
to target doctors
prescribing Lortab and Vicodin
and flip them to OxyContin.
The upgrade
is a million dollars.
Do you know who created
the IMS database?
Arthur Sackler.
It's been kept secret
for years,
but this is a family invention
that was sold off years ago.
And now you're telling me
we should deny all this data
that only exists
because of my fucking uncle?
Purchase the upgrade,
and increase the sales force.
Thank you.
I need you to stop
thinking like my cousins...
And start thinking about
how we can cure the world
of its pain.
Thank you. Thank you.
♪ ♪
I prefer his father.
You will be part
of the largest sales force
in pharmaceutical history,
bringing this new miracle drug
all across this great nation.
See, doctors want pain relief
for their patients.
They just don't want
to get them addicted.
So your first talking point is
also what makes it so special:
less than 1% of people
become addicted to OxyContin.
It's amazing, right?
Now, all your doctors are gonna
be asking you the same thing:
"How? How is this
even possible?"
Well, the answer lies in the
MS Contin time-release system.
This system limits
the flow of oxycodone
over a 12-hour period,
which not only makes it
essentially nonaddictive;
it also discourages abusers,
because they cannot
get a quick high off of it.
Um, if it's nonaddictive,
doesn't that mean
it can be used to treat,
like, almost anything?
That's exactly right.
Backaches. Toothaches.
Uh, headaches.
Joint discomfort.
Arthritis. Hangovers.
The possibilities are endless.
Now, our initial rollout
will be focused
on southwestern Virginia,
eastern Kentucky,
and rural Maine.
And do you know why? Anyone?
Um, they're mining, farming,
logging centers, uh,
places where folks get injured
doing labor-intensive jobs.
Correct.
These people are in pain.
They have hard lives.
And we have the cure.
So we are sending you all
into the wild
to flip these country doctors
from Percocet and Vicodin
to OxyContin.
When I was selling Vicodin,
doctors could get skittish
about opioids.
This bias is exactly
what you'll have to overcome.
But step one is just
getting in the door.
All right, make your doctors
feel special.
Get dolled up. Take them
to expensive dinners.
Offer to fill up their car
with gas
just to get ten minutes
to pitch.
Bribe the receptionist
with a mani-pedi
so she'll let you
in the office.
All right, you have to get
to know your doctors,
which is why we will give you
full psychological profiles
on each of them.
If they've got kids, get them
tickets to Disney World.
If they're going through
a divorce, uh, get them laid.
Whatever it takes to win their
friendship and their trust.
I love the Pradas,
by the way.
And, uh, is that a Gucci suit?
It's very, uh, stylish...
while being, you know,
work environment-appropriate.
Are you gay?
What? Uh, no.
- Are you sure?
- 'Cause you sound like a fag.
Wow. Uh...
I guess that depends
what you're into.
Hmm.
I dated a guy at Harvard
just like you.
He used humor to compensate
for his small penis.
Wow, you, uh, called me
dickless and dropped the fact
you went to Harvard
in under 30 seconds.
Is that, like,
a record for you?
- Please.
- I usually drop it faster.
- Amber Collins.
- Hey.
Billy Cutler.
Nice to meet you.
Um...
would you like to go out
and get dinner sometime, Amber?
Or, like, a cocktail?
I know a bar
that does great cocktails.
See you around, Billy.
Yeah.
♪ ♪
Dr. Finnix.
I, uh, understand
you're a breast man.
I know how busy you are.
I just thought we could
take a few moments
over a bucket
of Kentucky's finest.
I can tell you about a drug
that's gonna change
this mountain forever.
Best fishing I ever did--
Colorado River.
My dad would
take me trout fishing,
and then we'd just
grill them up
right there by the river.
Oh, man.
Cook them up
with some butter,
add a little garlic--
Oh, boy, that's perfection.
Yes, sir.
- You from Colorado?
- No.
No, I'm from a, uh,
small farming community
outside of Omaha.
You?
From a town
in southwest Pennsylvania.
I never thought I'd end up
in a town this small.
How'd that happen?
Met a girl in med school.
She wanted to provide
free health care
for people in Appalachia.
She made it pretty clear
she was gonna do it
with or without me.
Well, there's nothing like
chasing a girl.
Nope.
Well, I've got another patient
coming in here
in a few minutes, so--
Of course. I won't
take up much of your time.
You're probably
already familiar
with our drug MS Contin.
Used to treat severe pain,
many patients with cancer.
MS Contin
is a very good drug.
So what Purdue did is,
they took the same system,
uh, the Contin system,
and they produced a opioid
for chronic and moderate pain.
I would never prescribe
a narcotic for moderate pain.
There's a pretty long history
down here of pill abuse.
Less than 1% of people
get addicted to OxyContin.
That's not possible.
But it is.
The FDA actually created
a special label
to say that it's less addictive
than other opioids.
Right there.
Your
most effective talking point
is the FDA label.
These are your new magic words:
"Delayed absorption,
as provided
by OxyContin tablets..."
Delayed absorption,
as provided
by OxyContin tablets...
"Is believed to reduce..."
The abuse liability
of a drug.
I've never seen a label
like this
on a Class II narcotic.
It's the first
of its kind.
Opioid use is being totally
redefined in this country.
Untreated pain is a--
Is an unnecessary evil
when you have a nonaddictive
opioid like OxyContin
that can be used
to cure everyday suffering.
And we're not supposed
to hand out samples,
but, um, it'll be our secret.
And I'll leave some coupons
with Leah
so you can, uh, redeem
for a few more bottles.
Trust me, these miners' lives
are gonna change overnight
when they get a taste
of OxyContin.
You're not gonna let
your patients suffer
when they don't have to, right?
♪ Dancing where
the lonely nights are dim ♪
♪ Oh ♪
- I-I can't.
- What?
- I can't.
What's wrong?
Hey.
♪ Painted-on smile ♪
♪ She's caught in the middle ♪
Did I do something wrong?
♪ A long, long while ♪
I want us to be together.
♪ Half in the shade ♪
I want us to go live
somewhere else.
Well, w-where would we go?
I-I gotta stay
in the mountains.
I know.
I found a place.
Eureka Springs, Arkansas.
It's a mountain town
that's gay-friendly.
We can go live there.
Well, do they have mines?
What?
♪ Holding on
to just a memory ♪
No, I'm trying
to get you out of the mines.
Well, I don't--
I don't want
to get out of the mines.
What are you
talking about?
♪ There's no one to blame ♪
Well... four generations
of my family built America
right here in this mountain,
and no one thought
a girl could do it.
Not even my dad. He didn't
want me down there either.
You know, everyone thought
the mountains were done, and...
I proved 'em all wrong.
But we can't be together
if you stay underground.
You'd choose coal over me?
- Of course not. No, Grace.
- Then come away with me.
Coal is a job.
It's not a life.
Look at you.
You're in pain right now,
and you're pretending
you're not
so you can keep
going down there.
That's no way to live.
My dad will never speak
to me again if I came out.
♪ ♪
- Hello.
- Hi.
Hi, Billy.
This is Richard Sackler.
- Um, hello, sir.
- Uh, it's an honor.
How--how were
the initial responses?
Um, they're very good,
uh, I think.
And, uh, you know, it's taking
some of the doctors a moment
to accept the fact
that less than 1% of people
get addicted to it, but...
Ah. Well, keep pushing.
It's--it's crucial
they understand this.
Yes, sir.
I won't let you down.
Good. Good.
Keep at it.
Thank you.
♪ ♪
I know. It's hard.
It's hard convincing them that
it's essentially nonaddictive,
but just keep pushing.
Yeah. Good.
Good night.
♪ ♪
Honey, you shouldn't
call sales reps.
It makes you look desperate.
I've always
despised that piece.
♪ ♪
- Why didn't you tell me?
- I would have taken it down.
No.
I like waking up to it.
Years before Uncle Arthur died,
he became addicted
to buying Chinese art.
It totally consumed him.
I think he paid $3 million
for that.
And look at it.
It's so ugly.
♪ ♪
If I can stay laser-focused,
I think I can make this
the biggest drug in the world.
We're here
for the final dissolution
of the marriage
between Paul Mendelson
and Bridget Meyer
on no-fault grounds.
The couple has been married
for three years
and has no children.
You may proceed
to sign the papers.
Are you okay?
- Yeah, I'm fine.
- Yeah?
You all right?
I--
- You look nice.
- So do you.
Um...
All right.
You be good to yourself, okay?
We should be done here
around, like, 6:00.
So let's say maybe 8:00.
But don't be mad if I have
to cancel last-minute.
- It's a job thing.
- I won't be.
But it doesn't matter, 'cause
I will pick you up at 8:00.
Great. See you then.
How long you been
seeing this guy?
We've gone out twice.
- You sleep with him yet?
- No.
He hasn't even tried
to kiss me.
He is going slow.
Wow.
He must really like you.
Right?
Absolutely.
Or he's advertising
to be my brother.
Or that.
♪ ♪
DEA! Don't move!
- Hey, stop right there!
- DEA! Freeze!
DEA! On the ground!
♪ ♪
- Do not move!
- Go to the right!
Right there!
♪ ♪
Tell me now
who the supplier is,
and you may just get a break.
Okay, talk.
What are these pills?
You don't know?
Wise guy.
What the fuck is this?
So you got anything
on a prescription drug
called OxyContin?
Have there been any spikes
in crime related to it?
Yeah, I'll hold.
Foster care--
The foster care occupancy
has tripled?
Increase in child abandonment.
How long have you seen
this trend?
Local jails overflowing.
Increase in prostitution.
Yes, um, do you got anything
on a prescription drug
called OxyContin?
Uh, your lawn mower was stolen?
No, I-I can't help you
with that.
So they just broke
into the pharmacy
and only took OxyContin?
Nothing else?
♪ ♪
This is Bridget Meyer
with the DEA.
Um, I know it's late,
but I wanted to confirm
some intel I got
about your pharmacy.
I know this is
Diversion's domain.
That's correct.
But in a raid
on a mid-level cocaine bust,
we uncovered a bag
filled with OxyContin tablets
for distribution,
so I did a little digging.
This drug has only been
on the market for three years,
and there's already been
a spike in overdoses
and crime rates in rural parts
of Kentucky, Maine,
Ohio, Pennsylvania,
and Virginia,
all areas where this drug
was first launched.
Jermaine,
where's Diversion on this?
Opioid use has been
totally redefined
in the last few years.
They're completed accepted
in the medical community.
The prevailing sentiment
is that not prescribing opioids
is considered inhumane.
So Diversion isn't concerned
with illegal opioid sales?
With all due respect, sir,
the diversion division
is the most underfunded
and understaffed unit
- in this building.
- Excuse me?
I'm just stating a fact.
We're also the most demoralized
since you make it pretty clear
the DEA's priorities
are not illegal use
of prescription drugs.
And how many Diversion agents
get killed
on the job every year?
Zero.
I got Operation agents
like Bridget here
dying on the front lines.
And she's doing it in high
heels and a quinceañera dress.
So excuse me if I don't have
time to give you a pep talk
about stopping
Joey Sticky Fingers
from stealing Daddy's Vicodin.
Sir, I understand
stopping Joey Sticky Fingers
isn't a priority,
but there might be a unique
situation brewing here.
I thought we could start
with the FDA
and try to tighten up
sales of this drug--
The FDA granted OxyContin
a unique label
saying it was less addictive
than other opioids,
so they're not gonna be
interested or helpful.
Curbing opioid use goes against
the entire national narrative
on the subject.
♪ ♪
So I heard
there's a new guy.
Is he down
with you carrying a gun
and storming into buildings?
Uh, yeah. He kind of digs it.
Hmm, well, that's
a needle in a haystack.
But I guess
those days are done,
since you transferred
to Diversion.
I didn't transfer.
I'm just interested
in OxyContin.
I understand
it was given a label
saying it was less addictive
than other opioids.
Is that unusual?
It was a first.
How'd that come about?
The wording of the label
or the approval of it?
- The approval.
- Was it standard?
Curtis got some pushback.
Curtis?
Curtis Wright, he's
the medical review officer.
He approved the label.
What was the pushback?
That there wasn't a need
to give it a label
differentiating it
from other Class II narcotics.
- And why was it given?
- I don't know the details.
I just know
that there was pushback.
Is there something
I should know
about the approval process?
Was there any kind
of internal debate
over the wording of the label?
I would call it
a disagreement.
Some people didn't think
that Purdue had proven
their claims were true.
Hmm, did they have
any studies
that showed
it was less addictive?
Those studies
weren't conducted.
And why not?
Purdue agreed
to a Class II classification,
which meant that they agreed
that it could be abused,
so they argued that
there was no need to test
for what they were
already agreeing to.
So let me
get this straight.
The FDA approves
this unprecedented label
because Purdue claims
it's less prone to abuse.
Correct.
They are argued that
because
of the time-release system,
they should be given
a unique classification.
Curtis Wright just
take their word for it?
Ms. Moles cannot comment
on Mr. Wright's state of mind.
Have you spoken to Curtis?
We wanted
to get background first.
Is he still the review officer?
You don't know.
And then, uh,
less than two years later,
after the drug hits the market,
Curtis Wright resigns
from the FDA.
You want to take a guess
where he lands?
You're kidding me.
He ends up at Purdue Pharma
as executive director
of medical affairs.
So the FDA grants
an unusual label
that turns out not to be true,
and the guy who approved it
goes to work for the company
that made billions
off the label?
- Mm-hmm.
- That is correct, sir.
We'd like to open
an investigation
into Curtis Wright.
Yeah, I think you should.
- Well, he seems engaged.
- For now.
See what happens when
Main Justice hears about it.
You think
that DEA agent was right?
We're gonna get shut down
by the higher-ups?
Wouldn't surprise me.
I'll meet you downstairs.
♪ ♪
Hello.
Yeah.
Bets, I'm gonna lift that shirt
up for you now, all right?
- All right.
Kind of hurts to move,
though.
- All right.
- I'll be careful.
- Okay?
- Mm-hmm.
Oh!
Tell them to leave.
- We'll go pray for you.
- Leave, Mom!
- Dad, close the door!
- Okay. Yep.
Is that tender
when I touch it?
- Yeah.
- Yeah. All right.
All right.
You're gonna have
to take some time off.
You can't go down
in the mines like that.
I'll talk
to the management myself.
No, they won't listen to you.
I can't lose my job.
I gotta make enough money
to get out of here.
What are you talking about?
I never told no one
this before.
Bets, I delivered you.
You can tell me anything.
I'm, uh...
Bets.
I know.
And I...
I can't stay here no more.
I gotta be myself.
If I can make enough money
underground,
then I can go live somewhere
where I can just be me.
I love those mines.
I know it sounds strange,
but I do.
I just can't live
like this anymore.
- You know...
- there's not a day goes by
that I don't think of Shelly
since I lost her.
People shouldn't be allowed
to love somebody
as much as I loved her.
If you gotta go on
and get out of here,
well, then you do that.
I'll even help you,
if you need it.
- Okay.
- All right?
I can't take off a month,
though.
Is there anything
you can give me?
A shot to make it heal faster
or something?
There's a new drug
that I've been reading about
in the journals.
They say it's a miracle drug.
I don't know about that.
The FDA and journals
all say it's safe.
Now, I'm gonna give you enough
for a three-day supply.
You take one now, and then
you take one in the morning.
- All right?
- Okay.
All right.
You only take two a day.
One in the morning,
one at night.
Then come on in
and get an X-ray.
All right.
It's gonna be all right.
I'll talk to your mom and dad.
All right.
♪ ♪
Dear Lord,
please protect our daughter.
I know she's not perfect,
but we love her so much.
But's a hard life
deep under that ground,
and, uh, sometimes we--
We get hurt.
And a lot of us have
to live our entire lives
with that hurt.
Of course,
we're always grateful
for what You've given us
and the...
the mountains
that provide for us.
I beg You, dear Lord,
please take her pain away.
Please save my little girl
from her pain.
♪ Fly away ♪
♪ Little pretty bird ♪
♪ Fly ♪
♪ Fly away ♪
♪ Little pretty bird ♪
♪ Where the cold ♪
♪ Winter winds ♪
♪ Don't blow ♪
These people
carry the burden
of building this nation
on their backs,
and they deserve to do it
without pain.
So if this drug can help,
well, then
I'm willing to try it.
We have created
the greatest painkiller
in the history
of human civilization.
This works better than
anything I've ever used before.
There is something unique
about this drug.
There's already a spike
in overdoses
and crime rates.
They will soon be
the largest profits
this company has ever seen.
That is really good.
How many kids in your school
are on OxyContin?
I don't know.
You think maybe that
miracle drug you're selling
might be a little more
addictive than you said it was?
We're all
really worried about you.
It's not the drug
that's the problem.
It's the addicts
who are abusing it.
No drug is going to work
perfectly for every patient.
That's not our job.
Our job is to sell, bitch.
How dangerous can it be?
Everything
we've compiled shows
that Purdue consistently
oversold the benefits
and trivialized the risks
of OxyContin.
Those executives
belong in jail.
I want Purdue
to feel some pain.
Let's shake every tree
and see if we can find
some hard evidence.
Let's do it!
People's lives are at stake.
And a pharma company is lying
about their medicine.
They will go down.
- Don't worry.
- We'll figure this out.
It's an excellent drug.
♪ ♪