Shh!
You told me you stayed
in Banshee because of me.
I had to make sure
you were okay.
I'm not.
Hey, listen.
You don't seem surprised
to have a gun in your face.
That's a symptom of a life spent
looking over your shoulder.
Who are you?
I'm Special Agent
Robert Phillips,
FBI Internal Investigations.
I didn't realize the FBI
had internal affairs.
That's because you're
not really a cop.
But we'll have plenty of time
to talk about all that later,
once you get dressed.
There was a time...
when I was the one
who would watch you sleep.
You were such
a beautiful child...
...with so much promise.
It was never my intention
to disappoint you, Mother.
Oh, Kai.
You could never disappoint me.
I just wish I could believe...
you were content.
Who will love you, Kai?
Who will you love?
Mr. Proctor?
I... I just wanted
to make sure you're okay.
Promise me after I am gone...
...that you will move Rebecca
out of this house.
It's not proper.
It's not healthy.
Promise me.
I should never have left her.
I should never have
left her on the farm...
...with my father.
It's okay.
She needed me.
All those years, she needed...
She still needs you.
And you're here for her.
Hi there.
You know,
they say a man's home is...
a window into his mind.
Yeah, I've heard that.
Glock 17.
9 mil.
Really?
Yeah.
Gets the job done.
You should know
some things about me.
My superiors demand results,
but they're not in the least
concerned how I achieve them.
So if I were you,
I would exercise some...
caution.
And if I were you,
I'd do the same.
Agreed.
Why don't you put those on?
So you're Proctor's
big bad watchdog.
You don't look so tough
from where I'm standing.
So here's the plan.
First, I'm gonna kill you.
Then I'm going inside and I'm
gonna slowly gut your boss
and his
Little House on the Prairie niece.
I don't think so.
Ah! Ah!
Nola.
Let me die.
You already did.
It's time to start living again.
What the hell
is a data skimmer?
Exactly what
it sounds like.
It scans and saves metadata
from encoded smart cards.
We stealing real IDs from them
so I can make fake IDs for us.
That's all you had to say.
That wasn't so hard, now, was it?
Lord knows it ain't never easy.
This one's yours.
Now, I want you to...
Testing!
It works.
Do your best
not to fuck this up.
That is the third
time this week.
You think they're trying
to tell me something?
I need six IDs.
Try not to move your lips
while you're counting.
Okay, I got to grab it.
Three more.
Running out of time.
One more.
Oh, I had some keys...
Oh, there they are.
- One more.
- Thank you.
I got it.
Get your ass out.
I got a big business meeting
and I can't get nowhere
without these keys, you know?
Thank you so much.
What?
If we were never
going past the lobby,
why you got me wearing
this damn suit?
'Cause there ain't no such
thing as sweatpants Monday.
You can drive.
Sh...
You know, I prefer classic rock,
but, you know, country music that
soothes the soul, don't you think?
How did you find me?
You know, I have a rather
specialized job at the Bureau.
I'm a fixer of sorts,
so I investigate dead
and missing agents.
Of course, the missing ones almost
always turn out to be dead, too.
Like Jim Racine?
Instead I found his body outside an
old farmhouse in upstate New York.
Really?
Well, what was left of him.
He was burned up pretty bad.
But not the slug
that killed him.
Glock 9 mil?
No.
.308 rifle round.
Isn't that interesting?
Not as interesting as the inch-thick
file that he was keeping on you.
You know, it turns out
that the NYPD's
John Doe Capital Diamond thief
turned out to be the new sheriff
of Banshee, Pennsylvania?
That's quite a leap.
Maybe, but the story
gets better.
Especially the part
about the church,
the gunfight.
I mean, it takes
some king-sized balls
to take on a guy like
Rabbit in a way like that.
And when I think about an
ex-con posing as a sheriff,
well, I think maybe
those are the same big balls.
Well, I'm flattered,
but you're wasting your time.
You know something about
wasted time, don't you?
I don't get it. I mean, you could
have gone anywhere when you got out.
You could have found a black sand
beach somewhere in paradise,
a new golden brown señorita
every night of the week.
My God, that's what
I would have done.
Oh, not you. No.
You came to Banshee.
You played dress-up
right down the road
from the woman who stole
15 years of your life.
She must be something.
Or else there's
something inside of you
that still wants to be punished.
What do you think?
I think you talk too much.
That's what my third
ex-wife told me.
Okay, get out.
You're letting me go?
No, I'm letting you take a piss.
It's a long way back
to the city.
We're not gonna
stop another time.
- I'm good.
- I'm not asking. Move.
- And if you try anything...
- Yeah, you'll shoot me.
- I get it.
- Yeah. Come on.
Hey, you know what?
- I think I changed my mind.
- How's that?
Well, I don't think I want
to go back to New York.
You make it sound
like you have a choice.
Well, there's always a choice.
I want to report
a robbery in progress
at the Capital Diamond
warehouse.
211 Saw Mill River Road.
I'm Detective Julias Bonner.
It was my team that
took you down tonight.
Congratulations.
You are smart enough to know
that whoever you're
working for set you up.
May I?
May I offer you something
to drink while you wait?
Coffee? Tea?
Something stronger?
The way I see it,
you know you got jail
on the other side
of this conversation.
You aren't going home
for many years.
Time to wake up, asshole.
Hey.
There he is.
Sorry to keep you waiting.
Hopefully my associates
have made you feel at home.
As you can see,
comfort is a priority
for a man of my dimensions.
Some travel is unavoidable,
but cars, vans, planes,
they all present
indignities for me.
Well, you could try eating
a salad now and then.
I think fat jokes
are beneath us both.
Well, that's hard to say
seeing as I have no idea
who the fuck you are.
My name is Raymond
Walton Brantley.
Brantley, that's the guy
you stole the money off, right?
Look, I saw some shit
I wasn't supposed to see.
Brantley...
Brantley is a paranoid fuck.
Yes?
No?
Maybe?
The only thing I know
for sure about you
is who you are not.
And you are not Lucas Hood.
Isn't that right?
It's okay.
Despite a particularly
nasty beating,
Agent Phillips here
of the FBI's rat squad
remained as quiet as a mouse.
Where is Jason Hood?
I have no idea who that is.
Really?
Yes.
No.
Maybe.
I... just... He's dead.
He's dead.
He's de...
Give me Jason Hood...
and Agent Phillips
will never cause you
discomfort again.
To tell you the truth,
I've never really been
worried about Agent Phillips.
So if you can find
your dick in there,
why don't you go fuck yourself?
If I were you, I'd take a moment
to consider how tenuous
your bargaining
position truly is.
Maybe you got a girl...
...alone in the dark waiting
and wondering what happened.
I told you I should have
handled Proctor's house.
You'll get your chance
soon enough.
That's what you keep saying.
Let me hit him where it hurts.
Show Proctor
that we're in control.
You're not ready.
Don't make me tell you again.
Chayton.
You guys take a walk.
Hey, Tommy.
I haven't been out
this way since high school.
You should not have come here.
Why'd you steal
those guns, Chayton?
If I didn't know any better,
I'd say you were training an army.
But that would be crazy, right?
Crazy.
Crazy is allowing
the reservation
to become as corrupt
as the outside world.
- How many...
- But that's just what Longshadow
and George Hunter have done.
They call us outlaws,
gangbangers.
Treat us like we're the problem.
Because you treat violence
like it's the solution.
I will do anything to protect
our land from men like Proctor.
All you're doing
is hurting more of our own.
This is bigger
than any one person.
Tell that to the dead Redbone
they pulled out
of Proctor's pool.
Or the other one in the ICU.
Casualties of a righteous war.
You know, when we were kids...
and you and Tommy
came to live with us...
you were so shy.
So gentle.
I told everybody
you were my real brother
because I wanted it to be true.
Now I barely recognize you.
You sure can take
a hell of a beating.
I'll give you that.
Why don't you
just tell him the truth?
- He knows you're lying.
- He doesn't know shit.
- He thinks I'm lying.
- What's the difference?
Come on, Agent Phillips,
that's basic psi-ops protocol.
The only way to overcome
a physical advantage
- is to establish a psychological one.
- A psychological one.
There you go.
You remember.
Yeah, I slept through
that class at Quantico.
No, you didn't.
You know, you can play
all the mind games you want,
but we're not
leaving here alive.
You know that, right?
Way I see it,
I'm better off in here
than I was in the back
of your car.
Well, if that's really true,
you have to ask yourself
just how fucked up
your universe really is.
The thought has crossed my mind.
You know, I have cracked
some pretty twisted minds
in my time, but you...
You're not gonna
give up on me, are you?
Uh-uh. Not a chance.
Where were we?
You just asked me
about Jason Hood.
And you told me
to go fuck myself.
We're all caught up.
I'm gonna fucking kill you.
Hey, Emily, it's me.
Just checking in.
Um...
Anyway, call me back, all right?
- Is everything okay?
- Couldn't be better.
I'm... I'm clocking out.
Any word from Hood?
Nope. Nothing.
I'm thinking we should turn
his office into a game room.
What do you think?
I'm pretty worried. I've
been trying to reach him all day.
Really?
Well, your paperwork's
not going anywhere.
Why don't you head over to his
place and see what's what?
- Yeah?
- Yeah.
Okay.
- Thanks, Brock.
- Sure.
Let me know when you find him.
- All right.
- You heading out?
- Yep.
Anywhere good?
No, just having an afternoon
drink with an old friend.
Platinumm, what the hell
was I thinking?
Sorry.
You know, there is worse things
than getting some
from your hot ex-wife.
No, I know.
There's always a flip side with her.
- You don't know Emily.
- I know there's nobody
forcing you
to bump uglies with her.
That is true.
That is very true.
But, you know,
it's... complicated.
Ugh. How come every time a
guy goes sticking his dick
someplace he shouldn't,
it's complicated?
- Well, I just...
- No.
You know,
sometimes when I...
Your ex knows
exactly what she's doing.
She's got you exactly
where she wants you.
Losing your fucking mind
over some bomb-ass pussy.
I know. I know.
I know.
You already know what to do,
but you're not gonna do it.
You're a wise woman,
Platinumm...
Hey, shithead!
You kill him, you'll
never get what you want.
Agent Phillips is right.
Are you gonna tell me
where he is?
Give him some fresh air!
Afternoon, Deputy.
Can I get you something?
No, thanks. Have you
seen the sheriff?
He missed his shift today.
No. No, I haven't.
But he'll turn up.
He always does.
You know him pretty well, huh?
I could say the same about you.
- Could you?
- Mm.
I'm not so sure.
Some people,
you can know them
before you know about them.
Maybe. Or maybe that'd
sound a lot more profound
if I had had a few beers.
Yeah, I don't doubt that.
All right, well,
if you hear from him...
Will do.
Now or never, mystery man.
- Where is Jason Hood?
- He's dead!
He's fucking dead.
I told you.
And why should I believe you?
'Cause I killed him, all right?
Thirty seconds.
I doubt a word,
you become roadkill.
The kid offered me 50 grand
to take out your man in
the fancy suit, all right?
Twenty-up front,
twenty-five when it was done.
You killed Quentin?
Well, it took some doing...
...but, yeah.
Go on.
So after I killed Quentin,
Jason, he didn't
want to pay up...
and he threatened to expose me.
So you killed him
and took the money?
Fair is fair.
Where is my money now?
It's back in Banshee.
- All of it?
- Yes.
And exactly how much
is all of it?
Brantley, he likes to deal
with this sort of thing
up close and personal.
Sixty-two thousand.
I will take you back home.
You will show me
Jason Hood's body.
You will return my money.
Who is going to stop you from
shooting me the moment I do?
You're not on the list.
Mmm.
Seems I will be taking
a trip south of the border
after I retrieve my money.
Sadly, Agent Phillips,
your home is not
on the itinerary.
Wanda, tell Mr. Cole
up front to pull over.
My associates will escort you
to your next destination.
Where the hell is that?
Safe travels, Agent Phillips.
Let's go.
Wanda, tell Mr. Cole
to take us back to Banshee.
The boys will catch up later.
And mix me a drink.
Bulleit Old Fashioned,
extra sugar.
Right away,
Mr. Brantley.
You're going back into a cell.
You're facing
eight to ten years.
Life as you know it is over.
Hey!
Get out of the way!
Stay down.
- Get back!
- Down.
Check the back rooms.
Make sure everyone's out.
Raven, hey, it's Brock.
Look, I've got a 211
in progress at the Savoy.
Looks like five assailants
and possibly two dozen civilians
trapped inside. Hurry.
Get up.
Fuck.
True gundog, Quentin.
He could flush out
the best of them.
Tell me, how'd you beat him?
No, I'm not telling
you anything.
Not until you tell me
why you came so far
for an asshole like Jason Hood.
I mean, a guy like you
doesn't come all the way
across the country for 60 grand.
A guy like me would come across
the country for 50 cents.
Start digging.
My body has failed me.
I failed it.
Either way.
Things that you take for
granted, I can't do.
Simple trip to buy groceries
or have a meal at a restaurant.
I can't even fuck anymore.
But one thing I do have
is my ledger.
I keep my own books
and I keep everything balanced.
Not a decimal point
out of place.
The devil is in the details.
And the details
are all that a guy like me has.
In that case,
I bet you'd love to know
what Jason Hood's
last words were.
Tell me what he said.
He said to tell you...
he'll see your fat ass
real fucking soon.
Up here now. You, outta here!
Get outta here!
Move!
Down now!
Stay here.
What are you doing?
No!
You have it.
Mr. Cole.
- Wanda, where are the shotgun shells?
- Cabinet, bottom right.
- Look away. Don't look at me.
- No.
Everyone listen up.
Listen up.
We're not here to kill you.
But when I'm done here...
you're all gonna
have to find new jobs.
Drop your weapons!
Hands in the air!
Don't! Don't you
fucking do it.
Nobody move.
I said to drop
your weapons, fellas.
Son, that knife gets
any closer to her neck,
I'm gonna blow
your fuckin' head off.
Ah!
Wanda.
Sheriff's Department!
Put down your guns right now.
Tommy!
Tommy, it's Billy Raven.
You and your boys
need to surrender now
and no one else gets hurt.
No one except for you, cop.
Damn it, Tommy!
You need to listen to me.
No!
Alma, we need EMTs
at the Savoy now.
I'll clear the back rooms.
- Stay still.
- Fuck you!
No, thanks.
Don't fucking move.
- Raven, you okay over there?
- Yeah.
Knife!
Where the fuck is Hood?
That's deep enough.
Turn around.
You don't want to do this.
Killing a federal agent
will get you the needle.
Good-bye.
I didn't kill Racine.
I know.
So what the fuck
are you doing here?
I was curious.
I was tasked to find
a missing agent.
You're not part of that story.
The Bureau doesn't know
anything about you.
So what's stopping me from
leaving you in this hole?
You're doing a pretty shitty
job of saving yourself.
Seems we both need
to work on that.
Agreed.
So we're good?
Yeah.
We're good.
But you should know...
...I had to do something
to cover my ass
when I thought you
would turn out to be...
who you weren't.
What did you do?
Sorry.
We don't even know
what to call you.
What is it?
What?
Gottverdammt!
Your life, that life, is over.
- I work alone.
- No, you don't.
You had someone
in that building with you.
And you two weren't
performing some remote hack
on some of the most advanced
security systems on the market
while rappelling from the roof,
so by my count,
that adds up to three guys
not counting Mr. Rabbit.
What, do you think I work
for some criminal mastermind
that goes around
calling himself Mr. Rabbit?
Yes, I do. Yes, I do!
Give me Rabbit.
Give him to me
and I'll cut you a deal.
Maybe you get 18 months.
You'll be out after a year.
I would offer you
witness protection,
but you don't have an identity,
so my guess is that
you won't need a new one.
Who the hell are you?
The way I see it,
you know you got jail on the
other side of this conversation.
I used your prints
to pull your file.
There isn't one. We don't
even know what to call you.
You're a ghost. Life as
you know it is over.
You aren't going home
for many years.
You're going back into a cell
and tomorrow at this time,
you'll be in Rikers
awaiting trial.
Come on, this case has Rabbit
written all over it.
What, do you think I work
for some criminal mastermind
that goes around calling
himself Mr. Rabbit?
Give me Rabbit.
Give him to me
and I'll cut you a deal.
Okay.
This is for the record.
State your name.
John Smith.
What are you doing?
Are you fucking with me?
No, you're fucking
with me.
The deal is real.
You said you wanted
to take the deal,
you stupid motherfucker.
Maybe,
but I'm not gonna sit here
and do your fuckin' job for you.
It's your funeral, asshole.