LINCOLN: You ready?
Didn't think
I'd be this nervous.
Now or never.
All right, papi.
Let's do this.
He's over there.
You must be Michael.
Your friend Fernando
tells me you could
use my services today.
Very much so.
And I assume
that's the other half
of your team.
You look beautiful.
Thank you.
It's my understanding
you'd like to
keep this simple?
We've never actually managed
to keep anything simple.
(BOTH LAUGH)
You can try.
Well, let's begin
then, shall we?
Family and friends,
we gather here
to celebrate the union
between Michael Scofield
and Sara Tancredi.
(BAND PLAYING UPBEAT MUSIC)
(SINGING IN SPANISH)
Hey, papi. This one
has Puerto Rican blood
in her, I think.
Look at her.
(LAUGHING)
(POLICE SIREN WAILING)
Sorry to
break up the party.
LINCOLN: What the hell's
going on?
We have an arrest warrant.
LINCOLN: What?
Wait, wait, wait.
Talk to Agent Paul Kellerman
in DC. We settled
this with the Feds.
We settled this
with the Feds weeks ago!
Sir, back up.
We were exonerated.
Sir.
We were exonerated!
AGENT: Back up!
We're not here for you.
We're here for her.
She didn't do anything.
She wasn't involved.
AGENT: Don't make
this escalate.
Sara Tancredi, you're
under arrest for the murder
of Christina Hampton.
LINCOLN: What?
She didn't kill anyone!
Funny, surveillance camera
footage says different.
Michael.
POLICEMAN 1: Please.
POLICEMAN 2: Right this way.
Michael. Michael.
POLICEMAN 1:
Second car, please.
Second car.
MAN: What's going on?
AGENT: Back up, please.
They're not gonna
let me see her.
Why did Kellerman send you
if you can't do anything?
They're trying to
break both of you.
Look, she has
a constitutional right
to reasonable visitation.
I'll draw up an order
to show cause and get it
before a judge immediately.
While you're at it,
can you argue
self-defense?
How?
Anything that might help her
is out-of-frame.
Security camera only shows
Sara stepping up
and firing at the victim.
Pull the trigger,
Michael.
Drop the gun!
(GUN CLICKING)
Misfire.
(GUNSHOT)
She worked
for the Company.
To you.
To a jury,
she's Christina Hampton,
technology consultant.
And because she was so good
at hiding her true identity,
we can't prove
otherwise.
Look, you were all exonerated.
It did not sit well
with law enforcement.
If they can make Sara
pay for it, they will.
How much time
is she looking at?
Twenty-five to life.
(BELL RINGING)
You, over here.
You, here.
This one's yours.
Am I supposed to be
in a different facility?
I don't think so.
I haven't been convicted
of anything yet.
I'm supposed to be in a jail.
This is prison.
Overcrowding
and budget cuts, Fish.
This is the jail.
That's the prison.
What's up, homie?
You need some help?
Got everything
you need over there?
Why don't you go help
her make her bed?
Don't let them spook you.
They just like to intimidate.
They're good at it.
Look, this jail/prison
hybrid thing is BS.
Come on,
the other one's
practically empty.
You can ride it out
till your court date there.
Thank you.
Here. This should be
a little bit more
comfortable for you.
Okay.
What's going on?
You know, at first
I couldn't place
your name, Tancredi.
Sounded so familiar.
Then Hucks
here figured it out.
I remembered your pretty face
from the papers.
You're not going
anywhere, Fish.
This is gonna happen.
Half a dozen guards
lost their jobs
and pensions at Fox River,
another dozen
were put on probation,
after you decided to leave
a door open for your boyfriend
and his seven convict pals.
And we ain't gonna
let anything like that
happen again.
(GRUNTS)
Don't worry.
We won't hit
the baby basket.
That's right.
Look like that welcome wagon
ran over your face.
It looks that way, huh?
I just came by
to help you get adjusted.
If you need something,
I know all these guards.
Most of them owe me.
I appreciate that.
But I can
take care of myself.
Oh!
My bad.
I don't know what
made me think you couldn't
take care of yourself.
(ALL LAUGH)
All right.
Well, if you need something,
you just ask for me.
Everybody calls me "Daddy."
Special delivery.
You know, all we need
is a little cash
to spread around the place.
I told you,
the government's
bruising my assets.
You telling me
you can't get your hands
on your cash?
I mean, that's the least
you could do,
considering
you was gonna kill me
not too long ago.
Goodbye, Theodore.
You ain't never been
incarcerated before
and I ain't never been
incarcerated here before,
and let's just say
this handicapped con
ain't got the juice he had
back in Fox River.
Your pathetic existence here
could be ameliorated,
as can my life,
all with a little
Roberto Dinero.
One of our friends
has been apprehended
by the authorities.
Looks like we've got
a new neighbor.
KRANTZ: I'm never gonna
get out of this prison alive.
I know that.
I want to bring my enemy
down with me.
I want her dead.
Either way, it's gonna
require capital,
capital you no longer have.
My rainy-day fund,
you know where it is.
Jonathan, I'd assumed
that that would be
used for your defense.
It's good money
after bad, Joe.
They're not gonna let me
out of here, no matter
how many shysters I hire.
Get that to our friend
in the sister cells
across the compound.
(LAUGHING)
Excuse me.
SUSAN B.: Bad move.
Last time someone touched her
they got a cracked kneecap.
You're much braver
than I gave you credit for.
Either that or
you're amazingly naive.
Why do you think
I want to talk to you?
Just saying, a woman
in your position might opt
for some protection.
Join a prison gang?
I don't think so.
Not a gang, no...
A family.
They don't call her
"Daddy" for nothing.
That's her wife
and those are her kids.
(COUGHING)
Are you okay?
You stay the hell
away from me.
I need to go
to the Infirmary.
You can't go to the Infirmary
without a release form.
I'm having
muscle contractions
in my throat,
and my jaw
is tightening up.
It's strychnine ingestion.
It's rat poison.
No, that's that
government cheese.
You'll get used to it.
If I don't get
to the hospital
in the next 15 minutes
I will die
and my baby will die.
Please.
Cowler, why don't you
let her go see the doc?
(GASPING)
Please.
This is Cowler.
We have an inmate
going to the Infirmary.
We were able to administer
the charcoal lavage in time.
You and your baby
are gonna be okay.
You know the strychnine
didn't get into my meatloaf
all by itself, right?
Well, then,
you need to talk to
the warden about it.
Then how about
talking to me
about your face?
Do you want to tell me
how that happened?
I caught an elbow
playing basketball.
We should discuss
your situation.
As I'm sure
you've ascertained
this isn't going to be
a run-of-the-mill pregnancy.
Do I deliver in here?
No.
The day we induce,
we'll secure you
in an ambulance,
take you to Saint Lucia
down the road,
we'll cordon off a room.
There'll be three armed guards
in there with me
when you give birth.
Do I get to see my baby?
You'll have 30 minutes
before we take it away.
I've seen this process
a dozen times.
After the mothers come back
here, the depression
is almost unbearable.
My advice, it's a lot less
messy if you just think
of yourself as a surrogate.
(CELL PHONE RINGING)
Yeah.
Michael, it's Blue Phillips.
Listen, your wife
had an incident
earlier today.
Someone tried to
poison her.
What are you talking about?
Michael, I need
you to focus.
Do you have any idea
who might've done this?
Michael? Michael.
All right. Let him in.
If I had a list of
all the people
who might come to visit me,
your name would be
at the bottom,
somewhere below
Jesus Christ
and Scooby Doo.
Someone tried to
poison Sara today.
Mercy!
Only you would be
depraved enough
to think that
killing an innocent woman
and her unborn child
would bring you
some kind of peace
before your execution.
Sara is with child?
Congratulations.
This is like the 4th of July
and Christmas day
rolled into one.
I'm asking you,
father to father,
to leave her alone.
You can kill me
if you want to kill me.
I'll trade my life for hers.
But leave Sara alone.
Michael, if you were killed,
your pain would last a moment.
If Sara were killed,
your pain would last
the rest of your life.
Now, that's got to be
appealing to whoever
put out this hit.
But don't worry, Michael,
if I find out anything
I'll be sure
to let you know.
WARDEN: Prison life
can be tough.
If I remember correctly
you have two missing toes
that can
attest to that fact.
I don't think you understand.
She's not safe here!
Please. Please just
approve the transfer
to another facility.
If I grant her a transfer,
everybody is gonna want one.
What about
segregated housing?
Is there something that
I should know about the
structural integrity of SHU?
Great. I can see
where this is going.
I know who you are
and I'm not gonna let you
turn my prison
into the next Fox River.
All I'm trying to do
is keep my wife alive.
You do know
she's pregnant.
I don't care.
Here.
Thanks.
In case I haven't
made myself clear,
Sara Tancredi is not getting
any preferential treatment.
Well, you've made yourself
perfectly clear.
Thank you for your time.
LINCOLN: What happened?
The General
wants Sara dead
and the warden's
just gonna let it happen.
Look, we got a lawyer
on the case, and he's gonna
get her out, all right?
There's not enough time.
If she stays in that prison,
someone's gonna kill her.
I guess we don't
have a choice.
We're breaking her out.
LANG: In my 16 years
in the Bureau,
I've worked cases under
43 different agents.
Alexander Mahone is
the smartest, bravest,
most honorable man
I've ever had the pleasure
of serving with.
SULLINS: Well, as one of
those 43 agents,
I can't help
but feel a bit offended,
because, obviously,
I'm not as honored as this
drug-addicted murderer.
Alex has been clean
and sober for four months.
And he's been
completely exonerated
of all crimes associated
with his involvement
with the Company.
That doesn't include
the shooting and murder
of one Oscar Shales
and burying his body
under the birdbath.
That is just an allegation.
Let's move on, shall we?
All those in favor
of reinstating
Alexander Mahone
as Special Agent
in the Federal Bureau
of Investigation.
Aye.
All those opposed.
All right. All right.
(EXHALES)
Thank you
for the invite, Richard.
It's always a pleasure.
You know, Alex,
this ruling can be revisited
if you are able to
sufficiently demonstrate
just how committed you are
to a life of service.
Now, as you may know,
Sara Tancredi
was arrested recently
and is currently being housed
at the Miami-Dade
State Penitentiary.
We have concerns
that Michael Scofield
may have other plans for her.
(LAUGHS)
So this... This is why
you invite me in here?
SULLINS:
Well, obviously,
if Scofield
were to be able to
pull off this plot
of another breakout,
the public embarrassment
would be immense
to the Bureau.
So, having someone to get us
credible information,
that would be worth
something to us.
Agent Wheatley
is set up in Miami.
He would be your contact.
You're something else.
Now, we both know
how badly you want
that badge back.
Give me a reason
to give it to you.
What's your plan
after we break her out?
We on the run again?
First things first.
Let's get her out of there.
Hey, papi, the Fed
that arrested Sara,
he's outside, staking us out.
Look, if you're worried about
getting into trouble again,
go back to Chicago,
go back to your family.
I'll understand.
Are you kidding me?
After all the crap
we've been through,
I'm just gonna
leave you here
and Sara in there?
You shut up and
don't bring it up again.
What's all that?
Newspaper clippings
covering seven different
escape attempts
from Miami-Dade State Pen
over the last 60 years.
None of them...
None of them successful.
So, we read them all
and we learn
what not to do.
Well, the prison officials
learned a lot.
They reevaluated,
they retrofitted.
Prison's practically
escape-proof.
You all right?
I'm fine.
Okay, so if we can't
go through,
what if we go down?
Like down into the prison,
like we parachute in.
Yeah.
Yeah, you parachute in,
you find her,
and we get her out.
Are you kidding?
I'm serious.
That's suicide.
Hey! Hey, hey.
Newspaper clippings are
only gonna get us so far.
We need some more information
about the prison.
So let's do
some recon work.
"Camera,
electronic tape measure,
dry ice." What's this?
It's a shopping list.
You need to
come with me, doll.
I have a doctor's appointment
for my pregnancy
in 15 minutes.
It'll wait.
In here.
Hold it.
I don't know what you want,
but I promise you,
I will go down fighting.
Damn, baby,
I ain't gonna hurt you.
Hell, I ain't even
gonna touch you.
See, I run the motor pool
detail in here,
and I was thinking,
if you want to get yourself
a little fresh air
and not have to worry about
getting stuck in the back,
then you could come
and work with me.
You're the Fed
from my wedding.
Yeah, you can call me
Agent Wheatley.
I could call you
a lot of things.
Where you headed?
SeaWorld.
SeaWorld?
There isn't one in Miami.
My loss.
No, what'd really
be your loss
is getting your wife killed
by doing something stupid.
Are you
threatening Sara?
No, no, no.
Not at all.
I'm just saying,
if you were gonna try
and revoke her sentence,
bullets fly, Michael.
And if she were
to get hurt,
that'd be on you.
Funny, hearing that
from the guy who put her
in prison in the first place.
No, I didn't
put her in prison.
The State of Florida did.
It's just my job
to make sure
that she stays there.
So, where's all
your little buddies?
All right. Drop in
some more dry ice.
(CAMERA CLICKING)
(BEEPING)
Fence line is four feet
from the road.
And 32 feet from
the east camera.
Hurry up.
They're gonna see the laser.
I'm going
as fast as I can.
(CELL PHONE RINGING)
He follow you?
Yeah, but he's gone now.
You guys almost done?
Almost.
Great.
I'll meet you back
at the loft.
Why, you just a natural.
I bet you was
a hell of a surgeon.
Handing out condoms
to cons don't make you
no damn surgeon.
What in the hell
is the matter with you?
You ain't even ask me
if she can
come on over here!
One day! Morrill!
Can't we go one day
without your mouth? One!
Let it be today.
I'm sorry. You got to
forgive my old lady.
She...
You just a little bit
easy on the eyes,
and she's just
the jealous type,
you know, so...
Crazy type
is more like it.
What? You want to
watch your tongue, Agatha?
Sorry.
Or you want me
to take off my belt?
AGATHA: All right.
(LAUGHS)
Kids.
It's rough.
It's hard running a family.
It's important though
that you have one.
I have a family.
I have a husband.
Oh. You got a husband?
Is he here?
They let him bring you in here
with you when you came?
No.
Yeah, I had a husband, too.
Eighteen years
is a long time to wait.
So, you know,
if this ain't for you,
that's cool.
Then you pick up that
nasty oil, and take it out
and put it in the repository.
Okay.
We gotta go, bro.
Get your hand off me.
When I'm good
and ready.
What's Burrows doing
by the fence?
Please don't make me
ask you again, Sara.
Nobody here to help you
but yourself.
Are you gonna answer me?
You tried to kill me.
Wind it up, cons.
Back inside.
You, get back
to your detail now.
I want you to pass along
an offer to your boy.
What he's paying his people
to dust that Tancredi chick
in bitch pop,
my woman will do it
for a cut rate.
Just what kind of discount
are you proposing here?
Tell him, if he's offered
100 grand,
my girl will take 30.
No, 40, 40.
Perfect. I'll tell him.
Hey, five-star.
So, you have no cash
whatsoever?
I'm sorry. I couldn't
hear you over the sound
of that broken record.
Got it.
I won't ask again.
DADDY: You act as stupid
as you look...
Oh. To what do
we owe the honor?
I've been thinking.
Well, no need to be shy,
just spit it out.
Changed my mind.
Yeah, well, maybe Daddy
changed her mind.
Maybe she don't want
you here anymore.
DADDY: Squirt's right.
I recently have
rolled up my welcome mat.
Peace.
Please.
Please what?
Please, may I be
a part of your family?
Take a walk.
Take a walk!
I would love that.
I... Sit down.
I really would.
But see, it's not that easy
as just saying, "I do."
See, you're making
a commitment to a family.
It's something
you gotta prove.
That's right.
We all did it.
DADDY: It's a commitment
to the family code.
It's a code you gotta wear.
(SCREAMING)
(TIRES SQUEALING)
Alex.
Hey, papi.
Hey, Sucre.
How you doing, Linc?
What's going on?
We gotta talk.
All right.
They're watching you.
We know.
We got a Fed on us.
No, not just one.
The whole department.
Sounds a lot like
inside information, Alex.
What did you do?
Make a deal with the Feds?
They offered me
my old job back if I came
down here to spy on you.
(CHUCKLES)
Now, the Fed
you're talking about,
his name is Wheatley.
He's running point.
So now we know.
So, if you're really
gonna do this,
you gotta do it right.
And I'll help you
if you need me.
What else did you get?
Sara was working
motor pool today at 4:00.
Motor pool is here,
visible by
two security cameras
along the perimeter
of the prison.
What about
secondary entrances?
No loading dock,
no personnel entrance.
Fences?
Fifteen feet high,
covered in razor wire.
SCOFIELD: Electrified?
SUCRE: No, why?
If Sara can get herself back
to motor pool, I think
we can find our way inside.
With all the different
retrofits over the years,
the fence line
was widened.
But the security cameras
remain exactly
where they've always been.
They never accounted
for the difference.
There's a blind spot.
Yeah. Right here.
If Sara can get back
to that spot,
we can breach the fence.
LINCOLN:
It's risky, Michael.
It's all we've got.
Now we just have to tell Sara
where we're going to meet her.
How? We got no visitation
and no phone calls.
It's clean.
Take it to Tancredi.
SCOFIELD:
Remember what I taught you
about flowers?
I wish I was with you now
to see you
holding one in your hand.
To see you
Tomorrow, p.m.,
7:00, oil dump.
(DOOR OPENING)
Sure looks like
you've been busy.
You have a warrant,
Agent Wheatley?
(LAUGHS) A warrant.
No, I don't need one.
My testimony will be
that your brother let me in,
and once inside,
saw all this evidence
right in plain sight.
What judge
is gonna take your word
over mine?
What evidence?
Those pictures were taken
from public property,
and that prison was paid for
by the tax payers.
So all you have evidence of
is an exonerated citizen
standing on a public road
taking pictures
of a public building.
Last I checked,
it's not a crime.
What if I said that
I could get you on attempt
just for having
all this stuff?
What if I told you
that all of this
was a peace offering?
The warden
won't let me see my wife,
so I figured if I found
a few lapses in security,
pointed them out
as a gesture
of good faith,
she might change her mind.
Is that so?
Find anything yet?
No, looks airtight.
You sure about that?
Nothing that some
scumbag can exploit?
Airtight.
Well, thank goodness
for that.
But you guys will let me know
if anything comes up, right?
You'll be the first
to know.
I won't keep you.
On the outside, I was known
for getting the job done
no matter what.
I got paid well for it.
Now I'm broke.
But I still need things.
Like what?
A favor?
I don't do favors
for cons.
Really? It's not
what it says
on the bathroom wall.
As I understand, you do favors
for those who reciprocate.
Is that true?
Hey, this is bullshit, boss.
I'm gonna
fight her out here.
Ain't no reason to toss me.
You... Hey...
You know me.
Looky, looky here.
No, that brown
ain't mine, boss.
You know this.
I don't do no drugs.
Who put that in there?
You... Get your hands off me.
I know where the hole is.
What you looking at?
I don't do no drugs.
Somebody is going down
for this.
I love you, too.
Sofia is making arrangements
in Central America.
Once you break Sara out,
we're on a boat
and we're gone.
(CELL PHONE RINGING)
Hey.
It's Blue.
Just got the decision
from the court.
They are ordering the warden
to allow
supervised visitation.
(SIGHS)
Where you going?
They're letting me see Sara.
Wait up, wait up, wait up.
They're going to be
listening to
every word you say.
You gotta be careful
about this.
If she understood my letter,
she'll find a way to tell me.
How? She gonna
blink Morse code?
Oh, my God.
Who did this to you?
I'm okay. Baby's okay.
Sara, I'm so sorry.
You're in here
because of me.
I'm sorry.
It's just hard.
I miss you so much.
No touching.
I miss you, too.
You just have to
hang in there, okay?
I'm trying,
but my protection's gone.
Did you get my letter?
I did.
I know sometimes
it's hard for me to express
what I wanna say,
but I hope you understood
what I meant to tell you.
I did.
Is he getting cute?
You were there for me.
I will be there for you.
Okay.
All right, that's it.
Time's up.
See you soon.
Bye.
WOMAN OVER PA: Attention
all inmates and visitors.
Visiting hours are now over.
Please proceed
immediately to the exit.
Michael.
I was thinking a lot
about the photos
and the mockup
that you showed me
at the loft,
and I ran a few tests.
Lo and behold,
I found a blind spot
right along
the fence line over here
due to a retrofit.
You didn't know about this,
did you?
No. No, of course not.
Because you would've told me
or the warden about it
if you did. Right?
It's a good thing
I found this when I did
before anyone
tried to escape.
Well, if we can't go
through the fence, then
that leaves under or over.
Look, how's she gonna
climb that fence
without being seen? Huh?
I'm guessing
there's no telephone wire
for her to climb across.
Then she's gotta
go under.
All right.
Let's get some shovels.
What was that
you were saying
about parachutes?
MAHONE: Parachutes?
Guys, come on.
You can't be...
Parachutes?
MAHONE:
A couple of thoughts
on that.
A, we don't have a plane.
B, we don't have a pilot.
Have you ever
worn a parachute?
Don't worry.
I think I've got a plan.
But we're gonna need
some help
from an old friend.
Who?
You want a favor from me.
Just hear me out.
Of course, I mean,
when you and Michael
sent me back to that prison,
you did give me
a piece of chewing gum.
I mean, what kind of man
would I be if I didn't
quid your pro quo.
Look, all you gotta do is
set off the fire alarm in here
tomorrow night at 7:30.
That's it.
You're breaking her out?
Krantz has put
a hit on her.
It's our one shot
of keeping her alive.
Well, you're in a pickle
covered in jam, Lincoln.
We'll put five grand
in your kick once
this whole thing jumps off.
The love of Michael's life.
That's only worth $5,000?
It's the best we can do.
I need six figures.
It's all we've got.
Well, lucky day for you,
I know somebody who does.
The General's man.
He's got the payout
for Sara's hit.
You wire that money to me
by 7:00 p.m. tomorrow,
and we're in business.
What's his name?
Get your brother
to use that noggin of his.
Come on, you gotta give me
more than that.
Tomorrow, 7:00 p.m.
Go on, fetch.
You're a tough girl
to get alone.
I know he's breaking you out.
I'm coming with you.
Relax.
Krantz sent me to kill you,
but after what
he's put me through,
I'm done taking orders
from him.
You were sitting
next to me in the mess
when I was poisoned.
You think you would've
lasted this long
if I wanted you dead?
I want you dead.
You're still alive.
You think it's hard to
stay alive when you know
who's coming after you?
There's 200 women
in this prison.
Could you even
get out of Gen Pop?
I'm coming with you
or nobody's going.
(SNIFFING)
You should've seen the look
on Michael's face
when he saw me
fixing that fence and
installing that camera.
You did a great job.
Well, job's over now.
If Michael has this
misguided belief that
Sara's life is in danger,
he's gonna find a way back
into that prison.
Your job won't be over
until you give us
enough evidence
to put him back
behind bars.
So, what's the latest?
There's nothing concrete,
but I'll let you know
when I get something.
All right.
Good man.
(SIGHS)
Well, if you're watching this,
I'm glad, because
that means you're safe.
How does he think
he's gonna
do this, bro?
He's gonna jump out
of a plane.
I know he's gonna jump,
but the question is,
can he land?
Not without
getting caught.
And how's
he gonna get her out
of the cell block?
Even if T-Bag...
It's a big "if."
Trusting T-Bag
is just crazy.
Michael, we really
have to rethink this.
I have, and there's
no other way.
Okay, I'm gonna drop down
into this outer area here,
and I'll cut the parachute off
before anyone can reach me.
They're gonna be
right on your ass.
I can hide
behind this building,
wait for a window.
And I'll make my way
over here.
That's the chapel,
where hopefully
Sara will be waiting.
LINCOLN: Why the chapel?
During a riot in '88,
prison employees escaped
through the
administration building
and wound up here,
outside the fence.
The administration building
is connected to the chapel,
which means that
somewhere in that compound
there's
a subterranean exit.
If we can get through it,
you can meet us there.
How's Sara
gonna get to the chapel?
She'll have to
find a way.
Look, we're doing this
at 7:00 p.m. tonight
just like we planned.
Where have you been?
What did I miss?
I need you to find
a plane and a pilot.
And I need you two
to take care of T-Bag.
Find out exactly
who has this money and
where they're keeping it.
And then
we have to get it.
By 7:00 p.m. tonight,
or Sara's gonna die in there.
Is everybody onboard?
Yeah.
Okay.
Tell me you've completed
your assignment.
Well, I've got the cash,
but there may be
some delay in final delivery.
The woman we hired
is having trouble
getting near Sara Tancredi.
Then hire somebody else.
Call it open season.
Put a bounty on her head.
I don't care how you do it.
I want Sara Tancredi dead
by the end of the day.
GUARD: Open cell, one hour.
Yo, we're about to play cards.
Do you want in?
I'm okay, thanks.
You should. With Daddy gone,
you gonna need your backup.
Hell, we all do.
I've got a prenatal thing.
It's cool.
Thanks.
Not too smart, though,
for a girl with
a bounty on her head.
Or ain't you heard?
Tancredi, you have
a visitor.
Say hello to
your husband for me.
(DOOR BUZZING)
What's wrong?
Look, I know you don't
have any control
over what's happened here,
but things
aren't working out.
Okay.
I've been trying to
find a way to do this,
but from where
we stand right now
there's only one option.
Do you need more time
to think?
No. No, it's not that.
I've made up my mind.
There's really nothing
you can do about it,
except
pray for us tonight.
Pray for us?
You can pray for us
to be together.
Maybe I'll do the same.
How can I rob someone
if I have no clue
who he is?
The log book outside says
that Krantz had one visitor
yesterday. Joe Daniels.
Well, using the power
of deduction,
I'd say Daniels
is your bagman.
You know how many Daniels
live in Miami?
Thousands. I need more.
Well, you better get cracking,
'cause if I ain't
got that money by 7:00,
you ain't got your fire,
you ain't got
your fire alarm,
and that means Pretty
ain't got his Mrs. Pretty.
Listen, my friend,
you're in no position
to make demands.
(SHUSHING) Okay.
I ain't talking about
backing out of the deal.
I'll put my ear to the ground
and come up with some details.
Good. Now go fetch.
(SIGHS)
We got a pilot.
It's a guy I busted
20 years ago running drugs
across the Gulf.
Went legit,
runs a charter business now.
You must've jumped out
of a few planes, huh?
Yeah. Several.
Some for sport,
some necessity.
It's a big difference,
Michael.
It's not easy hitting the X,
especially at night.
Don't worry.
I can go alone.
What do you got?
It's a test.
See, the prison
was built in the mid '80s,
so that exit in
the administration building
is probably protected
by an electronic coded lock
modified by
a security card.
Those locks don't have
power protection, which means
you can override them.
And you can't just
go to the building's
generator and blow it out?
No, a 1,200 volt power surge
will just set off
the other alarms.
Not to mention
maybe kill you.
It's why we have to
find another way.
Yeah.
(CELL PHONE BUZZING)
Talk to me, Mahone.
What do you got?
Nothing yet.
I don't need updates
on the hour.
I need evidence.
Intent, it's not crap.
Call me when
he's in the process
of committing a crime.
Yeah.
I'm not gonna let him
walk away from me
like he did from you.
He's going down
if I gotta shoot him
in the back.
Sorry.
Time for me
to get paid, now, Fish.
(WOMEN SHOUTING)
Are we friends now?
Get out of the way.
What happened here?
I didn't
see anything, sir.
Move.
Me neither.
What?
Bad news.
Agatha Warren is dead.
Who did that?
No one's talking.
But I hear it's those fish,
Tancredi and Morgan.
No!
MAHONE: Here he is.
If you don't like this guy,
we can still
find someone else.
Good to see you, Sidney.
What you getting
into here, Mahone?
Jumping at 1,500 feet
ain't going to be easy.
You going back
on your word already?
Let's not forget
who's doing
who a favor here.
Favor?
Favor? Did I bust
your old lady
for trafficking?
No, I did not.
If anyone asks,
I was flying a tourist
to the Keys
and it's not my fault
he jumped.
Sounds good to me.
If you don't like this guy,
we take a day,
we come up with a new plan.
No. There's no time, Alex.
It's not just
Sara's life at risk.
I understand that.
I know you do.
That's why I also know
I can ask for your help.
Yeah. What do you need?
If I don't make it,
I want you to make sure
Sara and my brother
get out of the country alive.
I need to know
they're gonna be okay.
And I'm gonna trust that
you'll do everything you can
to make that happen.
Take this.
I trust you, Alex.
Remember that.
Special delivery.
What is it?
Don't exactly know.
Came via messenger
from the ladies' side.
My man on the outside
needs to know who to call
for the birthday present.
Whose birthday is it?
Okay. See to it
it gets back
to the same place.
Will do.
This is Joe Daniels'
number, right?
That's it. Is that
enough information,
or you need a social
security number, too?
It'll do.
Remember, I want
that money wired
to the account number
specified.
No wire. No fire.
You boys do me wrong,
I have no qualms at all
about singing loud and clear,
you understand?
You know what?
Just be ready.
(SPEAKING SPANISH)
That was Sofia.
She'll meet you
in the San Andres Harbor
in the Dominican Republic
and then you guys
can fly to Costa Rica.
Cool. I know
where Daniels is.
And after we rob him,
I'll take the money
to Quik Green
and wire it to the bank.
And you're gonna meet us
at the airstrip, right?
I'll give it a shot, yeah.
Okay. This is it.
(SIGHING) We're ready.
Thanks, buddy.
For everything.
Good luck, papi.
See you on the other side.
Nobody's talking, huh?
Girl's dead and
no one says anything.
I made it
in the woodshop.
Want to give my daughter,
Emily, her birthday gift
on her actual birthday.
That's why I need to
get out of here.
How very sentimental.
I'm not.
It's just for her.
We need to
get to the chapel.
We?
There's no way
out of here, right now,
I'm gonna need you.
Yeah.
Mr. Daniels,
American Paint Company
here for the job.
Well, this is Mr. Daniels
and I didn't
order any painters.
It's Wednesday, sir.
I believe you did.
Okay, hold it right there.
I'm calling the police.
Get out.
SCOFIELD: This is it.
I'll be right back.
I gotta get that parachute.
Michael, come here.
There's a better way.
GUARD 1: Mess!
Mess, half hour.
GUARD 2:
Okay, let's go, girls.
GUARD 3: Clean up.
Little faster.
We don't have all day.
GUARD 4: Let's go.
Got any ideas?
Yeah.
Keep your head down
and follow me.
I'll think of something.
GUARD 4: Single line!
Single line!
You better think
of something fast
'cause we have company.
GUARD 1: Keep walking,
keep walking.
I hope you're ready
for a fight, princess.
This one's to the death.
Do you think
you can overpower her?
Yeah.
I don't think it's her
you have to worry about.
Just be ready.
(CELL PHONE RINGING)
Hello.
It's me. I got the message
about the birthday present.
Was the gift earned?
What in the hell
are you talking about?
The birthday present.
The birthday present?
Two guys showed up
at my house,
they took the money
and they
beat the crap out of...
Howdy, General.
I just thought
I'd let you know
I came into some green.
My personal preference
is two Zagnut bars
and a copy of The Times.
So I'll see you
in the a.m.
You worthless
son of a whore.
Go to hell!
Careful I don't
get there first,
lest I become king
of that prison, too.
All right, from takeoff
to prison's
gonna come up real fast.
So whatever
you got to do
to get ready, do it now.
We got it.
You got the money?
Sucre just dropped me off
on the way to wire him.
Good. That means
T-Bag's set.
I'm gonna see
how long it's gonna
take him to get going.
You sure that thing's
gonna hold you up?
Yeah, it'll be fine.
What about you?
It's not my first time
inside a prison.
Hopefully,
it'll be my last.
(DIALING)
Think about all
the amazing stories you'll
be able to tell your kid.
You're gonna be
the type of father
our dad never was.
Someone to look up to.
Take care, Michael.
WHEATLEY:
Unless you've got details,
I'm hanging up.
You can forget about
getting your badge back.
He's got a plane.
He's gonna
parachute into the yard.
What?
Yeah. I swear to God.
He's gonna be over
prison airspace at 7:00.
Call in reinforcements.
I want 20 armed COs
in the yard.
And be ready to turn off
all exterior lights.
Scofield won't see
what's coming
until it's too late.
And bring me Sara Tancredi.
Wait. Wait.
What you think
happened with Agatha,
it's not what happened.
I need to make this
right with you, okay?
Go ahead.
I was hoping
I'd see you here.
You know I still owe you
one big juicy favor.
Later, blue eyes.
I swear to God, she wanted
to kill me and I was
just defending myself.
Remember this?
Yes, I do.
My mama gave me that.
Told me I was going to
give it to
one of my kids one day.
I never did get knocked up.
But I grew up a family.
And I practically
raised Agatha.
She was no killer.
Now, I can't say
that much for myself.
You don't even know
what I had in mind yet.
Okay, listen, you're right.
Agatha isn't a killer.
She's just a real bitch
who bit off
more than she could chew.
(GRUNTS)
Skittlez.
Okay, we're cool.
We're cool.
(STAMMERING)
We're cool. We...
GUARD: Cowler, Simms wants
you to bring Tancredi
to her office.
All right. Okay.
(GRUNTING)
(ALL SCREAMING)
(SCREAMS)
Son of a bitch.
They'll be coming back
through here, okay?
Federal Agent Todd Wheatley,
I need to
get inside right now.
Emergency team
takes priority, sir.
I'm the leader
of the emergency team.
Now let me inside.
Sir, I have strict orders.
Go talk to your supervisor.
Come on.
Yo, Evans,
let the suburban through.
The planes will be
overhead any minute.
Hey, fellows,
kill the lights.
As soon as he hits the ground,
that's when
I want you to start firing.
Stand by.
We're standing by.
Easy there.
Hold your fire.
Stand by.
Now.
Let's go.
POLICEMAN: Move in, men.
GUARD: Hold your fire!
Hold your fire.
Sixteen, hold your fire.
Moving in.
Where the hell is Scofield?
Emergency team
takes priority, sir.
I'm the leader of
the emergency team.
Now let me inside right now.
I have strict orders,
no one gets inside
at this point, sir.
I don't care
what your orders are.
Go talk to your supervisor.
(ALARM BLARING)
(ALL SCREAMING)
WARDEN ON RADIO:
Why isn't Tancredi
in front of me right now?
Well, we just
got this situation
under control.
We're looking
for her right now.
WOMAN:
I didn't do anything.
Oh, my God.
Are you all right?
It was Morgan.
Check the kitchen.
They might be
in the kitchen.
I'm not gonna
make it on my own.
Either leave me
or don't, Sara,
but make up your damn mind.
You gonna be able
to make it?
Yeah.
Okay. It's now.
POLICEMAN: Hold up.
(ALARM CONTINUES BLARING)
No, I think we're good.
POLICEMAN:
Don't move!
In the dirt, now!
Please, I just...
On the ground.
You here alone?
Damn it, con!
When I ask you
a question, you answer.
Is there
anyone else here?
Yes.
Who?
God.
Excuse me?
He's always here.
I was worried about
my little girl
on the outside.
So I came to pray.
See if someone
would watch over her.
Go check it out.
GUARD OVER RADIO:
I want some asses over in
the women's cell block now!
We got to get these
animals locked down.
We better
head over there.
I hope that daughter
of yours is a hell of
a lot smarter than you.
So do I.
Hey!
You ready to go?
(SIGHING) Yeah.
WHEATLEY: Nobody gets in
or out of this prison.
I don't care
if it's the president
having to take a piss,
you tell him
to turn the hell around.
And get a team.
I want every inch
of that fence line checked
for points of compromise.
Yes, sir.
Michael said
this is where
they're gonna come out.
You think Sucre
made the drop on time?
Don't know.
(BANGING ON DOOR)
No, no, no, no!
AUTOMATED VOICE:
Please enter
your account number.
Nine, two, four,
eight, pound.
Your account balance is
zero dollars and zero cents.
If you would like to access
another account...
Nine, two, four,
eight, pound.
Your account balance is
zero dollars and zero...
What the hell do you think
you're doing, Fish?
We in lockdown.
What for?
Something's going on
in bitch block.
I don't know.
What's it worth
to you to find out?
We gotta
get through here?
On the other side
is a kind of escape hatch
for the administrators
in case of a riot.
If this is the same system
they have in Fox River,
that door can only
be opened remotely
from the central control room.
That's why we had
to ask for help.
T-Bag.
Tell them
what you told me.
Michael Scofield's about
to stage a prison break.
And I know exactly
how he's going to do it.
Exactly what did
Scofield ask you to do?
Just light a fire in my cell,
and the rest will
just take care of itself.
Fire alarm.
When that goes off,
what's your protocol?
State law,
mandatory evac.
Yeah, he wasn't gonna
break her out, he was gonna
get you to escort her out.
Shut up.
Get him out of here.
All right. Evacuation's only
going to get him
out in the yard.
Whatever he's up to,
he needs noise
and he needs chaos.
Deactivate
the smoke detector system,
the fire alarm,
and while you're at it,
kill the horn.
If anybody so much
as bends a blade of grass
in this place,
I want to be able
to hear it.
What are we waiting for?
We made a deal.
For the right price,
T-Bag would set off
the fire alarms.
(ALARM STOPS)
That's what
we were waiting for.
Michael, there's a...
It's okay.
See, there's only one thing
you can count on when
you're dealing with T-Bag.
He's a rat.
Anything?
So far, just
a female inmate
loose in the yard.
Tancredi?
No, Morgan,
first name, Gretchen.
Over by the chapel.
All right.
SCOFIELD: All right.
Great. Let's go.
Okay, down there.
Okay.
Beyond this door should be
a hundred yards of tunnel.
On the other end
of that is Linc,
and after that there's a boat
bound for white sand
and blue water.
I'll power-surge this system.
It will override the reader
for just a few seconds,
just long enough for you
to open the hatch,
so get ready.
Three, two, one.
One more time.
I was afraid
this might happen.
That's okay.
It's all right.
We're gonna keep moving
and we're gonna find
another way out of here.
I know what I have to do.
I need units
to the chapel now.
POLICEMAN:
Unit five-three, ten-four.
Where are they?
I don't know.
They should have
been here by now.
The battery wasn't
generating enough power.
We have to blow the system
for the whole building.
Okay, what do
you want to try?
This is the main fuse.
If I yank that, everything
will go dark for a second.
If I reconnect
these two cables...
these two cables,
there'll be a lot of noise.
Every light bulb
in this place
is gonna blow.
As soon as that happens,
you need to open that hatch.
And then I want you to
start running.
Okay. What about you?
Michael?
Sara...
Someone has to stay here,
and someone
has to open the hatch.
And that someone's
got to be you.
Okay. So I'll leave it
open for you.
You don't understand.
This is the only way.
I'm not leaving unless
you're coming with me.
I am coming with you.
I love you.
God! I love you too.
(BANGING ON DOOR)
Go.
Go, Sara. Go.
Downstairs.
Where's Michael?
Sara, where's...
Where is he?
He's not coming back.
(LINCOLN BREATHING HEAVILY)
What?
What do you mean,
he's not coming back?
What do you mean by that?
He's not coming back.
LINCOLN: He'll be here.
He's gone, Linc.
Linc, we got to go.
We got to go.
MAHONE: We got to go.
GUARD: The gates are gonna
be open in a minute.
T-BAG: Why am I
being punished?
I'm the guy
who blew the whistle.
You aided and abetted
an escape, Mr. Bagwell.
As far as the authorities
are concerned,
you're an accomplice.
Scofield!
Michael asked me
to give you this
if he didn't make it out.
He said it would
help you understand
why he did what he did.
It's his blood work.
This is
the General's money.
I was supposed to
wire it down to Costa Rica
for you to pick up, but
I ran into some trouble.
I'm sorry.
You take care
of that baby, okay?
of yours.
This is for you.
He never said
anything to me.
Why didn't
he just tell me?
Because he knew
you'd try to stop him.
He knew you'd do anything
to protect your family.
But I didn't.
MAHONE: Well,
you will soon.
Take it easy.
Sara.
Thank you.
Yeah.
(SIGHS)
Well, if you're
watching this,
I'm glad,
because it means
you're safe.
And that's all I ever wanted.
I wish I could
be there with you.
But as you probably know now,
I wouldn't have had
much time anyway.
So, I made my choice,
and I don't regret it.
Anyway, not too long from now
there's going to be
another little Scofield
running around.
And, Linc, I want
you to promise me,
no matter what, they're going
to grow up knowing
their uncle’s never far away.
And Sara, I want you to
promise me that you're
gonna keep an eye on Linc.
As you may have noticed,
he has a tendency
to get in trouble.
(LAUGHS)
You know, we spend so much
of our lives not saying
the things we want to say.
The things we should say.
We speak in code
and we send
little messages, origami.
So now, plainly and simply,
I want to say
that I love you both
very much.
And I want you to promise me
that you're going to
tell my child...
That you're going to
tell my child how much
they're loved every day.
And remind them
how lucky they are
to be free.
Because we are.
We're free now.
Finally.
We're free.