NARRATOR:
Previously on Prison Break:
MAN: The price of the operation
is the safe return of Scylla.
GRETCHEN:
See if the buyer left him a message.
SELF:
Yeah, it's a Miami area code.
The item.
I'm sure you understand
no one can know where Scylla's going.
Do you know who took it?
-No, but Self and Gretchen do.
-Then you've got your team.
-I'm not working for them.
-There are holes in your résumé...
...that Gretchen, or Self,
or even Bagwell can fill.
-What happened?
-He got away.
-What's this?
-My resignation.
Whatever plan you're working on to
get us out, we better make a move on it.
You're not getting out here, Michael.
I made a deal.
Your life in exchange for Scylla.
You think you can do that, knowing
what you know about the Company?
Wanna know what I know
about the Company?
Mom worked for them
before she died.
And I'm gonna do everything
and anything I can to end this.
[PHONE RINGING]
-Hello?
-Sara, it's me.
Where are you?
Miami.
The guy who took Scylla's here.
You're actually trying
to get it back for the Company?
I'm gonna give it back to the Company
so we can walk away from this.
-How's Michael?
-I don't know. I don't know.
Two guys from the Company came
and they brought me to a hotel.
And I was given flowers
and a fruit basket...
...and absolutely no information
about Michael.
-Is Fernando with you?
-Sucre split.
We left some messages with Mahone
telling him where we were.
-That was two cell phones back.
-Sorry, who's we? Who are you with?
People I don't trust.
Okay, listen.
Lincoln, I know why you did it...
...and I'm grateful to you,
because he was gonna die.
But do you think they're gonna
let us live when we give them Scylla?
You know what?
I'm doing my best.
Just call me if you hear anything
about Michael, please.
Linc. Company's data tech
finally got a hit on our guy's cell phone.
It's a number
and it goes to this address.
-The Grafton. It's a club.
-How many calls?
Three, all outgoing.
BAGWELL:
How do we know he's still in Miami?
That he hasn't sold it already?
Not that I'm complaining.
I've had some filthy times
in this state.
Don't screw this up, all right?
Because that's our only lead on this guy.
Be thankful I haven't killed you.
Oh, yeah?
What are you, Eliot Ness now?
Were you upset
because I screwed you?
Don't act like you haven't done that
to 10 times as many people.
All right, we're just crooks
that got caught, Lincoln.
This guy, this isn't gonna work.
Why don't we all just focus
on who's got Scylla?
What do you say?
[SIGHS]
MAN:
Hey, Scofield.
-Where am I?
-He's awake.
I said where am I?
It's a house in the woods,
60 miles from anywhere.
Swept clean of weapons so you don't
need to worry your head about that.
There are no bars
on the windows or the doors.
Three types of mountain lion
in the area.
-So you might wanna stay close by.
ROGER: I'll take it from here.
Dr. Roger Knowlton, Michael.
How are you feeling?
-Are you some kind of neurologist?
-Psychiatrist.
Given that you've got some free time,
the general asked if I'd sit with you.
A cigar's a cigar. Are we done?
You've been operating under some
misconceptions about the Company...
...and the general wants
to open the books.
I'm here to provide facts
and to help you process them.
If by facts,
you mean what's on Scylla...
...and that my mother
once worked for the Company...
...I already know these things.
ROGER:
Worked?
Your mother works for us.
Your mother is alive.
Had to come in to look for a fight.
-Hey, we don't open till 3.
-Sorry, I'm just looking for someone.
I haven't got the guy's name.
Called here yesterday
about three times.
New Yorker, dark hair, bits of gray.
You know where I can find him?
Yeah, can't help you, sorry.
You sure?
You need to check your ears, he said we
don't know who you're talking about.
-Is that right?
-Yeah, that's right.
Well, what about blondie?
You got about two seconds--
-How about it?
-I don't know his name.
He works--
This girl works here, he dates her.
Then you'll take me to her.
MICHAEL: Well, this is all just fascinating,
doctor.
ROGER:
I don't know how to say this.
She left you and your brother
to protect you.
From the dangers
of solar synthesis work?
I know what's on Scylla.
ROGER: There were threats
you and Lincoln might be kidnapped.
You were in imminent danger.
MICHAEL: Really? Where was she
when my brother...
...was strapped to an electric chair?
She'd been working
in a Madagascar rainforest...
...without satellite access.
Or she wasn't alive,
hasn't been for 25 years.
And this is all fiction.
ROGER: There's a million acres of corn
and soy outside Córdoba...
...that was arid scrub
before your mother's research.
That's not fiction.
That's food for thousands.
Millions.
There's so much more on Scylla
than you know.
Sounds like we have a lot to talk about.
Why don't you get her on the phone?
-When you're ready.
-No time like the present.
When you're ready to join her.
Us.
That's what this conversation is about.
Joining the Company.
Hey, Erica, it's me.
So are you coming?
I really need to talk to you.
[PHONE BUZZING]
She's on her way.
Oh, my God.
Why'd this guy call the club's phone
and not Erica's?
I-- They fight a lot.
So when she doesn't answer,
he calls the club.
So, what do you want with this guy?
He took something that belongs to me.
I want it back.
There. There's Erica.
Wait here.
WOMAN:
He's got a gun!
[GUNSHOTS]
Ugh!
SCOTT:
Get him stitched up.
Big guy, shaved head. Crazy.
-Who the hell is he?
-I don't know.
And he bought the whole thing
about this chick?
Yeah. He didn't know
I was with you...
...and by the time he did,
he was trying not to get shot.
Hey, hey, hey. You did good.
I just need a smoke so bad.
-Oh, no.
-What?
My wallet.
This is the chick who set me up.
We find her, we find our guy.
GRETCHEN: Busting up clubs,
throwing shots in public.
Keep that up and we're not
gonna last here much longer.
I don't plan
on staying here very long, you?
That's why I have to give it up
to the general.
He puts four enemies together,
guaranteed dissension.
And no alliances formed against him.
This is our guy's girlfriend's address.
She's probably gone,
but see what you can find.
GRETCHEN:
This is Tia.
You wanna know what I think
they were talking about?
I don't care, just as long
as they keep out of my way.
Same with you.
Send her in.
Sara, you're looking rested.
How was the hotel?
I would like to offer my professional
assistance in Michael's rehabilitation.
Kind, but he's receiving excellent care.
There's nothing for you to worry about.
Whatever it is you have planned for him,
I would like to help maintain his health.
And that's appreciated,
but it's impossible.
Believe me, you serve Michael best
at a distance right now. Trust me.
I have no agenda apart from simply
wanting to see that he's okay.
And in three days to a week,
he'll be back in your loving arms forever.
Okay, I'm not that patient.
Indulge yourself.
Sit by the pool. Envision the future.
Financial security.
Michael's talents
being utilized on a global scale.
You beside him, innovating.
Michael's talents
being utilized on a global scale?
I'm simply trying
to maximize his potential.
Yours too.
What's being done to him?
I'm putting an end
to this exhausting cat and mouse.
Thank you for stopping by.
Radical architecture is a rejection
of all formal and moral parameters.
-From your thesis.
-Someone else's words.
Heavily paraphrased.
It pertains to buildings, structures.
I think you meant it as a metaphor.
For what?
That the ends justify the means?
Which neatly coincides
with your mother's philosophy.
Do you know that she had
an almost identical quote in her thesis?
From 30 years ago.
-You've done a lot of homework.
-Just a few conversations.
Let me guess.
You two had some kind of moment...
...at the Company Christmas party?
I've known your mother for years.
Well enough to know
you've got the same brilliant mind...
...and same sense of humor
for that matter.
I'm guessing this isn't about
my sense of humor.
She was just as resistant
to joining the Company.
But then she learned the truth.
If the truth is that the Company is
all about saving the world, I don't buy it.
And if my mother is so brilliant,
and actively Company...
...what do you want with me?
A fully functioning Scylla project
would exist on a global scale.
It can't be managed by one person.
But two?
Equally formidable,
working in lockstep.
Absolutely.
That's very good.
You've clearly thought of everything.
Michael.
If I weren't telling you the truth...
...how would I have gotten this?
[PHONE BUZZING]
BAGWELL:
Go, go, go.
This is just a stupid girl
who dates a criminal.
This is a waste of time.
-Signature of Burrows' leadership.
-All right, we need to make a shift.
I'm telling you,
if I make my play and you go soft...
...I will sail you off that loft balcony
and no one will bat an eye.
My aim is true, Don.
-Keep it in your pants.
-I'll keep it in my pants, all right?
All right, all in favor
of changing the regime, say aye.
-Aye, aye, captain.
-Aye. All right.
Burrows is out.
Good, go ahead. Send it.
Company's e-mailing
Tia's credit card history.
You know, I'm thinking more and more
that this is an inside job.
-Why?
-A couple reasons.
The hardware he brought to the meet.
He could read Scylla right on the spot.
Since he's disappeared, I should be able
to find this man, and I can't.
People you can't find
are usually Company.
-How does that change anything?
-It doesn't, it makes everything harder.
-Lincoln?
-Yeah?
When are we gonna get this
out of the way?
What?
With all the mercenary humps
I've thrown at guys in my lifetime...
...I think I'm due for one I want.
Don't flatter yourself.
Too late.
Name it.
And I do mean anything.
BAGWELL:
Big old fat load of nothing.
Big old goose egg.
Nothing.
Old address books, some photographs.
Hard drive from her computer. I checked
her e-mails, nothing from our guy.
You sure this route is the way to go?
This is starting to feel like a wasted trip.
How long is it gonna take
to pull everything off this?
A couple hours.
All right, this is the deal.
Look, we appreciate your effort,
but Bagwell and I took a vote.
And this being Florida and all,
you came up a little bit short.
-Meaning?
-You're not in charge.
-Who is?
-Him.
Yeah, the routine might have worked
when you were stealing gumballs.
But our asses
are on the line now, okay?
We all have deals with the general.
So that's the way it's gonna be.
If you notice, even Gretchen
hasn't leapt to your defense.
-Linc, just let him wear his crown.
-I would if he wasn't gonna sell this.
Am I the only one who's thought
about that? Here's the deal.
At some point, you'll have a vote.
Until then you're done.
We're shutting you down, okay?
You're no longer in charge.
[DOOR OPENS]
GRETCHEN:
Uh-oh. Look's like there's been a recount.
-Bad time?
-No, perfect.
The second you stop doing
what I tell you to do...
...I'm gonna blow your brains out.
-Bring her back.
-It's not gonna be the same.
ROGER:
Stirred any memories?
I was 10. We were on a camping trip
in Jackson Hole.
Fishing, hiking, family huddled
under a blanket in front of the bonfire.
-You can stop now.
-Why?
Because two years later it was gone?
You know, three of the four people
in this photograph are still alive.
So, what are you suggesting?
Grab my fishing pole?
Time for a family reunion in Wyoming?
Or wherever you like. Don't tell me
it's something you haven't wished for.
I wished for a lot of unrealistic things.
-I got over them too.
-Why, when we can make this happen?
These pictures could have been taken
anywhere at any time.
Before you were incarcerated,
you'd go to visit her grave.
-That's enough.
-You'd bring a bouquet, sit for an hour.
When you'd leave, you'd take a flower
and pin it to your lapel.
She watched you do this every year.
She's seen the pain you carry.
-She wants to make amends.
-All right!
So you did a little digging,
good for you.
But everything out of your mouth is a lie,
and I don't believe a word of it.
So let's just stop.
Let's just stop.
SELF: That's Tia's address
right there. Pull it up.
All right, she lives here, works here,
but yesterday...
...she used her credit card
to buy a drink at the Pelican Club.
Then she picked up
something at the gift shop.
-Waiting for her boyfriend to de-bark.
-Disembark.
LINCOLN: He was already in town?
-Yeah.
Then he lives in the marina.
Or this is another reason
to think it's an inside job.
If he's working with the Company...
...they wouldn't want their names
on any flight manifests.
They're trying to get Scylla
out of the country by boat undetected.
MAHONE:
Let's go.
-Alex.
-Yeah?
Thanks for coming when you did, man.
You helped me
like you said you would.
I owe you.
SELF: Okay, I'll do the talking.
You guys wait here.
Alex, let's go.
Afternoon.
SELF: How's it going?
-What can I do you for?
MAHONE: Recognize her?
SELF: Her name's Tia Hayden.
Can't say I do. Wish I did.
Nice little tomato there.
She was in here yesterday with a man.
Can't help you. Sorry.
I'm Don Self with Homeland Security.
-And this is my partner, Bruce Liberace.
-No relation.
Our department is working with
the Office of Foreign Assets Control.
-Have you heard of them?
-Yup.
We're looking into the smuggling...
...and contraband transportation
of Cuban cigars.
None here, swear to God.
All right, that's for us to decide.
It's gonna take a week and it involves
shutting down this entire marina.
-Oh, yeah.
-For about a week.
-Or what I'm gonna--
-She was here.
With that guy you were talking about.
He wanted to know which berth
a private charter was in.
He asked me to move it further down.
-Further away from the Coast Guard slip?
-I didn't ask.
I didn't accept any money.
If he said he paid me, he's lying.
-What's the point of departure?
-Nassau, Bahamas, round trip.
-When does it arrive?
-Arrived.
SELF: Hey, everybody.
Okay, my name is Don Self.
Homeland Security.
My colleagues and I...
...are hoping that you guys
have a wonderful and safe trip.
Unfortunately, we're gonna have to do
a quick luggage-check search.
Shouldn't take more than a minute.
Your cooperation is all that's required.
Open your bags, folks.
That's fine, thank you very much.
LINCOLN: Get on your knees.
MAHONE: Give me the backpack.
Where is it? Where's Scylla?
What have you got here?
It's three joints.
I'm on probation.
Is this gonna send me back?
MAN:
Make yourself a helmet, pal.
Just like old times.
-Bring her back.
-You know I can't do that.
But look, there's some stuff
that I can do.
It's not gonna be the same,
but we're gonna figure it out.
And no matter what,
it's still gonna be me and you.
I'm thrilled that you're enjoying
your trip to the mountains...
...but it's not an open-ended vacation.
Scofield's exhausted, despondent.
He's resistant. Classic abandoned
childhood. He'll come around.
-Time frame, doctor.
-Unaided? Three days.
With the Pentothal?
Well, sooner,
but it's nearly a chemical lobotomy.
But if he turns on his own,
it'll be his decision.
His reasoning. We'll own him forever.
Scofield's squirrelly.
I won't trust him
till he walks hot coals.
-I think I can get him there.
-Good.
But if I find out
he's been playing you, doctor...
...you'll get the same lobotomy
as Scofield.
Just get it done.
[PHONE RINGING]
MAN:
Let's go.
In the van.
Go.
If you fight when those cuffs are off,
the guards will stomp the life out of you.
Yeah.
Forgive the dramatics. The Company
can't know I'm talking to you.
You are the Company,
you're his daughter.
-Do you wanna find Michael Scofield?
-Of course I do.
It's 60 miles northeast of downtown.
And I'd move quickly.
-What are they doing to him?
-Having lemonade.
They're carving out his personality.
That's how they recruit.
-Or you're setting me up.
-Clandestine warfare isn't pretty...
...but the rules of engagement
don't include killing the innocent.
At least not for me.
Michael is the object
of a quick and nasty process.
And you're wasting time. Out.
Out.
[TIRES SCREECHING]
Ask if the foreign--
MAHONE: We need the footage
from that security camera.
Not to offend you, I took the liberty
of calling my attorney...
...to find out the scope
of your authority is.
-And he tells me there is no--
-I need the tape, all right?
Sure.
[WHISTLING]
-Either we missed Scylla--
-No, no, no, we did not miss Scylla.
We searched every bag.
Then maybe the buyer
was already on the boat...
...and was disembarking, right?
If they don't want their names
on any flight manifest...
...maybe they just eased back on in.
That wouldn't be the worst news.
That means they're in Miami.
Right, so get yourself back down
with your disgraced badge...
...to Steamboat Willie and have him
cough up every name on that boat.
Okay, that's good.
Because they probably
would have traveled in...
...on a low-grade charter
from the Bahamas.
And used their real names, right?
That would be a good plan.
MAHONE: How is he?
-He's alive.
-So we get Scylla--
-And we're free.
All of us. Pam, L.J.
All of a sudden
the Company grew a heart?
They're just tired of us.
They want Scylla back, and that's it.
We never really had
anything they wanted.
Exactly. Now we got leverage.
Well, we don't have it yet.
LINCOLN:
Anything?
No, nothing yet.
Nothing.
No, the way she said recruit
made my stomach turn.
They're gonna torture him.
He can take care of himself for one day
until we get Scylla.
Lincoln, he needs to be in the ICU.
What's your plan? Break him out?
I don't know, I don't have one.
Well, you're putting him and us at risk.
Just stay in the hotel
until we get back to L.A., all right?
[PHONE RINGS]
Yes?
Tancredi got the location
on her shining knight.
She may be heading there now.
-Exemplary, Bagwell.
-Thank you, sir.
A deal's a deal, right?
Not to be a broken record--
ROGER: I think we're making
some real progress, general.
The Scofield-Burrows family would've
been a formidable asset to the Company.
But since his lapdog insists
on complicating matters, we move on.
-General, we can handle a lone female.
-If indeed that's what we're dealing with.
But it's my experience
that with the one comes many.
Do it now, doctor.
I need an hour, he ate.
I don't want him to aspirate.
Now, doctor.
I want Scofield pliable for transit,
and your vehicle arrives in 20 minutes.
And if we can't revive him?
C'est la vie.
[KNOCKING ON DOOR]
ROGER:
Michael, come out. We need to talk.
MAN:
Make yourself a helmet, pal.
That's it. That's our guy.
LINCOLN:
And there's Tia right beside him.
We gotta pull that image, get it to
the Company and have them match it.
Where's Gretchen?
How'd you find me?
Once I found your mug shot...
...it really wasn't that hard
getting your legit cell number.
Well, now I'm here.
What do you want?
You never bothered to ask
back in Los Angeles.
You were busy planning on killing me,
but I actually worked for the Company.
I know who you are.
And I'll ask it again.
What do you want?
Solve your problems, Scott.
I mean, it is what gets me up out of bed
in the morning.
You have a big problem.
And so does whoever it is
you're working for.
And you know that, or you wouldn't
have graced me with your presence.
-You can make that problem disappear?
-Quickly and completely.
With an extra added bonus.
Crucial, I might add.
And then feed the Company a story
that has them looking elsewhere.
Meaning you're invaluable,
please don't kill you.
Yeah, without the please.
-How much?
-A lot.
And it's about to double if you don't
look at me when I'm talking to you.
You go run and talk it over
with your boss.
Call me with a number.
I'm authorized to negotiate
on their behalf.
If you serve up whoever's looking for us
and get the Company off our scent...
...10 million.
Best and final offer.
Ask for a penny more
and I'll shoot you in the chest...
...and take my chances.
ROGER:
Take it easy, Michael.
This is for your own good.
[SQUEAKING]
MAN 1: What was that?
MAN 2: Sounded like the water heater.
It came from the bathroom.
Pick it up.
MAN:
You're never getting out of here.
Now give the doctor his medicine.
ROGER:
No.
Bedpost.
MAN 1:
In here! In the bedroom! Come on!
Get the cuff key, now.
That's great. Thank you, perfect.
Let me know
if you hear anything else.
-The hell you been?
-Figuring this whole thing out.
I know who it is, the buyer.
Lawrence Wilcott. He's been working
for the Company for 10 years.
-How did you figure that out?
-I still have friends on the inside.
Been putting together a profile,
narrowing down candidates.
Wilcott got on a plane in Bogotá
and flew to the Bahamas yesterday...
...and got on a boat.
The guy who took Scylla,
we pulled his image off security tape.
Company's running
a recognition match.
Gonna take all day.
Do you know where he is now?
With Wilcott, we need to go now.
Because better yet,
I know where Wilcott's staying.
Okay, we need to move
before Scylla does.
Let's go. Let's go.
-Come on.
BAGWELL: Nice job.
Turn around.
Hands on your head.
MAN 1: We gotta get out of here.
MAN 2: It won't start.
SARA:
Michael, get in.
GRETCHEN:
He's rented out the entire top floor.
Security at every point.
You might wanna get to an employee,
bribe one.
Top-level Company
in a big glass building.
[GUN COCKS]
SCOTT:
Nice and slow. Get your hands up.
-Is this everyone?
-You whore.
You're a whore,
and your mother was a whore.
And her mother, and your father
used to turn tricks at a gas station...
...because he was a whore too.
Bye, auntie.
Sorry, but right now I want my life back
more than I want your money.
LINCOLN:
Where's Scylla?
-Let's talk about that, okay?
-Let's. Where is it?
-I can get it.
MAHONE: No, he can't.
He's stalling, Linc.
-It's gone.
SCOTT: You're right.
You guys can kiss my ass. There's only
one thing I wanna accomplish right now.
MAHONE: Lawrence Wilcott,
the whole Florida hotel rented out?
Made it up.
You have no idea
who this guy is working for.
GRETCHEN:
No. No clue.
-We gotta pull the pin here.
SELF: Just because she switched sides...
...doesn't mean she wasn't gonna kill us
two minutes ago, okay?
Kill her. All right, we're not
leaving her here for the cops.
-We're not taking her to the hospital.
-Why?
I didn't let you get slaughtered.
-She's got a kid.
SELF: So what?
The kid doesn't even know
it's her mother.
Come on, pull the trigger, do it.
Her name's Emily,
she's only 8 years old. Come on.
Do it.
We're not them.
Keep your mouth shut
and you get to see your kid in visitation.
I know what the general will do to me
if I talk in prison.
Believe me, I know him well.
SELF:
Are you serious?
BAGWELL:
Go. Let's go, let's go.
What happened?
You haven't said a word.
I think my mother's alive.
[PHONE RINGING]
SELF:
That's his cell phone, answer it.
Hello.
Hello?
Your boy is dead.
And now I'm coming after you.
You hear me?
Whoever you are,
I'm coming after you.
MAN:
Who was that?
It was my son.
Lincoln.
[ENGLISH SDH]