NARRATOR:
Previously on Prison Break:
You have a hypothalamus hamartoma.
The doctor feels
that you need surgery.
You could die.
MAHONE: You're not following orders.
-Oh, I'm following orders, sir.
Just not from you anymore.
I would have died on this table
if it weren't for you, doc.
-What?
-Time to come home now.
-You're gonna help me find a buyer.
-His name is Vikan.
He's not a buyer. He's a conduit.
Let's go. And Bagwell's staying here.
I warned you not to screw me over.
It's been a long time, Gretchen.
Who's he?
The guy that's holding Scylla.
VIKAN:
It's incomplete.
There's a piece missing, slick.
[CELL PHONE RINGS]
Hello, Don.
I believe you have something
that belongs to me.
Come and get it.
Just so it's fresh in your mind,
this isn't a magic elixir.
You still need a hospital.
You need real equipment.
You could use a doctor who's still got
a license to practice medicine.
Well, first, we get Scylla,
then I'll go to the hospital.
-You finished?
-Just about.
[CELL PHONE RINGS]
-I take it you're ready to talk now?
-Actually, I'm ready to meet.
I got a better idea.
Everyone, out.
[GUNFIRE]
[CELL PHONE RINGS]
You're surrounded. Come out
with your piece of Scylla, Michael.
You first.
SELF:
Come out or I'm gonna gas you out.
If it's the latter,
I have a full magazine with 30 rounds.
Wanna bet one of them
can outrun you?
What makes you think
I'd keep the piece on me?
Oh, I know you. You're not letting that
out of your sight.
MICHAEL:
I stand by my original offer.
-Come and get it.
-Okay.
Stay low. Let the gas rise to the ceilings.
This is a big space but it won't take
many of those before we asphyxiate.
Where is Lincoln?
SELF:
Here we go, Michael.
[GUN COCKS]
[SELF GRUNTING]
Now we take a ride,
and we pick up Scylla.
-Or I put a bullet in your head.
-It ain't gonna happen.
Try me.
[GUNFIRE]
GRETCHEN:
Good morning.
Okay.
All right, now that we all have guns
pointed at us, let's talk, okay?
Fine. You can start by telling me
who I'm talking to, Don.
You're talking to a guy who spent 17
years in service of his government.
You know what the sum total of it was?
Nothing, nada.
Well, we're very similar.
And fundamentally, we want the
same thing and I have a way to get it.
-How's that?
-I got a buyer for Scylla.
A guy who wants to destroy
the Company as much as you do.
He's willing to pay
a lot of money for it.
How much?
Nine figures.
In an offshore account
of your choosing.
So there it is.
Or you could stand by your principles.
I'll pass.
Look, I burned you, right?
And I'd apologize, but what's the point?
We're all out in the cold now.
We're not gonna be able
to hide from the Company on a budget.
Who's the buyer?
An ex-Company guy with a bone to pick.
Just like your father.
Michael?
I need to meet him first.
That could be arranged.
And just so you know,
this wasn't personal.
This was just business.
We'll be in touch.
We stick to the plan, all right?
We're gonna get Scylla.
We wait for Alex
to come through on his end, all right?
MAN:
Hang on a second.
WOMAN:
Hello, Alex.
You came.
I always do.
To the detriment of my pay grade.
These last few weeks,
I've been part of an operation...
...under the hand
of Homeland Security.
Felicia, the people I'm working with...
...we're this close to the one thing
that can destroy the Company:
Their little black book. We can get it.
The names, numbers, operators.
I don't wanna get caught up
in some inter-agency politics.
-If this is Homeland--
-Homeland buried the operation.
We can't come back in.
We can still take the Company down.
So my question to you is:
Who do you know in the bureau
you can trust?
It used to be you, Alex.
I've lost a lot of things
these last few months...
...not the least of which is your trust.
But I don't come to you hat in hand.
Scylla is real.
Now, if you don't want anything to do
with it, that's all right. I can walk away.
Yeah, there is someone
who might be able to help.
FERGUSON: Sir, there are over
10 million faces in Los Angeles.
Even with NSA and CIA satellite linkups,
we're gonna be sifting through millions...
...of gigabytes of image data.
The chances of finding Don Self
and Scofield and Burrows, it's not good.
Well, let's improve the odds.
Self and the brothers
may have stolen Scylla...
...but none of them have
the connections to offload it.
Add Gretchen's face to the search.
She won't be welcome in Scofield's
camp so connect her image with Self's.
We find those two within five feet
of each other anywhere in Los Angeles...
...and we've found Scylla.
Are you friends
with my Auntie Gretchen?
Go play in your room.
Mommy will be in soon.
Where's her daddy?
Gretchen doesn't talk about him.
So Emily doesn't know that you ain't--?
That Gretchen's her momma?
No. And I'd like to keep it that way.
Cute girl.
RITA:
Don't hurt my little girl.
If you have to do something,
do it to me.
What do you think I am, a monster?
You're holding us prisoner
in our own home.
I'm just as much a prisoner as you.
Eggshell white.
Bold lettering. Double embossed.
I was Cole Pfeiffer.
Respected businessman.
Top salesman in the northeast region.
And now I'm back being prisoner
of my own identity.
Theodore Bagwell.
Convict.
To hell with it.
We are who we are, right?
What were you selling?
Never you mind.
You just pray your sister
comes through.
The Company gets destroyed
and we get paid. Great deal.
This guy is just another General Krantz
waiting to happen.
Let's say we sell it
and the Company burns.
You know what happens?
Another company
is built right on top of that one.
We're not selling.
Sucre pulled it off.
LINCOLN:
Great.
GRETCHEN:
Is this gonna work?
SELF: It's like an ultrasound.
It can see through everything.
You're building up a tolerance.
Then we'll up the dosage.
Yeah, I have, and at this point,
a higher dosage...
...would have more side effects
than the tumor.
Then I'll manage without it.
Sit this one out.
Let me and Sucre handle it.
I'm going.
[SIGHS]
Why can't he understand
I need to finish this?
Everything that happened,
it all started with the Company.
Maybe not for Lincoln.
Maybe for him, this all started with his
little brother breaking him out of prison.
Michael, you saved his life.
If anything happens to you, he spends
the rest of his life feeling guilty for that.
Tell me something, at what point
does a noble deed become fanaticism?
Fanaticism is the only way
to beat them.
Even if it kills you?
SELF:
Hey, pop the trunk.
LINCOLN:
Michael?
Sucre just sent a text.
He's found Gretchen and Self.
Good. Good.
-You all right?
-Yeah, for now.
All right.
-Linc?
-Yeah?
After your trial,
the day I came to see you at Fox River.
What about it?
I thought you did it.
I thought you killed
Terrence Steadman.
Along with everyone else.
But by the time I left...
...I knew you were innocent.
And I had to get you out of that place.
So however this plays out...
...I have no regrets.
SELF: Scofield's hiding something
in the washroom.
I think we just found our piece of Scylla.
Call Vikan.
I wanna talk to my daughter first.
Just call him, okay? They're fine.
I have a history with Vikan.
No money exchanges hands
unless I tell him you're legit.
I wanna talk to my daughter now.
[SELF SIGHS]
[CELL PHONE RINGS]
-Yeah?
-Put the daughter on the phone.
-Is there a problem?
-Just put her on the phone.
-Hello?
-Emily, baby, it's your Auntie Gretchen.
Where are you?
I'm not far. Are you okay?
There's this mean man here.
Emily, do you remember the mean man
that used to live with your Mommy Rita?
-The one that used to yell at you?
-Roy?
That's the one.
And what happened to Roy?
He went to the store one day
and never came back.
That's right.
And I think
that if you don't like this mean man...
...then very soon, he's gonna leave
and he's never coming back.
You think so?
-Baby, I know so.
-All right. That's enough.
Emily, baby, put the mean man
back on the phone.
Listen to me. I'm gonna call you in two
hours with the location of the exchange.
If you don't hear from me,
kill them both.
[DOORBELL RINGS]
-You expecting somebody?
-No.
Look lively.
Buttercup, why don't you go play
with your dolls or something?
It's okay, honey. Go to your playroom.
Hi there. My name is Ralph Becker.
And I'm selling Bibles to raise money
for the Church of the Holy Trinity.
I wonder if I could spend five minutes
of your time and talk about the Gospel.
We're a bit, uh, indisposed
at the moment, Ralph.
Can you come back tomorrow?
Well, actually, today is the last day
of the fundraiser.
I said we're busy.
Well, never too busy for God.
And what's a few minutes of your
afternoon for a place in his kingdom?
You're a bit pushy for a Bible salesman,
ain't you, friend?
I'm on a mission.
Yeah, I'll bet you're on a mission,
right.
[RALPH GRUNTING]
-What are you doing?
BAGWELL: Close the door.
This guy is Company.
-What's Company?
-Get me rope.
-This guy is a Bible salesman.
-Give me the rope now!
Good choice for a meeting spot, Alex.
Crowded place, a few exits.
A corner table
with a full view of the room.
Looks like you're getting acclimated
to life on the run.
I hear you got promoted.
Your own field office.
That's impressive.
When you're neither a disgrace
to the bureau nor a drug addict...
...good things happen.
-He's clean, Mark.
-Thank you, Felicia.
Oh, look, I know you, Mark.
You're a good agent. Ambitious.
Let me appeal to the side
that likes to see your name in print.
You wanna be on a shortlist
for deputy director, huh?
Right. Lang filled me in.
You've got solid gold intel.
But I don't know if I'm more skeptical
of a burned out ex-fed...
...or the mythical cabal
known as the Company.
You came all the way here for a myth?
What do you want, Alex?
Felicia tells me you have
the attorney general's ear.
That's right.
The bureau is compromised.
Homeland Security is compromised.
I need someone I can trust.
Can I trust you?
You get me credible intelligence
against the Company...
...I'll walk you into
the attorney general's office myself.
You'll get it.
[CELL PHONE RINGS]
Alex, talk to me.
I found someone in government
we can trust.
-How close are you to getting Scylla?
MICHAEL: Very.
Michael, we're in escrow here.
You gotta come through with the house.
Don't worry. We're getting Scylla.
All right.
Look what I found.
But we have no way to shoot them.
Yeah, we do.
But I need you to buy some hairspray
and a lighter.
[AGENTS CHATTERING
INDISTINCTLY]
What's this?
My resignation.
Lisa, I tried to shield you from everything
I didn't think you could handle.
The only thing you shielded me from
was knowing who you really are.
Now I know.
I wanted a son.
FERGUSON:
Sir...
...taken less than an hour ago.
You were right. Gretchen's with Self.
KRANTZ: Your mission
is the safe retrieval of Scylla.
-What are the rules of engagement?
-There are none. Shoot on sight.
Fauntleroy Hotel. Downtown.
Who sent you?
-The Church of the Holy Trinity.
-Liar!
[RALPH GRUNTS]
Are you out of your mind?
You're beating up a Bible salesman.
I ain't Scofield.
I ain't Burrows. This ain't my lot.
Leave me alone.
I'm not a part of this Company.
-I-- I don't know anything, I swear.
-Look at him. Please, just look at him.
Does he look like some kind
of an undercover agent to you?
They blend in.
That's how they get you.
Look at this, okay? His wallet, okay?
He's got a driver's license. Ralph Becker.
He's got a library card and a prayer card.
-That is pretty convincing.
-Look at this.
Freedom, honor, country. Southeastern
Military Academy. Class of '98.
How many Bible salesman you know
graduate from a military academy?
No, I didn't go to Southeastern.
It's my kid brother's ring!
He died in Baghdad last year.
It was a car bomb.
[SOBBING]
I swear.
RITA:
Listen to me.
-Please.
-That made sense.
Can we--?
-Please.
We're not going nowhere!
Not till I get a phone call.
It's 25 for the hour.
-We don't need a room.
-I'm looking for my sister.
Her name is Gretchen Morgan.
Tell me what room she's in.
You want information, call 411.
How about now?
No Gretchen Morgan.
No refund.
She's about 5'7".
She's got black hair and blue eyes.
I imagine she'd stand out
in a fine establishment like this one.
-Room 308.
-Thank you so much.
No urinating in the stairwell.
That's the golden rule.
[PHONE RINGS OVER LINE]
-Yeah?
-Yeah, they're on the third floor...
...front of the hotel,
just to the left of center.
MICHAEL: Got it. Thanks.
-Yeah.
Third floor up, just left of the balcony.
Why don't you set up
on that rooftop over there?
Scylla's almost complete.
Is everything ready?
-Let me talk to Gretchen.
-No, no. You're talking to me.
The buyer has touched down.
This isn't the person you keep waiting.
Likewise.
Make sure he has the money.
Listen to me, you mook.
You're in the deep end of the pool now.
At least act like you can swim.
Next time I call
I wanna talk to Gretchen.
Listen to me. The next time you call,
tell me that the money's ready.
You understand?
[TELEPHONE RINGS]
-Hello?
-I thought you should know...
...a man and a woman came in
looking for you.
Scofield found us.
-How?
-Who cares? Get ready.
-How long ago?
-A couple of minutes.
I don't want no trouble in my place!
I'm gonna recon the hallway.
Anything goes down...
-...get Scylla, get out. I will find you.
-Okay.
[BOTH GRUNTING]
[COUGHS]
[GRETCHEN AND SUCRE GRUNTING]
[GRUNTS]
Let's go! Go! Go! Go!
Like I said before, this is just business.
[GUNSHOT]
FERGUSON:
Don't move!
Get in.
[GUNFIRE]
Help me get him in the back of the van.
LINCOLN:
Michael!
What is that?
SARA:
It's the warehouse.
The chip.
-You sure it's here?
-Yeah. I'm sure.
From the schematic,
it can only be in one place.
Look, don't be stupid, okay, Gretchen?
You're gonna get your daughter back
and your money.
I'll see you in the car.
MAN:
He was brought in like this.
Who's there?
MAN: I'm giving him 10 cc's of
clonazepam and taking him downstairs.
We'll know more soon.
Try and relax.
Don't worry.
We're gonna get Michael back.
How? Self took the piece.
We got nothing to trade for Michael.
SARA:
He's sick, Lincoln.
If they haven't killed him already.
We'll get him back I promise.
[CELL PHONE RINGING]
Hello?
Hold on.
It's Alex.
-Yeah.
-Did you get it yet?
No. Self's got it. All of it.
-What?
-Just forget about Scylla.
The Company's taken Michael.
Your friend in government,
can he do anything for him?
No, I don't think so.
There's no reason for you
to come back, Alex.
I'm sorry.
Yeah, me too.
I should have known.
SELF:
Vikan's meeting us here?
We'll be off
of the Company's radar here.
[CELL PHONE RINGING]
-Yeah?
-We've got a problem.
It can wait.
We're in the homestretch here.
Grab the sister and the girl. I'm gonna
call you back with the location.
I'd love to, but a, uh, third party
has been introduced into the mix.
Who?
I'm not sure yet.
-He might be a Company operative.
-So kill him.
He could also be a Bible salesman.
Then he should have no problem
getting past Saint Peter. Kill him.
Go in the playroom
with your daughter.
-What are you gonna do?
-Go, now!
Please, please, please don't kill me.
Please don't kill me.
Please. Look, I won't tell anyone.
I won't tell anyone. I promise.
Please don't kill me.
I swear I won't tell anyone.
-Don't do this.
-I told you to go back yonder. Okay?
You don't wanna see this.
Cole Pfeiffer wouldn't do this.
Cole Pfeiffer ain't here no more.
Just old T-Bag.
Our Father, who art in heaven.
Hallowed be thy name.
RITA:
You wanna be free?
Start now. Right this minute.
If you pull that trigger,
Cole Pfeiffer's gone forever.
Don't do this.
[RALPH SOBBING]
Don't do it.
BAGWELL: You know my daddy
was a religious man too, Ralph.
Just like you.
We used to pray together
in my room at night.
And I used to lie on the floor crying
just like you now.
When I couldn't take it no more...
...my daddy would recite a particular
piece of scripture that he was fond of.
Weeping may endure through the night.
But joy cometh in the morning.
Psalms 30:5.
-Rita.
-Yeah?
Have you got a car?
My car is in the-- It's in the garage.
You get in that car right now...
...and you drive far,
far away from here, right now, okay?
Here.
Take this.
Rita?
Thank you.
What are you gonna do to me?
BAGWELL:
I want you to go.
I want you to be free.
Be as free as me.
RALPH:
Thank you.
Thank you so much.
[RALPH SHOUTS]
Yeah, I got one.
Not Gretchen.
It's Bagwell.
I'm bringing him in.
DOCTOR:
The growth is malignant.
It's pushing up against his temporal lobe.
It will kill him if it's not removed.
Have you seen anything like this before?
This advanced?
Once.
FERGUSON:
Sir.
You'll never guess
who just came through the door.
I wanna see my brother.
Thank you, gentlemen.
Mr. Burrows won't be a problem.
Will you?
It started with me and ends with me.
Let Michael go.
I think you made the right decision.
Let's go downstairs
and see your brother.
VIKAN:
Gretchen.
Don.
-This better be the real thing this time.
-It's all here.
Yeah, well, no offense,
but I'll check it myself.
So the buyer's on the way?
He will be here shortly.
And he's bringing the money?
Yes, Don. He is bringing the money.
Scylla is complete.
Gretchen...
...you did it.
What I wouldn't give to see the look
on the general's face.
GRETCHEN:
What are you doing?
-We need him alive to sell this thing.
SELF: You heard what he said.
Buyer's already on the way.
You think I'm gonna give this clown
30 percent for just making introductions?
RALPH:
Come on. It's a glass door.
[CAR HORN HONKS]
Okay, right. I hear you.
We'll be right out.
Well?
The attorney general's willing
to hear you out.
You know, from where I'm sitting,
it looked like....
Your flight to Dallas leaves
in 45 minutes.
Can I trust this guy?
We better go.
Come on, Alex.
It's a short trip to the airport.
The attorney general's waiting.
There is no meeting
with the attorney general, is there?
Thank you, Felicia,
for everything you've done.
Everything.
-What did you do to my brother?
KRANTZ: Michael needs an operation...
...to remove a tumor
from his temporal lobe.
And he needs it now.
The Company can provide
such an operation at a cost.
What do you want from us?
Not us, Lincoln, you.
The price of the operation
is the safe return of Scylla.
If you bring back to me
what you stole...
...then I will make sure Michael
gets the finest medical care in the world.
The Company
has science and technology...
...that's years ahead of anything
available to the public.
And it's all right here. In this facility.
Now, I would imagine that working
for me will be difficult for you to accept.
LINCOLN:
What's this?
Added incentive.
[ENGLISH SDH]