NARRATOR:
Previously on Prison Break:
SELF: These are GPS ankle monitors.
Now, step up, take one and put it on.
When the exchange is over, you and I
are gonna spend some quality time.
MAHONE:
These aren't release papers.
I did the best I could. You need to sign
those so I can collect Roland's device.
You want me to give up the one thing
that makes me valuable?
You knew the deal
when you came onboard.
Wanna flush it down
because you made a bad move?
This man just came
into a $100,000 inheritance.
-I don't recognize him.
-If you see him, please give us a call.
RITA: You don't work for the IRS?
-I don't.
RITA: Who do you work for?
-As of now, myself.
I'm an associate of General Krantz.
The general, he likes his privacy.
I knew you were rotten
from the beginning.
I want you to walk me through this...
...and if you can't,
well, I'm gonna call the authorities.
Cole Pfeiffer.
[GRUNTS]
Who the hell are you?
[SIRENS WAILING NEARBY]
[GROANS]
The last time
a pretty little filly like yourself...
...knocked me senseless
and tied me to a chair...
...I had to pay for it.
You still might.
That book was a gift
from a very dear friend of mine...
...who left this realm all too soon.
The only thing that James Whistler
ever gave anybody was the clap.
You have 30 seconds to tell me
something that I don't already know.
I followed that book, uh,
from Panama City...
...where James Whistler and I
were co-incarcerated...
...to a bus locker in San Diego.
Inside was information
pertaining to this apartment.
Scylla.
How about that? Does that ring a bell?
What do you know about Scylla?
I'm the one holding the keys.
Because without me...
...that bird book's about as meaningful
as a fart in a windstorm.
I've commandeered Whistler's alias.
I infiltrated his place of business...
...because it's the gateway
to the whole damn thing.
Where's the location?
What are you bringing to the jamboree,
darling, huh?
Aside from those baby blues
and a knife?
This is me.
[BAGWELL GROANS]
This is Scylla.
And this is you.
I'm gonna get Scylla.
[BAGWELL GASPS]
And it can either be with you...
...or through you.
[YELLS]
So why don't you give me
that informed decision right now...
...before I spill your hillbilly guts
all over the carpet.
Because you're messing
with the wrong bitch.
How may I be of service?
SELF: Unbelievable.
-We were planning to move on Scuderi...
...when he chartered the flight.
No chance you dragged your feet
waiting for Scuderi to charter the flight?
Yeah, we wanna drag this out.
The location's pretty convenient,
wouldn't you say, Linc?
Scuderi splitting town
kind of caught us a break, huh?
Would you shut him up?
[SUCRE AND ROLAND
SPEAKING INDISTINCTLY]
SELF:
We could wait till he comes back.
AgriSow makes farm chemicals.
It's not Fort Knox.
You wanna bet?
Their patents are worth billions.
Which is why companies tend to keep
a very close eye on those patents.
We could breach through security,
in a week.
We could get in the guy's house,
week, minimum.
We could follow the guy for 12 hours and
have card five by midnight. How's that?
How does this sound? If you're not back
by midnight, you're going to jail.
-Yeah, don't I know it.
-Let's talk outside.
So, what's the plan?
We're going to Vegas.
Oh, hell, yes. Yo, I call shotgun, huh?
Who's got--? Hey. Yeah?
MAHONE: What do you wanna
talk about, Agent Self?
I've been part of hundreds of operations
during my career...
...and I've never been
on the top of someone's hit list.
-What are you talking about?
-If this hit man can find me once...
...it's only a matter of time...
...until he creeps up in the back
of my rear-view mirror again.
That's not true. You'll never see him
coming at all if he's coming after you.
-That's comforting.
-You think I want that? You're dead...
...we're all back in jail.
You were an agent longer than me.
What's my play here?
Ha, ha. Okay,
let me get this straight...
...you turn your back on me
and now you wanna know my play?
That was your fault.
What would you have done?
I've tracked down rapists, killers,
even former military...
...but a structural engineer from Illinois
was able to get to me.
-You wanna know how?
-Yeah, I wanna know.
He stopped running.
He got aggressive.
He took the game to me.
That's your play.
That's your only play.
I shouldn't have to remind you
that killing a federal agent...
...is a complicated matter,
even in our line of work.
Perhaps Mahone
is just the tip of the iceberg.
We've been searching for the link...
...between supermax
and Burrows and Scofield.
I believe we've found it.
If Scofield and Burrows
are working with the government...
...we've got a much bigger problem than
one bureaucrat at Homeland Security.
But it begins with that bureaucrat.
And if Don Self
is the head of the snake....
Make it look like an accident.
My fee just doubled, by the way.
-Hello?
-Uh, hi, is this Brad?
Yeah.
TRISHANNE: You came by my office
a couple days ago...
...looking for a guy
who had inheritance coming to him.
Right.
I know where he is.
BELLICK: She wants 2 grand first.
I'm meeting her at noon.
The card's more important, so Vegas
first, then we deal with T-Bag?
Shut up.
MAHONE:
I'll stay.
MICHAEL:
All right.
Linc, take Sara and Sucre...
...and Roland to Vegas.
The rest of us...
...we'll handle T-Bag.
You heard the man. Let's go.
Hey. Um....
-Promise me something, would you?
-Yeah.
Can you get me
Carrot Top's autograph?
Because I just think that would make
this whole thing worthwhile.
Be safe.
Hey, yo, Vegas, bitches! Ha, ha!
MICHAEL: He should have
the information by now.
What the hell's taking Bellick so long?
[PHONE RINGING]
Yes?
BELLICK [OVER PHONE]:
She wants more money.
MICHAEL:
How much more?
BELLICK: I don't know.
You gotta come talk to this chick.
Hold on. Hold on.
What's going on, Bellick?
Believe it.
Sorry, guys, I walked right into it too.
BAGWELL: Let's go, man. Go.
Go. Come on, tie them up. Go.
BELLICK: You have no idea
who you're working with, honey.
Why don't we skip the theatrics
and you just tell us what you want?
I'd love to put a hole
right in your head.
Tie him up.
Him too.
Let's all get in the van.
Come on. Let's all get in the van, now.
You too, Mahone.
Mahone.
[GUNSHOT]
[GRUNTS]
BAGWELL:
I remember the day we met, pretty.
You were a scared little college boy
sitting up on those bleachers...
...trying to keep your ass
out of the game.
Now look at you. Cold, hard.
Like a dried-up flower
wanting to get watered.
Just tell me what you want.
I want to make you bleed.
I wanna release the sinner
inside of me...
...that got me incarcerated
so many years ago.
But it seems
you caught yourself a break, pretty.
I need you.
Now...
...you're gonna cooperate right quick,
or so help me...
...I'm gonna stump you
till you can't stand.
Pages. Look at them.
-Looks like some kind of map, right?
-I don't know.
You know enough to chase me down
looking for this.
Now, don't lie to me.
Whatever's in that book,
it is bigger than you and me.
What, like Scylla big?
This is not a game, Theodore.
Now, you need to tell me
who you've been talking to.
I don't need to do a damn thing.
That's the benefit of being the man
with the gun.
Now...
...you're gonna write down everything
that you already know about Scylla.
And everything you learned...
...in that book.
Or I'm gonna paint these walls
with your gray matter.
Get to work.
[PHONE RINGS]
Hello? All right, I'll be right there.
MAHONE: Self.
-Hey.
Michael's position hasn't changed
since you called.
Bagwell's a psychopath with a plan.
He needs something from Michael.
And as long as Michael doesn't
give it to him, he'll keep breathing.
-All right, well, I'm coming with you.
-No, no, no. I got it.
Stick to the plan.
ROLAND:
Forget about Maricruz.
Think she didn't know her sister
was trying to set you up?
You better get some ass in Vegas.
We're here to copy the card,
then we leave, you got it?
LINCOLN: You heard from Michael?
-No. Why?
Nothing.
I want this thing done.
Vegas ain't my town.
What a fool, huh? How could anyone
not love this place, right?
Check this out.
Right there, the Asian guy.
I know I've seen him someplace before.
So, what do you have for me?
-So, what's GATE?
-Excuse me?
It's on that box.
-Why do you wanna know?
-Just curious.
What if I was to tell you
I think you're just stalling.
Biding time till you can figure out some
MacGyver way to get you out of here.
You've got that gun pointed at
the one person who can help you...
...so stop wasting my time.
-Come here.
TRISHANNE: Aah!
BAGWELL: Come on.
TRISHANNE: Ow! Ow!
Ow! Please don't hurt me. Ow.
BAGWELL:
How about her, huh?
How about her, Michael?
Any reason why I shouldn't kill her?
[TRISHANNE CRYING]
Let's do a test, huh?
TRISHANNE:
Oh, no.
-How far gone is Michael Scofield, huh?
-Michael, just tell him what he wants.
TRISHANNE [SOBBING]:
Please.
How far gone is Michael Scofield?
TRISHANNE:
Please don't let him. Please.
BAGWELL: When did it happen, Michael?
TRISHANNE: Please don't let him.
BAGWELL: When did you stop caring
about hurting people, huh?
Fox River? Sona?
You gonna keep dragging your feet
while I put a bullet in her brain?
Why don't you put that gun down?
-I'll put it down when you start writing.
BELLICK: Let her go, T-Bag.
T-Bag, come on, man, let her go.
-Last chance. Three, two, one.
BELLICK: T-Bag. T-Bag.
All right. All right.
The pages, they fit together.
But it's not a map.
It's a blueprint.
For what?
[PHONE RINGING]
[TRISHANNE SCREAMS]
TRISHANNE:
Please.
Bellick is wearing a government-issued
ankle monitor.
My guess is that Scofield has one too.
I knew that son of a bitch
was slow-walking me.
Any minute, federal agents
could come blasting through that door.
So, what do we do?
I need you to get the make
and serial number off that monitor.
Feel free to pitch in here.
If Scofield finds out I'm involved,
this is over.
We need to keep him on point. Now,
get out there and get that information.
-What about the agents?
-Let them come.
[BEEPING]
How do we even know
this guy's out gambling?
The guy's got $300,000 in credit
and a comp room.
He's here. Keep looking. Hey, Sara.
Hey. This may not be the best time,
but I still haven't heard from Michael.
-They must be dealing with T-Bag.
-Come on.
-What?
-Vegas just isn't your town?
Everything I've heard about you,
that would be a change of pace.
-I guess so.
-Lincoln?
Please talk to me.
-Michael told you about mom?
-No.
They were much alike.
They got the same mind.
As mom got older,
she started to lose it.
We later found out it was a symptom
of a brain tumor. Hama--
-Hamartoma.
-Yeah.
As a kid, she got nosebleeds.
They stopped.
In her 30s, they started up again.
She later died of a brain aneurysm.
You're telling me this because Michael
and his mother are similar in that way.
He had nosebleeds as a kid.
They stopped, and the last couple
of days, they started up again.
How old was your mom
when she passed away?
Thirty-one.
Michael's just turning 31.
[PHONE RINGS]
Um....
-Yeah?
-I found him.
LINCOLN [OVER PHONE]:
Keep an eye on him.
SUCRE:
Okay.
[TAPPING ON GLASS]
GRETCHEN:
Andrew Blauner?
Uh, yeah.
Can I help you?
I hope so.
Any boyfriends or roommates
I should know about?
No.
Any deliveries scheduled for today?
I'm giving you one more--
What is all this?
You okay?
They told me not to talk to you.
They? Who's they?
This is Whistler's blueprint.
It's the building
where we can find Scylla.
In other words, it's GATE.
Where's Scylla?
I can't be certain
until I see the building itself.
I'm pretty sure it's somewhere
down here below this office.
-What is Scylla?
-It's the Company's little black book.
I want you to take me to GATE, now.
Because you can smell that
Scylla money, can't you?
That's what you're in it for,
just like me.
Say it.
Come on. I want you to say it.
I'm in it for the money.
You see...
...we ain't so different after all.
[LINE RINGING]
[PHONE RINGS]
-Yes?
-Don Self is not at his house.
Looks like he cleared out.
Notify our people inside the bureau
and L.A.P.D.
I doubt that he can
have gotten very far.
-Sir?
-Not now.
Don Self is here to see you.
MAN:
What would you like to do?
Here you go, sir.
Gotta warn you, friend, she's cold.
[PHONE RINGS]
SCUDERI:
Good luck, pal.
Stay with him.
-Scofield's getting somewhere in there.
-Man works fast.
He can't get any further without seeing
my former place of employment.
Did you take care
of our little troll problem?
[LOCK BEEPS]
Don't even think about doing this to me.
My name is on the door.
If I didn't think you were valuable,
you'd be dead already.
Grab a leg.
BLAUNER:
Wait.
It's just a little sensory overload, guys.
There just wasn't any room for the card.
If we turn the device on in the casino,
it fills up on all the data from the slots.
Yeah.
-Like when they're about to pay out.
-It's completely unintentional.
Really? It's not why you built
the thing in the first place?
-If we didn't need you--
-No. But you do.
So just take a brewski and chill,
all right?
Okay, we need to figure out a way
to get Scuderi alone.
[PHONE RINGS]
-Yeah?
-The old man just showed up at the pool.
From what he's wearing,
there's no way he's got the card on him.
LINCOLN [OVER PHONE]:
Stay with him.
The card's in his room.
Tell me, Donald, how did you play
this moment out in your head?
Did you picture yourself
coming in here...
...chest out, jaw squared,
ready to demand answers?
Did you, at any time in your fantasy,
imagine that you would be this nervous?
Honestly, I didn't think much past
giving you these.
KRANTZ:
Berlin.
Nigeria.
The Comrie Group.
Why not JFK and the Lindbergh baby
while you're at it?
Son, these matters have been
fully vetted. They're relics.
I had nothing to do with them.
If this is why
you've been pulling data on me...
...I could have saved you
a lot of trouble.
Well, these records
and a sealed letter...
...explaining my investigation into
your involvement with these matters...
...were sent to five lawyers across
the country. If anything happens to me...
...if I go missing, anything. If I wind up
dead, that letter is to be unsealed--
And they will find cold trails
that lead nowhere near me.
It doesn't matter.
If a government agent looking into you...
...is found floating in the L.A. River
or whatever else you have planned...
...your life, general,
will change dramatically.
There will be questions,
media coverage and surveillance.
Whatever you and the Company
are trying to do...
...with your Laos game
or whatever else you have planned...
...will be next to impossible
with thousands of eyes on you.
Okay, so back off of me.
You are not the first person
to attempt something like this.
Most of the others
I now fondly call my colleagues.
They've learned to put their
determination and focus to better use...
...and with far greater compensation.
Wrong guy.
We'll see.
"Dear Mr. White,
due to unforeseen circumstances...
...I regret to inform you that I will
no longer perform services at GATE.
I thank you for this opportunity.
I am sorry if this places you
in a difficult position.
I have simply not been able
to escape these circumstances.
Thank you for the wonderful,
enriching opportunity."
Blah, blah, blah.
Does it sound like you?
Yeah.
GRETCHEN: Good.
-Yeah.
Look,
I don't even know who you are, okay?
-Just let me go.
-Shut up.
And you wondered how I got to be the
top salesman in the Northeast region.
BLAUNER:
I'm sorry, okay?
I'm sorry.
Consider this a warning.
BLAUNER:
Oh, God.
[SCREAMS]
[BLAUNER STOMPING]
Old Teddy Bagwell
may be Coosa County trash...
...but Cole Pfeiffer's a man
of refinement.
One of the GATE Corporation's
tippy-top sellers, matter of fact.
Step into my office.
Well, there should be a room, 8-by-10.
-Whistler's point of entry.
-That's a closet.
No, it's not.
Hi. Tonic and lime, please.
Thank you.
I'm in the middle of a nightmare.
I wonder if you could help me.
It's my 22-year-old cousin's
bachelorette party.
-That's hardly the salt mines.
-Oh, wait for it.
There's a scavenger hunt...
...and my team has tasked me with
getting a photograph in a whale's suite.
I'm a whale?
You have a very scary bodyguard
and a very gorgeous watch.
You wanna take a picture in my room?
I realize it's a completely
inappropriate request...
...but they're already calling me
a wet blanket.
I'm sorry, I just can't help you.
What if I said please?
I'm actually a little desperate.
Best of luck.
Drink's on the gentleman.
-Have a nice day.
-You too.
Don't take it personally.
You're not his type.
Right before you sat down,
he asked me if I like to party.
-Absolutely not. No way.
ROLAND: Come on.
Take one for the team.
Maricruz will never know.
-I'm gonna snap his neck.
-Get to his room, stay two minutes.
-In the meantime, what? In the elevator?
-Play hard to get. Let him nuzzle a bit.
ROLAND: Whoa, whoa, whoa.
-Hey, hey, whoa. What option we got?
Come on, man, what option we got?
Give me one.
You can't. Here.
Go ahead, there's nothing back there.
MICHAEL:
I know.
[HOLLOW KNOCKING]
[SOLID KNOCKING]
Do you have anything sharp?
So, what are you hearing
Scylla's worth?
Me, I'm hearing millions.
Is that a rough ballpark
in terms of what you've been told?
What do we have here?
You better back up.
You and me in a dark hole.
Just like old times, pretty.
You first.
How the chips falling for you?
Spent my last buck on the beer.
What are the options
when you're broke in Vegas?
I guess I gotta work that out, huh?
[SCUDERI CHUCKLES]
What if you didn't have to?
I may have a little business
to throw your way.
What kind?
The easy kind.
With a thousand-dollar payout.
What's your cognac?
I never had it.
I got a 200-year-old bottle in my suite.
Join me.
This is private business...
...between men.
They're on their way up.
-Get ready.
-I love it. Mr. Macho-Man.
[MICHAEL PANTING]
Unh. Well, well, well.
What's next?
I don't know. Why don't you figure
it out? I'm done helping you.
Sounds like someone's caught
in the old captivity of negativity.
Let's get you
in a more affirmative mindset.
What's next?
I think I'm gonna lock you
in this room.
And then you're gonna be arrested
and taken back to Fox River.
Ha-ha-ha.
Now, just how do you plan on--?
[MEN GRUNTING]
BAGWELL:
Y'all have no idea what you're doing.
-Scofield, you can't do this without me.
-Self's on his way.
BAGWELL: Michael!
-I got your message.
Y'all have no idea what you're doing.
Thanks, Alex.
[BAGWELL BANGING ON DOOR]
-Great city.
-I guess so.
That's the thing about Vegas.
It doesn’t judge you.
Any form of pleasure's
acceptable here.
Ahh.
Am I crazy,
or is there a note of plum in there?
Maybe.
Have a seat.
-Did you serve?
-Serve who?
SCUDERI:
In the military.
You look like a devil dog.
No, sir.
I've never been in the service before.
Filling up nice.
Sucre must be in close proximity.
Getting oiled, most likely.
One and a half tours in Vietnam.
Purple heart
in a friendly fire exchange near Hue.
I'm sorry to hear it.
What I learned at Hue...
...though valuable...
...also cost me a great deal.
Specifically, 3 square inches
of upper-groin thigh meat.
And with that...
...my reproductive and sexual function.
-So you can't--?
-Mr. Villalobos...
...I'd like you to meet my wife.
I'm Alexa.
You want me to bang your wife?
I'm gonna pay you a thousand dollars.
[ROLAND SIGHS]
He's got a minute,
then I'm going after him.
-Did you copy the card?
ROLAND: Yup.
All right, download that.
We got five minutes.
ROLAND: Well?
-His wife was up there.
And...?
Stays in Vegas.
WOMAN:
Come on, darling.
Uh, hey, guys.
I'm gonna go hit the head
and I'll be out in a minute, all right?
Yes.
Two-- Two-- Two-- Two pulls.
All right.
Two spins.
[MACHINE CHIMES]
SECURITY OFFICER: There he is.
-Two pulls and he won the progressive.
SARA: Where the hell is he?
-I'll go get him.
[MACHINE CHIMING]
-Mr. Glenn.
-We got a problem.
It was made clear you weren't welcome
in any Nevada gaming establishment.
-I was told there was a five-year ban--
-No such thing was said to you.
-What's that do?
-It's a battery pack for a game console.
You'll need to buy a new one.
I already downloaded the card
onto my laptop.
And I can build another device.
You said this one takes months.
We don't have months.
You know what? We ought to
leave your ass in the desert.
Let's get back to L.A.
and let Self sort him out.
Let's go.
[LOCK RATTLES]
[BAGWELL GRUNTS]
No!
[GROANS THEN YELLS]
[YELLING]
Michael.
[BAGWELL YELLING INDISTINCTLY]
He has some set of lungs.
-How's Bellick and the girl?
-All taken care of.
I'm gonna keep T-Bag in protective
custody until we get Scylla.
I'm gonna make somebody
at the Illinois DOC very happy.
But more importantly,
what was that room downstairs?
That's not where they keep the device
that decodes Scylla?
No. That's just what T-Bag thought.
The road to Scylla
only begins down there.
This is the room
where we've got T-Bag now.
Past the south wall,
there's an access tunnel...
...that runs for about 300 yards or so.
We get through that, we're in.
That's where we decode Scylla.
-This is where General Krantz's office is.
MAHONE: There you go.
I was there. The security
in that place is unbelievable.
And according to the blueprints,
the substructure is exposed.
Shouldn't take more than 24 hours
to get in.
SELF:
It's only gonna take 24 hours?
All we have to do
is get that last card first.
Well, based on
what I've deciphered so far...
...we're gonna need around-the-clock
access to GATE starting immediately.
If you can get us suits and IDs, we could
go in as IRS agents auditing the books.
Considering the racket they're running,
nobody would have a problem believing.
-Can you make that happen?
-Yeah, I can do it.
[PHONE RINGING]
MICHAEL:
It's under the can.
Hello?
GRETCHEN [OVER PHONE]:
We have a lot in common.
Yeah? Who is this?
GRETCHEN: Just another interested party
in what you're up to.
-Yeah, what's that?
GRETCHEN: Scylla.
Line 569
Line 570
Line 571
Line 572
Line 573
Line 574
Line 575
Line 576
Line 577
Line 578
Line 579