NARRATOR:
Previously on Prison Break:
Your mother works for us.
Your mother is alive.
-I'm thinking that this is an inside job.
LINCOLN: Why?
GRETCHEN:
The hardware he brought to the meet.
He could read Scylla right on the spot.
LINCOLN:
Hands on your head.
-Punch it! We gotta get out of here!
-Whoa, stop!
SARA:
Michael, get in.
Sorry, but I want my life back
more than I want your money.
LINCOLN: Where's Scylla?
-Let's talk about that, okay?
-Let's. Where is it?
-I can get it.
No, he can't. He's stalling, Linc.
-It's gone.
CARRUTH: You're right.
You have no idea
who this guy's working for?
No clue.
Your boy's dead.
And now I'm coming after you.
DOWNEY: Who was that?
-It was my son.
Lincoln.
SELF:
What is this?
Don't know.
Just found them on the doorstep.
Son of a....
They lay one hand on my mama,
and I swear on my life....
-She's in a state home?
-I thought we were working...
-...with these people.
-So did I.
I'm gonna make a call
and find out what's going on.
[PHONE DIALING]
[LINE RINGING]
KRANTZ [OVER PHONE]: Mr. Burrows.
-We had a deal.
Our deal is contingent
upon the retrieval of Scylla.
And based on the mediocrity of your
performance on that front thus far...
...I thought it best to make sure
you're all properly motivated.
Just tell me
how your team is progressing.
I swear to God, man,
when I get ahold of you--
If I were you,
I'd be doing everything in my power...
...to demonstrate my competence
right now.
We killed the guy who came to Miami.
We found some keys on him.
We're looking into them.
-Are we done?
-Not quite.
A new competitor
has joined the search.
We're the ones getting Scylla.
Well, that's good to hear...
...because the competing party
is your brother, Michael.
Michael's with you.
Michael's getting treatment with you.
Apparently, Michael's a little more
headstrong than either of us imagined.
But don't worry, we have a lead on him,
somewhere in central Arizona.
Mr. Oren is waiting in his limousine.
If you speak to Michael, tell him to find
a very good hiding place...
...because if any of my men spot him,
they've been given a green light.
Only 500 miles to go.
If we take turns sleeping,
we can be there by tomorrow.
Should we call Lincoln,
let him know we're coming?
Michael, he took the Company's deal
to save your life.
For what it's worth,
I might've done the same.
Then you'd be wrong too.
You know,
this promises to be a really long ride...
...so how about we just call truce,
all right?
Forgot napkins.
[GUNSHOT]
MICHAEL:
Get down!
Come on.
If he comes anywhere near my kid....
You know, Don, you seem to be taking
this whole thing pretty well.
Yeah, I'm a pretty calm guy.
All I'm saying is,
my mama, his son, his wife.
-We don't know who they got on you.
-Because it's none of your business.
All right? All you need to worry about
is that I'm here to do a job.
The company that manufactures
the keys, it's called Hold Secure.
Each key is implanted
with a computer chip.
That chip sends out a unique signal
that opens its lock.
Something that high-tech,
I'm telling you, they got a database...
...that'll tell us exactly where
each key's lock has been installed.
Look at that.
These keys run about 500 bucks each.
You only spend that kind of money
if you’re protecting something important.
Like Scylla.
Someone just tried to access
Carruth's account at Hold Secure.
And what information
was compromised?
We don't know yet.
-And who was trying to access it?
-We don't know.
Thank you for bringing that
to my attention. Good work.
-Yes?
-It's your son.
We already have safeguards in place
to deal with Lincoln.
I'm talking about Michael.
He's escaped Company custody.
He's coming to Miami right now.
Christina?
If only they understood
what it is I'm trying to do.
SARA:
Thank you very much.
MICHAEL:
Thanks.
Okay, what now?
We'll think of something.
Michael, we can't afford to buy a car,
and we can't fly.
It's time to call your brother.
Got it.
We've got the locations
of those two locks.
One's in Little Havana,
the other one's down by the water.
Linc, why don't you and I--
You take Self and go to Little Havana.
We're gonna head south.
Oh. That's a surprise.
Bring your suntan lotion.
Be right there.
[CELL PHONE VIBRATING]
MICHAEL: It's me.
-What's your problem?
-I need you to hear me out on this.
-Everything was set up, and you blew it.
You couldn't let me handle this.
If by "handle" you mean give Scylla back
to the general, then, no, I couldn't.
It's more complicated than that.
-Actually, it's not.
-Listen, I want my life back.
And this is the only way
we can do that.
I don't believe that's true.
You know what, man?
You need to grow up.
Look, if that’s
how you really feel, Linc...
...I should warn you I'm gonna do
everything in my power to stop you.
I had a deal with the general.
You blew it.
-If he finds you, he's gonna kill you.
-Surprise, surprise.
I did this for us, Michael.
You, me, Sara, L.J.
So you could be with Sara.
Two seconds, think of your family.
Feels like family's the only thing
I can think about these days.
-What does that mean?
-Michael.
Linc, Mom is alive.
-What?
-I guess I'll see you in Miami.
We gotta get out of here.
Sir, you mind if I ask
where you're going?
-Dallas.
-Mind if we hitch a ride?
I got 100 bucks. Gas money.
Please? Sir?
Cab's not big enough
for the two of you.
If you wanna ride together,
you're gonna have to ride back here.
Done.
[MICHAEL GRUNTS]
Get comfortable. It's gonna be
eight hours till we stop again.
[LATCH CLANKS]
[ENGINE STARTS]
Hey, Linc. If Scylla really is in there...
...there's gonna be security.
I need your focus.
Yeah.
Hey, Linc. I'm going up there.
All clear upstairs.
-You find something?
-Picture of my mom.
Someone must have known
I was coming.
Someone who's
working with Carruth...
...and who knows you well enough
to get their hands on that picture.
There's only one person I can think of
that fits that description.
You saying my mom's in Miami?
If she was operating out of this house,
she had access to money.
She's a Company agent. Gretchen said
she thought this could be an inside job.
Linc.
Your mother could have Scylla.
She used to bake cookies
when we'd come home from school.
Play kickball with us in the backyard.
There's just no way
that woman was a Company agent.
You did read her file, didn't you?
I saw medical reports that said
she had the same diagnosis I do...
...and that Company doctors
operated on her too.
I'm wondering if they took her to a little
cabin in the woods after they were done...
...introduced her to a friendly shrink.
How else could someone
just stand by and watch...
...while their own children
were hunted down like dogs, huh?
Maybe she didn't know.
She knew.
-Maybe it was over her head.
-Or maybe she didn't care.
I'm just surprised
the general waited so long...
...to drop this bomb on us.
Actually, I think
that part makes sense. I mean, it--
Your mother didn't want you to know
she was alive...
...or you would've known years ago.
And the general's
just keeping that secret, right?
Keeping her happy,
keeping her working.
But now the game has changed.
Yeah, now he thinks
you might be useful.
Just like Mom.
KRANTZ:
Beyond question...
...he possesses the most gifted mind
of any man I've ever encountered.
Well, I'll try not to take that
too personally.
He drilled into your office safe...
...and copied your card
without you even noticing.
As I recall,
you were sitting right next to me.
If we could've turned
Michael Scofield...
...it would've been like having
30 more years of Christina.
Pull over.
That's my ride.
-What's going on?
-Goodbye, Jonathan.
This ain't the place.
-I could pick that lock with my stump.
SELF: No, no, no.
Remember what they say
about books and their covers.
When Harry Winston donated
the Hope diamond to the Smithsonian...
...you know how he got it
from New York to D.C.?
Registered mail.
It was the safest way to go.
After all, who is gonna be looking
for the Hope diamond...
...at the post office, right?
And who would be looking for Scylla...
...at some run-down storefront church
in Little Havana?
Let's say you're right,
they got Scylla back there.
You walk in there reeking that cop stink,
you won't last a second.
That's a good point.
That's why you're going in.
[BELL JINGLES]
MAN:
May I help you?
Yes, as a matter of fact.
I'm Charles Patoshik.
I'm a professor of anthropology
at Southern Florida University.
I'm doing some various research...
...on various different kinds
of Caribbean religions.
And perhaps you could start back there
where you do your services.
That is our sanctuary.
Only the pure of soul
may venture inside.
I know, and I have been
in many such rooms.
Let me see your hand.
Uh....
Your soul is black,
stained with the blood of the innocent.
I cannot let you pass.
I have never been so offended
in my life.
I suggest that you continue
your research elsewhere.
If you drop something by accident...
...you leave a fingerprint on it.
-She wanted you to find this.
-Why?
-You ever seen it before?
-No.
Do you remember anything
about that day?
I was 4 years old.
-Any idea where it was taken?
-No.
Hey, you okay?
-I mean, if I found out my mom was--
-As far as I'm concerned...
...she's not my mom. She's someone
in the way of my freedom, all right?
MICHAEL:
So on my 6th birthday--
My father was long gone by then,
so it was just me and Mom and Lincoln.
Mom hands me my present.
My only present.
And I just know....
I just know it's the Millennium Falcon.
-With the battle-alert sound?
-Exactly.
-I totally had that.
-Of course you did.
I'd been asking for this thing for weeks,
and the package is just the right size...
...and I rip open the wrapping paper,
and it's a birdhouse.
-Oh, no.
-Yeah.
Except it's not even a birdhouse.
It's actually a birdhouse kit.
[CHUCKLES]
I'm so sorry.
I didn't talk to her
for two days after that.
But when she finally got me
to open the thing...
...we sat there together,
put it together piece by piece.
And it was the first thing I ever built.
And I loved it.
And she knew I would.
She knew me better
than I knew myself.
That's what moms do, right?
Yeah, but the strange thing is...
...even though I haven't seen her
for 23 years, there's this part of me...
...that feels like maybe she still does.
[SIREN WAILING]
[SIREN STOPS]
Your truck looks
a little low to the ground.
-Mind stepping outside?
-I just got weighed 20 miles back.
You highway patrol?
Where you going?
[DOOR OPENS]
DRIVER:
You got no business in there.
Unless you show me a warrant,
you get the hell out of there right now.
[EXHALES]
Thank you.
[DOOR SLAMS]
DRIVER:
Goodness.
I got my weigh-station ticket
right here on the dash.
As soon as you see that....
We'll see. I got it right here.
Here you go.
I need you to follow me
back to Phoenix.
Are you crazy?
I gotta get this load to Dallas.
Well, that's your choice.
[LINE RINGING]
I got them.
I think we need to call your brother.
No signal.
We must be in the middle of nowhere.
Didn't Lincoln say
that if the Company caught you...?
Think I saw a side door back here.
-What about the main door?
-We'll never get that open.
-I'm sure it's latched from the outside.
-Can you open the side door?
Maybe.
[GRUNTS]
Sara, help me out.
[GRUNTING]
I don't think
we're gonna be able to move this.
Maybe we won't have to.
CHRISTINA: I have troubling news
about General Krantz.
-He's alive.
-I don't see how that's possible.
Well, what I'm hearing
is a helicopter with a medic...
...took off from Company headquarters
in Los Angeles one hour ago.
It landed for two minutes
in Canyon Country...
...and now it's back in Los Angeles.
So you got the corpse?
The helicopter landed
back at Company headquarters.
You know how important
getting rid of him is...
-...to what we're trying to accomplish.
-All right, I can still get this done.
Not in our time frame.
All right, I'm pulling the plug.
We need to start dealing
with the consequences.
Wait. First things first.
He knows I betrayed him.
I need to disappear.
-I think that's a good instinct.
-I have a house in Sun Valley.
I have another idea.
Do you mind putting me on speaker?
You know, Griff, you're a brave man.
And I thank you
for everything you've done.
It's been an honor.
-Now.
-"Now" what?
The car in this picture
has Florida plates.
Did you ever vacation there?
-No.
-Do you know anyone from Florida...
-...who came up to visit?
-No.
Why did they take this picture
in front of their car?
-We didn't. It's been doctored.
-I'm not sure about that.
I mean, the lighting, the shadows,
they all sync up perfectly.
But this is a '78 Zephyr.
Michael was born in '76.
You're the only one who could've picked
up on that. She doctored that for you.
Let's see what else
she might've changed.
-What's the license plate on that Zephyr?
-MLK-441.
Martin Luther King Boulevard intersects
with Route 441 five miles north of here.
Good. You guys are here.
We're outmanned at Little Havana.
We could use some backup.
We got a lead on the buyer.
-Great. What are we waiting for?
-I think I'm gonna do this myself.
No. Come on, let's stay together.
We're a team, right?
-I said I got it.
-After our special delivery this morning...
...each of us has an equal stake.
Now, whoever started this,
we're all gonna take him out.
The buyer,
we think it's Lincoln's mother.
-What?
-Like I said, I'm doing this myself.
Linc, if she has Scylla...
...she's not gonna hand it over any more
than the general would have.
You don't know that.
We always thought whoever had Scylla
would do what the general did.
-Maybe she won't.
-Are you serious?
Your mother is a Company agent?
She was.
She might be one of the good guys now.
I don't think you're in a place...
...where you can make
a clear determination about that.
This MLK-441 could be nothing.
But at the church there could be Scylla.
If I need you, I'll call.
MICHAEL:
This should work.
Christina, you need to acknowledge
that our chance of success...
...has substantially declined
in the last 24 hours.
There are people looking for us.
We need to think
in terms of contingencies.
Just a little while longer.
Only a few more days.
General Krantz refused to adjust
when there were threats against him.
That's the reason we have Scylla now.
Are you honestly
comparing me to him?
I understand what you think
your role is in all of this...
...and I appreciate your efforts,
but if you can't tell the difference...
...between he and I, perhaps you need
to ask the general for your old job back.
[CELL PHONE VIBRATING]
Oh, look.
Here he is.
Would you like to take the call?
[CELL PHONE BEEPS]
Jonathan.
-Good afternoon, Christina.
-It's good to hear your voice.
I assume this means
you've retrieved Scylla?
-Not yet.
-Oh, that's troubling news.
-Have any idea where it is?
-Where are you, Christina?
Johannesburg. Where else would I be?
I've had some of my contacts
in your area check out your house.
-There's no one home.
-Well, of course not.
As long as Scylla's in play,
that address is blown.
[OBJECTS CLATTERING]
Where are you, Christina?
-I don't like your tone, Jonathan.
-Excuse me if I sound a bit abrasive.
But it's been a while
since anyone's tried to kill me.
Oh, my God. Are you all right?
What happened?
Oren.
-Oren?
-We found his body executed.
I can only assume
that he's working with someone.
Someone who doesn't tolerate failure.
Now, where are you, Christina?
You listen to me.
If you're implying
that I had anything to do with this....
Where are you?
After everything I've given the Company:
my husband, my children....
I think it's time
that we had a sit-down, a talk.
Tell you what, why don't you
gather up the brain trust...
...that half-witted daughter
and your psychotic mistress?
Why don't you get together
and figure out where Scylla is?
Then call me.
[LINE DISCONNECTS]
MAN:
Mr. Burrows.
May I escort you to your table?
[EXHALES]
You haven't changed a bit.
I'm glad you got my message.
It wasn't the most straightforward mode
of communication...
...but I had to be sure it was you.
At least now I know
where Michael gets it from.
-I'm sure you have a lot of questions.
-Where's Scylla?
It's safe.
That's all I can tell you for right now.
-Then we got nothing to talk about.
-Really?
That's the only reason you came here?
Yeah.
I would've thought
you wanted to know the truth.
I know the truth.
You work for the Company.
The same people...
-...that set me up for murder.
-Lincoln.
The same people
that have been trying to kill me...
...ever since we escaped Fox River.
You can think it as much as you want,
I'm not a monster.
Twenty-three years,
and not even an apology?
If I thought an apology
would do any good...
...I would offer it.
Please.
Please sit down.
[EXHALES]
Leaving you two boys...
...was the hardest thing I ever did.
But you did.
Then you went off
and worked for the Company.
You know, you think you know
what the Company is, but you don't.
It's a body
that bends to the will of its head.
And right now it is bloodthirsty
and war-hungry...
...because that's
who General Krantz is.
But what if a woman,
a mother, ran it?
Can you imagine the difference
that would make?
You think you're a mother?
A mother's priority is her family.
If I give Scylla back to the general...
...he leaves me and Michael alone, and I
get to spend time with my son in peace.
I could sit here for days...
...and try to explain to you
why I did what I did.
Suffice it to say I couldn't protect you
then, but let me protect you now.
What if General Krantz
were no longer in the picture?
Once he was dealt with,
no one would come after you.
But I need time, Lincoln.
I need two days
to put everything into place.
If you give me two days...
...then I can give you and Michael
your complete and utter freedom.
[EXHALES]
All right.
I'm gonna get started right away.
But if Krantz suspects any of this,
he's gonna hunt us both down.
And for that reason,
I can't risk being seen with you...
...until all of this is over.
-How do I get in touch with you?
-You can't.
I'm sorry.
[BREATHING HEAVILY]
MICHAEL: Once we pull this box down,
it'll push the water machine...
-...through the side door.
-We're slowing down.
-I think we're getting off the highway.
-We're almost ready.
Would you grab that strap over there.
All right, hold it.
[CREAKING]
MICHAEL:
Come on.
You all right?
[BRAKES SQUEALING]
After you clear the area,
I don't anticipate any problems, all right?
-Scylla or not, here we come.
-All right. Hold on, hold on.
What the hell are those guys doing?
We're not going against
any additional people.
-We wait until they come back out.
-All right.
So Lincoln's mother is really the buyer?
It appears that way.
I hope he understands that if I need
to take her out to get to Scylla...
...I'm not gonna hesitate to kill her.
No question.
Well, let's just hope
it doesn't come to that.
-You serious?
-Am I serious if we can get Scylla...
...without killing Linc's mother?
That's the preferable outcome.
Wait a second.
If I'm gonna be in a foxhole with you,
I need to know that you have my back.
Miss Burrows has the item,
and the only way to get it is to kill her.
What is your move?
I pull the trigger.
There they go. Come on.
Don Self, Homeland Security.
We're investigating
a cruelty-to-animal charge.
I have no idea
what you're referring to.
We're referring to ritual slaughters
of chickens, okay?
That might be allowed where you come
from, but in America, that's no más.
Chickens? This is preposterous.
This is because I'm Caribbean?
I swear to God, I smelled chicken blood,
worse than the place down the street.
Hey, you wanna turn this
into something? Sit down.
If there aren't any chickens,
there aren't any.
We're not gonna know
until we take a look around.
-The smell was coming from back there.
-That is our sanctuary.
I cannot let you disrupt it.
I understand your concerns,
but I need to go back there.
I insist, you cannot do that.
Best I can do is have you accompany us.
Please. Please.
You, come on. Let's go outside
until they're done. Let's go.
[GRUNTS]
That's not a very heavenly thing to do.
[COVER CLATTERS]
BAGWELL: Find anything?
-Oh, yeah.
[MAHONE EXHALES]
[INHALES DEEPLY]
BAGWELL: What the hell are they up to?
MAN: I don't know.
-He just asked to rent that closet.
-Did a woman ever come here with him?
Yeah, once.
I'm telling you, that's all I know.
[GUN COCKS]
Drop it.
MAN:
Don't.
Come here.
Both of you.
On your knees.
I said, on your knees.
I told you not to come in here.
-Where's the other guy?
-He ran. Let's go.
Come on, let's go.
-You all right?
-Yeah.
Let's go.
Come on.
[SIGHS]
[OBJECT CLATTERS]
[CREAKING]
-We won't make it back to the truck.
-I know.
-Here. Take this.
-All right.
-I'll be right back.
-Michael.
Michael.
[GRUNTING]
-You all right?
-Yeah, thanks.
[GRUNTS]
[MAN MOANING]
The general should know by now
not to mess with us.
The general didn't send me.
Who did? Who sent you?
[DOOR OPENS]
Lincoln?
We got some news.
So do I.
We're staying low for two days.
Christina's promised
to get rid of Krantz.
-I think she's lying.
-I know it sounds crazy.
She said she's gonna change
the Company and how it operates.
So, what, the Company's
gonna go nonviolent now?
-Just hear me out.
-I think she's lying.
It's from the church.
Some kind of credential.
SELF:
There were automatic weapons too.
If there's fake IDs and weapons,
something big is about to go down.
Your mom, she said after two days,
that's when she would make the change?
-Yeah.
-Look at the date on that laminate.
Two days away.
You think that's a coincidence?
You can't be surprised that a woman
that would abandon her kids...
...would be less than truthful
about her intentions now.
MAHONE: Hey, where you going?
-I need to talk to her.
Let's figure this out.
If she's looking to head the Company,
there has to be a more realistic plan...
-...than a one-man frontal assault.
-She'll listen to me.
She asked you not to come back, Linc.
That's a warning.
Lincoln's back at the plaza.
We need to realize he's more of a threat
than we gave him credit for.
He found the mansion.
His guys got the stash at the church.
He's not gonna stop.
I told him to stay away.
Christina, we have a clean shot.
Take it.
DOWNEY:
[ENGLISH SDH]