Doc! Help! Doc!
It stopped bleeding.
That's because your blood is freezing
as it's hitting the air.
Here. Apply pressure on it.
I think my leg is frozen.
That's the least of your problems.
The blade severed your femoral artery.
Am I going to lose my leg?
Frostbite's not too bad.
But I've got to fix your artery now.
This is going to hurt.
Are you going
to put that in me?
Glue's the best way to repair your
artery at this temperature.
It looks okay.
Here. Tear off some pieces.
I have to check your foot.
Blood flow looks good.
Your leg should be okay.
I thought I was done.
Yeah, like I'd let
anything happen to you.
You're the only one
who could fix the generators.
Okay. One, two...
Cate. Cate, are you okay?
Are you okay?
Hey.
I need help.
Who am I supposed to get?
Why do I even
give you an office?
New case. Psych department
asked for you personally.
The patient's a crazy person?
You're a crazy person.
The patient's a psychiatrist.
There's something wrong
with coma guy's cable.
He seems fine with it.
Your patient is an adjunct faculty
member here, but currently...
The budget committee voted to charge
for cable in the patient rooms.
Slippery slope.
Today, we withhold porn.
Tomorrow, it's clean bandages.
Talk to Carlson in Denn,
he runs the budget committee,
after you look at this.
After you
talk to Carlson, maybe I'll...
The patient is trapped
at the South Pole.
Any possibility
of evacuating her?
Well, that wouldn't be any fun.
And for the next two months, winds make
it impossible to fly anything in or out.
Could be appendicitis
or a gallstone.
Or a kidney stone.
That wouldn't be any fun.
If it's appendicitis down there,
her appendix ruptures, she dies.
There's nothing we can do.
If it's a stone, she takes pain meds,
stone passes.
There's nothing we need to do.
Could be a struvite
kidney stone.
Most kidney stones
are calcium and benign.
Why would you
suspect a struvite stone?
Because he said
kidney stones were boring.
It's possible.
She's on birth control.
Lots of sex could lead
to urinary tract infection,
which could lead to an infection-laced
struvite kidney stone.
Excessive Antarctic drilling,
bad for the environment
and the ladies.
If it's a struvite stone, she
needs to break it up quickly
before the infection
shuts down her kidneys.
This is where it gets fun.
These are the supplies and medications
she has available.
Nothing here that could
break up a kidney stone.
What else do they
have down there?
I just said...
I don't mean medical stuff. Other stuff.
Some geological equipment
breaks ice and rock
the same way
we break kidney stones.
Discovery Channel.
I like watching them blow stuff up.
Who doesn't?
That reminds me.
Coma guy needs cable.
Women's billiards is the only thing
that's keeping him alive.
I'm sure Carlson will be moved
by his plight.
Carlson won't listen.
He says I hit on his wife.
- You knew?
- God, no.
I thought I was hitting
on his daughter.
Look, you're on the committee.
He'll listen to you.
I'm an avid reader of Committees
with Hotties message boards.
Amoxicillin,
500 milligrams, IV.
Studies conducted
at major hospitals indicate
that happy patients recover faster.
Studies conducted in my apartment
show that TV makes people happy.
Premium channels
have a particularly striking effect.
Charging patients for cable is bringing
in 13 grand a month.
Until this injustice is righted,
I am going to waste 13 grand a day.
That's $2.49 down.
Get an EKG
and a cardiac enzyme.
If those check out, discharge him,
and tell him to get a snow-blower.
How much is 13 grand
divided by 4 cents?
I am not giving you cable.
You're gonna have to somehow survive
with the broadcast networks alone.
I'll be fine on Tuesdays.
If sound waves
from the flaw detector break the egg,
it should safely dissolve
your kidney stone.
This isn't going to work.
Well,
there's no reason it shouldn't.
Sound waves are sound waves.
Stones are stones.
Some are bigger than others.
Some are inside me.
How's it going, Team MacGyver?
Oh, great.
I can't get cable, but I can get
the South Pole on high-def.
We're almost ready
to start the test.
Test? Did Ford test the Edsel?
Did Coke test New Coke? Did Shakespeare
test his final play, Snow Dogs?
I'm guessing you're Dr. House?
I was wondering
when you might drop by.
Could she see me?
Oh, yeah.
You think Jagger shows up
for the sound check?
Okay, roadies, off the stage.
Go help Cameron in the ER.
Why? No way you're just
doing her a favor.
ER is standing room only.
Which means Cameron's bound
to make a mistake.
Find it so I can blackmail her.
As far as you know,
this is way more than just some silly
battle over cable.
Ready.
You might wanna
dial it down a smidge.
I am not doing this.
Your kidney stone theory hinges on me
having sex, but I...
Let me guess. You're as pure
as the driven snow.
Only if the snow
likes to be on top.
But I am here doing
psychological research.
Generally not a good idea to swap fluids
with your subjects.
Struvite stones are possible
in people who don't have sex.
They're certainly possible
in people who claim not to...
I've had no UTI's,
no pain on urination.
You do realize that only one of us
is a real doctor.
You do realize only one of us has any
control over my actions.
Dr. Milton, are you able
to run a CHEM-7?
Yes.
Well, that'd tell us if her kidney
function is declining.
If it is, he's right.
Struvite stone's
the most likely explanation.
If not, she's right.
Sorry. I know how you like to avoid
avoiding confrontation.
While we're waiting for that test to
prove me right, start IV cefuroxime.
Keep the infection in the stone from
wiping out your kidneys.
I'll send the CHEM-7
results when I'm done.
She's a great psychiatrist.
One session, I've got shrinkage.
House wants us
to spy on you, report back.
And you're
telling me this because...
We don't want to do it.
I don't see a problem so far.
If our choice is between pissing
House off or pissing you off,
that's not much of a choice.
So unless I give House cable,
you're gonna make
my life miserable.
Yes.
And you're telling me this so you won't
feel as guilty when you do it.
Yes.
Accommodating House's
every whim is not my job anymore.
But it is ours.
House will get what he wants.
Maybe we should just pay for it
ourselves and tell him she folded.
No.
Your CHEM-7 results showed
your kidney function is declining.
Sounds like
a kidney stone to me.
The decreased function
could be from dehydration caused by
vomiting due to a gallstone.
You agreed that the CHEM-7 would decide
if it was a struvite stone.
I agreed to do the test. The results are
up for interpretation.
I'll re-do the test in an hour
when I'm re-hydrated.
Have you noticed any improvement since
starting the cefuroxime?
Not really. Pain's
about the same.
While you're waiting, we should run
another test with the geology equipment.
You're not taking
the cefuroxime.
She's right-handed.
Means she would put
the N in her left arm.
Catheter in the arm
makes it hard to bend the elbow,
the way people do
when they drink.
We have a limited supply of medication,
and I am not about to waste it.
Last I checked you had
a limited supply of doctors.
Right before I got sick, one of my crew
members severed his femoral artery.
He needs the cefuroxime.
Right. He called dibs.
His need is definitive.
Mine is speculative.
You're breathing fast.
It's because I'm pissed off!
Lift up your chin.
Show me your windpipe.
My chest hurts.
It's deviating to the left.
Because her right lung
is collapsing.
Cate, is anyone there with you?
- Sean went to the mess.
- You need to call someone.
There's no time.
Get a syringe and a needle.
- Why am I doing that?
- Shut up and look.
She could pass out.
She needs to...
She needs
to re-inflate that lung.
Okay. Now, pull out
the plunger.
I want you to stab yourself
in your right side
between the second and third rib,
in the midclavicular line.
By the time we get someone else there,
you'll have suffocated.
Just do it.
See all the good stuff that happens
when you listen to me?
Means it's not a kidney stone.
Right side pain, vomiting,
and now a lung that gets traumatized
without any trauma.
Sounds odd. Probably is odd.
We should discuss this,
then call her back.
No, it's fine. I made sure we got
the South Pole long distance plan.
Her latest kidney
function test shows...
I know what it shows. I ran it.
The more you interrupt, the longer my
grandstanding is going to take.
Since when do you let patients
participate in differentials?
Since the patient and her doctor happen
to be the same person.
Your kidney function
is still declining.
Means
you have a kidney problem.
But not one that needed antibiotics.
Makes us equally wrong.
No.
Makes us both wrong. Not equally.
You were at least six wronger.
They run a PPD
before you shipped out?
On me and everybody else here.
It's not TB.
Excuse us a second.
Cancer explains her symptoms.
A tumor in her lung or kidney that threw
a clot to the other organ.
And you're worried the tumor might
overhear, realize we're on to it.
Cancer's a hard diagnosis for patients,
even when they're not in the South Pole.
We should figure this out,
maybe bring Wilson in.
Obviously, you two think
I'm in bad shape.
- Only if you count the tumor.
- House.
Probably in your abdomen.
But you don't have any advanced
imaging equipment.
You also don't have
a surgeon to biopsy it,
any stains to use on the slide,
or an oncologist to analyze it.
I'm too far away
to hold her hand.
I have cancer?
Possibly.
Since the only imaging equipment you
have is x-ray, let's start there.
X-ray your entire body.
I'll upload the images
when I'm done.
Good for you.
She's annoying.
Refused to take the antibiotics because
other people might need them.
She said she cares
about other people?
What a poser.
KUB is clean.
You don't like her
because she's a psychiatrist.
Mmm, I'm a complicated man.
I loathe her for many reasons.
Never before has a profession
been so decried
by someone who
needed it so badly.
You talk a lot of smack
about tranny hookers.
Enlarged mediastinal node.
- Lymphoma?
- Probably,
but we can't confirm it
without a biopsy.
We can't analyze
a biopsy without a stain.
We can't biopsy.
Since they don't have stains down there,
we need a substitute.
She can't biopsy that node
without a surgical team and an OR.
Anything with a strong color
could work as a stain.
Printer ink,
food coloring, coffee.
No, thanks.
I'll find a node closer to the surface.
One she can biopsy.
That makes sense.
That makes sense?
I said it first.
In a shockingly calm manner.
After I've just been
jerking you around for 30 seconds
without you complaining
or analyzing said jerking.
I was being mature.
In a lavender shirt.
You, for some reason,
are happy.
How dare you.
The x-rays don't show
any other abnormal nodes.
Abnormal nodes can be felt
before they can be seen on an x-ray.
You're wearing
that shirt for someone.
The Health Department.
They frown on topless oncology.
You're gonna do a physical?
Have to. You and Foreman are going
to be here looking for a stain.
I can do the physical.
There's no reason you need to watch.
I can think of at least
three reasons.
One of them is medical.
Where are you?
Not in your office.
You're not in the hospital.
No reason for me to be.
I'm not undressing for you
in your apartment.
You're not in my apartment.
You're three quarters
of a world away.
I promise not to get fresh.
I'm not taking off my clothes.
One of us has to.
Show me your place.
It's got walls, a floor,
and in some places, a roof.
I am not exposing myself
without some reciprocity.
It's my apartment.
It's not my soul.
Living room.
Slow down.
Huh!
Lots of books.
I'm betting all medical.
Only if you count Jenna Jameson's
autobiography as a gynecological text.
Fiction is a waste of time.
Unless you can laugh at it?
I love to laugh. Moving on.
Back up.
How bad is the insomnia?
Let me quantify that.
Do you drink two or three scotches
before passing out in front of the TV?
You are so far off.
It's bourbon.
No photos anywhere.
Family and friends
aren't important?
Well, you're sick.
You have 20 people down the hall,
and you've had exactly one visitor.
I don't want to panic anyone.
You don't like people.
You hide on that ice cube, so...
Stop projecting. You're antisocial,
so you assume I'm antisocial?
How about
if I just get naked, and you shut up?
If I thought I could get you naked,
I would have led with that.
You'd rather show me
your soul than your leg.
Great. You got me
all figured out.
You going to try
and fix me now?
I never said you needed fixing.
He's letting her take part
in the differentials.
Of course he is. He likes her.
Big shock. Spaghetti sauce doesn't work
as a lymph tissue stain.
I'll try the coffee.
He's annoyed by her, doesn't respect
her as a doctor,
constantly insults her.
That's House's version
of courtship.
Oh, God. He's been wooing me
for years.
She's the perfect
woman for him.
Willing to literally go to the end
of the earth for her career,
making her unavailable
for a real relationship.
And she's afflicted
with a mysterious illness.
Soy sauce is a no-go.
We're gonna be here all night.
How long
does it take you to get naked?
It's the South Pole.
I wear a lot of layers.
Okay. Ready.
I saw socks.
That's not naked.
Have I mentioned
it's freezing here?
When they discover lymph nodes in feet,
I will take off my socks.
Use your right hand
to palpate the nodes.
Any node you can feel
is the one we can biopsy.
Let's start with your breasts,
move down to the ass, then...
I was thinking go from the neck
and work my way down.
We could,
but I'd never forgive myself if we found
something before we got to your breasts.
I'm starting with
the anterior cervical nodes.
Turn your head.
Locate the SCM muscle.
I know how to find
my lymph nodes.
Did they teach you that before or after
the class on fondling your inner child?
No swelling.
No tenderness. And...
I can hear that, House.
Just thought
it might help you relax.
Anything in the axillary nodes?
All clear.
Both sides.
Now slide your hand
to your sternum.
Probe for nodes
moving slowly downward.
Down to what, House?
Sorry. Can't hear you on account
of your heavy breathing.
I'm supposed to be on oxygen, you tool.
Hold it.
Your fingers didn't go quite as deep.
Feel that node again.
It's swollen.
Looks like you're
doing a biopsy.
It's pretty numb.
Okay. Take a deep breath and
insert the needle into the node.
Come on, Cate.
Let's get this over with.
You used her name.
Just trying to move
things along, Bob.
Okay. I'm in.
You need to pull back
on the syringe.
You need to pull harder.
You Okay?
Yeah.
"Are you okay? u."
It's a valid medical question.
I have never heard you
ask a patient that question.
You've never asked me
that question,
and you've seen me fall down
a flight of stairs drunk.
You've slept with her.
She's 9,000 miles away.
And while a certain part
of me, unfurled...
No, I...
Somehow, you've been
intimate with her.
Why are you following me?
I thought you were
following me.
No. You are definitely
- Where are you going?
- Out to lunch.
You never go out to lunch.
Which means there's a reason
you're going out to lunch.
I assume that reason
is a human being.
Or a sandwich.
Sandwiches can come here.
So can human beings.
And yet, she's not,
which I find interesting.
I'm leaving, now.
Small world.
Are you going to
follow me into my car?
It's got two doors.
Okay, look, the reason
I haven't told you is...
Call off your dogs, House.
Your little helpers
are interrogating my patients,
swiping my charts, intercepting
prescriptions.
Why would you think that I...
Because I'm not a moron.
You had to be pulling
the strings, here.
You think that because
they make me miserable,
I'm going to give you cable.
Let's assume that's true,
and it certainly sounds
like it might be.
- What are you going to do?
- Nothing.
I resigned from
the budget committee.
I only joined the committee to help the
hospital. You made me a liability.
I now have zero influence over
the hospital's cable policy.
Well done.
It didn't work. There's nothing more
that we can do...
Put these up.
"Free Rottweiler puppies."
"Please call after 11:00 p.m.
and before 5:00 a.m."
Is this Cameron's home number?
I'd love a new puppy-
My last one
was delicious, very tender.
There's no point
in torturing her.
If she can resign, she can un-resign.
Go to DEFCON 1.
Forget waiting for a mistake.
Make her make one.
You want us to sabotage
another doctor,
possibly harm a patient,
all so you can have cable.
Harm suggests permanent damage.
Get her to screw up, then fix it.
Oh! And this time,
don't tell her what you're gonna do
before you do it.
So, how long do I let the lymph node
marinate in the red wine?
It should be ready, now.
Try increasing
the magnification on the camera.
You know, I emailed a couple of
colleagues at the hospital about you.
You're checking up
on me? Not House?
Yeah, well House is straightforward,
brilliant and an ass.
Two out of three good qualities.
Clear majority.
Whereas you, on the other hand,
have a perfect score.
You are responsible,
nice, human.
And yet, you're House's
best friend.
Hold there.
Makes you think
he's secretly nicer than he seems?
Makes me think that you're secretly
a lot less nice than you seem.
Do you always insult
your doctors?
It's not an insult. Indiscriminate
niceness is overrated.
No wonder he likes you.
Based on this slide
you do not have cancer.
Oh!
Thank God.
I do see some inflammation,
which could mean...
Cate? You all right?
My left side. It hurts.
It's the same pain
that I had on the right.
Your other kidney.
No. I hope it's, it's something,
it's maybe...
I'm screwed.
The bad news is you're O for two
in the kidney department.
Is there good news?
You're back at home.
Of course. There's cable.
- And freedom to work pant-free.
- That is good news.
Wilson found signs of inflammation
in your biopsy.
That, plus the two failing kidneys,
points to autoimmune disease.
Probably SLE or vasculitis.
Treatment for both is prednisone.
Start with
a hundred milligrams.
Autoimmune is just
your latest theory.
Like cancer before that,
and a kidney stone before.
Take the prednisone. You'll get better.
That will be your confirmation.
You practice medicine
like it's a fire sale.
You've wasted
antibiotics, x-rays...
That was not a waste.
We've ruled out...
We have a crew member here
who has asthma.
If he has an episode after I've used up
the prednisone, he'll die.
There's a good chance
he's going to die anyway.
Since there won't be
a doctor there to help him.
Show me proof
that it's autoimmune,
and then I'll take
the prednisone.
We should send her outside.
Right. Let's just tell her to head north
until she runs into a hospital.
Autoimmune diseases are basically
inflammation running wild.
Extreme cold has been used as treatment,
like putting ice on a sprained ankle.
She starts to feel better outside,
we know it's autoimmune.
Is that my wallet?
You can have it back.
I've already been through it.
I like your
ice on the sprain metaphor.
Makes it seem
like we're not killing her.
She'd only need to be outside
five minutes.
Without her mittens. Mom told me
that was a bad idea.
Especially that winter. It was 70 below,
and I had dual kidney failure.
This is a good idea. It's perfect
for you. Experimental, risky.
Wilson's right.
You care about...
You didn't touch the cash,
but you took the receipts?
A hundred and ninety dollar restaurant
tab. That's dessert, probably booze.
It means you lingered.
Means it's at least
a third date. Means...
- Where are you going?
- To talk to the people I pay
to come up with medical ideas.
There are no ideas.
The test for autoimmune is ANA.
Unless penguins poop immunoanalyzers...
Before ANA testing,
people had autoimmune diseases.
How did they know?
- C3.
- Before that.
LE Prep. But she doesn't have any
controlled pore glass beads.
You don't need them.
When you shake the test tube,
the paperclip will damage
some of your blood cells.
If you have
an autoimmune disease,
your immune system will gorge itself
on the damaged cells.
They'll get big and fat so that you can
see them under a microscope.
How you doing?
No change.
So, how long should I give the cells
to fatten up before I check them?
A couple hours.
Or you could stop being a hypocrite
and take the prednisone now.
Not bending to your will
makes me a hypocrite?
If your psych patients demanded lab
results you'd never make a diagnosis.
So, I'm wrong.
You sleep like a baby.
Your life is unfolding as you dreamed.
Everyone is miserable.
You don't change that
because people don't change.
You want to believe that
because then you're freed
from any responsibility for your misery.
Oh, shut up.
I get enough of this
from Wilson.
And yet, you keep
hanging out with him.
And, from what I hear,
you have spent more time with me
than with any other patient.
Sorry about that.
Call me when you get
the results.
How's your patient?
She has an autoimmune disease.
Tell the psych department
she's in denial.
I had to fire Cameron.
What? What happened?
A sixty-five-year-old man came
into the ER with a hip fracture.
Cameron gave him Demerol.
The guy was on an MAOI.
Put him into
a hypertensive crisis.
- Is he going to live?
- Taub caught the error in time.
If she'd just admitted
the mistake,
maybe I could have just
suspended her, but...
She's packing up.
If you want to say goodbye.
We should be hearing from the South Pole
in a few minutes.
That's it?
There's nothing to be done.
She screwed up. She's got
no one to blame but herself.
I've got to go talk to Cameron.
Cuddy wouldn't can her
for one screw-up.
And if she did,
she wouldn't come to me.
And if she did, she wouldn't open with,
"How's your patient?"
- And if she did...
- Why would she lie?
Timeless question.
In this case, she conspired
with your co-workers to teach me
that some things
are more important than cable.
I'm going to have to teach them
that they're wrong.
Come on. South Pole really
should be calling.
LE Prep test was negative.
It's not autoimmune.
You're basing that on a test done with
a paper clip. Just take the prednisone.
Either find another diagnosis,
or find another test.
There is one way.
You can take this experimental drug
called prednisone.
If your kidneys
start working...
There is another test.
I think Foreman may have just
broken up, there.
What he actually said was,
"There is no other test."
If you have
an autoimmune disease,
exposure to the cold should decrease
your kidney pain.
If I go outside,
we'll have our answer?
And you knew about this?
I rejected it because
if you're frozen solid,
it's hard to get the needles
into your arms.
How long do I need to stay out?
At least five minutes.
Eight minutes outside
would kill a healthy person.
And healthy people
don't suck on oxygen masks.
Healthy people can pee.
I'll go get Sean,
have him come with me.
Just take the prednisone.
Once I come inside,
if it's autoimmune.
Are you all right?
Oh, I'm sure she's just fine.
Cate?
Do you know if there's anyone down there
who has a cell phone?
It took the station mechanic
20 minutes to respond.
She'd already slipped
into a coma.
Started her on prednisone,
but no improvement.
Means it's not autoimmune.
Good thing she's in a coma.
- Or we'd have to listen to her gloat.
- And where are we going?
To find the useful
members of my team.
You're letting them
off the hook?
You happy? Because of you, I'm not gonna
be able to watch Law & Order in Korean.
Why am I here?
Because I want to ask you
about your girlfriend.
I must know who she is,
or you'd have told me her name.
She doesn't have a name.
It's some sort of birth defect.
There's only about
12 people we both know.
And I can't remember
five of their names,
so we're down to Cuddy,
your ex-wives.
Your mama.
You need to run
a kidney function test.
Yes. If only she wasn't in a coma, we
could get her to run a test
to find out why
she's in a coma.
The results
would likely be paradoxical.
It can't be Cuddy, because you're
straight. It can't be...
We could talk the mechanic
through the test.
Too complicated.
Unless he's thirsty.
Drink her urine?
If it has a strong,
concentrated taste,
it means the problems
are in her kidneys.
Watery taste means
it's her brain.
- And then you can fix it?
- Let's say, yeah.
How do I get
the urine out of her?
Take a straight catheter
and insert it...
Those are your only questions?
Not, "Is it safe?"
Or, "ls there another way?"
Or, "Are you
out of your minds?"
You wouldn't ask me if...
Wait a second.
You're in love with her.
That explains why you're so eager to get
her naked, then have a drink.
Because most guys like to go
the other way around.
Why do you care
how I feel about her?
Because now I know that I can get you
to do anything to save her.
Tell him how to tap the keg.
You got Cameron fired.
Cuddy wasn't supposed
to find out.
No kidding!
Get me cable. How tough can that be?
You cost a woman her job.
There's only one thing
you can say to keep me from firing you.
- Cameron wasn't fired. We...
- Wrong.
- You know?
- We're still fired?
That should be a hint
as to what you're supposed to say.
- We're sorry.
- Wrong.
I love you.
Wrong.
This is a game? First, we have to screw
with our co-worker,
now we have to try
to figure out what you want us to say?
This is insane.
I'm not playing.
Right.
You should have said this
two days ago.
Do not play games with me.
Number one, you are going to lose.
You're just not ready.
Number two, the game was to force you
to stop playing games.
I need you to stand up
to me. Challenge me.
I need you to stop worrying
about getting fired.
And go pay for my cable.
No!
I didn't mean on this.
Seriously. I need cable.
Milk, milk, lemonade.
It tastes kind of watery.
That's bad news.
Either increased
intracranial pressure
or something's wrong
with her hypothalamus.
How do you figure out
which one it is?
We don't do anything.
You're gonna drill
a hole in her skull.
If she regains consciousness,
it's increased intracranial pressure.
And if it's the other thing?
She'll die.
But if it's the hypothalamus,
she's dead, anyway.
If the problem is the pressure
in her brain, and I fix it,
is she going to be all better?
No, but it'll give us more time
to figure out what's wrong.
I have to get someone else.
I can't do this.
You love her.
You'd do anything to save her.
Not this.
I can't do this.
If she dies because of something
that I did, then I...
Listen. Listen.
I am not going
to let you hurt her. Okay?
Now, please. This is
her only chance.
Okay-
That was easy.
Okay. Her head is stabilized,
and the drill bit is sterile.
Place the drill bit against the upper
left part of her forehead,
about an inch above the temple.
It's not going anywhere.
Bone's harder than wood.
Lean into it.
The skull is only
a quarter inch thick.
Once you're midway through,
drill in shorter bursts.
If you come out the other side,
you've gone too far.
Okay. Now, what? Now, what?
Let the fluid drain.
She's waking up.
Sean?
What's going on?
South Pole doc
is out of her coma,
and now we have a new symptom.
Increased intracranial
pressure.
Why are we out here?
That's the patient room.
ICP plus kidney problems
plus lung collapse equals...
The most likely suspect
is a tumor throwing off clots.
We ruled out cancer.
But not clots.
What causes blood clots?
Bacterial endocarditis.
Not without a fever.
Deep vein thrombosis
plus an existing PFO.
PFO would have been discovered on her
pre-South Pole physical exam.
What if the clots aren't clots?
Atherosclerosis. Fatty plaque builds up
on the arterial walls.
Pieces break off, block blood flow.
Explains everything.
She has zero risk factors.
Forget fat. Think clots.
No.
- You're standing up to me?
- Maybe.
Just to clarify, you should do that
when you're right.
Sorry for the confusion.
- How could a clot...
- Could be a different kind of fat.
Fat emboli.
It's a perfect fit. Except it's
completely impossible.
Fat emboli requires
an un-repaired bone breakage.
Between the x-ray
and the exam, I've seen her entire...
See, that's what
I'm talking about.
Take off her socks.
I can... I can do it.
No. I got it.
Your toe is broken.
Oh, my God.
Bits of bone marrow have been
leaking into your bloodstream.
Those fat emboli have caused blockages
in your kidney, lungs, and brain.
It doesn't even hurt.
Cold numbs everything.
Does a particularly great job
on the extremities.
You'll need to close the break to stop
the marrow from leaking.
This one you will feel.
Will you do it?
He drilled a hole in your
skull after drinking your pee.
I think he's up for this.
Grab the tip of her toe
with your right hand.
Hold the break with the other.
On the count of three,
pull hard.
One, two,
three.
Splint your toe.
You'll be fine.
Thank you, House.
Don't thank me.
He's the one who saved your life.
He likes her.
A bottle of the Bordeaux
and some sparkling water.
Well, you didn't pick her up,
which means she's coming from work, too,
which means you're
comfortable enough to meet her.
Damn. I thought I lost you
when I walked backwards
through my own
footprints in the snow.
I think I've got it narrowed down
to three possibilities.
Better leave. If you see her,
it'll be cheating.
It's not one of your ex-wives.
Because they hate me.
They don't. They should,
but they don't. I called them.
It's someone new,
but someone I know.
Did you ever consider
being happy for me?
Briefly.
You ordering the wine
before she got here...
Girls are good, House,
and you know it.
You solved your case
because you cared about that girl.
You're demonstrating
the illusion of manly confidence,
which means you haven't
closed the deal, yet.
I closed the deal.
I just like her.
Still?
You knew your patient
hated having cold feet,
because you did a physical exam,
because you liked her.
Your theory is I cared,
therefore I let her keep her socks on.
If that's what love is, then I don't
wanna have anything to do with it.
It starts with warm feet,
but leads to other things.
Your mom and I will explain
when you're older.
If I'd made her take them off like I
should have, I'd have seen the toe
and solved the case days ago.
But you don't care about her.
Of course not.
House doesn't care about anyone.
Hi.
Sorry I'm late.
Cutthroat Bitch?
I call her Amber.
Was she on your list?