It's cold.
Good. Thank you.
There's a new girl
at the ice cream store.
She doesn't seem too fond
of buttoning her top button.
Let's go check her out.
What are we
supposed to be doing?
It's almost 4:00.
You got somewhere to be?
We know he likes
to manipulate people.
He's probably testing us.
To find out what?
How long we can
look stupid for?
He said he'd be here by 3:00.
He's obviously not coming.
- I'm going home.
- Nobody follow her.
She Pied Pipered nine people
right out of a job last week.
Would you mind holding
my metaphor for a second?
New patient, 37-year-old male.
Suffers from severe
ascending muscle weakness.
- Why are you late?
- To see who'd put up with it.
So, if we'd have left,
we would have been fired?
I was going to fire
whoever stuck around,
but since
everyone stuck around...
28% curvature of the spine
has caused reduced lung capacity
and he has reduced
the bone mineral density.
The patient has
spinal muscular atrophy.
It's genetic, incurable.
This is not
a diagnostic mystery.
You have just given
the state secrets to the enemy.
- What enemy?
- New patient, new rules.
Today, you're going to
split yourselves into two teams.
The first to figure out what's
threatening to deprive the patient
of the 20 or so
miserable years he's got left
with SMA
gets to keep their jobs.
Take off your numbers.
You look stupid.
And I think I know
who you are by now.
Wait, how do you
want us to split up?
Good question,
Overly Excited Former Foster Kid.
There's 10 of you. I was thinking
six against six? No, wait.
How about women versus men?
Excellent suggestion, Fat Twin.
More interesting
than evens versus odds.
Less interesting
than shirts against skins.
If your sex organs dangle,
you're the Confederates.
If your sex organs are aesthetically
pleasing, you're the Yanks.
Dr. House?
I'd like to be on the men's team.
Do your sex organs dangle,
Cutthroat Bitch?
Not yet.
You've never hired more
than one female
on your team before.
If you're going to
purge an entire gender
it isn't going
to be the danglers.
Sounds logical, if you don't think
about it for more than three seconds.
I just told you that
if the danglers lose, they're out.
So, I can only assume
you're hiding the real reason.
You don't think the women
will be aggressive enough,
will be good enough at science.
They'll be too emotional.
Can I switch teams?
If the danglers are okay,
I'm okay.
- We're not okay.
- I get it.
You don't like me because maybe
I'm a little bit competitive.
Manipulative.
"Cutthroat Bitch"
is your official title.
It's a game. You can either play
for fun or play to win.
If you want to win,
you want "Cutthroat".
No, thank you.
First thing we have to
do is get inside his head.
It's not psychological.
I'm not talking about the patient,
I'm talking about House.
He's insane,
but he's not irresponsible.
He wouldn't be playing this game
if he didn't already know the answer.
The first thing we do
is gang-bang the sucker.
There's five of us.
We can run dozens of tests.
We don't need a theory.
We just need brute force.
What about the assist dog?
Picks bacteria-infested things up
with its bacteria-infested mouth,
hands them over to the guy...
It's not the dog, wouldn't be fair.
- To who?
- Whom.
The men.
House knows I used to be a vet.
If the dog's the answer,
they'd be at a handicap.
What about the dog?
Assist dogs put
everything in their mouth.
Money, doorknobs...
- Great.
- That's not what I said.
- Why do you think a low sodium...
- I don't.
Patient took a trip to Thailand
two weeks ago.
Hey, write bigger and angle the board
more so they can see it.
This is wrong.
It's only wrong
if they cheat off us.
And if they cheat off us,
they're wrong.
They're not cheating,
but one of them is moving.
Hey. Stop playing with your sutures
or I'll have to re-do them.
Why do you guys keep a D-cell battery
in a urine specimen cup?
Because we pulled it
from a patient's intestine.
Why would somebody
swallow a battery?
Why do you assume
it was swallowed?
Bed five needs a bag
of Ringer's lactate.
Would have been worse
if he'd used a nine-volt.
Who said it was a "he"?
False assumptions. You're good.
You're trying to get me
to think like him.
And you're trying to kiss my ass.
Why are you talking to me?
Because House is turning patient care
into a game. It's dangerous.
The patient's going to suffer.
Maybe die.
Wow! You really need a shave.
See what I did there?
Whoa.
Interesting.
I need a crash cart in here!
I didn't do it.
When a person faints,
it's because they're
not getting enough blood
to their brain.
The act of falling
corrects the problem.
You faint again strapped into
that power chair where you can't fall,
you might not wake up.
Killed by an assistive device?
At least my death would be ironic.
I think when you
went to Thailand,
you picked up a threadworm
called strongyloides.
They usually go up
through your feet.
I didn't do a lot of walking
on the beach.
But I assume you did have someone
lay you down in the sand.
Bare back, bare legs increases
exposure tenfold over bare feet.
Two pills.
You'll be all better.
Can I have some water
for those, please?
Hey, take a number!
House didn't say anything
about taking turns.
What's she testing you for?
Don't. They'll spend all day
obsessing over my idea
instead of coming up
with one of their own.
And, hey, I might be wrong.
Seriously.
I'm worried that if we don't know
what she's given you,
there could be conflicts.
No, you're not.
House told me
he's keeping track of all that.
Ten doctors.
I should be getting ten cures.
We need blood, hair, and stool.
You poop and then you use the wooden
sticks to collect the fecal matter,
then rub it on the green box.
Hand it to my dog.
Only one of those things
I can do on my own.
And the last couple of days,
I haven't been doing that.
Is it all right with you
if we carry you into the bathroom?
If you want me there, that's the way
you're going to have to do it.
Okay-
- Ready?
- Mmm-hmm.
One, two, three.
Can I get a little head support, please?
Thank you.
Why are you here?
My offices are being used
by my teams.
Teams?
Which means this is the only place
where you can yell at me.
You have "teams"?
Two of them.
I wanted to deal
with the yelling today
because I noticed
what you were wearing,
and I wouldn't have to listen
all that closely.
You can't make a competition
out of patient care.
Without competition,
we'd still be single cell organisms.
- Can I go now?
- Not until after the yelling.
What's wrong with him?
I have seven of
the finest minds on it.
Along with three very special...
You wouldn't be doing this
unless you already knew.
I tell you, you tell them.
Game's over.
If you know,
you are obligated to treat...
Well, then, in that case,
I don't know.
Why would a guy voluntarily shove
a metal object
into an electrical socket?
I'm getting closer and closer
to knowing the answer.
What would happen
if I shut down this game?
I'd fire them all,
hire 40 new fellowship applicants
and start the game
all over again.
You do know what's
wrong with him, right?
It would be pretty irresponsible
if I didn't, wouldn't it?
Antibiotics aren't working.
Legionella could
explain the lungs, the fever.
If she had Legionella,
she'd have low sodium.
What can you tell me about her?
She likes body surfing.
Maybe picked up a virus
swimming off Jones Beach.
But she doesn't even have the energy
to finish her crossword anymore.
Her boyfriend said...
That's it.
- What is?
- Blurry vision.
How do you get blurry vision
from not being...
You don't stop a daily ritual
that cures boredom because you're bored.
She stopped doing
her crossword puzzle
because she's having
a hard time reading it.
What causes fever, boggy lungs,
and blurry vision?
Fungal
Aspergillus would explain
the pneumonia,
which explains the fever.
Start her on amphotericin.
Hey, guys. Great job.
If you were going to try to take
yourself out, why choose electricity?
You eat a bullet,
jump off a building...
I love the team thing,
by the way.
Bury yourself alive
in Cuddy's cleavage.
Teamwork, collaboration,
all for the greater good...
It could have been
a suicidal gesture
as opposed to
an actual attempt.
Interestingly,
the rain in Spain doesn't
actually fall
in the plain all that much.
But who puts
their internal organs
on a skillet
just to get attention?
Go ask him.
That would be cheating.
Got a diagnosis yet?
Get out of here.
Got a stool sample yet?
How could you know?
Oh, I talked to a nurse.
Pretty brilliant, huh?
I give you a move House will love
straight from one of his former fellows
and you let me join your team.
You're too late.
We already have our diagnosis.
He's lying because
he wants you to go away.
So do I.
How do we know
you're not a double agent?
Find out what we're thinking
then go back to the women.
Because I don't care
what you're thinking.
You want to know why
I want to be on your team?
Because you're idiots.
If I can get the women
out of the competition, I'm in.
And so are two of you.
So what's the big move?
It's called xenodiagnosis.
We let these bugs bite you,
then we test their feces for parasites.
Why can't you test my feces?
Because you've been chugging
milk of magnesia for the past hour.
You've got a lot going in
and nothing coming out.
Testing the bugs' feces is actually
more accurate than testing yours.
Smaller haystack,
easier to find the needle.
You okay? Get the bugs off him.
- Get the bugs off him!
- The test isn't done.
He's choking!
Patchy infiltrates
on the X-ray, but patient
improved with chest PT and oxygen,
consistent with aspiration.
So, now we have
another symptom to explain.
Why does his throat think
his lungs are his stomach?
And why are your
throats closing up?
Shouldn't we be in separate rooms?
You think I'm going to run
two differentials
at this time in the morning?
Grumpy, you're first.
I'm not grumpy.
Well, why would I call you that
if you weren't?
It's an unusual combination.
Unusual equals
exotic equals foreign.
It has to be connected
to his trip to Thailand.
You practice medicine overseas?
I was with Doctors Without Borders
for eight years.
- Ta-da!
- It's in my file.
David Blaine hides
the six of hearts in a beer bottle.
It's still impressive.
- You like exotic. Why are you here?
- I want this job.
Parent sick?
No. I... I just...
This is not the job you want.
This is the job
in the zip code you want.
You engaged?
Yes.
Ta-da!
Am I not allowed to grow up
and change my priorities?
You're allowed to.
People usually don't.
This is not a new symptom.
Our patient has
spinal muscular atrophy.
He has documented trouble swallowing.
The choking is not new.
So, if it's nothing new,
what caused the old?
Strongyloides worms explain
the fainting. We already treated...
So, he's all better,
woman who... Thirteen.
He hasn't gotten any worse.
That's a pretty passive approach
for the daughter of an alcoholic.
Wrong again.
We could stress his system,
put him on a tilt table.
If he stays conscious, it means
we made the right diagnosis and we win.
Then, why haven't you?
Six against four.
One of the men is going
to have to join the women's team.
On the other hand,
one of the men isn't
an actual doctor,
so I guess it's pretty fair.
Men, you're in the penalty box.
Who's not the doctor?
Glad you asked about that.
The reason I'm penalizing you
is time management.
In diagnostics,
you're always working against the clock.
The women came up with a theory
and they treated the patient.
You guys just
sat around in a lab,
hoping a series of blind tests
would give you a theory.
You wasted the patient's time.
Now, I'm going to waste yours.
Her gums are turning yellow.
Whatever it is,
it's in her liver now.
Fungal fit perfectly.
We were wrong.
And we're going to keep being wrong
until we're right.
Or until she dies.
Yeah. That was very helpful.
Need a team to tell me
we're mortals.
Look. I'm sorry. You're right.
Doesn't hurt to be reminded that
we're dealing with real stakes, here.
Liver failure is a bad thing,
but it's also a clue.
What does it tell us?
I can't let you leave
if I think you're still suicidal.
I wasn't trying to off myself.
No, that's right, you were
just trying to kill the wall.
I check this box,
and your next roommates
are going to be
Jesus and Crazy McLoonybin.
That guy never had a chance.
It's going to sound stupid.
Suddenly, you're shy?
You pooped your
pants in front of me.
It's one of the nasty
side effects of dying.
Last Saturday
I got in a car crash.
A drunk driver came over the line
and hit me, head on.
It was like slow motion.
I saw these headlights,
then,
I saw...
Paramedics said I was
technically dead for 97 seconds.
It was the best 97 seconds
of my life.
Okay, here's what happened.
Your oxygen-deprived brain
was shutting down.
A flood of endorphins
and serotonin was released.
That's what gave you the visions.
No. Believe me.
It wasn't chemicals.
I've done every hallucinogenic
there is.
This was way bigger than that.
There's something out there.
Something more.
Hey, can I have my knife back?
Nope.
Who the hell isn't a doctor?
House said we can't talk.
He meant we can't talk about the case.
House is just jerking us around.
That's what he does.
You're not curious.
Only one reason
you wouldn't be curious.
We should talk about the case.
He's punishing us for wasting time.
Maybe we shouldn't
be wasting this time.
Close that door.
You're going to get us all fired.
We need to find a link
between fainting and trouble swallowing.
We need to know if it's dysphagia
or full-blown achalasia.
Paraganglioma.
How would a nee-plastic growth
in his abdomen explain...
Not his abdomen. In his neck.
A carotid body tumor
causes trouble swallowing.
Food presses against the vagus nerve
and causes the fainting.
So, if this guy has cancer,
we get to keep our jobs.
If he's healthy, we're fired.
We need a CT to prove it.
And we need the women not to
figure it out while we're sitting here.
And does House's computer
have a built-in microphone?
There is a potential toxicity
with an experimental treatment.
I was never here.
Blood pressure is remaining stable
through 60 degrees.
No pauses on his EKG, no nausea.
Our treatment worked.
I need our patient.
Syncope's cured, Amber.
It's over.
You obviously haven't stressed
his system hard enough.
You crank it up high enough,
anyone will pass out.
This is incredible!
This is the most
I've moved in 20 years.
The tilt table test
showed that the patient's EKG,
BP and pulse
remained normal, despite...
Who are you, Thirteen?
My name's in the file.
The fact that you won't
answer my questions
tells me more about you
than answers could.
No, it doesn't.
We turned the thing up
to 95 degrees...
You don't think that non-answers
tell me anything?
Sure. Just not as much
as actual answers.
That's why they're called answers.
They tell me
you're hiding something.
Tells you
I'm hiding everything.
Tells me you've got something
worth hiding.
Was it Turkish prison?
Gay porn?
You killed a man just 'cause he was
asking too many questions?
Can I finish reporting on the patient?
No need.
See you in an hour or so.
Got to set some stuff up.
Thank you all for coming
to tribal council.
A man of your integrity,
I feel I can trust, Big Love.
And I don't call you that
'cause you're a Mormon.
Where's your team's sixth man?
She went rogue.
Broke the rules.
You also sinned. You have no right
to cast the first stone.
And atheists have no right
to quote scripture.
The rules said, "No talking."
I told them not to talk.
Out loud.
We were trying to save a man's life.
Key word being "trying".
Tilt table test confirmed
that you guys were wrong.
You're fired.
The prodigal son returneth.
You're also fired.
We thought there was a tumor
on the patient's esophagus.
We were right about the area,
wrong about the diagnosis.
Turns out the esophagus
is just straightening. It's scleroderma.
Explains the syncope
and the choking.
He needs steroids.
You did a CT scan?
- Obviously.
- After you were already proven wrong?
Good for you.
It's too bad you're wrong.
Straightening indicates weakening,
not hardening.
SMA explains the weakening.
Strongyloides infection
explains everything else.
You ladies have the honor
to give the patient a feeding tube.
Discharge him.
Show up for work tomorrow.
The rest of you...
You're a disappointment.
You make me
want to stop dangling.
It was the best
two weeks of my life.
I think I will miss you most of all,
Ridiculously Old Fraud.
Do you think
House could be wrong?
I thought he fired you.
No. He fired the men.
I don't think he's wrong.
If he is, how would I prove it?
I just said
I don't think he is.
Well, thinking
isn't good enough.
You have to run a blood test
for anticentromere antibodies.
Would you mind
running the labs?
You can't.
Well, I can, but...
No, I was making a statement.
You've been fired.
So, you no longer
have lab privileges.
You weren't
coming here for advice.
You were coming here
to con a favor to save your job.
Sorry. I'm not working
for him anymore,
but he can still
make my life miserable.
And you have a chance
to make his life miserable.
I'm insulted.
You conned Cameron by
appealing to her humanity...
I told her what
she wanted to hear.
And you told me
what you thought I wanted to hear.
If it's any consolation, I think
your motives are more interesting.
I cannot believe he fired you.
Go draw his blood.
I'll meet you in the lab
when I'm done here.
Guess you didn't find your tumor.
The other doctors tell
you that you were fine?
Yeah, in the sense it's just
my disease getting worse.
You come to terms
with this disease.
You know it's there.
You know it's waiting.
And every now and again
it takes something away.
Took my walking.
Took my modesty.
Now, it's taking one
of my last pleasures.
Well, there's an outside shot
that something
other than the SMA
is causing your
eating problems.
And if it is, we can fix it,
remove that tube.
Is that my blood? It's green.
What does that mean?
It means I'm not fired.
Is he a Vulcan?
If no, what makes
Nimoy bleed green?
Are we officially un-fired?
How do we know she didn't fake
the green blood?
'Cause that would be stupid.
And while she may be manipulative,
borderline evil, shallow...
They get it. I'm not stupid.
What contrast did
you use for the CT?
- ICM.
- His kidneys aren't working.
They didn't filter the contrast,
which, in ICM, is green.
Ten points.
Okay, let's add kidney failure
to our list of symptoms.
What are these points?
Is that how you're deciding who to fire?
I'm going to fire the next person
who asks me who I'm going to fire.
Now we're on the point system?
What happened to
men against women?
Forget the game.
What do you mean,
forget the game?
I mean, forget the damn game!
This guy's kidneys are failing.
We need to diagnose exactly...
I thought we were diagnosing.
You were diagnosing.
Now, I am, too.
I thought that Thirteen was right
about the strongyloides.
I was obviously wrong.
Okay, kidney failure,
aspiration, fainting. Go.
Kidney failure could be the result
of a gram negative bacteria.
Our patient wears
a catheter full-time.
It virtually guarantees
bacterial infection.
Which could have
migrated up to his kidneys.
Infection stresses his already
weakened system, makes his SMA worse.
That explains
the choking and fainting.
Put him on an IV amp and gent.
Our team's
scleroderma diagnosis still holds.
The test could have
been negative because
the blood was tainted
with the contrast.
Do a skin biopsy.
Get a side of lymph node
to confirm.
I could have you fired.
You already had me fired.
Just proves that I can.
Were the men wrong?
No.
- That doesn't change the fact...
- Why are you yelling at me?
Because performing
tests for someone
who is not a doctor
in this hospital...
You're frustrated.
You want help, I'm here.
If you just need to vent,
leave a message.
I like him better like this.
You?
Patient developed pneumonia.
His lungs are filling fast.
We started him on antibiotics.
Nothing. We were wrong.
And you're here to say?
We were wrong, too.
He doesn't have scleroderma.
Biopsy revealed
no fibrotic changes.
Cervical lymph node
has black flecks.
Just small areas of necrosis.
It's nothing.
You say, "Nothing,"
I say, "Cancer."
It's a bit of a stretch
to jump right to cancer.
I'm not jumping. Broad specs
haven't worked, so ifs not bacterial.
Failing liver despite treatment
suggests it's not fungal.
And her high lactic acidosis
points towards
anaplastic large cell lymphoma.
Also suggests infection, which is
a lot easier and safer to treat.
Large cell lymphoma
is incredibly aggressive.
She'll be dead in a week
if we follow the textbooks.
Unless it's infection,
in which case you irradiate her,
and she'll be dead in a day.
And I know you have
some experience with that.
I've seen
doctors do this before.
Go back to
the scene of the crime,
if you're right this time,
you purge yourself of past ghosts.
I know
it's contrary to protocol.
But I think it's more likely...
Ghosts are there for a reason.
So you don't make
the same mistake twice.
Switch her over
to third-generation cephalosporin.
You want to remove his eye?
Who told you?
You booked the OR.
Good.
You can't beat
me in a foot race.
I thought we were dancing.
Cervical lymph node
is a garbage dump.
A very small one.
Just one truck comes
and it only comes from one home.
Al Gore would be appalled.
The home...
The home is the right eye.
I get it.
Do a biopsy.
On my Way-
You're not doing a biopsy.
You ordered
an orbital exenteration.
Right. Because I don't want to
remove a little, tiny piece,
sit in the lab and confirm
what I already know,
while my patient drowns
in his own fluid.
But if you want me to,
I absolutely will.
How advanced is the pneumonia?
It's taking college courses.
Hey, Wilson!
I'm going to cut
some cripple's eye out!
Want to come watch?
Good times.
We good to go?
I thought melanoma
was skin cancer.
Technically, it's cancer
of the pigment cells.
The same cells that
give your iris its color.
Cancer?
Why not? What else
can God throw at me?
Hail, locusts,
smiting of the first born...
All depends on
how evil you've been.
House.
If it's cancer,
it's spread everywhere, right?
That's what's in my lungs?
My kidneys?
There is a chance, by removing the eye,
to get the primary tumor,
and three courses of radiation,
that could...
Could what?
A few months? Years?
More likely months.
Any of your other doctors
have any cheerier diagnoses?
If they do, they're wrong.
This is the answer.
It's the only way to help you.
I already can't walk.
I can't eat.
You're telling me
that the rest of my life
is in this bed,
puking and pain?
We can manage the pain.
I'd rather just
get this over with.
I've been trapped
in this useless body long enough.
It'd be nice
to finally get out.
Get out and go where?
I mean, you think
you're going to sprout wings
and start flying around
with the other angels?
Don't be an idiot.
There is no "after". There's just this.
House!
You can't let a dying man
take solace in his beliefs?
His beliefs are stupid.
Everybody lies.
Some for good reasons,
some for bad.
This would have been
a fantastic reason to lie.
Hi. Greg House.
Why can't you just let him
have his fairy tale?
If it gives him comfort
to imagine beaches
and loved ones
and life outside a wheelchair...
Are there 72 virgins, too?
It's over.
He's got days,
maybe hours left.
What pain does it cause you if he spends
that time with a peaceful smile?
What sick pleasure
do you get in making
damn sure he's filled
with fear and dread?
He shouldn't be making
a decision based on a lie.
Misery is better than nothing.
You don't know there's nothing.
You haven't been there.
Oh, God,
I am tired of that argument.
I don't have to go to Detroit
to know that it smells.
Yes. Detroit,
the afterlife, same thing.
You're not
getting enough oxygen,
so we're inserting a tube
directly into your lungs.
It should help us drain
some of this excess fluid.
Should make you
a little more comfortable.
SATs are still dropping.
The fluid's clear.
If this was cancer,
there should be blood.
Call House.
He just paged me.
Dr. House!
Maybe it was
just an accident.
It wasn't an accident.
Think his nihilism got the best of him
and he tried to kill himself?
- He paged me.
- He paged you?
- Why you?
- I assume because...
Don't assume anything.
Don't fall into that trap.
Is he okay?
Burned his hand pretty good.
His heart stopped
for nearly a minute.
But your cohort
managed to restart it.
But he has not
regained consciousness.
So, since I have you all here,
we should probably talk
about your actual patient.
Clear fluid from the lungs
indicates that it's probably not cancer.
So it would be nice if we could
come up with a new idea.
You're an idiot.
You nearly killed yourself.
That was the whole idea.
You wanted to kill yourself?
I wanted to nearly kill myself.
Is he better?
No. But he doesn't have cancer.
We think it might be
eosinophilic pneumonia.
Maybe you didn't want to die,
but you didn't care if you lived.
You insisted that I needed
to see for myself.
Was he discharged?
No. He's dying.
You've already had
two near-death experiences.
Not that guy,
the guy in the car accident.
With the knife.
I need to talk to him.
He died almost an hour ago.
Apparently, it's bad
to electrocute yourself
within days of suffering
massive internal injuries.
Why did you need
to talk to him?
Did you see something?
Eosinophilic pneumonia.
House? What did you see?
Nothing.
Whose idea was that?
Brennan.
"Nothing," you don't want
to talk about it, or, "Nothing..."
Which one's Brennan?
Is he the ridiculously old guy?
House, you've got
to talk about this.
If it's aggressive enough
it might have gotten past the steroids.
Start him on cyclophosphamide.
I already did.
Just looking at you hurts.
I'm gonna order up
some extra pain meds.
I love you.
How fast will this work?
New meds should start helping
in minutes, okay? Hang in there.
Vacutainer's full.
I need to replace it.
I don't think it's working.
Try and relax.
You must be wrong.
Stop talking.
Hurry up and get
the chest tube working.
Okay. I got it.
Can you get Hoover?
I can't...
Can you put m)!
Hand
on his head?
It's okay. Don't worry.
I'm not scared.
Oh, God.
Time of death...
You're looking better.
Stark's dead.
What are you doing?
Going to see our patient.
He's dead.
"Dead" is not a diagnosis.
- You really shouldn't be...
- Shut up and give me my cane.
I assume we're all fired.
Should I fire myself, too?
I thought it was strongyloides,
then I thought it was cancer.
- A little help, here?
- Ready? One, two...
Why did you call me?
Because if I pooped myself
in front of Wilson,
I'd never hear the end of it.
But why not one of the others?
You always have that phone
in your hand.
We all have cell phones,
that's not the reason. What is?
If I died,
you'd never get the job.
I knew you wouldn't
let that happen.
You don't think anybody else
has any reason to care?
I think this is starting
to come back to me.
It's right, left, then repeat.
Yeah. That works.
What did we miss?
If we knew,
he wouldn't be dead.
So, that's it?
You're just gonna give up?
No. We were defeated.
It's over.
Patient presented with syncope.
We thought it was thread worms,
gave him invermectin.
Thank you.
The patient seemed better
until his blood turned green.
Can we at least
remove the body before
launching into a purely
academic exercise?
The patient didn't respond
to antibiotics or steroids.
You okay, boy?
What's wrong with the dog?
He's dead.
There are only
a handful of viruses
that can cross
between dogs and humans.
But they may not
be connected at all.
The dog was old.
I've seen it before.
They hang on way past
their normal life expectancy
to take care of their masters.
Did you watch
him take the pills?
The invermectin.
Did you watch the patient
put them in his mouth
and swallow them?
I don't know. I think so.
What kind of dog is that?
English Shepherd.
- That's in the collie family, right?
- Not really.
- But they share the MDR-1 gene?
- Yeah.
What happens when you give a dog
with the MDR-1 gene ivermectin?
They don't.
I mean, it's used to treat
heartworms in most dogs,
but it would be
fatal if they...
Look familiar?
I think the last
time you saw it,
it didn't have
that dead dog's teeth marks on it.
I just put it on the bed tray
to get him some water.
When I asked you if you watched
the patient swallow the pills,
the right answer was, "No."
Take his body
down to the morgue.
If you hadn't treated this patient
as a game, he wouldn't be dead.
Feeling much better, thank you.
I'm supposed to
show you sympathy?
He died while his attending
was lying on a hospital bed
because he stuck
a knife in a wall socket.
He died because
a doctor made a mistake.
She was an idiot.
You employed her.
You're responsible.
Dr. Foreman.
How's she doing?
Fever's gone. AST and ALT are back
within normal range.
She should be out
of here in a few days.
Gutsy call.
- Thanks.
- It wasn't a compliment.
If you were wrong,
she'd be dead.
- I was sure...
- No, you weren't. You couldn't be.
There's a reason we have rules.
If every doctor did whatever
his gut told him was right,
we'd have a lot more dead bodies
to deal with.
It won't happen again.
Yes, it will.
Because you confuse saving her life
with doing the right thing.
I'm sorry, Dr. Foreman,
you're fired.
As soon as the pathologist
cut into the lungs,
we saw the threadworms.
Do you think it's
fair that I fired
all the other members
of your team
when you guys actually came up
with the right diagnosis?
I keep replaying it in my mind.
Did I drop the pills
when I put them on the bed tray?
Did I knock them over
when I turned to leave?
You know, he'd be alive.
His dog would be alive.
I know.
You forced us to act
on a false assumption.
- I know.
- Everything we built
from that step on,
every test, every theory,
every treatment...
I know. Forget the lecture
and fire me already.
If I was gonna fire you,
I wouldn't be giving you the lecture.
I know you're not gonna let
anything like this ever happen again.
I'll see you tomorrow.
I'm sorry to say,
I told you so.