There were some
nice guys there,
but they're all so quiet,
awkward smiles and sweaty palms.
I'm not expecting Brad Pitt
to walk into St. Theresa's,
just someone who makes me laugh,
has a nice smile, full head of hair.
You know, someone like you,
Mr. Franklin.
It's a shame they're
going to cremate you.
Can I help you?
Martin!
My purse is right there.
Go ahead, take whatever you want.
Irene, you call me?
Irene?
Irene!
How are you doing?
I'm fine.
FYI, if you ask me,
it's more the guys' fault than yours.
And House isn't
blameless, either.
If he hadn't pitted us all
against each other...
It was my fault. My mistake.
Was that always there?
Hello?
Sure.
It's House.
Good morning, angels.
As you will see from the file,
we have quite the interesting case.
It's not often you get a patient
who sees dead people.
What file?
What the hell?
I gave it to Bosley
a half-hour ago.
It was not a half-hour,
it was 10 minutes.
And he made copies
of the ER records first.
Less lip, more whip.
I only agreed to take this case
because you said that this mocha
frapalicious would have whip on it.
Fine. I'll refer
the case to Foreman.
Can't. Mercy fired him.
- Gimme.
- He got fired?
He disobeyed a superior officer under
fire. He's lucky he wasn't executed.
How do you know about it?
You keeping tabs on him?
Girls talk.
When Bosley drags
his ancient ass in there...
I'm here.
Twenty-four year old funeral cosmetician
suffered a grand mal seizure at work.
Why does he get to be Bosley?
You want to be Bosley?
Bosley's, like,
the asexual messenger boy.
She had a vision of being raped
by a cadaver before passing out.
Seizure rules out
psychiatric illness.
No history of epilepsy,
head trauma or drug use.
Bosley keeps his job while they replace
five angels over three seasons.
Could be a tumor
to the temporal lobe.
Not with a normal CT scan.
You mean, it appeared normal
to the doc in the ER.
Way to get right back
on that horse, Thirteen.
No, that was Amber.
Nice try, Cutthroat Bitch.
That was the worst Thirteen imitation
I've ever heard.
Funeral home prep rooms
are filled with toxic chemicals.
And cadavers. Everybody in that place
obviously died from something.
I have a question.
Is he the one who's not a doctor?
Bullets aren't contagious,
but infections, parasites...
You said one of us wasn't a doctor,
and you called him a fraud.
He's not a doctor.
Continue, Bos.
Could be an STD.
Why isn't he fired?
You're breaking up.
Going into a tunnel.
Dark Religious Nut.
What did you call me?
I'm sorry.
What do you people
want to be called this week?
Cole.
No, I'm never gonna
remember that.
Take Bosley and the other
visible minority to the funeral home.
The rest of you young, white people,
the world is your oyster.
Do an MRI with contrast,
EEG, LP and a blood panel.
And, angels, be careful.
Just because he's religious,
doesn't mean he won't kick your ass.
- You want to bet?
- No.
I want you to stop being
such a jerk to him.
$100.
Smart call. The guy's a wuss.
He'll be the next one
on the train.
Define "kick your ass."
Any physical confrontation?
Or verbal?
Define verbal.
Anything over 70 decibels.
And you can't start
suddenly being nice to him.
You realize what you're
encouraging here.
Yeah. Someone kicking your ass.
The space inside
is smaller than I thought.
Don't worry, Reena.
The doctors are gonna
take good care of you, right?
Once the Valium kicks in
you'll feel better.
And then we'll have
some nice, warm milk when you're done.
I'd rather have more Valium.
Oh, Reena!
Let's wait just a bit,
see how it goes.
Try to lie as still
as possible.
Guess Father Time's
a lock for one of the spots.
Thirteen's a lock.
He doesn't have a medical license
and he's still around.
She killed a guy
in a wheelchair and his dog.
He doesn't care about
our qualifications, our ideas,
he just wants to have fun.
And she's the ultimate fun,
because he can't figure her out.
This game is insane.
So quit. Happy to
lose the competition.
If it's gonna be on your résumé, it's
got to be better to quit than get fired.
Either quit or shut up.
Actually, with House,
getting fired might look better.
Dr. House
is a dangerous egomaniac.
That's why I left. We had
different ideas on how to practice.
Glad to hear it.
Tell me about Mercy.
To be honest, I don't think
Dr. Schaffer really gave me a chance.
Obviously not.
You were there for three weeks.
What happened?
I saved a patient's life.
That's usually not
grounds for dismissal.
Have you spoken to her?
Yes.
Then why are you asking me
what happened?
You have an excellent résumé.
I felt I owed it to you
to hear what you had to say.
What did she tell you?
That you defied her instructions
and hospital procedures.
That's what happened,
nothing more I can add to that.
You could tell me
that you were wrong.
Sounds like you didn't
leave House quite soon enough.
Cadavers were clean,
so is her food.
It's all organic, unprocessed crap.
It's got to be the embalming fluid.
Ethanol can have
psychoactive effects and...
Bosley, tell whoever's talking
that he's an idiot.
Bosley?
Either tell him he's an idiot,
or tell me why I'm wrong.
You're an idiot.
You actually think
that I'd take a patient
who had a seizure in a funeral home,
if the ER hadn't already ruled out
- embalming fluid?
- I thought we weren't supposed to...
Idiot!
From the old French, idiots,
meaning effeminate,
mentally deficient Moor.
I found something
in the mortuary's files from '05.
A 48-year-old male's cause of death
was listed as pneumonia,
but the symptoms
in the autopsy report didn't fit.
Confusion, memory loss,
depression...
Mad cow. Very cool.
No, she's a vegetarian and only
ate organic vegetables, at that.
Tell him he's an idiot again.
The disease can be
spread by brain tissue.
Which is very cool.
Run with it.
So, because the answer
might be cool,
you want us to do a brain biopsy
on a 24-year-old woman?
No, because the answer
is something cool,
I want you to do a brain biopsy
on a 48-year-old dead guy.
The guy's already been buried.
We dig him up.
I'm not digging up a body
without a court order.
Don't think of it as
digging up a body.
Think of it as keeping
another one from being buried.
I can't do it.
Are we gonna have another one
of those ecumenical discussions
where I tell you that your beliefs
are ridiculous and you totally cave?
I just got to be home at 6:00.
The Sabbath.
The Lord works for six days,
then tells the union he needs a rest.
You know, if I was all-powerful
I think I'd take at least two days.
It's Thursday.
Well, then it must be the kid.
You have oatmeal on your pants.
Do you have a camera in here?
Nope, I was guessing.
He had oatmeal on his pants yesterday
and the day before.
Have one of your wives
look after the spawn.
I'm a single dad.
Where's the single mom?
I have no idea.
Interesting.
You claim a lapse of judgment,
or are you gonna admit that
a lapse in judgment is a lapse in faith?
He's gone.
Fair enough.
Family comes first.
Dr. Cuddy? I'm Amber Volakis,
one of Dr. House's new fellows.
Sexual harassment claims
go through HR,
stress-related leaves
through workers comp,
and any accusations
of criminal activities
go directly to the
Princeton-Plainsboro police department.
Actually, I was wondering if you needed
any extra help in the clinic tonight.
You're not gonna score any points
with House by kissing my ass.
Understood, but I hear
Dr. House hates clinic duty.
If he were to hear through the grapevine
that I was willing to work overtime,
take some of it off his hands...
My advice to you is to do
whatever House wants you to do tonight.
And then tomorrow night
you can come back
and I will give you
extra clinic duty.
Does everybody around here
have trust issues?
I don't know what House wants you to do
and I don't want to know.
But if you really have
a problem with it, quit now.
It's only gonna get worse.
All right. Who's up?
Not me.
You haven't done
any digging yet.
I'm a surgeon.
If anything happens to these hands,
I'm screwed.
Let Bosley do it.
As long as he can keep
folding laundry,
his career...
Someone's coming.
Hey, shouldn't we be running?
If it's a cop, run.
Security guard,
I say we take him down.
Sorry I'm late.
Where the hell have you been?
I got lost.
We've been here
over three hours.
Really lost.
I brought coffee and donuts.
So, Thirteen,
you grow up around here?
We're digging up a grave
and you want to chit-chat?
I'm just making conversation.
It's what people do.
Why are you hiding everything?
And I'm asking you that question
because you're hiding everything.
There's something
seriously wrong with you.
I'm worried.
No, you're not.
Fine, but I am freaked,
because I don't think you're a freak.
I think you're doing this on purpose
because you know
House will be intrigued.
Yeah, I grew up around here.
Honey, I'm home.
Get the crowbar.
No, there's not enough room
to maneuver a crowbar down here.
Oh, God help us.
What the hell?
What is it?
Ankles. They buried the guy
the wrong way around.
The doctors' lounge
is covered in mud.
Thirteen and Cutthroat Bitch
had a disagreement.
Cafeteria was out of Jell-O.
There were pickaxes.
Either you had them dig up a body,
or you're building a rail road.
A little, tiny piece of his brain.
Seemed a waste.
He wasn't using it anymore.
That's your defense?
"We just dismembered him."
They're looking for
Creutzfeldt-Jakob.
You get the results yet?
Does my breath smell
bated to you?
Yes. Let me know
when you hear anything.
And get that mess in
the shower area cleaned up.
I know just the guy.
How many of them
agreed to dig up a grave?
Six. But don't worry, the one
who didn't, didn't stand on principle.
He just had a diaper to change.
I really think there are
no bad choices in this group.
You guys don't wipe your feet
when you come in the house?
Doctors' lounge, let's go.
Why me?
Well, I can't ask the black guy
or one of the chicks to do it.
That would be insensitive.
And you can't ask Bosley
because that'd look like you only hired
the non-doctor to do non-doctor stuff.
You keep stalling,
you're still gonna clean up,
but I won't let you
have the mop.
Sample came back negative
for Creutzfeldt-Jakob.
Well, that discussion
didn't last long.
I just don't know
what else there is.
We had an idea, it was wrong.
Well, we could go home.
I mean, we have no idea
what's wrong with her,
which means it could be
completely benign.
Or, on the off chance
that it's killing her,
we could take it again from the top.
You've already done everything.
We may have missed something.
I just want to go home.
I'm sure I'm fine now.
Reena, the doctors know best.
You had some
serious symptoms...
If I have another one,
I'll come right back. Okay?
If you have it
while you're driving...
You can drive me,
make sure I take it easy.
Who can?
My mother.
Your mother's here?
What are you talking about?
She's right there.
You sampled every bodily fluid,
peeked in her brain, violated
a cadaver's privacy, dug up a body,
but missed the fact
that she was still seeing
things that weren't there.
Neurological symptoms
are getting worse.
It'd be nice if one of you
angels/morons had a clue why.
We did a full history.
She never mentioned seeing
or hearing anything unusual.
Well, as long as she never
said anything, how were you to know?
Same thing with the spinal fluid?
She tell you that was fine?
The labs were all clear.
Then either we're about
to meet the Alpha and Omega,
or you missed something.
We missed the new symptom.
It's not a new symptom.
We always knew she had hallucinations.
Seeing your dead mother's
a hallucination.
Not knowing she's dead
is a delusion.
You keep this up, you're gonna have
to start wearing sexier clothes.
Carbon monoxide could also cause
delusions. A lot of haunted houses...
There's no headache,
no tachycardia.
I guess they didn't cover that
at your medical school.
What about a hereditary connection?
I mean, she's 24.
Her mother died
when she was 25.
In Ukraine, 20 years ago.
Good luck trying to get those records.
So we start new records.
Test for every hereditary disease
that fits the symptoms.
There are at least 40 different
mitochondrial disorders,
another couple hundred...
Start with amyloidosis and you
keep going until you reach zamyloidosis.
Now what are you testing for?
Or should I ask
what you are not testing for?
Well, we could narrow it down
if you could remember
what your mother died from.
My mother is not dead.
She's sitting right there.
Do you think
we're lying to you?
Leave it alone.
Convincing her that her mother's dead
isn't gonna make her better,
just miserable.
You lose your mother?
Do you think we're trying to trick you?
Why would we do that?
Because you're mean,
and you're not good at your job.
Reena, stop.
You're being cruel.
They're wasting time,
doing exactly what the guy
in the wheelchair said they'd do.
A guy in a wheelchair was here?
You know who I'm talking about.
He's been hanging around
ever since they brought me in,
complaining about
how incompetent everyone is.
He said you killed his dog.
It doesn't make any sense.
I'm not interested.
If you weren't interested,
you wouldn't be here.
I thought it was social.
No, you didn't.
You always think there's an agenda.
That's why I left.
That's why you're good.
- You need a job.
- I'll find a job.
- I need someone that understands House.
- They'll learn.
I need someone that can control House.
Keep looking.
It might take a while.
I'll cut the salary
of everyone else on the team 15%,
give it to you.
That's more than you'll
get anywhere else.
What does House say about this?
You're the one person
on the team that he always respected.
This restaurant is 20 minutes out of
your way, half an hour out of mine.
You picked it to make sure
House didn't drop in on us.
It's my decision, not his.
You tell him that, then run back to your
office while I get to deal with him.
I left for a reason.
That reason hasn't changed.
So,
what's the news?
Everything's negative so far.
Yes. Why wait to finish
before reporting to me?
I have things to do, you know.
She's seeing someone else.
That's not news, that's olds.
Damn it. Why did God design
the human body this way?
A guy in a wheelchair.
In a hospital? That's enough
to give you the heebie-jeebies.
He had a dog.
She's seeing Stark, our last patient.
Well, if it's Stark,
he wouldn't be haunting a patient,
he'd be haunting the doctor
who killed him.
She probably just overheard
someone talking about it, or...
Probably?
You think there's a possibility
that the alternative is true?
- No.
- Then go away.
We're wasting time. We ran 32 gels,
we could run 100 more.
Without knowing how
her mother died...
You're gonna have
to run 100 more.
By you, of course,
I'm only referring to the people
who care enough about human life
to put in a full day.
You want to carpool?
How do you expect me
to respond to this stuff?
Exactly like you just did.
I have a theory.
Maybe you can help me out.
Black Mormon means masochist,
means kinky.
I'm thinking that someone got hurt
making the bastard. Am I right?
You leave my son out of this.
I wasn't referring to your kid's
hypocrisy. I was referring to yours.
Why don't we just ask her
how she died?
Because she won't tell us.
She thinks her mother's still alive.
I don't mean ask the patient.
I mean, ask her mother.
Cool.
Come on.
What the hell does that mean?
You guys talking
your own language now?
I'm sorry. I'll try to include
some visual aids next time.
Now, what?
I'm Dr. House.
Ls your mom around?
Why should I tell you?
You're just gonna tell me
I'm lying or crazy.
I'm not gonna do that. I really
need to know what she has to say.
What do you want?
When you were young, was she...
No, not you. Him.
The man in the wheelchair?
No. He's old.
Actually, looks like you.
Yeah, that's Grandpa House.
Tell him to call back
on a landline.
Terrible reception in here.
How much pain was your mom in?
It's Walter.
He says his name is Walter.
Can I help you?
My patient's talking to
my Grandpa Walt.
You have a Grandpa Walt?
Nope.
Which is what made me suspect
that maybe she's not actually seeing
into the afterlife.
What is this sudden obsession
with the afterlife?
My only obsession is with the idiots
in the right-here-and-now life
who think there's an afterlife.
- And you want me to...
- Nothing.
Just needed a place to hang low for
a while. I'm pretending to be spooked.
Because?
Because if my soon-to-be-brain-dead
patient thinks that I believe her,
maybe she'll let me chat
with her mother's ghost.
The one you don't
believe exists.
Exactly.
The ghost is a hallucination,
which is the result of a delusion,
which most likely is the result
of a hereditary disease
that her mother died from
when the patient was four.
And you think you can
tap into her subconscious memory
by tapping into
her hallucination.
Mmm-hmm.
She might not know
what caused her mother's death,
but she will know
how she acted before she died.
You're quite impressed with yourself
right now, aren't you?
Who wouldn't be?
Well, that should
be long enough.
Back in a flash.
Take your time.
Is my grandfather still here?
No.
He should be right back.
He just went
to get some warm milk.
But your mom's still
here, right?
Yes, of course.
I know she's fine, now, but when
you were four or five, she got sick.
No.
You sure?
She wasn't in any pain?
I wasn't in pain.
No, she was just tired.
And sometimes
she would stay in bed all day.
Did she ever fall down?
Of course.
Everyone falls down
once in a while.
Sometimes, not that often.
How often?
Maybe it was actually
more than once in a while.
Remember that time
in the bathroom?
Mmm.
A few times.
Once she hit her head
on the bathroom sink.
There was blood all over the floor.
I got it on my sweater. I...
They took her away.
Yeah, to the place
where the doctor made her better.
But before that,
what about her arms and legs?
Did she ever walk funny,
like, sort of bent over?
I thought that was from
growing up on the farm!
What about her hands?
Did she ever have any difficulty
sewing, buttoning a shirt?
No.
But sometimes
my hands would shiver.
Like I was cold, but I wasn't.
I never quite understood.
She used to get the shivers.
Like she was cold.
Start her on L-dopa
and bromocriptine.
It's just Parkinson's.
Cole, how's it going
with your patient?
Still seeing stuff.
I hear House is
treating you like crap.
He treats everyone badly.
Yeah, but I heard
you're special.
Well, I can handle it.
Maybe you shouldn't. He's gonna
walk all over you if you let him.
That says nothing
about me, just him.
House respects people
who aren't afraid of him.
Get in his face.
Yell, if you have to.
I don't need his respect.
You do if you want the job.
Thanks for the advice.
You have to hold still.
I'm trying!
- Damn! Hold her down!
- No!
- Stop it!
- Let me do it.
No, no.
Hold her down!
No! No!
No!
Irene?
You stabbed me.
You were having a nightmare.
It wasn't real.
My arm is bleeding.
No. It's okay now,
your arm's not...
Lesions aren't explained
by Parkinson's.
Any theories?
What, ghost got your tongue?
I'm fine.
What about vasculitis?
MRI didn't indicate
any cerebral ischemia.
But she has shown some focal weakness,
urinary retention.
Yes. Those are her big
mystery symptoms,
not the hallucinations
that vasculitis doesn't explain.
Unless it's retinal vasculitis.
House, this guy may be smart, and I'm
sure he's great to share a beer with,
but if he doesn't know that
visual symptoms are an electrical issue,
not vascular,
two separate systems...
So are the banks and the power grid,
but if I don't pay my bills
my lights go out.
Vasculitis restricts blood flow to
nerves, messes with electrical function.
Acute intermittent porphyria
is a better fit.
If you're wrong about porphyria,
the treatment could box her kidneys.
Vasculitis is treated with
corticosteroids, relatively harmless.
- Start her on the steroids.
- House, he's not...
Then test for both
so he can stop whining.
Big Love, have I humiliated you
in the last half-hour?
No.
Check your e-mail.
How's it going?
Great.
The only way he can turn any more cheeks
is by pulling down his pants.
He's not a wuss.
It takes a lot more strength...
We didn't bet on
how strong he was.
So, you're gonna collect $100
and fire him because he has principles?
What's your agenda here?
You obviously don't care about the 100.
He's a decent, smart...
You don't care about the team.
Does it annoy Wilson when you
ask questions and ignore the answers?
Very much.
You only care about
who I hire and who I fire
because you miss
going through my mail.
You can't stop controlling me.
No one controls you.
- Want your job back?
- No.
Too bad, you can't have it.
She'll take care of this.
You can take it out of the 100
you're gonna owe me.
I met House at a conference
about five years ago.
- He's quite a character.
- Yes, he is.
Probably one of the best medical minds
of our generation.
I agree. I learned
an awful lot from him.
I'll bet you did. I see here
you just did a stint at Mercy.
Great.
It says here "'07 to Present."
How long were you there?
About a month. Dr. Schaffer was great,
but it just wasn't the right fit.
Wait, was that you with Dr. Schaffer
and the lymphoma patient?
It was... It was a tough situation.
I probably could've handled it better.
No, Dr. Schaffer's
got a stick up her rear, good for you.
What made you so sure
it was lymphoma?
There was an unusual lactic acid level
in one of her labs.
I had a similar case
a few months ago.
Beautiful.
God, I wish I had your stones.
Well, my stones
are on the market.
No, I mean, seriously,
I wish I had your stones.
I could cram you down
the board of directors.
But I don't. I'm sorry, man.
Good luck.
When your retinas
see something,
they send electrical signals
to your brain.
These lenses will pick
up those signals.
If the signals are misfiring,
it'll confirm
that an old man without a medical
license is smarter than all of us,
that your hallucinations
were caused by...
They're not hallucinations.
Tell them, Mom.
Honey, they're doctors.
They must know
what they're doing.
If they know what they're doing,
how did they kill that poor man's dog?
Come on, this has got to be
freaking you out a little bit.
I appreciate your concern.
There's nothing to
be ashamed of here.
If the ghost of a man you killed
doesn't screw with your head,
there's something wrong
with your head.
See, that freaks me out.
Someone must have
left it in here.
Absolutely, that makes sense,
some dog was in here
getting his eyes checked
and forgot to put
his jewelry back on.
This isn't working.
You're just making me sicker,
like he said you...
What's wrong?
My stomach, it hurts.
- Code in the eye lab.
- Lean forward, Irene.
- You're gonna aspirate.
- I can't. It hurts.
Why won't you help me?
Spleen's ripe to bursting.
You guys thought it was vasculitis?
You used to be on
House's team, right?
Yeah. Got a lot of
blood in here. Sponge.
You got any advice for me?
Nope.
You always put up
with his crap?
Yeah.
Was it a mistake?
It was irrelevant.
Well, he fired you.
He'll fire you either way.
Eventually.
- Dr. Cameron told me about...
- Don't want to know.
- Why not?
- Because House is watching.
Not a metaphor. Look up.
You guys gonna
shoot the breeze,
or you gonna do something
about all that bleeding?
That's not coming from the spleen.
It's the liver.
It's necrotic.
She's dying
from the inside out.
Enlarged spleen and
liver failure are classic AIP.
It's porphyria
and it's moving fast.
PBGs were negative.
If you read the reports...
PBG tests are only conclusive
if done during an attack,
which you would know
if you were a real doctor.
That is just great.
- What is?
- Which one of us is?
Both of you. Together.
Fighting. Passionate to
prove the other one wrong.
Couldn't care less about the patient,
but it all works out the same.
I hate Thirteen.
Not as productively. Continue.
It could still be vascular.
Vasculitis is off the board.
Steroid treatment didn't help.
Vascular isn't just vasculitis.
Something's got to be cutting off the
blood supply to her liver and spleen.
Do a visceral angiogram.
This is a joke, right?
He can't be right
every single time.
You're feeding him your ideas
just to embarrass us.
If I wanted to embarrass you,
I'd have you mop up the doctors' lounge.
Heavenly Father, I pray thee
that thou shalt give the Holy Ghost
unto all them
that shall believe in their words.
Irene, what are you doing?
I need to touch it.
Put your hand down.
No! Give it to me! I want it!
Give it to me! No!
What the angio say?
We couldn't finish.
She started groping me.
And you couldn't let her get to
second base just to get the test done?
I think that's third base.
She was convulsing, delirious
and hyper-salivating.
We had to knock her out
with lorazepam.
Well, that's definitely
not vascular.
What do you want us to do?
The question is,
what would Joseph Smith do?
This isn't the time for anti...
Casting out the demons?
The patient's not possessed.
She's dying. You can mock me tomorrow.
You believe that the book
has all the answers.
To morality, not science.
But the book is
inconsistent with science.
You know how many epileptics were
tortured because they were possessed?
How many teenage witches
were stoned to death,
because they took mushrooms?
Just shut up already.
We got a patient dying.
You either got to prescribe an exorcism,
or admit to me
that Smith was a horny fraud.
I know what she has.
You couldn't have spoken up
10 seconds ago?
You would have saved me 100 bucks.
Mushrooms weren't the only thing
that got people stoned to death,
jimsonweed, belladonna,
mandrake root and moldy bread.
It's ergot poisoning.
You'd need damp grain that's...
Completely unprocessed
and untreated,
like what's in that organic rye bread
she's been eating.
- Should I be going home?
- Is it 6:00?
It's why she got worse
on the bromocriptine.
It's an ergot derivative.
There hasn't been
a case in 50 years.
She kept asking for milk.
Dairy products counteract the effects.
You think she knew what she had
and was treating it?
Cravings based on actual needs,
it's a fairly common
evolutionary development.
You okay with an answer
based on evolution?
Yeah.
Hypocrite.
It's the stuff they make LSD from.
The treatment you're on should...
So, I've just been tripping?
It explains the hallucinations,
seizures, delusions...
Constricts the blood vessels,
which explains the necrosis.
She's not here?
I'm sorry, no.
The fact that you're even willing
to accept that answer
means the medicine
is starting to work.
But you'll live.
You're beautiful, Reena.
You too, Mama.
I'm going to miss you.
Mama.
As you know,
there are seven of you and...
One, two, three, four...
Only six roses.
Those are peonies.
But I'm sure they're
part of the rose family.
Actually, I'm surprised
there are seven of you.
You punch your boss
and stick around?
Give me the flower and shut up.
Don't overdo it.
Now, I would love to keep all of you,
but not enough to do anything about it.
So, according to my arbitrary schedule,
one of you has to go.
You're kidding!
I came up with the answer.
I robbed a grave. I...
Planted a dog collar in the procedure
room just to screw with my head.
No, I never.
What, you don't
believe she did it?
I'm sure she did it.
That's why she's getting the flower.
It was beautiful, she just overreached.
- She got into your head.
- No, I...
She owned you.
Planting the idea was good.
Letting it fester was good.
Leaving the collar was stupid.
Well-known fact,
ghosts don't leave things lying around.
So, am I gone then?
Oh, my goodness. I totally forgot
about you two. Well played.
Sorry, Henry.
We had some giggles.
You agreed with everything he said.
You finished each other's sentences.
That's why I got to go.
Don't need someone to tell you
what you're already thinking.
Funny, I was gonna say that.
- If you want to hang out...
- Yeah, I know.
Call Wilson.
The rest of you, 8:00 tomorrow.
Cash will be fine.
I bet you say that
to all the guys.
Take your blood money.
Who are you gonna protect next?
If I told you,
it wouldn't work.
I've re-thought some things.
Glad to hear it.
I'm prepared to come back
on a number of conditions.
I want the raise you promised,
plus five percent.
I want my own office
and a personal assistant.
That's not unreasonable.
I will give you none of those.
You can come back
at your original salary.
What's going on?
You haven't
re-thought anything.
You've just been black-balled.
You're "House, Lite" now.
The only administrator
that will touch you
is the one who hired "House, Classic."
The good news is she'll pretend
she's not doing you a favor.
I can start Monday.