[distant, somber music plays]
-[man] Hey! What do you--?
-[thud]
[glass shattering]
-[men grunting]
-[blows]
[whimpering]
[man yelling]
[thwack]
[thudding]
-[whimpering]
-[gunshots]
[somber music rising]
Oh my God.
[clears throat]
[retching]
[panting]
What time is it?
-Don't worry about it.
-Ugh…
-Here, want some water?
-Mm-mm.
Did they… Did they find him?
We'll talk about that later.
How about you try
and get some more sleep, okay?
Mm!
[gagging]
[vomiting]
[Bree coughs]
[ghostly echo ringing]
-Mr. B, that weird dude is in your office.
-Why'd you let him in my office?
Bastard got by me.
He's a quick little shit.
-Where's Cane?
-Not here.
What are you doing here?
Just feeling the boss energy
behind this desk. Whoo!
-It's not your desk.
-Okay, can I have that one? It's smaller.
What are you doing here?
Come on. It'd be fun to have my own desk.
Make me feel like I had a real job.
Plus, it'd be great for us
to really put our heads together.
We talked about this.
You should never come here.
Relax.
I brought payroll.
Besides, I'm not going anywhere, man.
I love it here. It's on the water.
I'm aquatic.
It's better if Reggie and Tim
receive all payments from your men.
-It's more discreet that way.
-[feigns snoring]
Come on, man.
[chuckling] You gotta lighten up.
You got the sheriff in your pocket.
Plus, I heard DEA is no longer an issue.
-I say we celebrate.
-This is a legitimate business.
Yeah, and what exactly
is your definition of… legitimate?
It is, first and foremost, a fishery.
We can't afford to attract attention.
Okay, look, uh…
I'm in a little bit of a bind.
I got an emergency shipment
that needs to fly ASAP.
-Not during operational hours.
-And it comes with a fat rush fee.
It'd behoove all of us if you'd gas up one
of those little boats out there, pronto.
I've made myself clear.
Yes, and your overreaction is noted.
But now let me make myself clear.
You need to start trusting three things.
Me, my process, and my judgment.
Maybe we aren't spending
enough time together, right?
We gotta sync up, man.
Let's see. Oh, you wanna go hunting?
Let's go hunting.
It's quail season. That'd be fun, right?
It's a good stress reliever.
You could use it.
I mean, no offense, but you…
You got, like, resting stress face.
For the last time,
we don't do impromptu runs.
You need to take your shipment with you.
Please, don't be so stubborn, okay?
I made a big commitment
to some very important buyers.
-Grady.
-Harlan.
Call your buyers and reschedule.
Now go.
[imitates Harlan] "Now go." [chuckles]
So serious.
I mean, it's so much, uh, gravitas.
I mean, I love it, but, uh…
I don't know,
it's kinda coming off a little bossy.
[tense music creeping in]
Wow, okay. [chuckles uncomfortably]
[door opens]
Oh, hello again.
Hello.
It's Grady.
I remember.
Well, it's good to see you.
Huh.
I thought it'd be friendlier here.
Hey.
How are you feeling?
-Like I want to use.
-[Cane] How long does that last?
Now until
forever.
How long does it stay in your system?
Well, heroin metabolizes pretty quickly.
The withdrawal is anyone's guess.
What about Marcus?
Uh…
Yeah, the motel housekeeping found him.
His body's at the morgue
until it's transferred
back over to Charlotte.
They're, uh, ruling it an overdose.
But I killed him.
-Heroin killed him.
-I pushed him to use.
I-- I didn't want him to die. I…
I took… I took photos of him, um…
So I could have something on him.
Blackmail or…
God, it was so stupid.
No, it wasn't.
You were protecting your family.
I'm not-- I won't rationalize it.
I killed a man.
But you didn't.
You guys met in rehab.
He-- He was a junkie
quick to shoot up, if not now, later.
No, that's too easy.
He's de--
[breathing shakily]
He's dead because of me.
[sorrowful music playing]
[phone buzzing]
Who's that?
It's Dad. He's wondering where I am.
-I bet Mom is freaking out.
-No, it's all good.
I told her you had car trouble.
Forgot to renew your AAA.
So you called me. It was late.
We left your car on the side of the road
and you just came and crashed here.
Okay.
Are you hungry?
You want something to eat?
Why are you being nice to me?
It's not like I haven't done this before.
I know.
["Nashville Money" by Myron Elkins
playing over car's speakers]
[Grady] Hey!
Hey, man. Buck Jr.
-What's up? You remember me?
-Yeah, Grady, right?
-Yeah. Why aren't you in school?
-We're on break this week.
All right. What are we doing?
Come on, let's get out of here.
Let's have some fun.
-Yeah.
-Ah.
It's not stranger danger here.
I'm good friends with your grandpa.
Come on.
-Come on, come on. Let's go. All right!
-Yeah, all right.
[howls]
We're about to have some fun!
♪ Gonna make a big star out of me ♪
How much is there?
Looks like 200,000.
That's more than you negotiated.
He's proven generous.
A crazy but generous nutcase.
No, he scares me. He's dangerous.
He can be controlled.
You just have to strong-arm him a little.
Run half through the fish house,
I'll run half through the restaurant,
but it'll take till the end of the month.
What's our timeline with the bank?
Have you talked to Freeman lately?
They're aware of our problems
and they're being very lenient.
We're not in danger
of default or anything?
We're okay for now.
Why are you smiling?
Oh, you're not?
Why? Things are working out
just like you wanted.
Why? We got lucky with the DEA agent
and the sheriff too.
-Is there something else?
-No.
I just don't like relying on luck.
It always runs out.
[phone buzzing]
Yo, HB. Decided to go hunting anyway,
and look who I brought with me.
-Hey, Grandpa.
-Diller?
We're at Tanner's Trail right now.
Grady said that you were coming?
Yeah, Tanner's Trail.
-What do you think you're doing?
-We're having trouble hearing you.
-Are you-- What? I think, I-- I-- Ugh…
-[both chuckle]
Goddamn it.
Jesus Christ. Jesus Christ, Harlan.
I'll go get him, don't worry.
Where the hell is Cane?
Oh my God. He called.
He's with Bree, they'll be late.
Jesus. Not the day.
-[ominous music plays]
-[door opens]
[Bree] I wiped his cloud,
removed the PIN and drive.
I was thorough.
I watched him, memorized his passwords.
[Cane] What happens if the DEA follows up?
He had theories, not a lot of facts.
We gotta destroy all this stuff.
Can't just trash it.
I don't wanna be, like, nosy or anything,
but where's Peyton?
Peyton took Savannah
to her folks' place for a while.
Oh, shit.
Yeah.
-How about you try and get more sleep?
-I can't.
Can't turn my brain off.
Just lay there thinking about him
and thinking about using,
and I can still see him.
His eyes stopped moving.
It was like Granddad.
What do you mean, like Granddad?
The night he died.
But you didn't see him, you were asleep.
They found you asleep in your bed.
Is that not what happened?
-I was staying with him that weekend.
-No, I know the story.
You know a version of the story.
[intriguing music playing]
I was still awake in the living room,
and we heard a noise.
I didn't know what it was, but he did.
Do you remember that closet
that was by the front hallway?
-Yeah.
-Yeah, he hid me in there.
And he told me to stay quiet
and not come out, no matter what.
But I could-- I could still see.
[grunting echoes]
And-- and there were two men.
Not one, like the cop said,
there were two of them.
And they did things,
and, uh, then he started screaming.
[man screaming]
And I was…
I was… too scared to help.
I was too scared to move, so…
[breathes shakily]
And then they were gone.
So I went to him.
And there was blood every-- everywhere.
But he was still alive.
[man groaning]
And then he wasn't.
Why didn't I know about this?
Mom made me promise
that I would never tell anyone.
She said if I pretended it never happened,
it would be the same as if it didn't.
But you were a child.
Our family doesn't talk
about the bad shit.
It's easier to pretend.
I'm… I'm sorry, Bree.
It is what it is.
And fuck Mom and Dad for what they did.
[voice breaking] Yeah, they suck.
Do you know what they didn't do, though?
[crying] They didn't burn down their house
with their child inside.
[sobbing]
I… I did that.
That was on me.
[Bree sobbing]
-Shawn, is Bree here yet?
-Not that I know of. You worried?
I don't know what I am
when she's concerned.
-Excuse me. Mrs. Buckley?
-Yes.
I'm Annie Whitley from the bank.
I work for Mr. Freeman.
-I remember you, Annie. How you doing?
-Doing all right.
Mr. Freeman asked me
to hand-deliver these documents.
He wanted you to have them
as soon as possible.
Can I ask you to sign for them?
Sure.
Thanks so much, Annie.
Thank you.
Hey, are you okay?
No, Shawn, I'm not.
I'm really not.
[tense music playing]
[loud gunshot]
[gunshot]
Whoa!
[chuckling]
-Shit knocked me on my ass.
-Yeah. That kick's strong.
You gotta make sure
you're tucking it into your shoulder more,
lean into it, you'll be good.
[Grady] Okay, right.
-What the hell is going on?
-Hey, HB.
This shotgun's got a little more kick
than I thought.
-Diller, you know better than this.
-Come on.
I thought it was all right.
He said that you were coming, so…
I don't know.
I mean, you guys are friends, right?
We're good friends. Isn't that right, HB?
-Time to go.
-Come on, you just got here.
Look, we haven't been hunting in forever.
I thought we could stay for just a little.
Right, Grandpa?
It'll give us a chance to finish our chat.
Did you open up your little box?
Yes, thanks for the extra, but--
Surely that buys me a hunting trip or two.
I don't know what you're talking about.
We gonna stay?
-We'll stay for a little while.
-[Grady] Yay!
Let's go kill things.
["Four By Four Play"
by Blackjack Billy playing]
You go hunting a lot, Diller?
-Oh yeah. Been hunting since I was nine.
-Whoo!
You start them young.
Remember the rules.
Safety on, eyes open.
Don't point at anything
you don't wanna kill.
-Right?
-Right.
Oh, yes, sir.
Bird.
[gunshot]
♪ Long way or the short way ♪
♪ There ain't no wrong way… ♪
Damn it. I can't get used to that shit.
-Diller, you wanna fetch those birds?
-Yeah.
You said you had something
you wanted to discuss?
♪ Girl, don't stop ♪
♪ Take it off-road
Take it off-road, take it off ♪
I just want us on the same page.
So do I, but the boat runs
have to be done my way.
That's all I ask.
And all I ask is for you
to show a little flexibility, okay?
-I just want a little respect.
-Respect is earned.
And it's my fish house, my rules, the end.
The end? That's it?
You just cut ties like that?
Wave bye-bye to all that money?
[bird chirping]
[gunshot echoes]
[Grady] Ah, goddamn it!
You have to lead the bird just enough.
When your barrel is over its beak,
then squeeze the trigger.
Settle in, breathe, relax.
[gunshot]
I know what I'm doing.
Been doing it a long while.
[gritty music playing]
[Wes] You showed up.
I thought you were gonna ghost me again.
[Belle] Thanks for meeting me.
-[Wes] Yeah.
-[Belle] So?
The bank sent this this morning.
I know what it is.
Yeah.
[sighs]
Was this your plan all along?
Lure me with the promise of partnership
and then screw me every which way?
Come on, that's not fair.
I wanted this deal to happen.
You were the one who blew it off, not me.
Why don't I believe you?
Because you're not an honest person,
and you think everyone's like you.
I thought this was gonna go another way.
If you're so honest,
please help me reverse this, Wes.
I wish I could.
Even though you hosed me.
I like you.
You're a complex woman, Belle.
Maybe that's the intrigue.
Can I…? Can I ask you a question?
Does Harlan even know about this deal?
You know, it took me a second
to figure that out.
I thought you felt guilty about the sex
but your guilt is… [blows] …so much more.
Listen, I can wire you $800,000
as a promissory.
That ship has sailed.
The foreclosure papers have been filed.
-You have 45 days to pay or forfeit.
-Please. Please.
This will destroy my family,
do you understand?
Maybe it's an opportunity.
I asked my wife for a divorce.
And it's a relief.
Now I can let the dust settle
and move on with whatever it is
I'm gonna move on to.
Can I give you some unsolicited advice?
Maybe it's time to take stock.
Tell the truth, do the right thing,
be a good person,
and the rest will fall into place.
It seems like you've lost your way, Belle.
I'm sorry.
Well, have fun.
Be safe, all right? Bye, baby.
Who's that?
Savannah.
-She's riding a horse today.
-[chuckles dryly]
When's Peyton coming back?
I don't know.
Does this have anything to do
with Jenna being back?
Not today's topic, Bree.
[gentle music playing]
Are you sleeping with her?
-Jesus Christ, Bree.
-What?
-I'm not-- I'm not judging.
-No. I'm not fuck--
I get it. I get it.
Look, you guys have a connection.
You always have, everyone sees it.
I'm sure even Peyton knows it down deep.
I'm married to Peyton.
Yeah, but be honest.
Would you have married Peyton
if she hadn't gotten pregnant?
Well, I mean,
that's kind of more you than me.
I just… thought we were being honest.
[sputters] Yeah, I--
I would've married Peyton anyway.
I mean,
what else was I gonna do?
Oh, up, up, up, up.
Ah, crap,
I didn't have the things lined up.
Don't worry about the sight line.
Trust your gut.
Oh!
[Harlan] Nice shooting, son.
Your grandson looks up to you.
Don't all kids?
Nope.
Not all of them.
[Harlan] Birds have slowed down.
Might be time to head back.
Come on, man, I haven't got one yet.
Well, take mine back to your boys.
Tell them some great story
and have a feast.
See, you do something like that…
it makes it impossible
for me not to like you.
Look, I'm willing
to chalk today up to growing pains,
but you can't just swing by the fish house
with an emergency shipment.
It's sloppy.
Okay.
I can hear you on that.
-[bird chirping]
-Oh.
-Here we go.
-Too low.
-Too low. Too low!
-No, I got it.
-[gunshot]
-[grunts]
Diller!
[frantic music playing]
Get the fucking truck!
I need help!
I got him!
Page the SOD and prep OR2.
[man] Got it.
Let's go!
-[Harlan] Hang in there, son.
-Sir, we'll come find you with an update.
[Cane] Hey, Bree.
You gotta get up.
We gotta go. It's Diller.
What?
[Shawn] Mrs. Buckley?
Harlan's been trying to reach you.
[tense music playing]
Hi, excuse me.
Um, Diller Hopkins, I'm his mother.
-104. I'll need to buzz you in.
-Thank you.
[buzzing]
Oh my God. Oh my God. Where is he?
-He's okay.
-What happened?
It was a hunting accident.
Doctor said he got grazed,
a little birdshot in his arm and chest.
He was shot? Who shot him?
-He's gonna be okay.
-I wanna see him.
-They're not done. You can't go in.
-Fuck that.
-Let me go!
-They're still working on him.
He's fine. He's gonna be okay.
-Everything is okay, I promise you.
-[crying]
He's fine. Just breathe. Just breathe.
-Hey.
Where is he?
Bree's in there with him right now,
but he's… he's okay.
Is it true that Grady shot him?
I don't know all the details, but… yeah.
-Unbelievable.
-Mrs. Buckley?
-Uh, yes?
-Your husband is asking to see you.
-I'll see you in a minute.
-Yeah.
I'm here to see my son, Diller Hopkins.
-We can only accept one visitor at a time.
-It's okay, hon. You go, I'll wait here.
You both have to wait.
His mother's with him.
This is the boy's father.
I can let her know you're here,
if you can take a seat.
-No, I don't think so.
-No, babe, not now.
Thank you.
Hey.
Wow.
You look like shit.
So do you.
We can't be in the same room together.
It's not allowed.
Yeah, well,
I'd like to see someone try to move me.
I'm not going anywhere.
[gentle music playing]
[line calling]
[phone buzzing]
Why are you calling me?
[Cane] What do you mean?
Thought we weren't
gonna see each other anymore.
I'm calling you on the phone.
You found a loophole.
Is everything okay?
What's wrong?
Uh…
A lot, a lot.
A lot is wrong.
Do you wanna talk about it?
Mm… No.
Do you remember
how anxious I was in school?
With every test and paper due,
I had so much anxiety.
Yeah, I remember.
And whenever I got worried or upset,
you would say,
"You're an idiot. What is your problem?"
"You're the smartest person I know.
You got this."
I'm gonna throw that back in your face,
you're welcome.
[chuckles]
Yeah, you always have my back.
It's easy, you're a good person.
I don't know about that.
It's true.
I really wish
I was the person you thought I was.
You are.
Well, thank you, Jenna.
Okay, good night.
Good night.
Grady shot our grandson.
I told you, it was an accident.
Are you sure?
I was there.
Listen, I want him out of our lives.
I don't care how bad things get.
This is too far, I won't stand for it.
I'll take care of it.
What does that even mean?
It means I'll take care of it.
Diller is fine, it scared him more than--
You are taking this too lightly.
I said I will handle it.
-You can't handle everything, Harlan.
-Let's just bring it down a notch, okay?
Don't you get it?
Our luck has run out.
It's all fallen to shit
right in front of us.
-We'll figure this out like we always do.
-You're not listening.
I know Grady is a problem,
but he's a problem I can fix.
You think you can fix everything,
but you can't.
Some things are out of your reach.
-Do we really need to do this right here?
-My God.
You think you can fix everything?
Fix this.
[foreboding music playing]
What is it?
The end, Harlan.
It's the end.
I told you our luck has run out.
How is he?
Uh, he's… he's in a little pain,
but the doctor said
overall his injuries are fairly minor.
How is getting shot in the chest
fairly minor?
I don't know, that's just what he said.
"Superficial lacerations, fairly minor."
[scoffs] How can you let this happen?
-He was with my dad.
-What was he doing with Harlan?
-Where were you?
-I was… I was helping Cane with something.
[Rodney] Oh, yeah?
-You feeling all right?
-I'm a little under the weather.
[scoffs]
-Why was he with your dad?
-I don't know, Rodney.
-Shouldn't you know?
-Fires, getting shot.
Does child endangerment
run in your family?
Shit happens, Georgina.
It was an accident.
They happen.
They are unavoidable on planet Earth.
Hey.
He wants to see you, but he doesn't
need you to yell at him or be mad at him,
so just go in there and be his dad, okay?
Hello.
-Hey, Mom.
-How you doing?
Your dad said he's gonna be just fine.
-Yeah, he's okay.
-Yeah.
What?
You've been using.
[exhales]
Nice.
And you covered for her.
Classic.
[exhales deeply]
You can't get anything past her.
I'm sorry.
It's fine.
No, it's not.
I'm sorry about Diller.
I'm sorry about everything.
[gentle music playing]
Oh God.
Hey, it's okay. I'll go get the car.
-Thanks.
-You're welcome.
Mrs. Buckley? Sorry, that's so formal.
May I call you Belle?
No.
Did you shoot my grandson?
[sighs] I mean,
I wouldn't put it that way.
But did you shoot him?
It was a terrible accident. I am so sorry.
Are you?
Well, it wasn't on purpose,
if that's what you're getting at.
It wasn't conscious,
but I guess subconsciously,
I mean, we can never be 100% sure.
-[thwack]
-[tense music playing]
Get the fuck off me!
You hit me!
You touch me, I will kill you!
You people!
Jesus Christ! Can't you tell
when you're only making it worse?
[intense music playing]
I'm fine. Kick his ass.
Hey!
[grunts]
[panting]
-[Shawn] Come here.
-[guard] Hey, what's going on here?
Uh, we're good, right? We're good.
-Yeah.
-Let's go, Shawn.
Fuck.
Let me see.
I'm fine.
Here. Left side.
My God.
Where did you learn to fight like that?
Gay.
Small-town Texas.
Do you need more?
Yeah, I do.
That was some pro-level shit.
Started doing jiujitsu when I was a kid.
I'm a black belt in taekwondo.
Those two men were in the restaurant
the other night. Who are they?
-It was a misunderstanding.
-Tell me the truth.
It was a misunderstanding, is all.
Did a little research
before I came to town.
Just stuff that's in the public record.
About the Buckleys.
Listen, there's been accusations.
-We've never been charged for it.
-No, not you.
Harlan's father would've been
if he hadn't been killed.
I guess it was stupid
to think you wouldn't google.
Two of your fishermen
wound up dead in a freak accident.
The sheriff dies, another accident.
Your daughter-in-law was attacked.
The first thing you asked me
was if I was with the DEA.
-Why would you ask me that?
-Shawn, it's complicated, okay?
Now is not the time,
and I wouldn't even know where to start.
All right.
Fine.
You know what? I'll take an Uber.
Thanks for the tissues.
Shawn, wait. Just come back to the house.
I'll fix your face, and we can talk.
That was some good fighting.
[starts engine]
What are you doing here?
Um…
Can I come in?
You made the rule, not me.
Well, I came to break it.
All day…
Everywhere I go…
[gentle music playing]
…all I can think about is, um…
What?
…what we should've been.
And what we're supposed to be.
Cane.
["Sinner" by Shaya Zamora playing]
♪ You dug too deep in my soul ♪
♪ And oh ♪
♪ You watched me bleed on the floor ♪
♪ I was begging you to love me, though ♪
♪ Now I'm a sinner 'cause I can't let go ♪
[music fades]
[clattering]
[thud]
[unsettling music playing]
It's awfully late, Grady.
I tried, man.
[chuckling] I really tried.
I wanted us to have
a special relationship.
To be friends, or family even.
That's why I thought
of the whole hunting trip.
I thought it would be
like a bonding experience, and then…
Someone got shot, and it's like…
suddenly everything's my fault.
It was your fault.
You know, I'm nice to your wife,
I get a bloody nose.
I'm nice to your son,
guy looks at me like I'm some freak.
And then there's you, Big Daddy.
I'll be honest.
My dad was a piece of shit.
I fucking hated him.
And guess what? He hated me.
So I got an open slot.
You should probably keep searching.
You know,
I recently came into this bonkers yacht.
It's souped-up, sexy as fuck.
Guy owed me some money.
I usually deal in cash, but let's face it,
when someone says, "Want a yacht?"
The only answer is, "Yes, please."
It's late. It's time to call it a night.
So I'm out yachting in my new yacht.
Like a G.
We decide to drop anchor in the sound,
do a little jet skiing.
I jump in without looking, and fuck me,
it's like a jellyfish convention in there.
Let me tell you something.
Those fuckers can sting.
Let's look at this like adults.
We're clearly at an impasse.
So the only thing to do
is you go your way, and I go mine.
The end.
What? No. No, no, no.
Look, when your son's disobedient,
do you disown him?
No, you just gotta
put him in his place, right?
[snaps fingers]
What the hell is that?
Your punishment for being a bad boy.
What the fuck did you bring in here?
Portuguese man o' war. A lot of them.
I told you.
I'm aquatic.
[unsettling music builds]
Hands off me!
Goddamn it! Get off of me!
Get off of me, goddamn it!
I'm sure you already know this,
but this is gonna sting a little.
-Know why your father doesn't like you?
-Turn him off.
-Tape his mouth. Shut him up.
-You're the most pompous little shit--
[grunting]
[Grady] This guy's slippery.
[water dripping]
You ready?
The tingling means it's working.
[Harlan grunting]
[grunting in pain]
Shh, shh, shh.
I want you to really
hear me on this, okay?
From now on, you're gonna do two things.
What I want, when I want it.
[breathing heavily]
Or I'll make you suffer
with everyone you care about.
If you think this hurts,
I promise you it is nothing
compared to what I'm gonna do to Belle
and Cane and Bree and Diller.
-And little Savannah?
-[grunts]
-Did I get her name right?
[grunts in pain]
Starting to get it, Harlan?
It's called the point.
Get it?
[yells]
[bloodcurdling screams]
["Albatross"
by Corrosion of Conformity playing]
♪ Well, I'm feeling left behind ♪
♪ Lord, what a waste of time ♪
♪ They're coming to get you ♪
♪ Run on ♪
♪ How can I respect your crime ♪
♪ When all you criminals whine? ♪
♪ They bought and sold you ♪
♪ Run on, run on, yeah ♪
♪ Well, you can call me crazy ♪
♪ You can call me wrong ♪
♪ 'Cause ♪
♪ See, I was born a liar ♪
♪ Albatross, fly on ♪
♪ Fly on ♪
[music fades]