[tense music playing]
[waves crashing]
[boat engine rumbling]
[music rising]
[waves slapping the boat]
[strong sea wind blowing]
[tense music continues]
[boat engine rumbling softly]
[man] Hey, Curtis, take a look at this.
Uh, they're early.
Coming port side.
Okay, let's open up the hold.
Let's be ready. I wanna go home.
[hatch creaks and squeaks]
[tense music continues and turns ominous]
[loud bang]
[metallic thud against hull]
[hull groans]
[waves lapping against hull]
Hello?
[sharp musical sting]
[dull thump on deck]
Troy!
[chilling music creeping in]
[music fades]
[ominous music playing]
[Curtis] Troy, what's going on?
[ominous music rising]
[sharp click of cocking gun]
[chuckles faintly]
["No Good" by KALEO playing]
♪ Can't fight the temptation ♪
♪ When you get the vibration ♪
♪ Won't do you no good ♪
You're making a big mistake.
On your knees.
♪ If you don't mind ♪
-[thwack]
-[body thuds]
♪ Hell, I never mind ♪
♪ Won't do you no good
Won't do you no… ♪
No!
[groans]
No, no…
No, no, no… [grunts]
Wait… Wait! No, no, no!
No, no!
[splash]
[music fades]
[music rising]
[ominous music continues]
[quickly tapping]
[breathing heavily]
[steady pulse builds]
-[exhales]
-[music builds]
[music stops]
[exhales]
[breathing deeply]
["The Farmer in the Dell"
plays faintly through phone]
[woman] Hey, babe.
[man] Morning, honey.
-Can I have the new iPhone?
-[woman] We talked about that already.
-What's wrong with the one you have?
-[girl] I want the new one.
Okay, you can get a new one when
the one you have now breaks. How's that?
[woman] Don't tell her that.
It'll be broken before lunch.
Hey, are you home tonight,
or are you out again?
I don't know. Are you?
I don't know.
[scoffs] Okay.
Bye, baby.
Daddy, I'm not being heard.
Hey.
No pooh face.
[woman] Finish up, sweetie.
We're gonna be late.
["The Devil Stole My Style"
by Ryan Bingham playing]
♪ Oh, I've been here and I've been there ♪
♪ Oh, I've been all around, my dear ♪
♪ I'm still alive, but I've been dead ♪
♪ I've been to hell and back again ♪
♪ So if I'm gone a little while ♪
♪ It's 'cause the devil stole my smile ♪
[indistinct chatter]
Sure. I've got it covered.
Oh, shit.
[ominous music playing]
-Hey. Sheriff Porter. If I can--
-Hang tight. I'll be with you in a second.
[agent] It's been abandoned.
Hull's been cleaned out.
No trace of contraband, residue.
-And the captain and the first mate?
-Nothing.
But I wouldn't rule out
accidental drowning.
Bad rope pull sent one over,
the other tried to help, both drowned.
Both of them? That's unlikely.
Who owns the boat?
It's registered to a Cane Buckley.
Why do I know that name?
Harlan Buckley's son.
They own the fishery.
They're a big family in town.
You should start there.
[intriguing music playing]
[grunts]
[breathes in]
[exhales]
[annoyed grunt]
[weak breath escapes]
[grunts]
[breathes in]
[exhales]
[groans]
[bottles topple and crash to the floor]
[panting weakly]
Rhonda.
[panting] Rhonda.
[bottles topple]
It's my heart.
What?
[exhales]
A heart attack?
-Oh my God. What do I do?
-Call my wife.
-Okay--
-No.
Call an ambulance. Then call my wife.
[shakily] Okay.
Yeah. Yeah, okay. Okay. Okay!
[labored breathing]
[bright music playing]
Oh, Ms. Belle, I'm so sorry.
It's all my fault. I killed him.
Oh, oh, oh, oh. Where is he, honey?
Uh, he's with the doctor,
and they brought in a crash cart.
Rhonda, honey, I got it from here.
All right?
You just go on home now
and find yourself a bra.
-I'll call you when I know something.
-Yes, ma'am, I will.
What happened to Curtis?
-[electricity crackles]
-Ow!
It keeps zapping me.
Your defibrillator's
sending random shocks.
Your heart's stable.
Eh, it could just be a malfunction.
-Well, it ain't but two months old.
-Is he gonna live?
[chuckling] Without question.
Oh, shit.
I'll call you back.
[doctor] I've restored the settings.
Let's see if that helps.
Where's Rhonda?
I sent her home.
-[slaps his back]
-Really, Rhonda? Christ.
Tommy called and said the Miss Glory
is sitting in the surf half sunk.
-Where the hell is Cane?
-I don't know, hon.
I'm in the ER with my husband.
-Help me get these off.
-No!
-I'm out, Doc.
-Jesus!
[gritty music playing]
-Hey, Cane. How you doing?
-Hey.
[knocking]
Well, Cane Buckley, it's been a minute.
Hello, Lynette. How are you?
What do you want?
I need to change ownership
of the Miss Glory to Curtis Sutton.
-That would be the registrar's office.
-Well, I need you to predate it.
[Lynette] And why is that?
Because you're my cousin
and family helps family, right?
What kind of trouble are you in?
You gonna help me or what?
I have $12,000 in credit card debt.
Are you gonna help me?
I can handle that, yeah.
-Good.
-Okay.
You need to sign at the bottom
to transfer the deed.
All right.
And, uh, what about Curtis' signature?
Oh, I'll just copy it
from his fishing license.
I'll notarize it myself.
[softly] Okay.
And, uh, this is legit, right?
Oh, yeah.
You want to put
the purchase back three months?
Say, um, I don't know, June 3rd?
-Perfect.
-I'll put it on Ollie's desk.
[inhales] Lynette, you are an angel.
I know.
[atmospheric music playing]
[exhales]
…platter and no shrimp and calamari.
-Excuse me.
-Mm-hmm.
-Hey, hon.
-Hey.
-Got your text. What's going on with Dad?
-It was a false alarm.
-His defibrillator had a loose screw--
-What? How does that happen?
I have no idea.
They're reprogramming it,
and he'll be fine per usual.
How about you get him
to put down the bottle, huh?
Oh, God.
So, what is happening with the Miss Glory?
It washed up on shore.
And Curtis and Troy?
You need to tell him.
Are you crazy?
What am I going to tell him?
"I did it, Dad.
It's the end of the almighty Buckleys."
Stop being so dramatic.
Just tell him the truth. All of it.
He's the one that stepped away.
He dropped this shit show in my lap
and he expects me to start printing money?
By the way,
have you spoken to your sister?
No, I'm not Bree's keeper.
She's been very nosy lately.
Do not tell her anything about this, okay?
-Keep it to yourself.
-She's the last person I want to talk to.
[crowd cheering]
[softly] Come on.
Come on, come on, come on, come on.
[indistinct encouragement from crowd]
[cheering]
All right!
[softly] Come on, now.
-[woman] Keep going, keep going.
-Let's go.
-What are you doing here?
-Same as you, watching a relay race.
You need court permission to see your son.
It's almost over, Rodney.
There's ten minutes left.
-Are you gonna go or do I call 911?
-All right, fine.
I'm leaving.
[woman] Typical.
One more word, bitch,
and I will slap you off this bridge!
That was a direct threat, Bree.
Are you recording this?
Jesus, you're pathetic.
[Rodney] You need to go.
You're a small man, Rodney Hopkins.
[crowd cheering]
[gritty music playing]
[woman] Hey! Come here!
Hello, sir.
DEA Special Agent Marcus Sanchez.
Oh.
-He's here about the Miss Glory.
-All right. DEA, huh?
What can I do for you? Thanks, Bree.
I'll stay.
It's about your boat, sir.
Miss Glory? Well, that's not my boat.
I mean, it's registered to you.
Yeah, well, it was,
until I sold it to Curtis Sutton.
Uh, is he okay?
I know his boat washed up on the beach.
Curtis has yet to be located.
When did the sales transaction
for the boat take place?
Uh, I sold it to Curtis
in a cash deal back in June.
He'd been after me
for that boat for a while.
He said he wanted to be his own man,
not work for anyone.
You know,
control his own destiny kind of thing.
And, uh, may I ask why the DEA
is interested in the Miss Glory?
You can ask.
Thank you for your time, Mr. Buckley.
Ma'am.
[Bree] Bye.
-What in the hell was that?
-Huh?
Well, he's gonna find out you were lying.
Curtis doesn't own Miss Glory.
-He does. He bought it back in June.
-How come I didn't know?
-We have lanes around here, remember?
-Oh my God.
Fish house is my lane.
Get back to your lane.
-Oh, that's right. You don't have one.
-Eat shit.
-Cane, I need to talk to you.
-Can it wait, Tommy?
-No. I mean, we gotta discuss this.
-Yeah.
Oh! Jesus Christ!
What the hell have you done?
Jesus Christ, Dad.
I wouldn't bother getting up.
[panting]
I'm just gonna hit you again.
Okay, we've got domestic on the left,
imported on the right, uh…
-Thirty-two different brands.
-This place is amazing.
Where are you from, Shawn?
-I'm from Galveston, originally.
-Mm!
-Texas?
-Mm-hmm.
-What brings you to Havenport?
-I wanted a change.
-And I also have some family here.
-Married? Got a girl?
Hey. Sorry I'm late, Michelle.
I owe you one.
Oh, excuse me a moment, Shawn.
Hi, honey.
Where've you been?
Everything okay? I've been texting.
Running late is all.
Is that the new bartender?
Yeah, I've been showing him around.
Um, what's going on?
The DEA was here
asking questions about the Miss Glory.
I'm as clueless as you are.
Let's keep a lid on that for now, okay?
Okay. I was thinking today was a good day
that I could get back in the office.
-It's too soon for that.
-Cane is terrible with finances.
Right now, I need you to get
the new bartender up to speed,
and I need to go check on the kitchen.
-I should be running the office.
-Not now, Bree.
It's been a morning.
You signed over a $300,000 boat?
They're investigating.
I need the distance.
Who are you running drugs for?
It was one run, Dad.
Don't you lie!
Okay, it was three runs, that's all.
I'll deal with it.
I'll talk to Hoyt today.
Hoyt Piper? Dealing with that little shit?
Jesus almighty.
I was gonna tell you!
I thought it'd look better
once some of the debt was paid off.
-We are upside down right now.
-What happened on that boat?
Where's Curtis and Troy?
I don't know.
They haven't found them yet.
Maybe they're hiding.
Where? The bottom of the ocean?
No, I don't know.
[tense music playing]
Something went wrong.
They-- they could be okay.
How much was the haul?
Upwards of $10 million.
That'll get you about 20 years.
We are in trouble here, Dad.
We're two minutes from losing this place.
Do you understand that?
It was a few runs to get ahead.
That's all!
Who were Troy and Curtis meeting?
Hoyt does all that.
Jesus, son. You can't be this stupid.
I will talk to him.
Yes, you will.
And you tell that idiot you're done.
It's over.
You cut ties right now.
Do you understand?
You reach for that Johnnie Walker,
I will chop your hand off.
[sighing deeply]
-How are you feeling?
-Angry.
[pours water with bar gun]
How much trouble is Cane in?
We might want to call Billy Pruitt
and get him on retainer.
You know what Cane's up against.
Overfished waters,
environmental quotas, gas prices.
Do not defend him.
I will lose my shit if you defend him.
[softly] Okay.
[ice cubes clatter]
[grim, driving acoustic music playing]
[music fades]
Hey, what the hell, Hoyt?
Are you wired?
What? Wired? No, man.
-Do not point that thing at me.
-You need to take off your clothes.
Are you serious?
If you want to talk,
take off your clothes.
No, I'm not taking off my clothes.
Then you should go.
Did you see this in a movie?
Why would I be wired?
Shit's going down.
I ain't trusting nobody.
Okay.
Unbelievable.
What happened to your face?
Don't worry about it.
Happy? There you go.
-You can leave your underwear on.
-Yeah, well, I'm not wearing any.
-God, why aren't you wearing underwear?
-Because… sometimes I don't.
[jeans land with a soft thud]
[Cane] What the hell happened, Hoyt?
-Hmm?
-[Hoyt] All I know is the boat was clean.
No drugs, no Curtis or Troy.
What about your brothers, huh?
How deep are they in this?
-[beer can cracks open]
-Not exactly self-starters, those three.
Look, man.
Owen thinks it was you.
-He thinks you're side-dealing.
-[Cane scoffs]
Why would I do this? Huh?
-$10 million worth of cocaine and opiates.
-Oh, come on.
-Do you need a better reason?
-Come on, man.
You know me.
Why would I do this? I wouldn't do this!
You've always been a little rich boy
thinking of ways to get richer.
Yeah, if that were true,
I wouldn't be working with you, would I?
You should go.
Hoyt, come on, man.
This could be real bad for both of us.
We're friends, you and me.
We need to help each other out.
You need to tell Owen I didn't do this.
Or better yet, I will tell him.
Is he here?
-I could square this away with him.
-He isn't here.
Then where is he?
What is the big secret around this guy?
Where can I find him?
I wouldn't worry.
Owen will find you.
-So you're the new bartender?
-Yes, sir. I'm Shawn.
I'll have a Johnnie Walker on ice.
-Uh…
-Something wrong?
Sir, I was told
not to serve you before 5:00.
Who told you that?
Your wife and daughter.
Several times.
But I want a drink.
[chuckles]
Could you maybe come back at 5:00?
That's not the answer.
What does your gut tell you to do?
-[scoop rattles through ice]
-Thank you, Shawn.
Hey, Clyde.
-Want a drink with me?
-I'm on duty, Harlan.
Um… could we have a word?
The DEA is all over this.
They think Curtis and Troy were smuggling.
There's no way. I'd know if they were.
Would you? 'Cause you ain't really
been around since your heart troubles.
Doesn't Cane run things now?
I'm still breathing, Clyde.
I know everything that goes on here.
Oh, so you know
that Curtis owns the Miss Glory.
I do. Cane sold it to him some time ago.
Yeah, I was at the courthouse earlier.
I saw the paperwork.
Anything else?
Well, I'm sure the Feds
will figure it out soon enough.
If they're cracking down, they've got
informants and undercover agents
all up and down the East Coast.
[tense music playing]
That's a good thing, Clyde.
Yes, it is.
Afternoon, Harlan.
[sighs]
[suspenseful music playing]
[music fades]
Oh, Jenna?
Cane?
Oh, my God.
Oh my God.
[both chuckle]
-You okay?
-[panting] No, I'm gonna pass out.
It's my first run in a while,
so I might die on you.
Well, don't do that.
[both chuckle]
What are you doing in town?
I'm just… here for a while.
Your dad?
Yeah, yeah, he's not doing so great.
Just here to, uh, help out at the store
and hang out with him.
I-- I heard about that. I'm sorry.
So, you still write
for the Atlanta paper, right?
Yeah.
Yeah, it's on Zoom now,
so I get to do it from here.
So you've been here a while?
About a month.
Yeah, Peyton didn't mention it?
We had lunch last week.
Must have slipped her mind.
-Yeah.
Yeah…
It's-- it's good to see you.
Uh, okay, well, I gotta go.
Um… we should catch up soon.
You come by the bar for a drink.
Okay.
Soon. [chuckling] Yeah.
-All right.
-[Jenna giggles]
-Bye.
-Bye!
[gentle music playing]
Are you drunk?
[Bell exhales]
[sighs]
When were you gonna tell me?
About now, actually.
It's been a crazy day.
[tosses off shoe]
[exhales]
We're gonna lose everything, you know?
Cane came to me six months ago.
A hundred grand per trip.
Just a few runs to catch up.
That's all it was meant to be.
Who else besides Curtis and Troy
are in on it?
Tim and Reggie.
The ex-cons?
That's why you hired them? [scoffs]
Harlan, the bank is on top of me.
We're gonna lose
the restaurants, the marina…
You had no right to go behind my back.
Behind your back?
We did it under your nose.
You were too busy
drinking and whoring around to notice.
Do not put this on me.
I was recovering.
"Recovering"? Is that what jacked up
on Viagra and bourbon is called?
This was your best thinking?
Christ, where's your memory?!
-You know what happened.
-If you're hell-bent on dying, do it!
Get it over with!
[exhales]
You think I want to die?
I don't think you want to live.
[scoffs] Christ…
Yes.
[releases cork]
-[pours liquor]
-Cane and I made a shit decision.
But we also kept the bank
from impounding every boat in the harbor.
You lived this with me.
You saw it kill my dad.
Destroy my mother.
I did everything I could
to get away from it.
[pensive music playing]
Well, here we are.
[music builds]
Just don't make it look
like I'm wearing makeup, please.
You know, you can always hit back.
Or learn to duck.
Uh-huh.
Uh, I ran into Jenna yesterday.
I know.
She told me.
We texted this morning.
Oh.
Sad about her dad, isn't it?
I don't think he's got much time.
Yeah, it's very sad.
You know, we want to do a dinner.
Her husband flies into town this weekend.
Maybe sometime next week?
Well, is that okay with you?
What are we, 12?
You dated in high school.
Please. I like Jenna.
We were always friends.
You know I hate
all the women in this town.
That's true.
-I'm happy she's here.
-Thank you, baby.
["Star of Monterey"
by Ben Chapman playing]
♪ She rode in on the Star of Monterey ♪
♪ Took my breath before she rolled away ♪
♪ Said she never meant to break my heart ♪
♪ Now all we were… ♪
Hey.
-What are you doing here?
-Hey.
I'm just, you know, wandering around.
Avoiding work.
-Are you wearing makeup?
-[awkwardly] No.
Mm.
-How's your dad?
-Fine. He's at home resting.
Do you have a black eye?
Come on, it's not that bad.
-Well, you've seen me way worse.
-Maybe. In high school, after a game.
You'd get so black and blue.
You always bruised easy.
Did they find those guys?
Uh, Curtis and Troy?
No, not yet. No.
-So awful.
-Yeah.
I remember Troy.
He was two years after us.
I-- I read some of your articles online.
-[laughs sheepishly] Okay.
-What? You're a good writer.
Thank you.
-You are.
-Hmm.
Peyton tells me
you're running the fish house now.
Mm-hmm.
I'm trying to, you know.
How come you never left?
That was the plan.
You were gonna play college ball.
What happened?
-The obvious. I wasn't good enough.
-Oh, bullshit.
-You were recruited by everyone.
-It was all hype.
-[scoffs]
-Yeah, not a single bite.
Seriously, I just wasn't good enough.
I got close, but yeah. Almost.
I'm really good at almost.
How so?
Oh, I'm just, you know,
almost good enough.
I'm almost a good guy.
I'm almost a good husband, father, son.
[makes shooting noises]
Just not quite, you know.
It's going to be
the name of my memoir. Almost.
What about you?
What's the, uh, title of your memoir?
I'll get back to you on that one.
No, no, no. Come on.
First thing that comes to your mind.
Okay.
-Okay, what?
-That's it. That's the name of my memoir.
Just Okay.
-Well, that's depressing.
-Worse than Almost?
[both chuckle]
[customer] Morning.
[Jenna] Good morning.
Uh… [whispering] Excuse me.
[softly] Go.
Hey there. How can I help you?
-I was looking for this shade right here.
-Okay, great.
♪ I'll let her in
Anytime she wants to stay ♪
[sighs]
♪ I'll let her win
Anytime she wants to play ♪
♪ I'll let her in
If she ever wants to stay ♪
[music fades]
Tim.
Reggie. I'm Harlan.
[Cane] Were you able to talk to him?
It didn't go so well.
He blames me, and he's right to.
Okay, that is bullshit.
It's a hard time for your dad.
His body's giving out.
It's not easy for a man like him. He can--
He can feel it ending.
Bullshit on that too.
You have a heart attack,
you put down the salt.
You don't keep carrying on like he does.
He disrespects you.
Listen, son.
You can't get everything in one person.
-[footsteps approaching]
-[Belle] Here he comes.
What was that about?
In a minute. You talk to Hoyt?
Yeah, I talked to him.
I wouldn't say it went very well.
-He thinks I took the shipment for myself.
-Nah, he's lying.
-Well, he thinks I'm the one lying.
-You're being played.
Ten to one, Hoyt stole the shipment
and is setting you up to take the fall.
Why would Hoyt do that?
It's so short-sighted.
Ten million blinds a man.
You need to find who he's working for
and go straight to the source.
You told me his name was Owen.
That's all I know.
Hoyt was very tight-lipped about it all.
He didn't even introduce us.
And you just accepted that.
Jesus, you're not cut out for this.
Yeah, no shit.
I screwed up.
That's been well-established.
But you've been down this road before,
so get off your goddamn high horse.
None of this is helping, Cane.
The difference is, my dad was in control.
This is someone else's operation.
You don't know who you're working for.
-Everything was fine until this.
-Because that's what this is.
It's all key lime pie until you come home
and find your wife and kid dead.
[Harlan exhales weakly]
Clearly you're up to something, Harlan.
What is it?
[atmospheric music playing]
You get Hoyt to come see me.
Tell him I want to resolve this.
I want to cut a deal.
Big money.
He'll be too stupid not to come.
And what are you going to do?
I'm going to take control of things.
[gulls calling overhead]
What is this about, Cane?
Look, my dad's got
a proposition for you, okay?
Just hear him out.
If it's about Owen,
you know I can't help you.
It's a waste of time.
Hello, boys. Come aboard.
We ain't going nowhere.
Just want to talk inside in private.
["Heaven Hill" by Sterling Elza playing]
[Harlan] Double Eagle. Ten years old.
That's a $3,000 bottle.
Thank you, Pop.
[boat engine starts with steady growl]
What the hell?
♪ Preacher man found dead by the bottle ♪
♪ It's a hard-living life on the sand ♪
♪ Tired of fighting this one-man battle ♪
♪ So he flew his white flag
And let Heaven Hill win ♪
What's going on?
Who are these guys?
Oh, Tim and Reggie?
They work at the fish house.
Compliments of the Carolina Correctional
Center Transition Initiative.
It's a great program
where some of the more hardcore offenders
get a second chance.
But don't worry.
They're completely reformed.
Let's drink.
♪ So don't you get it twisted
When the Devil comes around ♪
♪ He'll leave you high and dry
With nothing left but a frown ♪
[music continues]
[song stops]
[gritty music playing]
So, Hoyt,
tell me about this Owen fellow.
Turn the boat around. I want to go back.
My dad and I used to do what you do
back in the '80s.
With some Colombian fellas. Good men.
Respectful. Well-dressed.
Now it's just a bunch of roughnecks
looking for a payday
from any asshole with a poppy field.
[scoffs]
Is that what you think this is?
Hoyt.
We know you took the drugs.
-Does Owen know what a snake you are?
-He believes what I tell him.
Why is he doing that?
[unsettling music creeping in]
Uh, yeah, Dad. What-- what's that about?
Curtis and Troy were good men.
Both have wives and kids.
You killed them yourself,
or someone else do it?
Is that a shark?
And then you try to blame it on my son.
It's really stupid, Hoyt.
But you were dumb enough
to get on this boat, so…
No, no!
-Dad!
-[Hoyt] No!
[Cane] Whoa, hey! Stop.
-[Hoyt grunts in desperation]
-Dad! Dad!
-Stop!
-[Hoyt] No!
[screaming] No, no! Oh, God!
-Where are the drugs?
-[Hoyt] I don't know anything!
[bubbling and thrashing]
[screams]
Where is it?
-[loud snap]
-[gurgled scream]
[intense music playing]
[screams]
Don't you drop me!
-I wouldn't wiggle so much.
-Pull me up!
Dad, stop!
He's not gonna tell you anything.
Oh no, no, no, no!
[muffled grunts]
[intense music continues]
[gurgled cry]
[yells] It's locked up in a shed off 17!
Pull me up, god damn it. Pull me up!
-Once more.
-[Hoyt] No, no, no!
For me.
[scream drowns into muffled gurgle]
[Hoyt] No! No!
[Hoyt's screams echo in the distance]
Oh, excuse me.
[clears throat]
Hey, babe. I could have picked you up.
Dad dropped us off.
I need you to take us home.
Hi, Bree.
Hi, Miss Swanson.
You can call me Daphne.
I think we graduated to first names.
Mm-hmm.
I got us a table in the lounge.
[indistinct chatter]
[light jazz music
playing in the background]
Um, I'll just sit here.
Great.
I told you I wanted to go to a mall.
-I need new sneakers.
-You texted too late.
-I texted you.
-I didn't have time to file the paperwork.
Can this please be okay?
Diller, is that you?
Look at you growing by the second.
-Hi, honey.
-Hey, Grandma.
Mom, this is Ms. Swanson,
our court-appointed monitor.
-You can call me Daphne.
-Oh, hey, Daphne.
Isabelle Buckley, nice to meet you.
Uh, dinner's on us. Anything you want.
Mm!
[Bree clears her throat]
How'd you do on the relay?
We lost.
How's school?
Sucks donkey dick.
You dating any girls?
Boys?
[sarcastically] Mostly group sex.
Hmm.
How's Georgina?
She's awesome.
I mean, she even lets me call her Mommy.
Well, aren't you
a delightful little prick?
[ominous music playing]
It's in the shed.
[ominous music rising]
[engine stops]
[Harlan] So what was the plan, Hoyt?
Who's behind this?
I know it ain't you.
Some man from Jersey offered a better cut.
They're sending a truck for it.
[Harlan] Looks like you made a mess
with a whole bunch of people.
What's the code?
0624.
[lock jiggling]
[hinges groan]
[uneasy music playing]
[music rising]
Boy, this is some tight security
you got here, Hoyt.
[loud siren bursts in]
[Cane] Oh, shit.
[siren blares]
Let me do the talking.
[ominous music playing]
Evening, fellas.
Clyde.
This is a bit odd.
-What am I looking at here, Harlan?
-Maybe you should ask Hoyt.
They are dealing drugs.
They double-crossed their supplier.
-He's lying, Clyde.
-[Hoyt] I'm not. They kidnapped me.
Look, my hands are tied.
[whispers] I haven't told them anything.
Thank you, Hoyt.
I appreciate it.
-[loud gunshot]
-Oh! Holy shit!
[gasps]
[music rises sharply, then subsides]
[Cane] Oh, God.
[Canes exhales]
I guess that would make you Owen.
Oh, my son's firstborn is named Owen.
I just always liked the name.
-Guess I didn't know that.
-No, you wouldn't.
[panting]
So tell me, Clyde Owen,
how do we reconcile tonight?
Well, we've reached
a turning point here, Harlan.
-I don't know what that means.
-It means it's late, Cane.
We can go home. It's all good.
You know,
I always looked up to you, Harlan.
We're friends.
-Always have been.
-[Clyde] You would see it that way.
You're friends to everyone.
I mean, it helps coming
from that big house you grew up in.
Yeah, the mighty Buckleys of Havenport
now owe me.
[fateful music plays]
So, yeah. Yeah, we're good.
You know, my pipeline has sprung a leak.
And I need to fill it.
Now, I know you're used
to being the boss man.
[lock clicks]
So we can use
the word "partners" if you like.
We'll… sort out the rest of it later.
Uh… what about, um, Hoyt?
You can deal with Hoyt.
We've been playing nice with you, son.
It's time you got your hands dirty.
[brooding music playing]
[police pickup door closes]
[engine rumbling]
[Harlan] All right,
let's get this over with.
[groans]
Pick him up.
-You got it?
-Yeah.
-Okay, on three. Ready?
-Okay.
One, two, three!
[heavy splash as body hits water]
[Cane] Oh, shit.
Oh, Jesus.
[Harlan] You're gonna have to get in.
You shitting me?
No, I'm not.
Get in.
-No.
-[water bubbles]
-There's-- There's alligators in there.
-That's the idea.
Absolutely not.
[sighing] Okay, princess.
Grab an oar.
Try to push him down.
The tree's roots are all around.
We're going to push him down,
see if we can wedge him under one.
[foreboding music playing]
This is unbelievable.
[oar squelches through water]
[Cane grunts]
[thick sloshing]
Use some muscle.
He floats to the top.
What do you want me to do?
Put your back into it.
Yeah, I'm trying, okay?
If you just stop talking and let me do it.
God damn it.
[sloshing continues]
[Cane] Yeah, there it is. There it is.
[somber music swells]
[Cane] There.
I think that's it.
[oars clatter]
[exhales]
What now, huh?
We let the alligators do the rest.
What about the sheriff?
He's another problem. I'll han--
We'll handle it.
You realize we've crossed a line.
There's no coming back from this.
Don't have a meltdown
right here in the mud!
[grunts]
[Cane] Shit.
Ow. God damn it.
I'm sorry.
Do not apologize.
Jesus, what's wrong with you?
-You don't hit a man and then apologize.
-Stop, please, stop.
You let the hit sink in
and come back the next day--
-Will you stop?! Just stop!
-You can't even hit right!
Jesus Christ! Will you ever stop?!
Unbelievable.
You drink too much.
-It's going to kill me.
-Yeah, well, hurry it up.
[pensive music playing]
You did good tonight, son.
I'm impressed.
Why? Because I hit you?
No.
I never thought you'd touch a dead body.
You proved me wrong.
[Cane] Let's get out of here.
[engine starts]
I'll let you both say goodnight.
I'll be outside.
[Diller sighs]
The house looks new.
The perk of burning down a house
is that you get a new one.
No one was hurt.
Physically.
I know you act like you hate me,
but I know better.
Hold up.
Diller!
-Hang on!
-What?!
You said you wanted Air Jordans.
You didn't say what kind, so I…
I got you one of each.
Seriously?
So, you're trying to buy my love now?
Is it working?
No.
But I'll take the shoes.
One more.
What's wrong with you?
I don't know, sweetheart.
But I'm trying to fix it.
Cash works too.
That's pure lazy.
I love--
[bittersweet music playing]
[door opens]
[door closes]
[bittersweet music continues]
[door opens]
You know, you should close your curtains.
People can see right in.
What happened to the porch swing?
Yeah, that's been gone for a few years.
Oh, man.
What are you doing here, Cane?
Florida wanted me.
Scholarship. Full ride.
Hmm.
Why'd you lie?
Uh, I lie to everybody about it.
Mostly me.
My dad thought it would be a big mistake.
Said I might be good for college ball,
but I'd never make it to the pros.
-Where's his crystal ball?
-Yeah.
He said the disappointment would break me,
but I could live with the never knowing.
Jesus.
So I didn't go.
But who needs college, right? [chuckles]
Guess I was always meant
to be in the fish house,
but… what could be
better than that, right?
Did something happen tonight?
Yeah, a lot happened.
Do you want to talk about it?
[smacks lips]
I just wanted to tell you the truth.
I hate that I lied to you.
[Jenna sighs]
Do I need to remind the drunk person
that I'm married?
I'm married too.
[inhales]
Peyton's been really sweet to me.
And, um, I think you'd like Scott too,
if you give him a chance.
I hope we can be friends, Cane.
Okay.
[gentle music playing]
Just okay?
Almost okay.
You see what I did there?
-Put together our memoirs.
-Yeah. I got that.
[sighs]
Good night, Cane.
See you, Jenna.
[Jenna clears her throat quietly]
["Don't You Dare" by Ben Chapman playing]
[Belle] Hey.
What happened? Where's Cane?
I sent him home.
I'll tell you everything later.
I don't want to rehash it right now.
You're here.
That's all I want.
You here for a long time.
I took a step backwards today.
It was so easy.
Comfortable.
Like it was waiting for me.
♪ So if you're thinking
About breaking my heart ♪
♪ Don't you dare ♪
Let's go home.
[Harlan, softly] Mm-hm.
♪ So you got me where you want me ♪
♪ I ain't goin' anywhere ♪
♪ So if you're thinking
About breaking my heart ♪
♪ Don't you dare ♪
[music ends]
You're late.
I'm here now.
What do you have for me?
You need to check out Hoyt Piper.
Cane was with him again today.
[tense music builds]
[music fades and ends]
[closing theme music playing]