Here, take a swig.
And don't backwash.
Shit! Don't break it.
It's time for the nuns' rosary.
This is 8th-grade history.
Stealing the sacramental wine?
It's not sacramental
till they bless it.
All clear!
Are you gonna confess this?
I'll tell them I stole something,
not what.
Go! Form it up!
Form it up, let's go, boys.
Hustle, hustle, hustle!
There we go, straight lines.
Straight lines.
There you go.
Soprano, DiCarlucci, shake a leg.
Jumping jacks.
Ten of them, count them down.
- Three, four, five...
- Two, three...
six, seven, eight...
four, five, six...
nine, ten.
seven, eight, nine...
DiCarlucci, Barber, Soprano,
let's go! Sync up!
What's so funny? Care to share?
Sorry, Mr. Meskimmin.
Okay, kick-outs, boys!
Floor! Kick!
Return! Up!
I'm dizzier than shit!
Kick! Return! Up!
Fuck, here he comes.
Whoa, floor, kick, turn, up!
What's going on here?
Come on, stand up, on your feet,
let's go.
Whoa.
- Man!
- I don't feel so good.
I don't want any excuses.
Mr. Meskimmin, I gotta go
to the bathroom.
Is that alcohol on your breath?
Hey, how's the boy?
How am I? I got dust up the crack
of my ass, and I'm starving to death.
You're doing an excellent job.
Take pleasure in that.
He's been ragging in my ear all day.
I'd like to kill him. Hear that, prick?
Get him out of here.
Just get him the hell out of here.
- Is there a problem?
- You made your point.
- I made my point.
- What point?
- Enough with work stoppage.
This union safety official stays until
he deems this place is free of hazard.
- I have the money.
- You do?
Christopher, see if he's paid up
his union dues...
...then pop a wheel cover
to check the brakes.
I'll get right on it.
I'll get your money, okay?
We shall return.
Halle-fucking-lujah!
Give me your cell.
I gotta call Carmela.
You sure it was them?
They were drunk in gym class. Byron
Barber vomited all over the teacher.
I spat it out.
Anthony.
You're gonna lie to me now?
He's sorry, Father Hagy.
He'll be sorrier when he gets home.
Anthony, why don't you wait outside?
He's suspended for three days.
Let me pay for the wine.
This isn't just
a crime against property...
...it's an affront
to our holy sacristy.
I've asked Dr. Galani,
our school psychologist, to join us.
He's been keeping an eye on Anthony.
Meeting with his teachers.
Why don't you pick it up
from there, doctor?
Um, hi.
In many respects, Anthony is
a normal, healthy 8th-grader.
Sister Patricia, his art teacher...
...thinks he shows strong skills
in spatial orientation.
But the thing is, and it's not
just this one incident...
...Anthony sometimes has trouble
following the rules...
...weighing consequences.
At times, doesn't think
before he acts.
And...
...it's thought that there's a good
possibility Anthony could be ADD.
ADD?
- Attention deficit disorder.
- I knew it.
- I knew there was something.
- What is it?
It's an aggregate of symptoms.
Inattention, impulsivity...
...sometimes, although not always,
hyperactivity.
To be sure, we'll give him
a thorough evaluation.
He needs a whack upside the head.
If he's got an illness?
It's an illness, right?
You'd hit somebody who's sick?
You'd hit somebody with polio?
You hit Anthony?
Nobody gets hit in our house.
Not exactly my idea.
What's happening if you can't
do a little tarantella on the kids...
...when they step out of line?
So what happens now?
He'll be given a complete battery
of testing.
Psychological, behavioral, medical.
Let me ask you a question.
These other kids,
you keeping an eye on them?
Are you testing them?
The ones that aren't named Soprano?
There's no immediate plans for that.
We attend to every child at Verbum Dei
according to his own circumstances.
And so what do we,
as the parents, do?
Nothing?
Oh, no, I mean, Anthony's misbehaved.
He should be consequenced.
It's a crime!
To suspend that child from school
with all the money you give them?
That gym teacher shit a brick when your
friend puked on his boots, huh, Anthony?
Want to encourage him?
Whatever happened
to "boys will be boys"?
He stole from the church.
They don't make them any lower.
- What a loser.
- That's enough out of you.
Oh, his father was the same way.
I practically lived
in that vice principal's office.
Could we not, please?
You only remember
what you want to remember.
Yeah, well, I must've had
another son...
...who stole a car when he was
10 years old.
He could barely see over the wheel.
He was a hellion.
Him and his little crew...
...they stole lobsters on the boats...
...and sold them for a buck
on Bloomfield Avenue.
Really?
How many times must I say it?
I don't want that talk in front of him.
That is wrong, and I don't condone it!
Yeah. Sure.
- Who are you yelling at?
- What?
You stupe.
- What did you say?
- I didn't say anything.
What's he doing now? What's going on?
He yells at me...
Anthony, I thought this could wait
till after dinner.
Your father and I have talked.
You are not to play Mario Cart
or go skateboarding for three weeks.
And no TV.
No.
You won't sit on that Internet.
And every day, you'll ride your bike
to go visit Grandma.
Oh, that'll be nice.
It's not fair!
- Some fucking day, huh?
- I feel like a bomb went off.
You know that stuff the doctor said?
I never saw any of that in Anthony.
You never notice how he picks
at the tongue of his shoe?
Like he can't help himself.
If he even has this thing.
Something's going on.
- Carm?
- Yep?
- Do you think he knows?
- I don't know.
She knows.
- Are you...?
- Really?
- What makes you say that?
- Are you in...?
I don't know. Things she says. She
makes remarks, like this today with him.
- Are you in the Mafia?
- She talk to you about me?
Talk? To me?
Something happen on that college trip?
Happen?
Like what?
I don't know, she seemed peculiar
when she got back.
I think pretty soon we're gonna
have to, you know...
...talk to her about the business.
Yeah. The two of us
should sit down with Meadow.
Talk as a family.
With him, they'll test him
and we'll see what's what.
Right?
Good night.
Maybe I don't want to admit
something's wrong with my kid...
...but this sounds like bullshit.
What do you mean?
If he's got a disease, why punish him?
Isn't that bullshit?
ADD is a controversial subject.
Is it a disease, or a way for
psychologists to line their pockets?
Many children can really benefit
by professional intervention.
He got in trouble.
So you don't consider his behavior
out of the norm?
No.
I don't know.
What do I know about it?
What do you mean?
Oh, I gotta spell it out for you?
Do you see his behavior
as a reflection of your own?
Look, like I said, maybe I don't want
to admit there's something wrong...
...but if he's got this thing...
...we'll deal with it.
If he had polio, we'd deal with it.
You pick up the pieces
and you go on from there.
So that's what we're gonna do.
Do you want to say anything else
about this?
Well, last time you were telling me
that you had intimate feelings for me.
But you've not mentioned it.
Intimate feelings?
I think I said I was in love.
How are you doing with it?
I can't turn off my feelings because
you say it's a byproduct of therapy.
I never said to
turn off your feelings.
Well, I already got a girlfriend.
She's Russian, 24.
How old are you?
It's interesting it took you so long
to tell me you had a girlfriend.
How are you doing with it?
I gotta ask you one more question
about my son.
You think I should
go easy on him now...
...or press him harder?
That's difficult to say.
What, you want a raise, maybe,
to figure this out?
Anthony! Anthony Jr., you get up!
Why? I don't have to go to school.
I'm suspended.
No lying in bed all day.
We're not running a hotel over here.
Get up, have some breakfast!
I don't want any. I'm not hungry.
What you are gonna do today
is get up and go rake.
Then pull all of those leaves
out of the pool filter.
You're gonna do some work around here.
Mom, where's my gray jacket?
I left it downstairs.
What'd you do with it?
Hello?
Anthony, turn off that music!
Your father is sleeping!
You said I couldn't watch TV
or play Nintendo.
- What?
- You said nothing about music!
- Turn it off right now!
- Why?
Your father is sleeping,
for chrissake!
Mom, I can't find it. Where is it?
Hey, Johnny!
Johnny, come on!
Uncle Jun, why are you here so early?
Anthony, where's your dad?
He said he'd be outside.
Want me to go get him?
Did you hear the game last night?
Joey Pepitone, three RBIs.
No kidding.
My mom made me go to bed.
You miss your bus to school...
...you walk through
the colored neighborhood.
Junior! Big fancy car.
We're going to my sister's,
and you promised to...
Nonstop!
Don't you get sick of yourself?
Dad, could you and Uncle Jun give me
a ride to school?
Not now, Tony.
You be good, though.
Pay attention to what
those teachers tell you.
Okay.
- See you, Ma.
- Okay. Be good.
Hey, wait up!
Shit!
Hey, Rocco!
Come on, move, move, guys!
Move, move!
Hey, John, one more day, man!
One more day.
- There's gonna be a huge payoff.
- I'm gonna kill you!
What do you got?
What the fuck is this?
What the fuck are you bringing me here?
Who are you fucking with, Rocco?
- Fuck you!
- Motherfucker!
You asshole!
What are you bringing to me here?
Piece of shit!
What the fucking...?
Christ!
You're up.
Who the fuck can sleep
with all this shit going on?
I thought about Jefferson Airplane
this morning. How about that?
1967.
- Made me think of my father.
- What about him?
First time I saw him
whack the shit out of somebody.
What made you think about that?
Something to do with my son, I think,
what's been going on.
Why did your father
whack the shit out of some guy?
I never saw him do something
like that.
He used to whack us kids around
a little.
Really?
Yeah, the belt was his favorite
child development tool.
This was different.
You could tell he knew
what he was doing.
How did you feel about
your father after that?
I didn't want him to do it to me.
Seriously.
What should I say?
I was glad he wasn't a fag.
- How did you and your father get along?
- Good.
He was a good guy, my father.
Everybody liked him.
He knew how to have a good time.
He loved shellfish, clams, oysters.
Taught us how to eat them. You put
Worcestershire on, suck them down.
It's good.
My mother never ate anything raw.
But he wasn't around much.
What did he do for a living?
Retail meat and provisions.
And a little numbers,
extortion, loan-sharking.
How did you feel about that?
- How did I feel?
- About your father...
...being engaged
in illegal activities?
You know,
I never really knew about it.
When did you find out?
Who remembers?
You thought of that incident
this morning.
Are you concerned that your son is
going to find out about you?
Don't talk to me about
legitimate business.
What about chemical companies?
Dumping that shit into rivers and they
got deformed babies popping up all over.
Does he know anything?
I don't know.
Has he asked you?
No.
- How will you handle that?
- I don't know.
Did you ever talk to
your father about it?
Are you kidding?
No kidding, Tony.
That doesn't sound like Anthony.
Yesterday, he's a boy.
Today, I worry about him.
Teenagers.
My daughter gives me
feminist shit about this place.
How it "objectifies women."
Shit like that.
These girls pull down 1500 a week.
This bears no weight
with the principessa.
Meadow was one thing,
but this is my son.
Boys are different from girls.
Pussy, Kevin and Matt, they ever ask
you about this thing of ours?
I lied through my teeth,
but they knew. Fucking nitwits.
They love me anyway.
It's hard to raise kids
in an information age.
You know, to protect them.
Hey, what's up?
Who's got an anniversary
or a special occasion?
What are these, antiques?
I was picking up the Chinaman's vig,
and the FedEx van was wide open.
The guy went in for a burger.
No shit, FedEx. They're usually
pretty careful with those.
You did this in daylight?
Nobody saw me.
That's interstate commerce.
You want to be in prison
for a stunt like that, be my guest.
I'd take a licking
but keep on ticking.
I'm getting out of here.
Jesus Christ!
What's with his ass?
He's got a lot on his mind.
What do you think is going on
in this one, Anthony?
I don't know.
How many more are left?
The quicker you answer,
the faster we'll be done.
Whatever pops in your mind.
There's no guy?
Okay, good.
Where do you think he is?
Out buying food for the horse?
Anything else?
Watching TV, maybe?
Maybe he's watching South Park.
Number one's on tonight.
Aliens abduct Cartman and give him an
anal probe and it makes him fart fire.
You're home.
You know, if it's bad, the ADD,
they put Anthony in special ed.
The doctors say that?
Doctors don't know anything yet.
They started testing today.
I picked up these books at the mall.
Help Me To Help My Child?
Listen to this.
"About 50% of children
diagnosed with ADD...
...receive help from
special education teachers."
We don't even know
that's what he's got.
You're right. Let's just be ignorant.
Why worry about anything now?
You blame me, don't you?
Who said anything about that?
No, go ahead. You blame me.
I blame myself.
- For what?
- For what.
For staying with me?
I have two eyes.
Who do we blame our daughter on?
Straight-A student, National Honor
Society, featured soloist in the choir.
Yeah, this isn't going anywhere.
"Like father, like son," right?
What about "Daddy's little girl"?
My son's got your Uncle Lenny in his
gene pool. Do I blame you for that?
If it helps you.
Hi, Grandma.
Well, look who's here.
- Oh, look at that little face.
- Ow.
Pearl, meet my grandson.
This is your grandson?
He rode his bike all the way over
to visit his grandma.
How do you like that?
How come he's not in school?
- Because he was a bad boy!
- Ow.
Yes, he was, that's why.
He's a big one!
She had a stroke.
Now half her brain is gone.
So what shall we do?
What shall we do?
Let's see.
Let's play Scrabble.
You'd be surprised how good
your grandmother is.
I don't think so, Gram.
I'm kind of wiped.
Oh, you're a 13-year-old boy.
You're too young to be so tired.
They sent me to a psychiatrist
all morning. I took a million tests.
A psychiatrist?
You know, because I got
suspended and everything.
They sent you to a psychiatrist?
Yeah.
But that's crazy.
That's all nonsense.
That's nothing but a racket
for the Jews!
Dad goes.
- He does not.
- Yes, he does.
To a psychiatrist?
Yeah.
He does not.
He does too.
Why do you say that?
That's ridiculous!
I heard him and Mom talking about it.
What does he need a psychiatrist for?
Is it okay if I take
that pear, Grandma?
He goes to talk about his mother.
That's what he's doing.
He talks about me, he complains.
"She didn't do this, she did that."
Oh, I gave my life to my children
on a silver platter.
And this is how he repays me.
- Dad, what's that noise?
- Noise?
It's a flat tire.
I asked you to clean the nails
from the driveway.
I was praying for something like this.
I spent too much money on braces
for two years...
...not to take you to the dentist now.
Maybe we should call the Auto Club.
We change tires at our house.
Watch and learn.
Yesterday, with the psychologist,
how'd that go?
Okay.
Yeah? What'd you guys do?
He made me look at pictures. And then
I had to say something about them.
Did you talk about
anything interesting?
That's kind of between
me and my therapist.
He said I don't have to
say anything if I didn't want to.
That's what we pay extra for
at that school?
The other night at dinner,
you made a remark.
- No, I didn't.
- Yeah, you did.
I'm not mad. I just need to know
what you meant by it.
I didn't mean anything.
Come on.
Kids at school said some stuff.
What'd they say?
That you were in the Mafia.
What do you think?
I don't know.
The guys at
Uncle Jackie's funeral.
And those other guys writing
license plates and taking pictures.
Those were feds, right?
Like in Godfather I.
Uncle Jackie's funeral. Right.
I found this page with Uncle Jackie
on the Web.
It said he ran some union that ripped
off these pension things or something.
Uncle Jackie was a complicated man.
But you loved him, right?
Yeah.
You didn't see me on the Web, did you?
No.
That's right.
Give me a hand so we can
get the algae scraped off your teeth.
I'm going crazy with this shit,
what he knows, what he doesn't know.
He'll find out eventually.
What's the difference?
Me, my father. It's probably
in the genes, right?
You know, this ADD thing.
It's probably genetical.
What about Pussy?
He's an acquaintance of mine.
This guy is a stone gangster,
and he's got three kids.
One graduated,
and two are going to Villanova.
- How do you account for that?
- Then you got Leopold and Loeb.
They murdered this kid for fun...
...and their father was
a successful businessman.
Do you hold your father responsible
for what you've become?
Sometimes I think about
what life would've been like...
...if my father hadn't gotten mixed up
in what he got mixed up in.
How life would've been different.
Maybe I'd be selling patio furniture
in San Diego.
We talked last time about
how you felt when you became aware...
...of your father's criminal life.
Any more thoughts on that?
When you first started therapy,
you said you had this dream...
...about those ducks.
They flew away with your penis.
It was a bad omen...
...that something was going to happen
in your family.
Is this the terrible thing?
Look, if you know something, please,
quit fucking around.
I think it's important to remember.
You said you liked
the History Channel.
He who doesn't understand history
is doomed to repeat it.
- Let's talk about your father.
- My father.
Heads up!
Why are you smiling?
Just thinking about my uncle.
He used to throw the ball with me.
The one with whom you have
all the static?
Yeah.
Uncle Jun.
He was always practicing his curve ball
outside in front of the house.
I was probably about 8 or 9.
Then my sister came out.
The one who lives in California?
Janice.
How does she feel about your parents?
Who cares what she thinks?
She calls herself Vishnamantha.
Soprano isn't good enough for her.
Wannabe dot-head.
Why were you thinking of your uncle?
I don't know.
What are you doing?
I'm getting in the car.
Why? Where are you going?
Someplace.
Where are you going?
Can I come?
Your mom wants you to get
the screens down to the basement.
No, I want to go with you guys.
He said no.
Janice...
...you both won't be going,
you talk to your brother like that.
Go on.
My mother was inside, cooking the meat
for the gravy, you know, the "red lead."
Pork bones and veal.
It was a Sunday.
- But you said...
- I said we'd see.
What's the matter with her?
She won't eat.
You won't have to get me anything
for Christmas.
You won't have to tell me
to take the trash out.
I shouldn't have to tell you
Why can't I have this?
It isn't fair!
I don't want to hear about
that stupid electric organ!
It's not stupid, it's fun.
Enough! He won't give me
a moment's peace.
If Janice wanted it, she'd get it.
She always gets what she wants.
Where were they going?
Why couldn't I go?
Your sister does as she's told.
Right, I forgot.
Janice never does anything wrong.
She's just perfect.
You're driving me crazy!
No, I'm not.
She said what?
She was high-strung,
very dramatic.
Every night to her is
a night at the opera.
I could stick this fork in your eye!
She wasn't gonna do it.
Holy shit, that's why
I'm remembering all this.
- On account of where they were going.
- Where were they going?
I found out a couple Sundays later.
The toll now stands
at 11 dead and 600 wounded...
...as well as
hundreds of businesses...
Mom, I'm going to
the CYO to play ball.
Take a bat with you, what they're
doing on Springfield Avenue.
- looting and sniper fire
along Springfield Avenue continue...
...with Mayor Hugh Addonizio placing
blame on outside agitators...
Come on, Dad, let's go!
I'm coming, I'm coming.
Keep your sticky fingers off the car.
I just waxed the damn thing.
Can I steer?
Maybe on the way home, honey.
Here we are.
Come on.
Uncle Jun?
Buy something nice.
My heart was broken.
You felt your father was
showing favoritism.
I still remember that feeling
in the pit of my stomach.
Did you confront them?
Have you been listening to me?
Kids don't confront in my family.
How does this pertain to
the situation with your son?
This amusement park is where I found
out my father wasn't like other fathers.
I took the bus this time.
It was three transfers from Newark.
I had this candy bar in my pocket.
It had sand or lint
or something on it.
What you doing?
Where you spitting?
I ain't doing nothing!
You threw that wrapper on the floor.
- Pick it up!
- Leave me alone!
Come back! Pick it up!
What in the world?
Stop or I'll shoot!
You're under arrest!
Stop!
You're under arrest.
My leg!
Name was Cicchi Sasso, my
father's cousin on his mother's side.
Got out of Vietnam on account
of cops blew his kneecap off.
What's the matter with you cops?
Can't bring your kid to
an amusement park no more?
Daddy! Daddy!
It's okay, baby. It's okay.
You go home to Mommy, sweetheart.
Va fangool, why don't you go
lock up the melanzane?
They're burning down Newark.
I want my lawyer.
I'm not saying shit to you.
That's Johnny-boy Soprano!
Asshole, you're hurting my wrist.
Get the fuck in there, Clarabell.
He used Janice as a front.
They brought their daughters...
...so that their business
looked sweet and innocent.
That must've been devastating.
It turned out it was no big deal.
To see your father handcuffed
and led away by the police?
Well, at the time I thought
my head was gonna explode.
He looked helpless.
But when I got home, my mother
had a different perspective.
Which made me feel better.
So in her pain,
she reached out to you.
That's one way to put it.
Your father may not be home
for dinner. Go wash up.
- I know.
- What do you know?
I saw him getting arrested.
What did he do?
He didn't do anything!
They just pick on Italians.
Still, in my heart, I knew
my father was no freedom fighter.
So he went to jail?
He came home in a couple hours.
We were watching Ed Sullivan.
Hey! Livia!
Look who's home.
- What happened?
I got you cherry vanilla
at Nasto's.
That didn't take long.
Must be in good with the uppity-ups.
Let this be a lesson.
Those stupid cops,
they went to the wrong place.
Arrested the wrong guys.
How's my little girl?
You all right?
- I'm okay.
- Good.
Johnny-boy! Hey, Johnny-boy!
Good for you, Johnny.
Show those fucking sons of bitches.
What's up, Rocco?
So...
...everything okay?
I don't understand.
The man your father beat up...
...was the same one
congratulating him?
Yeah. One of them.
Rocco Allatore.
Why'd they arrest him?
He was in violation of his parole.
Association with known undesirables.
But nothing ever happened.
It just went away.
He'd been in prison?
He was away when I was a kid...
...but they told me he was
in Montana being a cowboy.
What?
My son is doomed, right?
Why do you say that?
This is the part where
I'm supposed to tell you...
...how terrible my father was
and the terrible things he did...
...and how he ruined my life.
But I'll tell you, I was proud
to be Johnny Soprano's kid.
When he beat the shit
out of that guy...
...I told the class
how tough my father was.
Is that how your son feels about you?
Yeah, probably.
And I'm glad.
I'm glad if he's proud of me.
But that's the bind I'm in.
I don't want him to be like me.
He could be anything he wants.
He could be like a guy
I knew in school.
His grandfather invented
ties for the end of salamis.
He made millions of dollars.
He's sitting on his ass.
Have you communicated this
to your son?
Not in so many words.
Probably not at all.
What's the difference?
You said it.
It's in the blood. It's hereditary.
Genetic predispositions are only that.
Predispositions.
It's not a destiny written in stone.
People have choices.
She finally offers an opinion.
Well, they do. You think everything
that happens is preordained?
You don't think that human beings
possess free will?
How come I'm not making
fucking pots in Peru?
You're born to this shit.
You are what you are.
Within that there's
a range of choices.
This is America.
Right. America.
So, Livia, what do you think, huh?
Okies and misfits,
that's who goes there.
Losers, the Beverly Hillbillies.
So now Rocco Allatore's a loser?
I've had to rough Rocco up because of
money, but he's got a fucking brain.
He's opening a new book.
After that gets up,
we get a little cash flow...
Oh, Mr. Cash Flow!
Big businessman now.
What do you know?
You're scared of your own shadow.
Reno is growing by
leaps and bounds, Livia.
It's a chance to get in
on the ground floor.
After Rocco gets the book up,
he'll open a supper club.
- He wants me to run it.
- A supper club? Are you drunk?
Jesus Christ Almighty!
Fucking albacore around my neck!
Every time I try...
Me and the kids'll go without you!
They are not going anywhere!
I'd rather smother them with a pillow
than take them to Nevada!
Always with the drama!
Livia, here you are.
Junior, you scared me to death.
I can't stay, but I didn't want
to let another day go by.
Business headaches
like you won't believe.
Oh, yeah, you and the other one.
With all your headaches.
Who, Tony?
Don't be so hard on him.
He's got a lot to learn, but he's
headed in the right direction.
Where to?
Overbrook State Mental Hospital?
What?
Hey, Uncle Jun. How you doing?
He's keeping his hair.
You see, what a good boy,
he comes to visit his mother.
My son's staying for dinner, Junior.
I don't suppose you have time.
You two want to visit each other.
Junior's very busy these days
with his headaches.
Not too busy to shoot the shit
with you, Tony.
We gotta catch a ball game.
Hey, you got my number. All right.
That man.
He's so full of himself
since becoming caporegime.
He makes me sick.
Remember the Allatores, Ma?
Oh, why wouldn't I?
They moved to Nevada.
They're billionaires now.
Oh, that Rocco Allatore,
he was a real go-getter.
- Didn't Dad want to go with him?
- Your father? No.
Yeah, he did.
I remember you guys talking about it.
Allatore would start a business,
Dad would do it with him.
Rocco just got him all worked up,
that's all.
What is this with all
these questions?
Dad wanted to go with him.
You wouldn't let him.
Let him?
What do you mean?
You just tell me one time
your father didn't do...
...exactly as he wanted.
I don't know. Maybe this was
his chance to get out.
Dad was no choirboy, but maybe
with a little bit of support...
Mr. Sensitive now.
Well, if it bothers you, maybe
you better talk to a psychiatrist.
What are you talking about,
a psychiatrist?
That's what people do when they want
somebody to blame for their life.
You're a real stone player,
aren't you?
You threatened to smother
his children.
What does that mean?
Everybody thought Dad was ruthless,
but I gotta hand it to you.
If you'd been born
after those feminists...
...you would've been
the real gangster.
I don't know what
you're talking about!
Please, sit.
I know you're probably eager to hear
the results of our testing.
- How's Anthony doing?
- Good, I think. Don't you think so?
Yeah, I think so.
Okay.
Well, good.
Let's get to it.
The good news is, no evidence
of learning disability.
Cognitive function, verbal
and nonverbal intelligent testing...
...arithmetic and reading
evaluation...
...all within normal range.
- Thank goodness.
Got a clean bill of health.
No soft sign on
the neurological, either.
That's all the good news.
Why don't you tell us the bad news?
Well, as to whether
Anthony has ADD...
...the results were interesting.
The APA Standard is for the subject
to manifest six out of nine...
...possible symptoms of ADD.
In testing, Anthony manifested
five of those symptoms.
Five, really?
He often has difficulty
awaiting his turn...
...is often quote-unquote "on the go,"
or acts as if driven by a motor...
...often interrupts or intrudes
on others...
...and often fidgets
with hands or feet.
He fidgets with hands or feet?
That's right.
You mean, like, he fidgets.
Uh-huh.
And that's a sickness, to fidget?
Mr. Soprano, it's one of nine
possible symptoms.
What constitutes a fidget?
Tony...
No, no, what constitutes a fidget?
So what if he fidgets?
Who doesn't fidget in school?
The kid's in puberty.
He gets a hard-on every 10 minutes.
Anthony is a borderline case.
He's not a case,
he's a 13-year-old boy.
Every time you see a problem,
you turn it into a disease.
He's a kid who made a mistake,
and he'll pay for it.
But he's gonna be fine. Come on.
I think he's right.
And I don't think we should have to
pay for this testing.
To oppose this
massive force bearing down on Midway...
...Admiral Nimitz had no battleships
in shape for the fight.
However, he had the carriers...
...Yorktown, Enterprise and Hornet.
This might prove to be the trump card.
Studying?
Government.
It's not the end of the world, Anth.
I'm depressed.
You're not depressed.
You're sad because you did
something stupid, and you got grounded.
You can't watch TV or play on your
computer for a couple weeks.
It's gonna stay like that.
It isn't fair.
You got that right.
What are you doing?
What's it look like?
Can I have one too?
This one's yours.
Gonna need sprinkles.
Okay.
You want nuts?
Yeah. M&M's?
Pretty good.