http://hiqve.com/
Lottie.
"Dearest John,
"I don't even know
if you're getting these letters.
"I hope so.
"I hate to think of you in that place alone.
"I wish they'd let me visit.
"Life just goes on,
"but not for me.
"Not without you.
"The days are so long.
"I haven't seen Sister Harriet yet,
"but Mr. Cleary says
she seems to be bearing up.
"I don't know when the trial is.
"The groundbreaking
for the new hospital is next week,
"so Mr. Barrow has been
walking around like a peacock.
"I assisted in a previa surgery the other
day with Bertie and Dr. Edwards.
"It's hard with Bertie.
"He's still mad.
"They lifted Dr. Gallinger's suspension,
but he still hasn't returned to work.
"That's all I have for now.
"Please, write if you can.
"I miss you terribly and want so much
"to know how you are.
"I wish I could see you, my love.
"Yours, Lucy."
And if you want, I could, uh, tattoo her lips
to make them appear more plump.
I'll only charge you four vials.
No, thank you.
Well, two, then.
- Mrs. Showalter.
- There you are.
- Any luck with the mayor's office?
- No.
They're more afraid of the news
spreading than the disease.
Any more cases?
Not in the last five days.
Those first cases were the only ones.
- Is any food getting in at all?
- Nothing. They won't let anything in.
I'll try and get the health department
to speak to the police chief.
Miss, I told you not to get close.
There's sickness in there.
Plague is carried by rodents and fleas.
You think your wooden
barriers are keeping them inside?
Dr. Feng just said there are no new cases.
There's no need for the quarantine.
Mayor Phelan says them
coolies got it, and I trust the mayor.
Mother Superior.
My child.
Did you come all the way
from Ohio to see me?
I wanted to.
I brought something.
It's what you gave me
your third year at the convent
on the date of our Virgin Mother's birth.
The day that you committed yourself to God.
And I always carry it with me when I travel.
I was so proud of you, how far you'd come
since that little Irish girl
abandoned by her mother on the train west.
You saved my life.
You brightened ours.
Brave, tenacious, spirited.
A heart as big as the moon.
Lost and then found.
Is it true?
I... I could say that God
sent an angel down to instruct me
or there was something divine about it,
but there wasn't.
The women just needed help
and I helped them.
So it's true.
I am what they say I am.
Then what you are is a devil on Earth.
A murderer of innocents.
You have disgraced me,
the sisters who loved you,
the convent that saved you,
the nurses who taught you,
the Catholics who nurtured you,
and the God who loved you.
This is all that's left of you in my heart.
I should have let you die.
Hmm.
There are some
straw-colored striae that are visible.
How's the peripheral vision?
Some issues.
Put this over your right eye.
And how do these appear to you?
Wavy on the left.
And a bit better on the right.
Have you had any blows to that eye recently?
Yes.
Well, those blows detached your retina.
Seems to have almost completely separated
from the rear wall of your left eye.
And the treatment?
Not much to recommend.
Uh, rest in a recumbent position
for several weeks
may bring some relief.
So, it could heal on its own?
Or get worse. There's no way of knowing.
And any further blows
could prove catastrophic.
Are there any other procedures?
Experimental?
They're all unproven and much too risky.
What about this one, Everett?
Looks to be about
the right shape and color.
Dorothy?
You have a wonderful eye, love.
You're certainly lucky
to have a sister
with such a wonderful set of teeth herself.
How long are you visiting from Philadelphia?
As long as she needs me.
Dorothy has been a godsend
ever since I pulled Eleanor out of
Dr. Cotton's abysmal madhouse.
I often get a new batch
of teeth from the morgue
on Thursdays if you'd like me to return then.
No, I want to finish now.
She'll do 14 miles an hour
and never need a drink
of water or a bucket of oats.
Uh, just plug her in and she'll do the miles.
I can drive her good, too.
The man who sold her to me taught me how.
And you say you own it? Legally?
Got a bill of sale and everything.
And you want me to pay you to drive this?
Ah. You put, "Knickerbocker"
up there on the side,
people will be making
themselves sick to take a ride in her.
Ah, she'll go perfect with the place uptown.
Show everyone that we're, uh, modern and all.
And what if it runs out of electricity?
There's places all over that'll
swap the battery off the bottom in a jiff.
Bolt on a full one and I'm on my way.
No more hooves to the head.
No more tacking up.
No more horse shit.
I doubt that.
I'll give you $45 a month
to cover the automobile,
ten of which comes back to me,
and you pay for all
repairs to keep it running.
Mr. Barrow, you just got
yourself the finest ambulance
in all of New York City.
Come on.
We are in business.
It's a little dark.
I'm having trouble seeing.
Nurse Baker, light, please.
Retract more, nurse.
What do you notice?
Calot's triangle.
There are two cystic arteries arising
from the hepatic instead of the usual one.
It occurs in about 15% of cases.
Nurse Baker, has our
next patient been prepped?
- He has.
- And the one after that? The tonsils?
- I'll make certain.
- Thank you.
We'll need to separate out
and ligate both arteries.
Hmm.
The inferior one is
exceptionally underdeveloped.
It's hard against the hepatic.
You do it.
Me?
You've seen it done.
Now, it's time you do one yourself.
See one, do one?
Teach one.
- Dr. Gallinger.
- Edwards.
Uh...
Tell me, how...
How are things at home?
I am ready to resume my duties.
I see.
Well, I must admit that having
a third set of experienced hands
would be useful in picking up the slack.
But know this,
you come back,
you come back as subordinate to me,
with the full respect
and deference that implies.
I think I'll come back
when the chief of surgery returns.
I'm acting chief now.
And I intend to make that permanent.
You think this hospital
will go along with that?
You're as dumb as you think I think you are.
Come in.
Nurse Elkins.
I miss you calling me Lucy.
It's your title in this institution.
I think a woman such as yourself
would be glad to receive
any sign of respect at this point.
You don't have to be mean.
It's not in your nature.
What do you want?
It's just that it's your birthday tomorrow.
I always like to get my presents early.
Makes your special day feel longer
'cause it starts the day before.
Aren't you gonna open it?
It's a caduceus.
It's real gold.
Must have cost you a lot.
I wanted to.
I can't accept this.
Well, I've been doing
my best on several fronts.
Our groundbreaking
ceremony is still on schedule
and will certainly attract donors' attention.
You've all approved the architectural plans
and I've set about hiring
the best contractors in New York.
Each is going through
a withering negotiation,
I can assure you.
Not a penny of your money
will be wasted on manpower or materials.
Very good. What's next?
Dr. Edwards is waiting
to give us a report on his efforts.
Bring him in.
Dr. Edwards.
Good day, gentlemen.
Algie.
Have a seat.
Despite being understaffed,
the surgical service has been able to average
over 40 surgeries per week
with no increase in complications
and an 18% decrease in mortality.
Also,
we have added several new procedures.
Four of which we have perfected ourselves.
When will Dr. Thackery return?
The news I've received
indicates that the man
is in no shape to return
and likely never will be.
He seems lost to his addiction forever.
If that ends up being the case,
I would like to put myself forward
as a candidate for the
permanent job as chief of surgery.
I'm sure you would.
At the very least, I think it
would be prudent to start a search.
For a fourth surgeon, yes.
No, for a man to take your job
atop the department.
There are the right sort of men
at several institutions around the country
who would make excellent candidates.
I know a very good junior man at Dartmouth
who would be eager to make a step up.
Before we go casting
about New Hampshire for new blood,
let's put together a set of criteria,
most of which I'm sure
Dr. Edwards already fulfills,
and begin a more formal process.
Agreed.
I may have a solution to the problem
of the fourth surgeon you requested.
I was recently able to lure Dr. William Mays
out of private practice and to our hospital.
In addition to being an excellent doctor,
he was also trained as a surgeon.
You hired a surgeon without consulting me?
I hired a doctor, which is my job.
I know Mays.
A good family and a decent sort.
His wife's a member of the
Women's Temperance Society.
An irony if there ever was one.
Gentlemen.
If I may be candid.
Dr. Mays is a general practitioner
and not up to the surgical
standards of this hospital.
He is connected to
the wealthiest people in New York.
I know you're hot about the meeting, Algie,
and I don't blame you.
Waiting in the hall,
like a child outside of
the principal's office.
And then for Barrow to go behind my back.
Do you think he ever would
have done that to Thackery?
You're not Thackery, for better or for worse.
You see Havershorn's face when you said
you wanted to be made permanent chief?
If I hadn't known better,
I would have prescribed him
something for impacted constipation.
Look, I know you're absolutely
qualified to be chief of surgery.
But you above all people
know that we have to move carefully.
The other board members
have neither the progressive mind
nor the courage to make the sort
of change that you and I want.
The world may not be
moving fast enough for us,
but it's likely moving
much too quickly for them.
These are not the kind of men
who like to make history.
They'd rather tout their
ancestors' place in it.
You might remind them
of your ancestors' place in it.
We'll get you what you want.
We're just gonna need
to bring them along slowly.
Then I'll trust you to do that.
Phillip, you're home so early.
I didn't expect you until 6:00.
I told you this morning
I'd be back after lunch.
- We have the opera tonight.
- Of course.
But I thought we could spend
some time together this afternoon.
Where are you going?
- I need to run an errand.
- Can it wait?
It can't.
What are you up to?
- Nothing.
- Mmm-hmm.
I'm helping a sick friend, that's all.
I'll be back in time to make the curtain.
Could be mine.
Yes, come in.
Here are the rest
of the patient files you asked for.
- Thank you.
- Anyone who was admitted
with bubonic plague is in that pile.
- Including the ones who died?
- Yes.
Thank you.
Let's see.
Italian immigrant.
Polish.
Italian.
Hungarian.
Are any of these patients wealthy?
Could afford private rooms?
Hardly.
Most couldn't have even paid their bills
had they not been put here by the generosity
of your department and the city.
Something isn't squaring.
If this many were here
plus a bunch over at Bellevue,
all recent arrivals to this country,
how the hell did they get
through immigration at Ellis?
They check them before
they let them off the island.
Send some back,
even hospitalize some there.
Will this be sufficient?
If you're asking,
that means you've got more to give.
There's a dozen more wagons coming.
Wonderful. Make it quick.
Don't, there's plenty
of food for everyone.
If you could all form a line.
Please, don't shove.
I'm Dr. Gallinger
from the Knickerbocker Hospital.
I'm here to see Dr. John Thackery, patient.
I'm sorry, we have
no patient here by that name.
Yes, you do.
Are you family?
No, a colleague.
I don't know under
what name he might be registered,
but he is here and I will see him.
Our patients require privacy...
The fella he wants
won't care a whit about that.
Follow me.
Mr. Crutchfield.
Is it time for my...
Everett.
Hello, Thack.
What time do you have?
Um...
- 10:15.
10:15. You see that clock
on the wall says 10:10.
I am due my dose in 15 minutes, not 20.
You tell that Dr. Hackett that I'm on to him.
We all are.
They love to experiment here like we're mice.
But I don't need to tell you that
after what you went through with Eleanor.
But, uh, you don't know
how to control your environment like I do.
You know, I'm like all eyes and ears.
What time is it now?
A minute later.
You're no better than when you came here.
No, no, this place is good for me.
- Good for you?
- Yeah, they have excellent treatment here.
Excellent. They're, uh,
just a little stingy with it.
John, you are desperately
needed back at the Knick.
I'm not going back.
No.
I, I can't go back.
You're staying?
While you're here,
you could do me a great favor.
They keep all the drugs
locked in Dr. Hackett's office.
Okay? Pay him a visit.
Tell him you're there
to discuss my treatment.
And then grab me a couple
of vials of cocaine and heroin
and I'll meet you
at the kitchen entrance. Huh?
Yeah?
Agreed?
I'll figure something out.
Cornelia?
Cornelia, come into the parlor.
I have a surprise for you.
Just arrived from New York.
I'm just gonna run upstairs.
What happened?
It looks worse than it is.
Oh, my God. What happened?
Cornelia.
I went to Chinatown to help.
I bought them supplies.
I suppose I should have told you.
You suppose?
You could have exposed
yourself to the Black Death.
You suppose you should have told me?
What if you were pregnant?
You'd be exposing our child...
I'm not pregnant.
Where'd you get the money
for something like that?
Sold some things.
What things?
Some jewelry, that's all.
Your grandmother's earrings.
The sapphire ones your mother gave me.
I know they were important,
but when I thought
of all the good they could do...
Mr. Showalter.
Cornelia.
What... What are you doing here?
He took the train from
New York to surprise us.
I had some business up in Oregon.
Timber and salmon.
I thought I'd stop off.
I'm sorry you had to see us squabble.
It's my fault.
It's the fire that Phillip loves in you.
I...
I want to explain
about your mother's earrings.
They were yours
to do with as you wished.
Having purpose is important,
but you already have one.
As a wife, a future mother.
Perhaps being so far away
from the good example
set by your own mother
and my dear Eunice
clouded that a bit.
Perhaps a bit.
It's so different out here.
How can a New York girl
be expected to get
her bearings in a place like this?
- I don't think I've been unduly influenced.
- Hmm.
What if I arranged it
so that you could return to your family?
Leave San Francisco?
But Phillip loves it so.
I'm sure he loves you more.
What matters is your marriage,
being close to family
and the people who love you.
I've just built some apartments
at the bottom of Central Park.
I'd like you both to have one.
With 11 bedrooms, you can bear
as many children as you want.
I'll have to talk it over with Phillip.
He's already decided.
We were discussing it when you arrived.
Thank you for letting me know, Dr. Hackett.
Goodbye.
Hello. A word, please?
Has Dr. Thackery contacted you?
No.
Nurse Elkins...
He hasn't.
Is something wrong?
He disappeared from
Cromartie Hospital sometime last night.
- He disappeared?
- Mmm-hmm.
How?
Hello?
Help!
Hey!
Hello, Thomas.
I brought you a few things.
Some hard-boiled eggs, some nuts.
- The guard will just take it all away.
- Ah.
Let's eat it now, then.
Have they, uh, set a court date yet?
Week after next.
Any word in the papers?
Not much yet.
There will be once the trial starts.
You never should have taken
that job without me.
Harry, we were a team.
You'd have brung me
and we wouldn't be in this pickle.
I'd have known if the
coppers were waiting for you.
You were off getting pissed
down the Donegal Pub.
All right, fair play.
My name hasn't come up at all, has it?
No.
You thinking of turning yourself in?
Christ, no.
I'm just slagging you.
Since when did you forget
how to show your teeth?
Since you got penned up in this place.
You can sleep easy.
Your secret will go to my grave.
Well, I am not gonna
let you rot in this shitbox,
even if there's plenty of other folks
who want to pretend like you ain't here.
What are you going to do?
Dig me a tunnel out?
I'm gonna do what rich folks do.
I'm gonna get you a real clever lawyer
with nice suits and a lot of smart words.
Best money can buy.
With what money, Mr. Carnegie?
- My money.
- Really?
Don't be doing anything foolish, Thomas,
or you'll end up in here.
Pouncey'll be the one
bringing you the undercooked eggs.
The eggs is fine.
Don't you go selling me.
Don't you go selling me short.
I've had a little pile
stuffed in my mattress.
Made some real smart investments.
I'll have you out of here in no time.
Another early payment.
Just some judicious
scrimping and saving, that's all.
You'll have no problems from me.
You run a good, clean establishment.
Much better than Collier ever did.
Mr. Collier had very little pride.
He didn't respect his women.
He beat his girls, spoke to them rudely.
They barely saw a doctor.
Well, it's not easy to get
a doctor to do that kind of work.
It is when you own the man
who runs a hospital.
I think I see what you're getting at.
But parading a horde of prostitutes
through the Knick for examination
would take more than a little doing.
I need my women clean.
I can't lose my precious
inventory to disease or whore babies.
My customers trust me
to provide a healthy product.
Once a week, I will bring
women to you to be examined.
Respectfully, Mr. Ping,
the hospital, like this establishment,
is a business.
I can't just give my services away for free.
I would have to make certain arrangements.
What do you propose?
Perhaps a two dollar reduction in my debt
for every girl examined?
Gunner's knot.
Not difficult to tie, but impossible to undo.
Drink.
My father made me memorize
every sailing knot
before he'd let me set foot
on one of his boats.
Where are we?
The Atlantic.
What the hell is going on?
I'm cleaning up the mess you've created.
You untie me now.
- I won't.
- You son of a bitch!
You take me back to Cromartie
and you get me my drugs or I will kill you.
I swear I will kill you!
- Can you sail?
- What?
- No.
It's tricky business.
Learning to read the charts alone
is enough to drive a man mad.
- Meaning?
- Meaning you won't be killing me
and that you only have two options.
Get well or jump off.
Everett!
Please, untie me.
I'm feeling much better.
I could use some of that whiskey.
- You take me back.
- No!
God damn it!
At least, you're more in control today
than you were yesterday.
We're not there yet.
You don't understand.
The need will never go away.
Then you'll fight the need!
Don't you dare tie me up again.
I'm gonna make this simple.
You want to go to shore,
show me you can learn to tie
the first ten knots on the chart in there.
Then I'll know you're in control again.
Ten knots!
Where were the bodies found?
Behind the ship's boilers. Stowaways.
Too poor to even afford steerage, I guess.
Rats?
All over the hull.
Were these two seen
anywhere else on the ship?
It's hard to say.
Most stowaways stay hidden
until the ship docks,
but once at sea,
they might want some fresh air,
some food and water.
Some do take to cooking rats
if they can't steal from the kitchen.
Is that what got 'em, you think?
State of the bodies, the rats,
it's bubonic plague.
We'll know for sure once we get to the lab.
I'll need to see the ship's manifest
and a list of everyone
who went through immigration.
This is private property.
Heel-toe it out of here
or we'll toss you out on your ass.
I'm with the health department.
I'm just here to check up
on a couple friends of mine.
Get a good look at what will be killing you,
what you will be bringing
home to kill your families, too.
Babies are the first to go, usually.
Dead in a pool of their own vomit and blood!
Shut your trap. I'm on your side.
I'm glad you're here.
There's been some sort of
monkey business going on around here.
- What do you mean?
- Meet me back here after six o'clock,
and I'll show you the immigration records.
Okay?
And stay off my dock, you fucking turd.
Uh...
Come in.
Good morning, Doctor.
Good morning.
Any word from Gallinger?
He's used up his last chance with me.
Right.
Well, I had little hope
he'd take orders from you.
Who's assisting me
with the tubercular osteomyelitis patient?
I only saw my name.
I'll put Mays on it with you.
Mays? Not you?
It's a fairly routine procedure.
I'm... I'm sure he can handle it.
Great.
That's quite an abscess.
Let's hope
we won't have to amputate.
Perhaps I'll begin.
Nurse, knife.
I will dissect down to the bone
and see how much pus is in there.
Unless you have other thoughts.
Oh, no, I think that sounds right.
I'm, uh, well acquainted with your father.
We were recently seated near each other
at an art society dinner.
You know, it was really more of
an excuse to drink good wine
and show off our French.
That's nice. All right, I'm through.
Suction wand.
Will you be leading the way
on cleaning it out?
Yes, of course.
Do you need assistance?
- I'm not exactly an expert in this technique.
- Gauze.
Nice work, Dr. Chickering.
Very nice.
Thank you for being here, Mr. Mayor.
This groundbreaking is made much more
special by your presence here today.
You couldn't have done this in April?
I'm freezing my balls off.
Well, I am sorry about that.
Allow me to introduce you to our architect.
This is Mr. Frazier H. Wingo
of the firm Bradley and Wingo.
- Mr. Wingo.
- It's a pleasure.
We have to grace our city with the finest,
most beautiful hospital in the world.
Yes, and it won't cost you a dime.
All private funds.
Which we are still raising.
We will get there.
Captain Robertson assures me of that.
Oh, is he here today?
August has always been
a strong supporter of mine.
He wanted to be. He is in Norfolk.
Seems he's having some new ships built.
But his son Henry is here instead,
representing the family quite well indeed.
Point him out to me
so this isn't a complete waste of time.
Yes, of course.
People will know
the names of the men,
of the families, really, who gave
generously to build this hospital.
Aside from our name on a plaque
and our portrait in a hallway,
there's no real payoff.
The payoff, Prettyman,
is assuring your place in God's kingdom.
Yeah, well,
your family can think about legacy,
but I'm still building my fortune.
Every penny I have is tied up
in winning the contract to build
the new subway line.
Where will it run?
From City Hall all the way
up to 145th Street.
Do you have all the funds you need?
Enough to rig the bid,
but short of what I need to get it done.
Oh, look at that.
You were looking to empty my wallet,
but I might just end up emptying yours.
Guess who.
- Uh, Daisy.
- No.
- Constance?
- For heaven's sake.
I've barely been gone and you've already
run roughshod over every girl in New York.
- Neely, doll!
- We're back.
I, I didn't expect you so soon.
I wanted to be here for the groundbreaking.
Oh, uh... Harold. You remember Harold?
- Yes. Good morning.
- Good morning. How are you?
We'll finish talking about
that opportunity later.
I swear to you,
I will never leave this city ever again.
Well, I won't let you.
- Where's Phillip?
- Well, he's taken the baggage
and is getting us settled
in our new apartment.
Algie. Algie, look who it is.
Cornelia?
Oh. He's as surprised as I am.
She's back, for good.
Come with me. I have something to show you.
Stand there together.
What is that thing?
A moving picture camera.
Purchased it from Mr. Edison's company.
Stand closer together.
A little to the left.
Henry.
Mayor Van Wyck
would love a word if you have a moment.
Excuse us. Yeah?
Mayor Van Wyck, this is Henry Robertson.
- Phillip.
- Algernon.
- Welcome back, Phillip.
- Thank you so much.
You couldn't miss this, could you?
- Not for the world.
- Mmm.
How's the apartment?
- Not finished, apparently.
- What?
My father assumed it would be completed,
but ran into some slowdowns
while he was traveling.
We could live with my parents.
It's all been taken care of.
Dad felt terribly about the delay,
so he insisted all our things be
brought to their house immediately.
An entire floor has been
prepared for us, so...
We'll be living in your father's house?
For how long?
Four months at the most.
Maybe five.
It'll be fun.
Ah! All right, everyone.
We're all set.
Let's man our shovels, shall we, gentlemen?
Right this way. Very good.
Photographers, reporters, this way.
Up front. Thank you.
Gentlemen, if we could come to
the lip of the stage for the photograph.
Thank you.
All right, my friends.
Shovels ready.
Now, remember, this will be
in every paper in the city,
so let's give it our all.
Hold on a moment.
I seem to have one too many shovels.
Dr. Edwards.
Please, come join us.
It's only fitting that
our acting chief of surgery
shows us how to
make a first cut into the earth.
Could've given it to the police chief.
- Is this your idea of taking it slow?
- I couldn't resist.
All right, everyone, on the count of three.
One, two, three.
Mr. Wingo.
Masterful. Well done.
I've had a revelation.
If I was up against a medical problem,
I would look for a cure.
Stop the disease.
Mend the bone, staunch the bleeding.
That's the goal anyway.
If I treat my desire for drugs
not as a craving, but as a sickness,
that means there must be a cure.
And if there is,
I'm gonna find it.
Number ten.
Let's go home.
Nice view.