Yeah, I said I'm sorry.
I'm just not feeling too hot.
You're sneezing.
You could do that in a movie theater.
Yeah, and I'll be
in a nice soft chair when I collapse.
I'm exhausted, babe.
Oh, come on.
We're gonna be late.
Episode Four never comes
to the big screen.
This is the pre-Lucasized version,
remember?
None of that Greedo
shooting first crap.
Go without me.
What are you talking about?
You love Star Wars.
Don't you?
Ben?
Since when?
Since just before
I started pretending I loved it.
I'm sorry.
I was just trying to be supportive.
Fine. I'll go alone.
Baby, I'm sorry. Me, too.
I'm so woozy
I can hardly think.
We'll hang out at home.
No, you should go.
Did you just feel something?
Feel? Like what?
- Is there an earthquake?
- In New Jersey?
- Oh, God.
- What?
I think I'm,
like, hallucinating.
Call 911.
Twenty-six year old female,
gas main exploded under her building,
she was pulled out of the rubble
after six hours.
Two surgeries
for multiple fractures and burns.
I'm thinking the broken bones
are a response to the building
falling on her head.
And the fever?
She's the only collapse victim
whose body temperature was...
Put her on antipyretics.
Already have.
The fever is holding at 104.
Fluctuating consciousness.
Can't take the case.
I don't have a team.
So hire a team.
What for? I don't have a case.
Have you even
interviewed anybody?
You test-d rive a car
before you buy it.
You have sex
before you get married.
I can't hire a team
based on a 10-minute interview.
What if I don't like
having sex with them?
You've spent the last two weeks
doing absolutely nothing.
Concert is over.
In what twisted universe
does mastering Eddie Van Halen's
two-handed arpeggio technique
count as "absolutely nothing"?
Take the case,
or you will spend the next month
helping the collapse team
change bandages.
I diagnose her alone, by the end
of the day, you go away for a week.
Done.
It's not gonna work.
If he solves the case,
we cure the girl.
And prove
he doesn't need a team.
He's not gonna solve the case.
Not that fast.
- Why not?
- Because he needs a team.
- And this will prove to him...
- Wanna change his mind?
You need a more convincing argument
than "you promised."
Fever?
Non-responsive to antibiotics,
antipyretics.
Fluctuating consciousness.
Go!
You talking to me?
Yes.
Imagine that the roof
of the storage closet
collapses on your
favorite floor buffer,
which then starts overheating.
Why would I have
a favorite floor buffer?
Okay-
Maybe the electrical works
got banged up in there
from stuff falling on it?
Hmm. Interesting.
Brain damage, leading to
hypothalamic dysregulation.
Nah.
If you're brought in covered in rubble,
it's all about the MRls.
We'd have seen that. Come on!
Gotta earn that fiver.
Or stuff leaked in the holes,
messing it up.
Lacerations lead
to multiple portals for infection.
Bacterial would have responded
to the antibiotics.
It's too high for viral.
Parasites or fungus
is possible.
Or maybe lupus?
My grandma has lupus.
Okay. Auto immune, I'll run
a lupus panel. Infection fits best.
A complete history
would be helpful,
which leads to the worst
part of the job,
dealing with the
floor buffer's family.
We talked every
couple of weeks.
But Ben would
know better than I.
No farms,
no travel anywhere weird.
You get that, Dr. Buffer?
No travel, no farm.
The file says she was sick
before the building collapsed.
Yeah, I figured
it was just a cold.
Why, do you think it's related?
Her being sick and her being sick?
Often is.
She was unconscious
when I found her.
We'd been fighting.
I just want to...
Just tell me
she's gonna be okay.
I'm not even sure
if you're gonna be okay.
We're gonna
make her all better.
Show off.
You ought to be
nicer to people.
Where are we going?
You know how the laughter
of little children is infectious?
Well, parasites and fungi
are even more so.
We're gonna find out which one
is making her brain bubble over.
Where, the building?
EPA's doing that job for us,
they say it's clean.
Which means we're making a pilgrimage
to Castle Blackberry.
Her name's Bradberry.
I should've asked them for keys.
No need, I'm sure we can find
a large rock somewhere.
I'm not breaking
into somebody's house.
I got principles.
I got some loose change here
says you don't.
I'm not doing this
for less than $50.
Where's the restaurant?
What restaurant?
The one you said
you were taking me to for lunch?
Oh! Uh...
This one's homier.
Dibs on the cold pizza!
I'm sure it looked
easier on YouTube.
Oops.
Yeah. You don't need a team.
You can't even
get arrested without company.
You're right. Only one solution,
never replace them, ever.
Do you need help?
Yeah, yeah.
Patronize the poor cripple.
Ow.
- Let me get that.
- I got it.
Will you just let me get it?
I'll check the bedroom.
There's some
interesting mold on the windowsill here.
It's gonna take me a while.
I'll cover the bathroom.
She had a secret diary.
Is there any other kind?
What are you doing?
There's a sale on liquid Tide.
If you're broke,
I could lend you a tiny bit
of the money I owe you.
No, no.
I wouldn't put you in that position.
What does the diary say?
Basically a list
of her sexual encounters,
boys, girls,
vibrating appliances...
If it was, you'd be quoting,
not summarizing.
It's just a parade
of sad banalities.
"I can hardly get out of bed.
Feeling blue."
Then, three months ago,
turns into a parade of happy banalities.
"It's starting to turn the corner.
Job's looking up."
We can stop swabbing.
Her cliches are getting healthier.
Or she's less depressed.
Aren't there pills that do that?
Anti-depressants
don't cause fever.
Not on their own. But the ER didn't know
she was on MAO inhibitors,
so they gave her Demerol,
that's a nasty combo.
So, all you have to do
is convince this kid
that his girlfriend had
a secret doctor,
and a secret stash
and a secret life.
It's been a while since a patient
took a swing at you. Can I watch?
I only have to
convince the mother.
Actually,
I don't have to convince anyone.
This is total crap. If she was seeing
a psychiatrist, I'd know.
If she was on drugs, I'd know.
Mrs. Bradberry, please sign the forms
so we can start the dialysis.
But why anti-depressants?
I don't understand.
Mrs. Bradberry, please sign the forms
so we can start the dialysis.
Stop saying that.
Dr. Buffer, what is going on?
What aren't you telling us?
He's a janitor?
More significantly,
a blabbermouth.
House, shut up.
I am very sorry how Dr. House handled
this. It is completely unforgivable.
Except if he's right.
Dialysis will filter her blood.
There's nothing to filter.
Save her life.
She wasn't depressed.
I'm miserable around Ben.
Not me, I like Ben.
February 12th.
Either she's depressed
or she just thinks you're a jerk.
Neither suggests
that you should be the one
directing her
medical treatment.
Does the diary say
my daughter's taking these drugs?
No, but medically...
Did you find drugs
in their home?
She's probably hiding them
in her purse.
I thought it'd be rude to go searching
under a thousand tons of rubble.
This was months ago.
We were in a fight.
It doesn't mean she's depressed
and it doesn't mean
she doesn't love me.
Fine.
Maybe the diary proves nothing.
On the other hand,
half the country's on anti-depressants
and it fits
her symptoms perfectly.
No ring on your daughter's finger
means you make the decisions.
I'm not sure that I know her
well enough anymore.
You really wanna risk her life
on how well he knows her?
Wilson, you idiot.
Listen
carefully, and no one will get hurt.
You must follow
the instructions.
Any attempt to contact the FBI
or other law enforcement agencies,
or Cuddy,
will be met with the...
And a large Coke, no ice.
- Give it back.
- What happened?
Did someone kidnap your guitar,
a $12,0001967 Flying V
or something?
Where'd you hide it?
I'm flattered you would consider me
this bold and brilliant.
Yeah. It takes a...
It takes a criminal mastermind
to pull off a heist from an unlocked,
unguarded room down the hall.
What do you want?
Me? Nothing.
But I'm sure the kidnapper wants
whatever a kidnapper wants.
To see you interview five to seven
well-qualified fellowship candidates.
I don't need a team.
You were bouncing ideas
off a janitor.
And solved the case!
Hi. I'm Dr. Cuddy.
If you can hear what I'm saying,
blink once.
You can't talk right now.
You have a tube down your throat.
And try not to move your head.
You've been in a terrible accident,
but it looks like
you will have no permanent injuries.
You've had a bad fever,
but it's gone now.
I've been here the whole time, honey.
Okay? I'm not leaving.
This is very important.
I need you
to blink one for yes, twice for no.
Were you seeing a psychiatrist?
Were you on MAO inhibitors,
the anti-depressant?
Megan, it's okay.
It doesn't matter, okay? I love you.
Honey? Honey, what's wrong?
Megan, are you all right?
What's happening?
Are we upsetting her?
Heart is beating too fast.
Get the family out of here.
Megan?
- Megan!
- Charging to 200.
Meg. Meg! ' Megan!
Clear!
We shocked her back into sinus rhythm,
but she's still tachycardic.
Fascinating. Equally fascinating is,
why are you here?
I was gonna leave you alone
if you won the bet.
But you lost.
I explained the fever,
which is all we were talking about.
She confirmed
the anti-depressants.
Go bet with someone else
if you wanna explain the heart problems.
She confirmed them by winking.
Maybe there was a cute guy
across the room.
She got better when I treated her.
Even I'm not that cute.
Two unrelated symptoms.
Just a coincidence?
Or you're grasping at straws
to avoid admitting
you can't do this on your own.
Fine.
What explains the fever
and persistent tachycardia?
It could be anything.
Endocarditis?
No. Fever, no infection.
- Um...
- Keep going, you're doing great.
You win.
- I don't believe you.
- I'm not gonna play this game.
Just give me the damn résumés.
And my guitar.
I don't have it.
Although I did hear some plangent
strumming from under that couch earlier.
Wow.
This kidnapper isn't just bold.
He's diabolical.
I guess he realized he probably
shouldn't give it back to you
until after you've had
the interviews.
Huh!
You didn't write anything.
So, what you're saying is,
you didn't find that one big explanation
'cause there isn't one. Clever.
Well, let's just say
your anti-depressant theory
does explain the fever.
What about the heart?
And don't say a building fell on her.
Okay.
- A structure collapsed...
- Shut up.
Come on, it fits. Crushed musculature
releases potassium, causes V-tach.
You'd think she'd get crush syndrome
after she was crushed,
not two days later.
Microvascular occlusions, takes
that long for the blood to reperfuse.
She'd have a baggy heart.
Echo it to confirm.
Ls crush syndrome good or bad?
Does it sound good?
I mean, compared
to the other things it could be.
There are no other things
it could be.
Then why are you testing her?
Excellent question.
What? What is it?
The heart's fine.
Why is she sweating?
Her fever's back.
Why would her fever be back?
- I can't say.
- You don't know?
Well, I know. I just can't say,
'cause you'll hit me.
Let's discuss this
in front of witnesses.
The DT's?
So, she's an alcoholic now?
Her first fever was from
the medication for her depression.
Or you're wrong.
The second fever was from
the self-medication for depression.
This is insane.
You don't think I would have noticed
her being constantly drunk?
You were practically living with
Sylvia Plath. You didn't notice that.
Tone it down or I will hit you.
Fine. I'll do
liver enzyme tests.
Liver enzymes can also be elevated
from musculoskeletal trauma.
They'd be there whether she had
a drinking problem or not.
They don't know that.
Just pretend to confirm.
What's the treatment?
She's not an alcoholic.
Hair of the dog. IV alcohol.
Taper it off after a few days.
She's sick and traumatized
and half dead,
you wanna make her drunk?
Just do it.
You can't do this. We lived together.
We were gonna have kids.
You barely even know her.
Apparently, neither did you.
Hello?
Hi, can I speak to
Trevor Kaufman?
Yo, yo. This is Trev. What up?
This is Dr. Gregory House.
Can you come in tomorrow to interview?
House? Are you serious? Awesome!
Hey, I got the House interview!
Oh, look at me,
I got the House interview!
- Shut up! Would you shut up?
- I'm so cool.
Hey, give me the phone back.
Give the phone back, seriously, man.
I got a page.
No, you didn't.
They called a code.
No, they didn't.
You got a page,
but not from us.
Did you ever see
Raid on Entebbe?
Yeah.
In the end
they release the hostages.
How's that working for you?
The Ugandans played fair.
They didn't move the hostages
on the Israelis.
Once again, I'm in awe
of the kidnapper's tactical brilliance.
What is El Fuego Del Amor,
and why do you need 10 of them?
It's a telenovela.
I'm learning Spanish.
Say adios.
Are you erasing my TiVo?
House, not the season finale!
I don't negotiate with terrorists.
I smoke them out
of their hidey-holes.
Do you know what terrorists do
when you don't negotiate?
They terrorize.
Bring it on.
Fever's down. Sweating is abated.
Heart's working fine.
I guess House was right, again.
That's good news, right?
It is good news.
So, what does this mean,
she's an alcoholic?
There's no other explanation?
No, sorry.
It doesn't make any sense.
Dr. Cuddy, she's doing this thing
with her mouth again.
It's been on and off
for the last couple of hours.
Is she trying to talk?
No.
I think she's screaming.
Morning.
Huh!
Where did you come from?
Apes, if you believe
the Democrats.
I heard you were there
when I was proven right.
The alcohol treatment
took away the heart and fever problems.
Yes, I was also there
when you were proven wrong.
She'd been silently screaming
for two hours.
Amylase and lipase are through the roof.
She has pancreatitis.
IV alcohol could cause pancreatitis.
Okay-
You're not gonna argue with me?
No.
You think I'm right?
- Why not?
- No.
That's not really
a yes or no question.
Which is why
I'm not answering it.
If it's not
the IV alcohol, it's gotta be...
Not interested.
If I'm wrong,
she's gonna die.
Are you sure you're still
Dean of Medicine?
I'm not interested in arguing because
I'm not interested in enabling you.
You need someone to bounce ideas
off of. You need a team.
Don't follow me.
MAO inhibitor caused the fever,
alcohol caused the pancreatitis,
alcohol withdrawal
caused the V-tach.
Your logic is irrefutable.
You're wrong.
Well, who are you gonna believe?
A classic toy,
or a woman who,
if she had any confidence in her ideas,
wouldn't feel the need
to distract you with a water bra?
Are you really just gonna treat
the pancreatitis?
Are you here to enable me?
I don't want her to die
because you're stubborn.
Wow. So, you can enable and rationalize
at the same time.
Guess you are still
Dean of Medicine.
If you're right, then this guy,
who's not an ass, who's not
a workaholic, who's not a sociopath,
has somehow missed both
her depression and severe alcoholism.
Yes. Imagine that,
a couple with secrets!
Why would she lie?
Okay, alcoholism,
you don't wanna advertise, but...
If you're right, there'd be
an abnormality on the pancreas.
At least do an MRI to confirm.
Oh, my God!
This guy means business.
Or guys, could be multiple guys.
Or gal. Who knows?
All I can say is,
this reeks of boldness.
Lam not hiring a team.
You ever tighten a guitar string
really, really slowly?
Past the point
it can handle the strain?
It makes this weird sound,
almost like a scream.
I thought
this was gonna be fun.
I mess with you, you mess with me,
eventually you give in.
But you've shown a startling
lack of humor, which got me thinking.
Oh, God.
What's the real reason
you won't hire a team?
I told you.
I don't need a team.
Then hire three people
and let them sit on their asses.
That wouldn't be right.
Three years ago, you hired a team.
What's changed?
I've become a man of principle.
I've gotten smarter.
What answer will make
Socrates shut up?
What's changed is,
you hired a team.
You connected with a team,
you worked with a team
and you lost a team.
Damn.
There's no abnormalities
in her pancreas.
You fall in love. You get married.
50% chance it'll end in misery.
Hiring employees
can be even tougher,
because you know, eventually,
they're gonna leave.
There's increased T2 signal
on her hepatic capsule,
if you know what I mean.
You got hurt. Get over it.
Now, if you'll excuse me,
my patient's about to start bleeding
out of her mouth and anus.
Internal bleeding.
Not anymore.
Now it's all over the place.
Why are you here?
That's my patient down there.
You're here because I'm here.
I am done enabling you.
I know.
The alcohol didn't cause the
pancreatitis, the internal bleeding did.
The question is,
what caused the internal bleeding?
I hate myself.
You do know that the patient had
a building lying on her.
Four days ago.
Bleeding can start at any time.
She's bleeding
from five different sites.
Do you think they synchronized
their watches?
She got Warfarin
after her hip surgery.
It's designed
to mess with bleeding patterns.
Fever, heart and bleeding.
Three problems,
three completely different explanations.
She must be the unluckiest woman
in the world.
I only cling
to this crazy theory
because it's been proven right
every step of the way.
Each treatment worked.
Yes. She looks
perfectly healthy.
This much bleeding
is a symptom of something more.
And you need a team,
because you're wrong
and you're gonna
kill this woman.
If I had a team,
this patient would be dead,
because they'd be here
instead of me
and they wouldn't notice the size
of this woman's uterus.
Hi. How's it going?
Mind if I observe?
Got a big room up top
with a big window just for that.
Stop that.
You wanna look at vaginae,
there are websites for that.
You think I'm made of money?
Can you get him out of here?
Enlarged uterus means
that she was recently pregnant.
She's a good liar, but I doubt she can
hide a baby from her boyfriend.
Scraping in the uterus
indicates that she had an abortion,
and nothing
in her medical history.
Only one reason
to hide an abortion.
Boyfriend wants babies,
she doesn't.
She's bleeding everywhere.
Unless the guy was performing
an abortion with a shotgun...
Stop enabling him.
It's not the abortion,
it's what she did after.
The boyfriend would have
noticed condoms,
he would notice abstinence.
He would not notice the pill,
which means
I don't need a team!
Hey, where's your mother
in common law?
Dr. House,
this is Doug McMurtry.
His girlfriend
was working with Megan when...
She's dead?
She passed this morning.
Well, then why
are you still here?
I need the old lady's consent
to do some treatment.
What'd you find out?
I wish I could tell you,
but since you're not legally related...
What the hell did you find out?
Your girlfriend
had an abortion.
See why I didn't tell you?
I'd be insane to also tell you
that she's on the pill.
No, she's not.
If they'd known she was on it,
they wouldn't have given her
a blood thinner after her hip surgery.
The combination caused the bleeding.
It's good news. It's treatable.
Just give her Tamoxifen,
which is normally a breast cancer...
That's not true.
We wanna have kids.
Hmm.
See, I already did
the blood tests.
And either she lied to you,
or her blood lied to us.
Tell Megan I'm glad
she's gonna be okay.
How're you doing?
I got cancer.
You're on an oncology ward.
Everybody's got cancer.
You want sympathy,
you ought to try
the hardly-anything-
wrong-with-me ward.
In fact,
why don't I take you there right now?
How sick are you? Can you walk?
Are you a doctor?
Admitted today.
First day of a five-day chemo course.
Yeah, you can walk.
Come on, let's go.
Does Dr. Wilson
know you're here?
Well, if he didn't,
this would be really stupid.
'Cause then he wouldn't know
where his patient was.
He might think
he'd been kidnapped.
Now the room upstairs
is bigger, it's got cable,
better-looking
sponge bath nurses.
If you feel sick,
you call me directly, not Dr. Wilson.
He's getting his last sat
of hormone shots.
You put her on Tamoxifen?
An anticancer drug?
It blocks estrogen receptors.
Does it also block breathing,
and kidney function?
She's crashing.
Doesn't mean I was wrong.
This is Dr. Marvin. We're bringing
this patient over now. Thanks.
Anybody here a doctor?
Kidney failure, spiking fever,
breathing difficulties.
Any theories?
Am I in an
M. Night Shyamalan movie?
You're House, right?
Okay, I assume you know me
because I once insulted you,
your patient, or your relatives.
If that's so, I apologize.
I was drunk that day.
Patient initially presented
with crush injuries.
I know you because Dr. Cuddy
issued a memo.
Telling you
to cooperate fully with me?
No.
Figured that was a long shot.
Anybody here not get that memo?
Fungal infection.
Don't you have a patient?
She shot herself in the leg
while high on meth.
Wouldn't hurt her
to be in pain for a little while.
Fungal infection
would be in her eyes by now.
Haemophilus?
Doesn't explain the remitting fever.
You've heard that I've got
a job opening, right?
I just care about people.
Acute Respiratory Distress Syndrome.
ARDS doesn't explain anything,
except the breathing.
If you care about people,
you're not getting the job.
I was lying. Crush syndrome.
Doesn't explain the breathing.
- What was the problem with ARDS?
- Only explained the breathing.
- The crush syndrome?
- It didn't explain the breathing.
Are you a fan of symmetry?
- Sure.
- Weird.
'Cause your eyes are lopsided,
and by eyes I mean breasts.
ARDS and crush syndrome,
both reactions to severe trauma.
Why can't she have both?
Because...
Because then,
there's nothing we could do.
Boy, you remind me of someone.
Send me your résumé.
I'll put it on top of the pile
that I'm never gonna look at.
I couldn't leave.
You don't seem like the type of person
who would give up on giving up.
I love her.
You loved somebody.
Somebody who didn't drink,
wanted to have babies
and wasn't miserable.
I know she lied, but...
What are you doing?
Why are you saying these things to him?
The woman you love doesn't exist.
This woman is dying.
She has Acute Respiratory
Distress Syndrome and crush syndrome.
Her body's basically giving up.
We can keep her on supported dialysis
and hope for the best.
Never mind.
She has a lump in her arm.
Does that mean you're wrong?
Well, that'd be
good news for you guys.
We'll know after a biopsy.
Which patient is that?
- Megan...
- House's patient.
Yeah.
- Didn't you get my memo?
- Sure.
Got both memos.
Both.
And the second memo said
to ignore the first memo.
Yeah, seemed odd.
I did an MRI and...
Of course you did.
What'd you find?
It's kind of freaky.
She's got growths
all over the place.
She's got tumors?
Not exactly.
The growths are
eosinophilic granulomas.
They are usually
from allergic reactions,
so I'm putting her on steroids.
Allergy to what?
She doesn't have allergies.
We don't know.
Unfortunately, the only drug
she's had enough of
to have this kind of reaction
is cephalosporin.
And why is that unfortunate?
'Cause she was on it two months ago.
That's what you mean, right?
She took it for strep throat
so she can't be allergic to it.
It would seem so.
What is this hospital
doing to her?
She has had
three separate medical disasters,
and now she's dying of an allergy
she can't possibly have?
Mr. Lee.
I just have to check...
Sam? Are you okay?
What are you doing here?
I was taking a nap.
Where's my patient?
You stole my patient.
You kidnapped my guitar.
Give him back.
Only when you give her back.
It's a she?
It's certainly not a dude.
It's a guitar.
You took a human being!
Now who doesn't have
a sense of humor?
I'm monitoring the guy remotely.
What, are you listening
for the distant sound of screaming?
The nurses know to call me.
They don't know who he is!
His name's right there on the chart.
Now go away. I'm working.
They give him the wrong meds, who
the hell knows what's gonna happen?
House!
Bad things would happen.
He's in Room 318.
What are you giving Megan?
Megan? Nothing.
Nothing? What's going on?
What's wrong with her?
Her? Nothing.
Then why are you giving her drugs?
Just some amphetamines
to wake her up.
Everything could be explained
by her lying to you.
The anti-depressants,
the drinking, the pill,
until now.
Now she's allergic to something
the chart says she's not allergic to.
That's not her lying, that's the chart
lying, which doesn't make sense.
You know Liz Masters?
- No.
- Yeah, she worked with Megan.
That was her boyfriend
you met outside the morgue.
Mmm.
This is her chart.
She's on MAO inhibitors for depression.
She's on the pill.
She had an abortion a month ago,
and she's allergic to cephalosporin.
What's going on here?
What, are you saying this isn't Megan?
Yes.
Ben?
Since when?
Since right before
I began pretending I loved it.
She's the same size as Megan,
the same build, the same hair color.
They were both
horribly injured, unrecognizably.
EMT teams do not second-guess
family members' identifications
at accident scenes.
No. Liz died yesterday.
This isn't Liz.
I know Megan.
I know her hair,
I know her hands, I know her smell.
What's your name?
Liz.
On, God!
Your girlfriend never lied to you.
Oh, God.
I did it all by myself, Mommy.
You talking to me?
Go away.
I did it all by myself, Mommy.
How'd you know it was me?
There's a scent given off
by wounded feral cats.
You were wrong.
I got everything right,
just treated the wrong...
They had a good relationship.
He couldn't even identify her.
And you were wrong about needing
a team. She almost died.
So, I almost need a team.
You were content with
your "people are idiots" theory.
But Cameron would
never have accepted
that this guy knew nothing
about the love of his life.
And as soon as you claimed
it was multiple conditions,
Foreman would have done anything
to prove you wrong,
and then Chase would have done anything
to prove you right.
Any one of them
would have solved this days ago.
Hire a team.
I don't care how you do it.
Just do it.
Sometimes I am wrong.
I have a gift for observation.
For reading people and situations,
but sometimes I am wrong.
This will be the longest
job interview of your life.
I will test you in ways
that you will often consider
unfair, demeaning and illegal.
And you'll often be right.
Look to your left.
Now look to your right.
By the end of six weeks,
one of you will be gone,
as will 28 more of you.
Wear a cup.