Big Eye,
this is Cobra Zero Six.
Just entered Indian Country,
approaching way point four.
Request confirmation
to engage target on first approach.
Roger, Cobra Zero Six.
Big Eye waiting for
confirmation as well.
If we wait any longer, Big Eye,
we're not gonna have
any choice in the matter.
I can't exactly
do a U-turn here.
Roger that, Cobra.
Hold for confirmation.
Captain Cooper, are you okay?
What happened?
You weren't answering.
Because the damn comm cord
got disconnected!
You spend a billion
dollars on the avionics
and don't bother to check
the comm connection?
No, I checked that
twice before you got in...
And the next time you ask us
to test a prototype,
it'd be nice if your directional gyro
didn't spin like a top
when I'm supposed to be
500 feet off the floor.
I'm sorry.
I'll go review the simulation,
see if I can figure out what went wrong.
Who is this man?
Come on, take a shot.
I'm not gonna fire you every time
you get a wrong answer.
Neville Chamberlain.
You're fired.
Does this man look
like he's ceding Czechoslovakia
to a fascist dictatorship?
It's Buddy Ebsen, the actor.
He's dead. Why are we...
Buddy Ebsen was the original tin man
in the Wizard of Oz, for a day.
He was diagnosed allergic
to the aluminum dust in the makeup.
His lungs failed. He nearly died.
Question is, why?
Didn't you just
say he was allergic?
You may not have legs, but you got ears.
I suggest you use them.
I said he was
diagnosed allergic.
Since we are currently short
exactly one interesting patient,
we are gonna figure out what really
happened to Buddy Ebsen in 1938.
Now, on one hand,
he's not getting deader.
On the other hand,
your jobs hang in the balance. Se...
House?
I want seven alternate
diagnoses when I get back.
Did you forget how
to count to three?
I get a budget for three.
Doesn't mean I can
only hire three.
Actually, that's exactly
what it means.
I cut the permanent
salaries by 10%.
Over three years, that'll more than
make up for the breakage on the 27
that I'm gonna weed out
over the next few weeks.
There's 40 people in there.
Row D, you're fired.
I didn't actually
count all the resumes.
This is stupid.
You can't manage that many people.
You're just gonna keep
weeding them out arbitrarily?
Sure, and having them
sitting in my office
schmoozing about their
favorite Algerian surfing movies
is a much better system.
- Wait a second. Were you in Row D?
- Yes.
My apologies. My boss says
I'm being arbitrary and stupid.
Row D is not fired. Row C is fired!
- What?
- Great. Thank you.
See, that was not arbitrary.
Well, I'd love to chat,
but I've been paged.
That's interesting.
Apparently, I paged myself.
If you have a resume there,
I'm not interested.
But I wouldn't mind hearing
how you got my pager number.
It's not a resume.
$50,000.
Does One-Eyed Nicky want me to run
that to Jimmy the Nose?
It's for my medical bills.
I need you to find out
what's wrong with me.
Insurance is usually
cheaper than that.
Cash means there's
something to hide.
I'm a captain in the Air Force,
about to start
a new assignment.
NASA's astronaut
training program.
I discovered salt
and created FM radio.
Something is wrong
with my eyes, my ears...
Well, if it's fixable,
the Air Force will do it for free.
If not, it doesn't matter.
There are a hundred applicants
ready to take my place
who don't need to be fixed.
I need to do
this off the books.
I did the research.
You're the best, you break rules,
and you don't care about anyone
except yourself.
Well, let's say that's true.
You get a new job.
Hospital gets
a nice wad of cash.
What do I get?
I crashed a flight simulator
because I started
to hear with my eyes.
The aluminum could
have been tainted...
Don't care. New patient!
30-year-old female
with synesthesia.
New rules.
You generate a lab report,
you shred it.
X-ray, you melt it.
No notes, no records, nothing.
As far as you're concerned,
the patient is Osama Bin Laden
and everyone not in this
room is Delta Force. Any questions?
We're protecting
Osama Bin Laden?
It's a metaphor.
Get used to it.
Any more questions?
And you're not even gonna
tell us her name?
You think her name might be connected
to what's wrong with her?
Here's Osama.
Now, you all have numbers,
so we're gonna do this alphabetically.
8, 15 and 5.
Is the synesthesia new?
Yes.
Any history of
similar symptoms or psychiatric...
No, nothing.
Are you on any prescription meds
or use any other drugs?
- No.
- Should we trust her answers?
What, you think I'd pull
you off Buddy Ebsen just for a junkie?
Can we trust your answers?
You gotta trust someone, right?
No.
Has anyone close to you been sick
lately? A family member, co-worker?
No, not that I'm aware of.
Two down. Kitty Carlisle?
Do you spend much
time above 20,000 feet?
Why would you ask that?
People who fly are immobile
for long periods.
Could be a leg clot that embolized
to the brain through a PFO.
That's an unusual choice.
Well, like you said,
you wouldn't interrupt Buddy
with anything that wasn't.
The patient is
a frequent flyer.
13, 32, 39, get Osama
an EEG, MRI and angiogram.
How many of you think
that Oswald acted alone?
If, by alone, you mean
that he was unaware that the CIA...
Oh, shut up.
Split yourself into two groups.
Test her blood. Test her stool.
Who likes the
designated hitter?
You're wrong.
You're lucky you're not fired.
Two more groups
LP and cultures.
Who doesn't know what
a designated hitter is?
Okay, here's her address.
I want you to break in
and find out what she's hiding.
Why don't we just ask
the patient for the key?
Well, if you can find out
what she's hiding just by asking,
we'd have to redefine hiding.
You want to live in this country,
learn the language.
What do you want
the rest of us to do?
30 people for three openings
and I want you to wash my car?
This is not why
I busted my ass in med school.
We spend a half an hour
cleaning the car. Big deal.
It's demeaning.
Work is demeaning?
We're too good for this?
Oh, don't give me that
honest day's labor crap.
We all went to med school so we wouldn't
have to do an honest day's labor.
What about an honest
hour's labor?
In exchange, we get
a shot at learning
from one of the best
diagnosticians in the world.
No, we don't.
If we did, we'd be one of the ones
drawing blood or checking for toxins.
We're done.
He's just not gonna
cut us loose
until we've dusted his shelves
and starched his shirt.
I'm out of here. Who's with me?
Are we sure he wasn't joking?
Maybe this is just a test.
Everything's a joke and everything's
a test and he wants us to do it.
Come on, get up here.
Well, I could try,
but I pulled a muscle in 1987.
I didn't waste two years
repeating medical school
- to be arrested and deported.
- Why'd they make you repeat?
Not enough gym credits?
According to
the state of New Jersey,
medical schools in my country
suffer from not being from this country.
You know, if you get it open, you're
gonna have to come down and let me in.
Or, you could just
wait out here.
This is a competition.
Change your mind?
No.
- Then why are you here?
- Never intended to quit.
- Then why did you...
- Intended to get everyone else to quit.
Get off the car.
I need to clean it.
We need to clean it.
I stole his keys.
We'll take it to a car wash.
He's got people breaking
into a woman's apartment.
Obviously, respecting personal property
isn't one of the rules.
I told the super I was
worried about my niece.
She hasn't been
answering the telephone.
Nice guy.
Two daughters in Mount Holyoke.
No evidence of clots, and other than
elevated red blood cell count,
the blood work
was unremarkable.
You got a problem
with the naked female form?
Not at all.
Maybe she's just not used to seeing it
spooning with the naked dolphin form.
That's not a dolphin,
it's a porpoise.
There is a difference, you know.
Salary, for one thing...
You want us to
give you a minute?
High red blood cell
count likely means...
Carbon monoxide poisoning.
There are a lot of
different explanations
for elevated red blood cells.
Yeah, well, which one fits best
with the damaged flue
that your competitors found
in the gas fireplace
in Osama's cave?
Car's clean.
Did you just see a blond guy
with a pretentious accent?
Can't see an accent.
Good point.
Can I have my car keys back?
Give me the car keys,
put the patient in a hyperbaric chamber
and no more
prime numbers for you.
Thank you.
The high pressure and oxygen will flush
the carbon monoxide from your system.
This much oxygen for too long
can have some toxic effects,
so we'll do this in cycles.
Can I talk to you a second?
You're working that thing all the time.
Ls everything all right?
We're supposed to be watching
her heart rate and blood pressure.
Yeah, I was until you
pulled me over here.
I'm sending out a consult
on another patient.
Okay.
What? I'm not quitting my old job
until I'm sure I've got a new one.
- I didn't say anything.
- You had a look.
Yeah, I did. Sorry.
Hey, I think
she's having a heart attack.
No, I just feel a little funny.
Tachyarrhythmia.
Call the code!
Nothing.
V-fib. Where the hell is...
- Clear!
- Are you crazy?
You can't use those!
We're in a hyperbaric...
Clear!
She's on fire!
Her heart's beating.
And we are so fired.
We've started her
on nitro and blood thinners.
Electrolytes and post-arrest EKG
were normal.
The attack was not
caused by the procedure.
So, what does cause
synesthesia,
high red blood cell count
and heart attack?
Aren't we gonna discuss what caused
the sudden appearance of burnt flesh?
He brought charged paddles
into an oxygenated room.
And you didn't stop him.
Means either you thought it was a chance
worth taking, making you a hypocrite,
or you thought he'd fail,
making you a cutthroat little pixie.
- What causes...
- Takayasu's syndrome.
Not without a rash and a fever.
It's gotta be Whipple's.
No way. You ever see Whipple's
without abdominal pain?
Stop it!
This argument is distracting
every male and lesbian here.
You're both right.
In the sense that you've convinced me
that you're both wrong.
What about cardiomyopathy?
Structural abnormality
causes the heart attack
and throws clots to the brain,
leading to synesthesia.
How old are you?
I'm 21, unless it's relevant.
Okay, Scooter.
Do a transesophageal echo.
And since the positive divisors
of 26, are 2 and 13, have them assist.
The rest of you,
go to the cafeteria.
Document 10 things that
can cause infection, each.
I wouldn't.
Someone named 17 thinks there could be
lysteria in the cream cheese.
17's a stupid number.
What's Chase doing here?
You saw Chase?
Last night. Outside my office.
That's interesting.
It's more curious
than actually...
Chase took a job at the Mayo Clinic
in Arizona a week ago.
Interesting.
It wasn't Foreman or Cameron you saw,
but Chase, the one you fired.
Not interesting.
Someone who looked like someone
I used to know walked by my office.
It's always interesting when repressed
guilt starts unrepressing itself.
The only thing I feel
guilty for is this.
We're gonna feed this
endoscope down your esophagus,
try to find where your
heart might be damaged.
It's gonna feel uncomfortable,
but just keep swallowing,
I promise you'll be fine.
She's ready.
Go ahead, take a whack.
Right, so if we don't find anything,
House blames me.
Or you find something
and get a gold star.
Why don't you wanna do it?
House isn't gonna be impressed by a
gray hair doing his ten-thousandth echo.
So, you're just
being altruistic?
That makes you suspicious,
Doctor...
Call me 13.
I'm not getting invested.
Her heart's structurally sound.
No clots, no valvular defects,
no wall motion abnormalities.
Got that from
structurally sound.
- What did she say?
- Structurally sound.
I assume you're not all walking with me
to tell me you found nothing...
It showed a short
burst in the...
Okay. Who's next?
It showed a short
burst of atrial flutter.
I ran a rhythm strip twice
and got the same result.
Stop.
Okay, here's how we
diagnose in transit.
I lead, you draft, I move, you move,
I stop, you stop. Got it?
Flutter could mean
hormone overproduction...
Wait a second. Why did you do the test?
I gave it to Scooter.
We didn't think it mattered.
It doesn't.
It matters that you let her.
Okay, 10, 24, 39, run a TRH
stimulation test for hyperthyroidism.
That could cause
another heart attack.
Proving her first attack
was caused by her thyroid,
which is kind
of the point, right?
Uh-uh, uh-uh, uh-uh.
I ride alone.
The hormones
stimulate your thyroid.
Don't worry if you get flushed
or you start to sweat.
It means the thyroid's working.
And, if you want,
I can remove that mole.
I'm a plastic surgeon.
You're allowed a little vanity.
I'm fine with the way I look.
Good for you.
Although, I do find it a bit odd
that someone so self-assured
doesn't want her doctors
to find out what's wrong with her.
What are you talking about?
Why else am I here?
You're jerking us around.
You're handcuffing us
with all these restrictions.
I'm feeling warm.
Her pulse is 120. Stop pushing.
If House thought
this would handicap us,
he wouldn't have taken the case.
Or maybe that's
why he took the case.
He wants to see if
we can get it out of her on our own.
What did you find at her home?
- You were in my home?
- Nothing.
Travel pictures, yearbook,
her name on an employment slip?
We weren't checking
for that stuff, okay?
Obviously, House didn't
want us to.
You're gonna...
You're gonna out me, aren't you?
You're gonna ruin everything.
Nobody's trying to do anything,
just relax.
This is not a normal response
to the test. Pulse and BP are too high.
Get away from me.
Get away from me!
Don't touch me!
Paging me during Judge Judy,
not the best way to win my affections.
She had another
episode of synesthesia.
It set off a psychotic attack.
And now she ran in there, and must have
jammed something in the handles.
So, you call me?
The guy with one good leg
and zero leverage?
We break that door down, security
shows up and her name goes in a file.
Luckily, violence is
not the last resort.
Extortion is.
So, go ahead. Extort her.
If you don't open this door,
we're gonna break it down.
Clever.
An appeal to her deep concern
for hospital property.
Let's see how that works.
If you don't open this door,
you're going to die.
Go away!
Well, you seem
to be getting to her.
She doesn't care if she dies.
You think she wants to die?
No, but I think she only wants to live
under certain circumstances.
Open up, or I blab
your secret to everyone.
You don't know anything.
I do.
No!
Anybody think that
a sedative might...
- I'm trying.
- Okay!
Who's that?
Who is she?
Osama Bin Laden.
Is she okay?
She's stable. Who is she?
What did House tell you?
That she is on the run
from an international crime syndicate.
That's what he told us.
House may be your boss,
but I'm House's boss.
You wanna work here,
I better be okay with it!
Honestly, he didn't tell us anything
about who she was or what she...
Her name's Greta Cooper.
Wants to be an astronaut.
Doesn't want NASA to know her brain's
getting her ears confused with her eyes.
I went through her mail.
You're a virus, House. Now instead
of one liability, I've got 20.
Apparently only 19.
Which number was it?
From now on, everything you
do gets charted.
With pen, on paper,
in a binder that says,
"Princeton-Plainsboro Teaching Hospital"
on the cover.
Mom!
If you wanna run something
through the labs, I get a copy.
If you do scans, I get a copy.
If you think about doing scans,
I get a copy.
You know my current thoughts, right?
I don't have to put those on paper.
Three issues.
One, number 10, you're fired.
She told you?
Well, it had to be someone
who went to her home.
Number 26 is half asleep.
Missed his afternoon nap.
Obviously,
he doesn't feel guilt.
Number 2 is here on a visa,
she can't jeopardize.
You can't know.
And that chick's been pointing at you
since I walked in.
Issue two,
what causes synesthesia,
high RBC, tachyarrhythmia
and panic attacks?
Slight glucose elevation.
That says thyroid.
- Baseline thyrotropin's 1.1.
- 1.3.
Whatever.
Her thyroid's working.
What about her liver?
Original ALT levels weren't abnormal,
but were near the edge.
- She has patient data on her PDA.
- I do not.
I saw the lab values. You said
we couldn't write anything down.
I also said I wanted answers.
Liver cancer's the most likely.
Paraneoplastic syndrome.
We need to do an MRI.
Which brings us to issue three.
You're saying we
can write stuff down?
To you, I'm saying,
you're fired.
- To everyone else...
- But you said specifically...
I hate tattletales.
- She tattled on 10.
- Now, you've tattled twice.
Issue three...
Come on, let's go.
Issue three, how do we do tests
when we can't do tests?
Dr. Cuddy didn't say we can't do tests,
she said we have to chart.
If we chart, we won't get consent,
so we can't.
The patient's life may
depend on her consenting.
Her dreams depend on
her not consenting.
So, how do we do tests
when we can't do tests?
You've got an hour.
How do you scan a liver
without scanning a liver?
And what's Cameron doing here?
Interesting,
so you're seeing Cameron now.
No, not interesting,
because not seeing. Saw.
My patient won't consent
to MRis or ultrasounds.
You've dealt with more liver cancer
than anyone else here.
So, you want me to share the secret
scanning techniques I learnt in Nepal?
Unfortunately, the monks made me
swear a blood oath.
Where was she?
In the lobby.
I guess, we could palpate
the area around the liver.
Which won't work unless
the tumor's enormous, which you know,
which means you're here because
these visions are freaking you out.
Did...
She had blond hair.
Why would I hallucinate that?
Yes! Yes!
Why are you merging
Cameron and Chase?
We should find out before the next time
you see her, when she'll be black.
Because, of course, it's scientifically
impossible for a person
to go back and visit
somewhere they worked.
No. But since
she's not a dead cat,
it is scientifically impossible for her
to be in two places at once.
Physics joke.
Don't hear enough of those.
She just called
me from Arizona.
Notice the area code, 480.
They put an offer on
a place in Scottsdale.
Do you want to talk or should I?
I guess we could both talk.
Although, they're engaged,
and if you're staying in touch,
you might wanna buy them...
Maybe it's not repressed guilt,
maybe it's just panic.
Right now, you've got enough fellows
to build a rail road,
but you're gonna have to
narrow that room full of numbers
down to three people.
Any chance you could turn this creative
brilliance towards my patient's liver?
I think you're
gonna choose people
for reasons that have nothing
to do with their skills.
I think you're gonna choose people
just because you can't stand them.
Because if you like them,
well, that's just
stressful.
Stress.
I like it.
We need to stress
the patient's liver.
You mean make her sick?
I mean, make her
sick in a specific way.
If her liver's given to malfunctioning,
we make it malfunction.
Are we on the other
side of wrong here?
Don't we have an ethics board
that we should consult, or...
I fired you.
No, you didn't.
He fired you, you're number 6.
No, I'm not. I'm number 9.
I approve of
your shamelessness.
You're still fired.
So, how do we stress her liver?
Lying and paperwork, I get.
Shutting down organs, I think...
We could give her intravenous vitamin D
and stick her in a tanning booth.
If she goes into a coma,
we know it's a metabolic problem.
Nice.
But vitamin D's metabolized
by the liver and kidneys.
It wouldn't tell us
which one's screwed up.
We could get her wasted.
Give her shots of tequila and measure
how long it takes for her to pass out.
If it's too fast, then we know her liver
is not processing alcohol.
Means it's shot.
I like you, number 9.
You wanted to see me?
You a Mormon?
You're wearing
a ring from Brigham Young.
Or did your folks
just do the lawns?
The Church has a very progressive
attitude towards racial equality.
Don't care.
Actually, I'm thanking God.
You're the only
non-drinker we got.
We need a control group
to establish whether the liver's
deterioration is within normal range.
Got a big drinker, a medium drinker,
now I got a no-drinker.
Just do an MRI.
You really think the guy
who created heaven and earth
cares what you put in
your digestive tract?
Her dream shouldn't
outrank my religious belief.
Why not?
Her dream might come true.
All life is sacred, right?
We're not saving her life.
We're doing a diagnostic test.
Not even a real
diagnostic test.
Well, that fake test
might really save her life.
Would you pull an ass out
of a pit on the Sabbath?
Would you or would you not pull an ass
out of a pit on the Sabbath?
Fine. I'll do it.
Good.
Why'd you have to pick tequila?
I assume a single malt
would've worked just as well.
Wasn't our choice.
Okay, two minutes,
then round number five.
So, tell me about
the magic underwear.
Is that why you're here?
I'm the big drinker,
doing my part for science.
The interesting question is
why your religious beliefs
are suddenly less important
than her dreams.
You're reversing your argument?
I know what I believe.
I'm just not quite
sure what you believe.
Well, IDS doesn't try
to dictate every detail of our lives.
When a situation isn't clear, we're
encouraged to make our own decisions.
But your judgment
was to say no.
You used my judgment.
You made a good argument.
Rational arguments
don't usually work on religious people.
Otherwise, there would
be no religious people.
You're an atheist.
Only on Christmas and Easter.
Rest of the time,
it doesn't really matter.
Where's the fun in that?
A finite un-mysterious universe?
It's not about fun.
It's about the truth.
The truth is we're having this debate
because you wanna
figure something out about me.
What have you got so far?
Greta! Greta!
She can't breathe.
We need to intubate.
No!
At least oxygen.
NASA will need to know why!
I checked the tests
you ordered.
Did you just see Foreman?
You measured
the density of her teeth.
It's a shortcut
test for hypocalcaemia.
You had to have
just passed him.
So, you suspected hypocalcaemia
from her complete
lack of broken bones?
Is that why you also
ran three tox screens?
Patient might have
been sneaking uppers.
He was in a white coat.
Did you hire him back?
Foreman is running the
diagnostic department at New York Mercy.
Have you been drinking?
She was having
trouble breathing.
Refused oxygen and intubation.
So you put her on a treadmill?
Records will show
that we gave her oxygen
as a part of
a routine cardio stress test.
She gets to breathe,
your boss gets her paperwork.
Whose idea was that?
It was a joint decision.
It never is.
So, how old were you
when your brother left home?
- Why do you think that I...
- Why aren't you answering?
Did your mother
initiate the divorce?
We should probably focus
on what's wrong with her lungs.
Are you Wiccan?
She really can't breathe.
Okay. Hold still.
What are you doing?
Auscultatory percussion.
If you have
a good ear, you can...
You didn't have a lot of friends,
because you chose not to...
You can hear
while you're talking?
You can detect not only structural
details, but small, deep masses.
Game's over.
You either have lung cancer
or tuberous sclerosis.
We need to cut
you open and biopsy.
That'll
leave a scar.
NASA doctors will see it.
They'll know.
I never opened for Springsteen
or slept with Barbara Feldon.
You can live for years without dreams.
Without lungs...
Find a way.
Okay-
As long as you keep saying it strongly,
you won't die.
Find a way.
How do we force
a patient into surgery?
Texas bag scam? Saratoga Wire?
Paris Exposition Trick?
The problem's not the surgery,
it's the scars,
and we have a plastic surgeon
here who can hide them.
Not that well. NASA's gonna
check every cranny.
I say we just put ether in her oxygen
and do what we have to do.
She'll sue.
For what?
Making it harder for her
to lie to the government?
We don't need to hide them.
We give her elective
cosmetic surgery.
The incisions will give us
access to her lungs.
And she's got an innocent
explanation for the scars.
You mean, like, liposuction.
No, no. Those incisions
are too far from the lungs.
We don't subtract. We add.
Turn her Bs into Cs.
It's myth that fake hooters blow up
at high altitude. She'll be fine.
Just think of it as
one giant rack for mankind.
I fought for years
to be taken seriously.
Trust me, you'll be taken
more seriously. Just sign the form.
This'll make me a joke.
There's gotta be another way.
I've known a few people
who had dreams.
One thing they all had in common
was they got laughed at
and they didn't care.
You bumped a splenectomy
for a boob job?
Would you condemn
this woman to a life
where people look at her face
when they talk to her?
If you don't explain this,
I'll cancel the surgery.
Can I explain why you're here?
I think I just
told you why I...
I scheduled a diagnostic patient
for a boob job. Which is ridiculous.
So, obviously you
had to confront me.
With you so far.
But I'm gonna
give you a reason.
Not a good one.
No. Not even close
to a good one.
But here's the drag
from your point of view.
My explanation will make sense.
Not to the board,
not to a judge, but to you.
So you'll let me do it.
Then, you're gonna have to sit next
to me at the administrative hearing.
Don't you have
better things to do?
It's in the best
interests of the patient.
Trocar's in, you're good to go.
Deflate the lung.
There, a cyst.
Cysts, I count three of them.
Probably the same, if not more,
on the left lung.
Okay, so what's been working overtime
to kill Miss Bin Laden?
We know her name now.
Yeah, but I forgot it.
Say the magic word and get immunity
from the next challenge.
Alveolar hydatid disease.
Hits all the organs.
She'd have had multiple
seizures by now.
Pulmonary Langerhans'.
Doesn't explain
the red blood cells.
Come on!
Cysts, synesthesia, heart attack.
You guys have gotta...
Von Hippel-Lindau syndrome.
Raises red blood cell count,
causes masses on the organs.
If one of the masses
is a pheochromocytoma,
it could cause neurologic episodes
and a heart attack.
Do you see a blonde guy who still has
peach fuzz standing up there?
Yeah.
This is a closed procedure.
Gallery's off limits.
Not to the surgical staff.
Are you gonna hire
that guy instead of us?
Not a chance. I love you guys.
Please dig out the cysts,
histology to confirm Von Hippel-Lindau.
Don't forget her chesticles.
Calling Arizona was
a very nice touch.
You do have residual...
Not only do I not
have residual feelings,
I didn't even have
primary feelings.
- You freaked...
- You lied!
Because you knew it meant...
It meant nothing!
I saw him 'cause he was there.
Did Cameron follow her bashert
to the surgery department?
I think Chase followed her.
She's been a senior attending in the ER
the last three weeks.
A blonde senior attending,
to be accurate.
And Foreman,
is he back in neurology?
He's at New York Mercy.
He's been there a month.
- Did you see Foreman?
- No.
Doctor Chang to OR.
So, I'm cured.
You're fine for now, but
Von Hippel-Lindau is a genetic disease.
There's no cure.
Greta, you need to
come clean to NASA.
You said you got all the cysts.
They could re-emerge.
I'll go to radiology clinics.
I'll get regular screenings.
If something happened
while you're up there,
you'd be playing
Russian Roulette with...
Relax.
She doesn't have to tell,
and neither do you.
Turns out the NASA doctors even know
where the hyphen
in Von Hippel-Lindau goes.
You called them?
I'm not an idiot.
Those shuttles fly over New Jersey.
So, here we are.
The big moment!
Which of you gets to live
to be abused another day?
And which of you goes home
and rationalizes being fired
as character building?
The following numbers,
thanks for playing.
21, 19, 8, 34,
17,
29, 5,
36, 2.
The rest of you, 8 a.m. sharp.
I'll be in sometime
between 10:00 and 3:00.
Oh, and 26,
stick around a while.
I did nothing wrong.
Lots of people did nothing wrong.
Other people screwed up,
I never even...
Other people took chances.
26?
Buddy Ebsen actually was allergic to...
Yeah, I know. How old are you?
21.
You don't think it's relevant.
I'll likely have less time to use
the skills you teach us,
but I don't think
that's significant to you.
How about the fact that you
never went to medical school?
Which is why you let
the unlucky number do the trans echo.
At least you're
ethically unethical.
30 years I worked in the
Columbia med school admissions office.
Audited all the classes,
most of them, more than once.
I just never got a diploma.
You had to know I'd
find out sooner or later.
I know you break rules.
I thought maybe
you'd break one for me.
I can't hire you as a doctor.
But you can still
tell me what you think.
You could also fetch me coffee
and pick up my dry cleaning.
Until I can decide
whether or not to keep you.
So, I'm playing this whole game
to be, like, your secretary?
Assistant sounds marginally
less demeaning.
It's not my dream job.
Actually, it is.
It's just not your dream title.
Three weeks.
For someone who never misses something
small, you missed something big.
You're an idiot.
The hair, where I'm working,
or both?
The hair makes you
look like a hooker.
I like it.
Pulling pieces of windshield
out of car accident victims,
and reattaching fingertips
sliced off cutting bagels?
At least Chase's move
is only one step down.
I can do good here.
Get it out of my system.
Why'd you rat your
patient out to NASA?
I don't know who's been gossiping
about ethics instead of sex,
but I hope they've
already been fired.
- Which number was it?
- Greta.
- Number.
- No number, the patient.
How do you think she got
your pager number?
She came into the ER,
didn't want to talk...
I didn't rat her out.
You lied?
I suppose I should tell her
that before she keys my car.
Why lie?
I had to stop some leaky faucets.
What did it matter?
It was no one's business.
Right.
She's gonna be
the safest astronaut up there.
Certainly more vigilant than the guy
next to her who's got no clue
about the aneurysm
in his head ready to pop.
Right.
You got a better reason?
You couldn't kill her dream.