Remember when your high school
history teacher said that:
"The course of human events changes
because of the deeds of great men"?
Well, the bitch was lying.
Fuck Caesar, fuck Lincoln,
fuck Mahatma Gandhi.
The world keeps moving because
of you and me, the anonymous.
Revolutions get going
because there ain't enough bread.
Wars happen over a game of checkers.
Hey. Good night, turd.
[GUARD LAUGHING]
Hey.
Go, move it.
HILL: Prisoner number 92S1100,
Vernon Schillinger.
Convicted October 21st, '92.
Aggravated assault in the first degree.
Sentence: Eight years.
Up for parole in five.
I had a visit from my sons.
They're almost out of their teens now.
Almost men.
They live with their grandfather.
The man who taught me
everything I know about hate.
Yesterday, my boys
sat there across from me,
ranting and raging.
They were both fucked up on drugs.
They know I hate drugs.
That I'm in here because I hate drugs
and because I love them.
I yelled at them
and, uh, they just
laughed.
They laughed at me.
It's funny, you know,
with one eye, I could see, finally,
that
they are becoming the men I made them.
I got about three months
until I'm up for parole.
All I want is to get out of here.
Be there for them.
Try to help my kids.
That's all.
If I let you back into Em City,
you'll kill Beecher.
If I wanted him dead,
he'd already be dead.
You-
You say you've changed?
Why should I believe you?
Trust me, McManus,
you lose an eye,
you get kicked in the balls,
you get a face full of shit,
you become a different man.
PRISONER 1: King me.
ROSS: He's back. SCHILLINGER: Hey.
Where's Beecher?
He's still in the hole.
Put these on.
Get up.
Do you wanna touch my dick?
Get dressed.
-I shit all over a man.
-I know.
-It's not normal.
-No.
Get dressed.
Schillinger's back in Emerald City.
He says he won't harm you.
Tell me you won't harm him.
He burnt a swastika into my flesh,
he made me rip up pictures of my family,
he made me eat pages of a law book,
he made me wear women's makeup,
and he fucked me up the ass.
I know.
[CHUCKLES]
So now I just forgive him?
Yes.
Could you?
All right.
I forgive him.
Hey, roomie.
So, ahem, how crazy are you?
Crazy?
Well, you broke the glass,
you blinded Schillinger,
you took a shit on his face.
Hey. Hey, what the fuck
are you looking at?
O'REILY:
You see, this is what I'm talking about.
The old Beecher would've hid just now.
Yeah, well, I left
the old Beecher in the hole.
-I hear you.
-Hey. Don't get so close to me, okay?
Okay.
Look,
any day, the Muslims are gonna riot.
I may need you, crazy or not.
Need me to do what?
Be my brother.
BEECHER: Hey. Hey.
It's your move, asswipe!
WITTLESEY: Beecher. Watch it.
You're gonna have the fastest
turnaround time
in the history of the hole.
-Asswipe.
-I'll tell you, man,
you're gonna have to take Beecher out,
otherwise you're not gonna have
any jizz left in Em City.
Everybody's gonna think
you're a pansy ass.
I don't care.
Let them.
HILL: When you're playing poker,
you can't let anybody at the table
know which cards you have,
what you're feeling,
what you're thinking.
You gotta develop a game face.
In Oz,
we wear our game faces all day.
And into the night.
You wear your game face so much
that when you look in the mirror,
you're not sure which face
you're shaving.
-I bring them in, you sell them.
-A carton a day. That's it.
[SPEAKING INAUDIBLY]
WITTLESEY: What's going on?
There's a rumor that you're bringing
contraband into Emerald City.
-What?
-It's bullshit, right?
-Who did you hear this from?
-Tell me it's not true.
-It's not true.
-You're lying to me.
-No, I'm not lying.
-I have an eyewitness, Diane,
that saw you pass
cigarettes to Scott Ross.
An eye-fucking-witness.
-Who?
-Me.
Oh.
-So I'm fired.
-No, you're not fired.
Look, I know that
you're worried about money.
I know you're worried about
your mother and Didi,
-but this shit has got to stop.
-Yeah. Okay.
-Okay, I'll put an end to it.
-Today.
Okay.
I appreciate the second chance, Tim.
-I've been digging through your files.
-Yeah?
I know that Ross and your ex
were in the same biker gang.
Yeah.
You should have told me.
-Have you slept with Ross?
-What?
I'm just trying to figure out
if you fucked us both.
Wha-?
What is this?
You're trying to hurt me
for breaking up with you?
You're trying to prove
to me you've got a dick?
Oh, you know what,
I don't need this. I quit.
Oh, fuck! I'm sorry, I'm sorry.
-You're sorry?
-Yes.
I don't know what's going on with me.
Forgive me, please.
Forgive you?
Okay. Okay, I forgive you. I forgive you.
-You forgave me. We're even.
-Say you'll stay.
I got nowhere else to go.
ROSS: Hey.
I'm done.
I'm out of the cigarette business.
Wait. What happened?
I just can't take the stress.
I don't wanna get caught. I'm done.
It's not that easy.
What does that mean?
It means I have customers
that rely on me.
Yeah, so what?
So...
I'm not gonna let you fuck this up
with your guilt and paranoia.
I say it's done, it's done.
No.
You quit,
I go to the warden,
I tell him everything.
He puts me in the hole
for a little while, big deal.
You,
you lose your job,
you probably do some time,
leaving little Didi
a motherless child, scarred for life.
No, you wouldn't do that.
Why wouldn't I?
Diane,
you and me,
we're joined at the hip.
And ain't nothing you can do about that.
Turn on me again,
your life ain't worth shit.
She's a damn fine woman, our Diane.
Damn fine woman.
[BUZZER SOUNDS]
Hey, who's that?
Oh, new guy.
Some Polack.
[BUZZER SOUNDS]
If the Muslims riot, we're ready.
Angels, Aryans.
What about the Homeboys?
Adebisi says they're on our side,
but I don't think we should fight
the Muslims if we can avoid it.
Oh, what, are you going soft on me,
O'Reily?
No, I'm just trying to stay alive.
What?
Hey.
What are you doing?
Nothing.
Yeah?
Why don't you do it somewhere else?
KENNY: Stupid hacks.
-You're the lookout.
KENNY: I'm on the lookout.
Go on, look out.
Damn.
-Hey, I'm Anthony Nowakowski.
-You're late.
I had never been to Oswald before.
I got lost coming off Route 7A.
I'm Diane Whittlesey. This is Joe Mineo.
Don't be late again.
Another fucking newbie.
WITTLESEY: Joe's been around
for about two centuries.
There's been a lot of suspensions lately.
So I hear. Officers beating up
inmates on a regular basis.
-He killed one of our guys.
-Some of the COs decided
to take it out
on any prisoner they could find.
Things got a little tense,
but I'm hoping we're past it.
Yeah.
Also hear you got a couple
of celebrities in this cell block?
That's Kareem Said.
He's the big muckety-muck Muslim.
It's time.
I want you to start
an argument with the guard.
Get him to swing on you.
But he must hit you first,
you understand?
Yes.
And after he hits me...
[SAID SPEAKS IN ARABIC]
[ALL SPEAK IN ARABIC]
That's Eugene Dobbins.
-He's some classical kind of musician.
HILL: Hey, Dobbs.
WITTLESEY: Used to play the cello
till somebody smashed it.
HILL: Wanna go to the library?
DOBBINS: No.
Come on, man. Gym?
Leave me alone.
Now he sits in front
of the boob tube all day.
And that's Jackson Vahue.
Vahue?
Oh, yeah, man, you see
that game against the Bulls?
Fifty-eight fucking points.
That guy's amazing.
McMANUS: Rebadow.
Your factory supervisor says
you haven't been to work
-for a couple of days.
-God lied to me.
-God lied to you?
-Yes.
Well, why should God be
so different than anyone else?
Oh, shit. I'm late for a meeting.
I used to have meetings.
They never do any good, you know.
[INAUDIBLE DIALOGUE]
HILL: Prisoner number 65R814,
Robert Rebadow.
Convicted September 9th, '65.
Murder in the first degree.
Sentence: Death.
Commuted to life.
I'm beginning to think
I never really talked to God.
That everything I thought I heard
was actually my own powers of reason.
McManus, you're a man of reason too,
but you've gotten lost.
Yeah, well, right now I'm late.
Go to work, Rebadow.
WITTLESEY: Tim, I want you to meet-
-Later.
McMANUS: Hey, Ray.
MUKADA: Tim, how are you doing?
ALVAREZ: We get the hostages.
MUKADA: Hey, Miguel. Could
you guys excuse us for a second?
Hey, whatever you gotta say to me,
you can say in front of them.
MUKADA: Take a hike.
What the fuck is that?
Jose Torres got paroled.
Lucky prick.
So I hear that you're running
the gang now.
Ain't listening to gossip a sin?
Miguel... Hey, Father,
the only reason why I didn't beat
the shit out of you just now
is because you've been there for me.
Don't push your luck.
Okay?
-Okay, where was I?
-Losing.
-You-? You move this piece?
-No.
-Yes, you did.
-No, I didn't.
You fucking moved the pieces.
You've been doing it all along.
Every time I have to take a shit,
you move the pieces.
That's why I'm fucking losing!
-You keep losing because you suck.
-You motherfucking bastard!
WITTLESEY: Hey, break it up!
Hey, break it up!
MINEO: Get off of him!
[PRISONERS SHOUTING]
[PRISONERS CHEERING]
[PHONE RINGS]
-Yeah?
-Hunt, send Armstrong out here now.
Armstrong, get out there. Hurry up.
All right.
Hey, bitch.
O'REILY: Take that.
ROSS: Sucks, motherfucker!
[ALARM BUZZING]
O'REILY: Get down, motherfucker!
O'REILY: Get out of the way!
Get out of the way!
[PRISONERS SHOUTING AND YELLING]
Shit.
Miguel, Miguel.
No! Miguel!
Don't! No!
SAID: You all know what
you're supposed to do. Let's go.
[HONKING NOISEMAKER]
PRISONER: Easiest sucker yet. Come on.
[ALARM BUZZING]
GLYNN: Shut down all the cell blocks
immediately. Cut off the phones.
McMANUS: What's happening?
-Our worst nightmare.
BEECHER: Ah!
[GUNSHOT]
SAID: Now let's get organized.
[PRISONERS CHEERING]
-This is Warden Glynn.
PRISONER: Fuck you.
[PRISONERS SHOUTING]
Surrender immediately,
there will be no repercussions.
Fuck you!
GLYNN: ls there anyone in charge?
Is there anyone in there we can talk to?
Said.
[PRISONERS CHANTING] Said. Said.
Said. Said. Said.
Said. Said.
[CHANTING STOPS]
SAID: Gentlemen.
GLYNN: What's this about, Said?
If you have to ask, Glynn,
we got a long day ahead of us.
[PRISONERS CHEERING]
PRISONER 1: Because I made two dollars.
PRISONER 2: Man, fuck you.
PRISONER 3:
Yeah, motherfucker. Yeah, yeah.
Glynn has given us time
to come up with a list of demands.
But I think the most important element
is that we remain united.
-I don't have a problem with that.
O'REILY: Me neither.
As long as you get
a few ground rules laid down.
SAID: Such as?
Well, you're not the boss.
I am willing to share the power.
-That is why I asked you here.
-Yes.
You see, we can become a kind of council.
We will, together,
make all the decisions.
We can talk
parliamentary procedure later.
-How many guns do you have?
SAID: Just the one.
-I don't believe you.
-You'll have to learn to trust me,
just like I'm gonna
have to learn to trust you.
Yeah, but you got the gun,
and that gives you
one up on the rest of us.
That's right. You know, I hear you
talking about sharing power,
but I can't turn my back on you.
Okay. How would you like me
to demonstrate my sincerity?
ADEBISI: Give me the gun.
O'REILY: What?
Okay, okay.
How about we divide up
the responsibility?
Look, O'Reily, Ross, Adebisi,
you already have control
of the front entrance.
I propose O'Reily be our spokesman
when dealing with Glynn.
Ross, you be in control
of the distribution of food.
Adebisi, all of the comings and goings.
My men should have the hostages.
Okay.
You gonna have to give up Hunt.
-No way.
-We all have to give up something.
It is much more efficient
to have all the hostages in one place.
He's got a point.
Besides, as long as we got
control of the gate,
hacks aren't going anywhere.
So we all agreed then?
O'REILY: Yo. ROSS: Yeah.
All right.
So all that remains
is the list of demands.
Who wants to start?
ROSS: I want some more girls.
O'REILY: Ban on smoking is bullshit.
SAID: We gotta get the wounded
to a separate place, Arif.
-The shower room?
-Yeah, good idea. Go.
Dobbins? Yo, Dob-
Yo, can I get a hand here?
Could somebody help me, please?
Dobbins. Oh, man.
ARIF: Let's take him to the shower room.
HILL: Go ahead.
HILL: You'll always be my hero, man.
-That's me. Fucking role model.
It's priceless to me, and that's why
it's locked in the chaplain's office.
You'll do what I tell you to do
or I'm just gonna fuck you up.
Hey, Jackson,
you leave Dobbins alone, man.
VAHUE: You butt out of this, all right?
Hey, this is all I could find.
They burned everything else.
Oh, shit.
That don't look good, man.
Fuck, I had a friend in a fight
get stabbed like that.
He died right in the middle
of Polanski Boulevard.
Dobbins don't get to a hospital soon, he
gonna be trading that cello for a harp.
This fucking guy and his goddamn cello.
You broke it, didn't you? Didn't you?
-No, man. No, no. No, no.
-You gotta take him to ER.
No. All right, Hill, I go out there,
they kick my fucking ass.
They're gonna kick in
our asses anyway, brother.
No, man. Hey, this ain't my fault, Hill.
Yo, he is definitely not my problem, man.
I did not start all this shit, Hill.
What difference does it make, huh?
You think because of who you are
you can pick and choose
when to take responsibility. You can't.
Sometimes you got to step up.
All right? Look at him.
Hey, look at him.
Dobbins, that cello, that's all he had,
man. It's like me and that chair.
It's who he was.
It's like you and basketball.
Come on, man. You're all right.
It's okay. Good. Just hold on.
All right, all right.
All right, look. All right, fuck it.
Fuck it. Yo, yo, fuck it.
I been hit before. Come on, come on.
HILL: Just grab him, man.
-Come on, Dobbs.
VAHUE: Open the gate.
VAHUE: Come on. HILL: Come on, yo.
I gotta get Dobbs to the hospital.
ROSS: Fuck Dobbs.
-Yo, let us out!
-Yeah, let him out, man.
ROSS: What could you do?
ADEBISI: What's up, brothers?
-Dobbs is dying, man.
Let's dump him before he starts
getting moldy, all right?
-Okay.
-What about Said and Alvarez?
If you vote yes, that's a majority.
We don't need them at all.
Let's do what I'm saying.
If the three of us hang together,
Said's our bitch.
Okay. O'REILY: Let's go. Come on, man.
PRISONER: Hey.
We're letting out one wounded prisoner.
Tell Glynn.
Open the gate.
[BUZZER SOUNDS]
I'll see you, all right?
Yeah.
[BUZZER SOUNDS]
VAHUE: Hold on, man.
GUARD 1: Drop him, asshole!
VAHUE: Damn. Somebody help him!
GUARD 2: Shut up, basketball boy.
VAHUE: Fuck! GUARD 2: Cuff him.
VAHUE: Shit!
GUARD 1: We got one of those bastards.
DOBBINS: Ah!
Hello.
Hope you don't mind, I gotta take a shit.
Beecher, listen... Hey.
You know, I'm standing here
thinking about
all the good times we've had, you and me.
I don't wanna fight.
Oh, no, of course not.
You get into a fight,
you fuck up your parole.
And I hear for the next three months,
you're gonna be a good little boy.
So you can get out of Oz,
save your two sons.
You know, I think that's great.
But you know what I'm wondering?
What if Vern doesn't get out?
What if, as he comes up for parole,
he gets into a brawl,
a knockdown-dragout with his old roomie?
What if every time
he comes up for parole,
Vern gets into some ugly incident,
and has to serve his entire sentence?
And his two sons,
they become monsters.
[CHUCKLES]
That's what I'm wondering about.
Prag.
♪ I got it bad ♪
♪ And that ain't good ♪
HILL: We love to root for the underdog.
You know,
at halftime, when one team is getting
their asses handed to them
and they're headed to the locker room,
we say a silent prayer.
We pray that when they come back,
they'll turn it around, they'll score,
they'll beat those cocky
sons of bitches, yeah!
We love it when someone
comes up from behind.
We have to figure out a way to escape.
-How?
-I don't know, but I can't just sit here
-waiting to get raped.
-Or killed.
You really think they're gonna kill us?
No, they're gonna invite us for tea.
Armstrong?
Is he gonna be all right?
You sit down over there with them.
-What's the matter with Armstrong?
-Shut up, Hunt, sit the fuck down.
I'm in charge of you motherfuckers now.
I don't know how long
this shit's gonna last,
but if you don't give me any trouble,
you walk out of here alive.
Okay?
We've all been beaten badly.
Armstrong needs a doctor.
-Armstrong.
-Hey. Hey.
ALVAREZ: Hey.
-I'll see what I can do.
-I gotta piss.
WITTLESEY: Father, you're friendly
with Alvarez, aren't you?
I thought I was.
He let them take me
without lifting a finger.
You didn't really think that he'd
lift a finger to help you, did you?
He'd get whacked if he tried to help you.
ALVAREZ: You know what it's like
in the hole, right?
You get a bucket to piss and shit in.
Stays with you the whole time.
Go ahead.
Uncuff me.
[WHISPERING] No.
You know that joke
you made when my baby died?
[YELLING] Fucking cocksucker!
-Fuck you! Fuck you! Fuck you!
MUKADA: For God's sake, stop it!
Miguel!
MUKADA: What the fuck is going on?
-Look. Look, right now,
-I can't change shit if I wanted to.
-Maybe you can't change shit,
but you don't have to give in
to the brutality.
ALVAREZ: You're so fucking naive.
-Naive?
I'm not naive.
I'm afraid.
Yeah? Well, so am I, hermano.
So am I.
REPORTER [ON TV]: We have
unconfirmed reports that a riot
has erupted at Oswald State Penitentiary.
Correction officials and the governor
will neither confirm nor deny
that a riot broke out in the prison,
which has been plagued with violence
in recent months.
It's under the tight scrutiny
of the Devlin administration...
Move. SAID: Let him up.
REPORTER: -investigation into
the rash of murders there.
And though the warden,
Leo Glynn, has assured us
that nothing unusual is happening,
if recent events are any indication,
a riot would be almost inevitable.
So, Alvarez, how are the hostages?
They need a doctor.
Well, I say we get them one.
Because we don't wanna seem
like savages now, do we?
Of course, you're gonna have
to clear that with all the others.
Okay.
[SNORTS]
Adebisi, you gotta slow down
on that shit.
Why?
Because we need our fucking heads
to be together right now.
Besides,
if this situation gets worse,
we're gonna run out of that stuff.
And I don't want you detoxing on me
when I need you the most.
You worry too much, pretty boy.
Have some.
No.
I've been clean
since my time in the hole.
Clean for what, huh?
[LAUGHS]
KENNY: I'm gonna fucking kill you!
O'REILY: Hey! Hey!
Hey, break it up! Break it up!
ROSS: Fuck this, man! Fuck you!
O'REILY: Hey! Hey! Hey!
This is exactly what those dicks
out there are hoping for.
Said too.
Hey.
Why do you think
he gave you guys the archway for?
He's waiting for one side
to kill the other-
-And then-KENNY: Let's do that. Fuck it!
He's gonna kill whoever's left,
all right?
We gotta stick together, Wangler.
[ADEBISI CLAPPING]
Hey, Kenny, cool down.
Yo, there's a couple of hacks
that are in pretty bad shape,
so Said and I wanna get them a doctor.
How do you vote?
No.
Fuck that.
Yo, O'Reily,
it's 2 to 2.
You can break the tie.
PRISONER: Yeah, break the tie.
-What's it worth to you, Alvarez?
-What is it worth to me?
Yeah.
What will you give me for my vote?
Nothing.
Let the fuckers die.
Fucking bunch of niggers.
Had an uncle who was a drunk.
We tried to get him some new hobbies
to keep him from drinking.
Got him into sculpting school.
Didn't help.
Kept coming home plastered.
Oh, Jesus Christ.
Had another uncle
who was a rare-coin dealer.
One day, a couple of tough guys came
into the place and beat him senseless.
Stop.
Got another uncle
who owned a grocery store.
One night, somebody comes and caves
his head in with a case of corn flakes.
The cops think it might have been
-a cereal killer.
MUKADA: A cereal killer.
D'Agnasti, shut the fuck up.
Just trying to break the tension.
Sorry, no doctor.
MUKADA: You gotta do something.
-Yeah, I know.
I been working as an orderly
in the prison hospital, so...
Oh, so, what, now you're
an MD all of a sudden?
All you're good for is cleaning up shit.
Shut up, Eddie.
I used to work as a nurse's aide,
-I could give you a hand.
-No fucking way.
Look, we gave them a couple of hours
to come up with their list of demands.
Before we take any action, we might
as well wait and see what they want.
I say no negotiations.
I say we cut off
the water and electricity,
and then tonight, when they're sitting
in the dark, we fire tear gas.
What about the hostages?
Hopefully, the SORT team will reach them.
Hopefully?
We don't even know where they are.
Or if they're alive.
Said says he's got seven hostages.
-How do we know for sure?
-We ask to see them.
DEVLIN: The longer we wait, the more
chance we're giving them to dig in.
And even though we've sealed off
that section
and locked down all the cell blocks, the
other inmates know what's going on.
We're sitting on a time bomb.
I'm going public.
I'm sending in the National Guard
to surround Oswald.
[PHONE RINGS]
Yes?
Okay.
That was Hofmeister.
The rioters want food.
There's no reason to give them anything.
Oh, yeah, let's starve them out.
Governor, I see no harm
in sending in some sandwiches.
-I'll take them inside.
-What?
Yeah, as a condition
for giving them food,
we tell them they have to let me
check on the hostages.
You're going in there voluntarily?
Yeah.
You're even stupider than I thought.
Hello.
Leave it there. McMANUS: No. Uh-huh.
The deal was I get to see the hostages.
You, alone.
O'REILY: Dinner is served.
-Help yourself, boys.
-Who says your boys-?
-I fucking say-
-Oh, yeah? Fuck you.
-Fuck you.
For Christ sake!
We'll serve the sandwiches
the same way we do in the cafeteria.
Jesus Christ.
McMANUS: Where are the hostages?
I'll show you.
Okay, gents, line the fuck up.
One.
I said one, Wangler.
McMANUS: Are these two okay?
They'd be better off in a hospital.
McMANUS: How about the rest of you?
-We're fine.
No thanks to these cocksuckers.
-Diane?
-No one touched her,
if that's what you mean.
Was I talking to you?
Watch your mouth, McManus.
You ain't king of shit
around here no more.
Are there any other hostages?
WITTLESEY: No, not that we know of.
What would it take to get
these two and her set free?
Gotta put it to a vote.
Why don't you just stand?
McMANUS: So, um,
you let them go, I stay.
Three for one?
Not even trade.
If Mineo and Armstrong die,
you will be held responsible.
We're talking death sentence here.
So okay. The two of them go,
but Whittlesey stays.
Then no deal. ROSS: McManus,
I don't think you fully grasp
your current position here.
We don't have to let any
of them go, or you.
You taking me prisoner?
You gonna go back on your word?
We have every intention
of fulfilling our part of the bargain.
Why should we?
Because if we lie to them,
we become just like them.
And we won't get our list of demands.
I say we let Armstrong and Mineo go.
Me too.
Who else? Adebisi?
Yeah, fine.
Ross?
Oh, well, Whittlesey's gotta stay.
Said?
Okay.
[BUZZER SOUNDS]
This is a letter for Glynn from
McManus explaining the exchange.
Here's our demands.
Let's go. PRISONER: Let's go.
GLYNN: They want to speak directly
to the media, uncensored.
Sure, we'll put them on
right after Seinfeld.
GLYNN: There are to be no reprisals
or repercussions
to any inmate involved in the riot.
Oh, Jesus Christ,
why don't they just ask to go free?
You know, most of these
demands are harmless.
Bring back conjugal visits, smoking-
Yeah, well, I reject all their demands.
I won't negotiate with animals.
Then how do you expect me
to end the situation?
The old-fashioned way.
By force.
This is all your fucking fault, McManus.
-Shut up, Eddie.
-No. Goddamn it.
If I'm gonna die, at least I want the
bastard that got me whacked to know it.
MUKADA: How can you blame Tim?
How? Because of all
this Emerald City bullshit.
Because Tim thought
he could help these cocksuckers.
I've seen you in action, pal.
I've seen you fumble the fucking ball
every single play.
I just hope if we do die,
I get to watch you go first.
McMANUS: Oh, fuck.
Oh, Christ.
McMANUS:
I gotta see Said. I wanna talk to Said.
I don't know.
Please, Miguel.
I like that.
I like it when you beg, McManus.
Said,
I grew up in a small town
in upstate New York.
There was only one major industry there.
The prison.
Everybody's parents
either worked at the prison
or made a living from, you know,
motels, gas stations,
or, like my dad, had a diner.
Right across the street.
It was the fall.
We'd just gone back to school.
I was about to turn 100,
so I was very, very excited.
A few days before my birthday though,
there was this riot.
And it lasted four days.
But then the governor
authorized 2,500 troops,
state troopers,
to go back in, take it back.
They did.
Firing at anything that moved.
So when the tear gas cleared,
31 inmates and nine hostages were dead.
Attica.
Three of my friends' fathers were shot.
Instead of going to a birthday party,
I went with my family
to a, uh, memorial service.
So that's what this is all about?
Emerald City is your birthday party.
Look,
I built Em City
because I wanna make a better world.
For you.
For all of you.
Right now we're on the edge of oblivion,
we're on the brink of disaster.
Now, before we all join hands and jump,
I want another chance.
-Not mine to give.
-Yes, it is!
No, it's not!
Because even the best prison
wouldn't be good enough!
I'm gonna try one more time
with you, McManus.
Now, I am not saying that the men
in Oz are innocent.
I'm saying they are not here because of
the crimes that they committed,
but because of the color of their skin,
their lack of education,
the fact that they are poor.
You see, this riot is not
about getting smoking back,
conjugal rights,
it's not even about life in prison.
It's about society taking responsibility.
It's about the whole
horrid judicial system.
And we don't need more prisons,
bigger prisons, better prisons.
We need better justice.
Now, what can you do about that?
If we don't resolve this, you and me,
and soon,
people will die.
You could die.
I am willing to lay down my life
for change.
Now, those deaths at Attica,
they brought real changes,
with real reforms.
But everybody's forgotten
the lessons of your little hometown.
Time to wake this country up
again, McManus.
Said, we gotta talk.
You wanna save this place, right?
And I wanna destroy it.
Brick by hypocritical brick.
Wait, wait.
-Let me out of here!
O'REILY: This isn't working.
-What?
-The entrance way. Every ten minutes
I'm putting a fire out between
the Gangsters and the Nazis.
Well, put the Aryans in another part
of the cell block.
They'll want something in exchange
for giving up the security office.
Switch them with the Latinos.
They can take care of the hostages.
Okay. There's something else.
-What?
-We're out of heroin.
-Good.
-Says you.
Adebisi and his pals
are starting to fiend.
This is gonna get real ugly, real fast.
When and if that happens,
I will be ready.
What are you gonna do?
[SAID SCOFFS]
Don't you fucking
walk away from me, Said!
SAID: Enough!
O'REILY: Back off, Beecher, back off.
Arif!
Everybody go back.
[MUSLIMS SPEAK IN ARABIC]
I gotta find some-
-I'm dying for some tits, man.
-Me too, little buddy, me too.
They gotta be somewhere,
somewhere around here.
Follow me. Come, come.
Come.
Go through every pod.
See whatever drug you can find. Go.
Go. Go, go. Go there. Go, go!
Let's go. Go!
[PRISONERS SHOUTING]
ADEBISI: Where are the tits?
Where are the tits?
Where are the bloody tits?
-Where are the tits?
-I got no fucking tits, man.
ADEBISI: Where are the fucking tits?
Where are they?
Where are the tits?
Adebisi!
[KENNY CHOKING AND GAGGING]
It's finished!
It's over.
KENNY: Come on.
[ADEBISI LAUGHING]
ADEBISI: Whoo-ha!
[ADEBISI LAUGHING HYSTERICALLY]
Police. Police.
[BREATHING HEAVILY]
Execution day, baby.
Prisoner number 93A234, Simon Adebisi.
Convicted May 2nd, '93.
Murder in the first degree.
Sentence: Life in prison
without the possibility of parole.
[CHUCKLING]
Go ahead.
Kill me.
I don't wanna kill you.
I know. You wanna save my ass.
-Yes, I wanna save you.
-Please,
give me some tits.
Give me some tits!
Give me some fucking tits!
HILL: They say,
"It don't matter if you win or lose,
it's how you play the game."
I call bullshit on that.
It's all about winning, brother.
That's the object of the game.
ARIF: What is that?
SAID: The beginning and the end,
my brother.
The beginning and the end.
Okay, everybody,
they're about to make their move.
Bring out the hostages.
ADEBISI: Please, untie me.
You shouldn't have stolen
my fucking watch.
Untie me. Hey, don't be like that.
-Untie me!
-Stand in a straight line.
When they come in, you get hit first.
-Any last words?
-Suck my dick.
If only there were time.
[EXPLOSION]
McMANUS: Hit the ground.
PRISONER: Said.
[PRISONERS COUGHING]
Fuck. Open the fucking door, man.
Fuck.
Ah!
Yeah, motherfuckers!
[EXPLOSION]
[MACHINE GUN GUNFIRE]
[PRISONERS COUGHING]
[GUNSHOT]
HILL: Yeah, who cares
who lives or dies in prison?
We read the names in the morning
paper and they mean nothing to us.
[MACHINE GUN GUNFIRE]
They're faceless. Truth is,
we don't wanna put a face on them.
We don't wanna know who they really are.
Because then it might hit
too close to home.
And home is what it's all about, right?
Making a home no matter where you are,
no matter who you are.
At the end of the day,
everybody wants somewhere to rest,
somewhere to lay their bones,
even if it's in a land called Oz.
Yeah.
Like Dorothy says when she wakes up
in her own bed back at Aunt Em's:
"There's no place like home."
There's no fucking place like home.