Hey.
Don't bother.
He's dead.
You're dead, too.
The fire isn't.
You might want to get up and start
heading for the exit signs.
For all I know,
I already am up.
More interesting question is,
why would I hallucinate
an ex-employee
who I last saw with a
self-inﬂicted gunshot wound,
as opposed to
someone more busty?
Care to explain
why you're here?
The dead guy.
Who is he?
How'd you meet him?
I was in a car accident
last month.
I won a swimming trophy in high school.
Your turn.
I ran out of pain medication.
I got an orbital fracture.
It's just taking ages to heal.
Take off your shirt.
My eye's up here.
Orbital fracture means your
face went into the windshield.
Which means your chest
went into the steering wheel.
Painkillers can
suppress heart rate,
so unless you want me
to kill you,
take off your shirt,
let me do a heart exam.
I also wanted to see the ring of
burns around your collarbone.
How did you know?
The "codeine allergy"
you told the nurse about, that's shorthand
for "give me the strong stuff,"
which matches
your seen-better-days
- because-my-life-fell-apart
suit.
The two old burns
on your fingers
mean you tend to nod off
with a cigarette
in your hand. No reason you shouldn't
do that with one in your mouth.
May all your doctors be stupid.
Hold on a second.
That bruising
around your belly button.
You might get some fun drugs
out of this after all.
Cullen's sign,
but the ultrasound showed
air as well as blood. Now,
I know what you're thinking.
Hemorrhagic pancreatitis.
But I also know
what I'm thinking.
Doesn't explain
the pneumoperitoneum.
You took a new case?
You ran tests yourself?
I saw the chance to help someone
in need, and I instinctively...
No, wait, that was
someone else's instincts.
Wilson's dying,
your parole officer
is probably on his
way here right now.
How are you possibly
in a good mood?
Did you never see Dead Poets Society?
Carpe diem.
Air in his abdomen could
mean blah, blah, blah.
But blah, blah,
blah, blah, blah.
Blah, blah, blah.
Nobody cares
about the medicine.
Perforated ulcer.
Laparotomy to find the hole
in his tummy and close it up.
You didn't answer
the team's question.
Which is weird 'cause normally
when I talk to my own employees,
I'm under oath and hooked
up to a lie detector.
You were looking at
six months of prison
instead of five months
of Wilson.
Why happy?
Obviously I had a plan.
Obviously,
obviously you had a plan.
The more
interesting question is,
why you didn't tell the team.
I think it's because part
of you knew from the start
that the plan wouldn't work.
I need a meeting.
I'm busy.
Call my office.
Yes.
Because wobbly tables don't just
un-wobble themselves.
I need a meeting.
Thanks for fitting me in.
My team has eight urgent,
life-or-death cases
that they've been waiting
for me to accept or reject.
When is that not true?
Well, right now for one.
But tell my parole board
that I'm taking all eight.
That no one else
can crack them,
that you need me here
for the next five months
or eight people will die.
You're asking me
to perjure myself.
Just a tiny white lie.
No of fence.
Especially since from what I
hear nothing black is tiny.
Except your penis, I guess.
You really think I wanted
to cave in that ceiling?
It was a prank that went wrong.
Dock my pay, sue me...
Felony vandalism
should've added
another year or two
to your sentence.
It's a miracle the parole
board agreed to six months.
I will go to jail.
Eventually.
I will pay the price. I'd just
rather that Wilson didn't.
Come on.
Be a friend.
Okay.
But whatever cases you have,
you have to take them all.
"Be a friend"?
How many fingers
am I holding up?
Of course, you know it's three
because you know
everything I know,
everything my smack-addled
brain can remember.
Including that I actually
said, "Be a friend."
My point wasn't
that you said it.
My point was, once again, why?
I think it's because
part of you knew
you were going
to need a friend.
Part of you knew the plan, even
when it was working, wouldn't work.
And right now, I'm curious about
why you're sitting on the ground
instead of heading
for the door.
Guess we've figured out
why you're seeing me,
your suicidal friend.
He'll call you twice a day. Then
his wife will call you twice a day
to make sure she understands
what he told her you told him.
Which she won't,
because he didn't.
Maybe you want to
give this one to Connors.
Where's House?
Don't know,
don't care, working.
Excuse me.
No one has seen or heard from
him since two nights ago.
I'm sure he's enjoying himself.
Last time he went to prison
he maxed out his credit cards.
Last time he went to prison, he
thought he had you waiting for him.
You think he could have
done something stupid?
I think stupid is
our best-case scenario.
Why do you want
to kill yourself?
Here's a reason. I can't even get
stoned without some annoying jerk
deciding I need to
be deeply analyzed.
Isn't this just an incredibly
simple calculation?
I'm going to jail, losing my
job, losing my best friend.
Do I need more?
You think that's the sum
total of who you are?
A doctor, a friend to Wilson?
I'm also a tremendous baritone.
Now go away.
Even with your subconscious,
you're evasive.
Death's not interesting.
You exist for
what's interesting.
Puzzles' ideas, analysis.
Death is the opposite
of a cool puzzle.
It's eternal nothingness.
But you don't find life
interesting anymore.
Stop being an idiot.
Can I have Kutner back, please?
How much pathetic wallowing
do I have to sit through?
How are things in hell?
Is the humidity the big issue?
What happened next with
the guy's medical case?
Why?
Exactly.
Why am I, meaning you,
still obsessing
about this case?
Obviously,
we think it's relevant
to why we're still sitting on
the ﬂoor of a burning building.
There was a code.
Gotta be a clot in his lungs.
We need to get him to an OR.
No time,
his O2 sats are falling.
We have to suck it out here,
- bedside embolectomy.
- Float a catheter through his heart
and his oxygenation'll
get even worse.
He'll die before we can
finish the procedure.
House, we need a call here.
What are you doing?
What did you give him?
Five,
four,
three, two...
Naloxone.
We should have got suspicious
when his visiting cousin
signed in as Mr. Tar H. Horse.
The heroin caused
the respiratory distress,
the naloxone turned off the
receptors, causing your distress.
I'm not going to
stop doing drugs!
It's reality that sucks!
You're saying I'm lying?
To my subconscious?
People do it all the time. And
like it or not, you are a person.
He said every one of those...
But not then.
And not like that.
This guy was going nuts
from the naloxone.
He couldn't be rational
if you wanted him to be.
Which you did. Why?
I compressed
the story a little to...
Context matters.
You never talk to patients
for non-diagnostic reasons.
But this guy...
Feeling better?
I'm not going to
stop doing drugs.
You were a stockbroker,
son of a stockbroker,
married, children...
And I was miserable.
You say you were miserable
because you need to
rationalize screwing it up.
Except I didn't.
I mean, I did,
but I'm not miserable.
Not anymore.
I had a ski injury
and painkillers weren't enough
and a friend of mine
gave me some heroin.
The second it entered
my veins, it was like
God had taken over my body.
It was like there was
no more pain
or unhappiness in my life
or anybody else's.
But then you lost everything.
Everything wasn't enough.
Because it's reality
that sucks.
Are you arguing that
he's a good role model?
He's happy.
He's dead.
You heard what
you wanted to hear.
The more interesting question,
always, is why you
wanted to hear it.
You're stealing
this guy's oxygen?
There's oxygen everywhere.
You passed on all your cases,
reassigned them
to other doctors.
They weren't interesting.
They were my reason for getting
your sentence delayed.
Yeah, I guess
you'll have to tell
the parole board
something else.
Maybe that I was in the OR the
entire day the ceiling collapsed,
so I couldn't have caused
the plumbing problem.
You set me up.
Not really.
You were going lo
basically perjure yourself
so that I could
delay jail time.
Doesn't it make more sense
to actually perjure yourself
so I can actually
avoid jail time?
Why are you doing this?
Why are you risking
destroying yourself?
There is no risk.
I know you.
You'll do the honest thing.
You'll lie.
No.
He's happy.
He's dead.
You weren't worried.
Of course I was worried.
My plan fell through.
The plan didn't matter. Your plan
to replace that plan didn't matter.
Wilson didn't matter,
jail didn't matter,
the only thing that mattered,
the only thing that ever
mattered was the puzzle.
I noticed a slight twitch
in his thenar eminence.
Which meant...
You're dying.
Because my thumb
is a little shaky?
Plus the thinning
of the muscle.
Plus that speech you gave
at Yankee Stadium
saying you were the luckiest
man on the face of the earth.
Add them up, it means ALS.
Lou Gehrig's disease?
You're trapped in your body.
You can't move or speak
while you just die?
If it makes you
feel any better,
at this rate, it'll be fast.
You're not symmetrical.
Wait.
Now you're standing
at the door.
What happened in the meantime?
And lo, there was a miraculous wonder.
I walked across the room...
No, you just skipped over
a chunk of conversation.
He swore that he'd live a
better, more selfless life
in his remaining lime,
blah, blah, blah.
After two blahs, I'd heard
enough and I moved to the door.
No. You're avoiding it.
Do you smell smoke?
Fair enough.
You're not symmetrical.
The veins on your right
side are distended.
What does that mean?
There's a bulge
in your supraclavicular notch.
There's something in there.
What?
I'm not that good a doctor.
Good news.
Your case is fascinating.
And good news for you,
you're gonna live.
You've inhaled a small branch,
probably while you were realizing
that it's all worth it
while you were passed out
on a park bench.
Anyone else would have coughed it
up, but 'cause you're a junkie,
your cough reflex
is suppressed.
And it grew?
Not unless you also
inhaled a chunk of the sun
and a drip-irrigation
system, you idiot.
It set off an autoimmune reaction
which, and I can't help saying this,
was the root of
all your problems.
You're smiling.
I was, and now I'm not.
Because a moment's
fun a few days ago
does not trump a friend dying.
Yeah, it does, you idiot.
Because after he's dead
you cry for a while
and then you go back
to doing what you love.
Every patient I've had,
in 70 years from now, they'll
all be as dead as Wilson.
Everybody dies.
It's meaningless.
When you solve a puzzle,
the world makes sense
and everything feels right.
And you'll always
have another one,
because people
will always get sick.
It's shallow and
it's insignificant,
but if you don't give
a damn if idiots live,
why would you possibly give
a damn about shallowness?
It makes you happy.
And why would you
need more than that?
Go home.
Foreman.
House would never leave food
out here rotting for days.
His suitcases are
in his closet.
If we had handled
this differently...
We did the right thing.
Hello?
I'll let his accountant know.
House no-showed on a
hooker two nights ago.
Outgoing calls.
Hooker.
Me. I didn't pick up.
The Chinese place...
Wait, wait, wait.
Who's that?
He called four times.
I don't know.
It's a total disaster. Do you
have any idea how hard it is
to schedule a cable appointment
with the hours that I work?
House has been missing for two
days, we know he talked to you.
Anything you can tell
us about his mental state,
or where he was headed,
anything at all...
Would be a breach of confidentiality
and a violation of the law.
Not if he's a danger to
himself or someone else.
Is this coming out
of our 50 minutes?
Is this your douchebag group?
Excuse me.
What makes you think
he's a danger to himself?
He hasn't been home, but he
didn't take anything with him,
not even his cell.
You're not saying anything,
which means he didn't
specifically mention suicide.
But you came out here
to talk to us,
so he must've said something
that worries you.
There are other ways
of reaching oblivion.
Vicodin? He always
has his Vicodin,
there's no reason
to calla shrink...
His last patient
was a heroin addict.
So I guess we're all done here.
The guy's address has
gotta be in the file.
What about God?
You were leaving,
and then you stopped.
Why?
Your theory is I'm not leaving
because I believe in God?
What?
He's calling me home?
Maybe falling through
that floor was a sign.
Maybe that the universe
hates you. Something.
You really don't believe?
Really, not in some deep
crack of some remote recess
of some dark corner
of your mind?
No.
Except that some deep crack
of some remote recess
of some dark corner
is here telling me...
That's enough.
In a burning building, facing imminent
death, that's more than enough.
Pascal's wager is facile.
Saying it's facile is facile.
Why is it wrong?
Don't be logical.
Be desperate.
You've gotta have
something to hold on to.
But you can't live your life based
on something you don't believe.
But you could end your life based
on something you don't believe?
What about love?
I lived with you for years.
I know you believe in love.
Foreman wouldn't help me.
Which means I need you
to take the fall.
You do remember
I'm dying, right?
Which is why you'll never
spend a day in jail.
Fresh-faced,
cancer-ridden.
It's tough to do both,
but you pull it off.
Your fingerprints are all
over those hockey tickets.
I never admitted to
flushing anything.
My prints make sense if I
gave those tickets to you,
as an incentive to stay alive.
And I was so angry that you
didn't respect my dying wishes,
Hook thousands of
dollars of season tickets
and ﬂushed them down toilets?
All you have to do
is create reasonable doubt.
Great. What if I do
more than that?
What if I end up in jail?
Or spending my final months
in endless hearings?
That's a risk
you're willing to take.
I have a reputation, I have
a legacy that could...
Wilson.
I don't want to lose
this time with you.
Okay.
Thanks.
I knew I could count on you.
Wait! Wait!
You want the fries back?
I'm not gonna take the fall.
Don't do this to me, Wilson.
It's our only option.
Exactly.
Because you overplayed
your hand with Foreman.
Because you knew
you had me as a backstop.
Even with me dying,
you just assumed
I'd be here to bail you out.
Since you are here,
and you are bailing me out
seems like
a pretty safe assumption.
Hey!
I won't be here soon.
If I do this, I'm teaching you
that your bad behavior
will always be rewarded.
You need to learn.“
How to act when you're gone?
If that's the lesson, we've a
really great opportunity coming up.
You'll just try to find someone
else, and it won't work,
and it shouldn't work.
So that's the great wisdom
you're imparting?
That I'll always be alone?
There's only one person
you can count on.
I thought there were two.
I need to do this.
For you.
Wilson's right.
He's always right. He's
always been your good side.
I always wondered why I
photographed so poorly.
And because he's
always played that role,
you've never had to develop
a conscience of your own.
People don't change. Consciences
don't spontaneously develop.
You're wrong, Greg.
Which is why you'll be
better off without him.
You've been looking to him to find what
you've gotta find within yourself.
Something you can find.
Hold your child.
This is a reason to die.
This is what my life could
have been, not what it can be.
If it could have been,
you're capable of it now.
You're married, Cuddy's gone.
We aren't the only two
people who could love you.
Why settle so easily?
These are just
idiotic fantasies.
Greg, don't.
At odds with every
logical bone in my body.
Get up.
You do not have to die in here!
Is this hell?
An eternity of people trying
to convince me to live?
Who says I'm hereto
convince you to live?
You're the last one
I thought would hate me.
I don't hate you.
I love you.
And yet you think
I deserve to die.
But not as a punishment
As a reward.
I think
you've suffered enough.
You've given enough.
I think you deserve
a chance to just
give up
Like Wilson did?
Like Wilson did.
You accepted his choice that ending
the pain is better than the pain.
Why can't you give
yourself that gift?
This is the address
House's patient gave?
Everybody lies.
Do you smell smoke?
Just lei go.
Just go to sleep.
I had a chance to avoid this.
You had many chances,
and you blew them all up.
No, this was different.
They're all different. But the
reasons are all the same.
You're arrogant
You're self-destructive.
You only care about yourself.
That moment with the patient.
That chunk of conversation
I skipped over.
I told him he was dying.
If it makes you
feel any better,
at this rate, it'll be fast.
Let me take the fall.
For you.
For that prank.
You don't owe me anything.
You tried to save me.
I failed. Motives don't matter.
Only actions.
Trying is an action.
Why are you trying to
talk me out of this?
You just fake the records, you say
I came into the clinic last week.
I'll tell the cops
you treated me like crap.
So I stole your tickets
and ﬂushed them.
Thank you.
And you're doing this
because you're dying?
I'm doing this because I
have nothing left to lose.
So when you were living, you did
nothing for anyone and didn't care.
Now that you're dying, you're
willing to help a virtual stranger.
Which means you're a better person
dying than you ever were living.
And the world's a better place
because I didn't save you.
Which makes me wonder
why I'm about to tell you,
you're not symmetrical.
What's your point?
That you cared about him more
than you cared about yourself?
You cared about the puzzle more
than you cared about yourself.
If I kept it to myself, then
it would just be a puzzle.
But I opened my mouth because
I thought it was more.
You know it's the same or you
wouldn't be bickering with me
while the flames lick
at your feet.
You're afraid of this decision,
and you are trying to argue until
fate takes it out of your hands.
You're taking
the cowardly way out.
And worse
you're too cowardly to even admit
you're taking the cowardly way out.
You're right.
But I can change.
He could have gotten out.
People are found sometimes.
Even in collapsed...
I think they're
pulling a body out.
The coroner confirms ifs him.
House hired me when
no one else would.
He got me fired.
He gave me the guts
to get fired.
He gave me the courage to quit.
Gregory was...
He was a good son.
He was a trying
boyfriend, but I
never stopped loving him.
He was my husband for real.
I couldn't help but love him.
He was my boss
and my employee.
At both times,
I learned from him.
He made me a better parent,
whether he meant to or not.
He was willing to kill me.
And I'll always be grateful.
He wasn't always easy
to deal with...
but somewhere in there,
he knew how to love.
He was my friend.
The thing you have to remember,
the thing you can't forget,
is that Gregory House
saved lives.
He was a healer,
and in the end...
House was an ass.
He mocked anyone.
Patients, co-workers,
his dwindling friends,
anyone who didn't measure up to
his insane ideals of integrity.
He claimed to be on some
heroic quest for truth.
But the truth is
he was a bitter jerk
who liked making
people miserable.
And he proved that
by dying selfishly,
numbed by narcotics, without
a thought of anyone.
A betrayal of everyone who cared about him.
Phone.
A million times he needed me
and the onetime that I needed...
Oh, come on!
This is a funeral.
Just get it.
This is embarrassing.
I'd sworn I'd turned this off.
This isn't my phone.
Hi.
How...
I got out of the back
of the building.
The body...
Just switched
the dental records.
You're destroying
your entire life.
You can't go back from this.
You'll go to jail for years.
You can never be
a doctor again.
I'm dead, Wilson.
How do you want to spend
your last five months?
When the cancer starts
getting really bad...
Cancer's boring.