Come on!
Yeah!
Hatchet! Hatchet!
Come on, Toros!
Let's make some noise!
Nice to meet the pride
of Trois-Rivières.
I still got your
Wings rookie card.
So what's that worth? Well,
it's a collector's item.
They don't make them
like you anymore.
So you want to go?
Square up. Good luck.
He didn't get a hand on you?
You're gonna be
a force in the show.
Hatchet! Hatchet! Hatchet!
Come on, Toros!
Get a trainer over here!
Capacity crowd is on its
feet, five seconds on the clock.
Ah!
How is it possible for one man to
be blessed with so much skill?
I had one just like this, except
it was Bruins and the Habs.
Where'd you get it?
Birthday present for someone
in pediatric oncology.
Twenty-two-year-old
enforcer with hemoptysis.
He's a hockey player?
No, he's a superhero.
He's coughing up blood because
he probably broke a rib
and punctured a lung while
breaking someone else's rib
and puncturing their lung
in the name of sport.
Nice conclusion, to which the
ER already jumped 18 hours ago.
Short man equals bullied child.
I was average height as a kid.
And never bullied.
Until now.
X-ray ruled out traumatic sequelae,
overt TB and lung cancer.
Sarcoidosis. Nodules could be too
small to show up on an X-ray.
But fighting's
the best part of hockey.
Without it, you've
got the Ice Capades.
Fighting has nothing
to do with hockey.
It's like the cheerleaders
at a basketball game.
Cheerleading's
the best part of basketball.
Without it,
you've got basketball.
He's a duck hunter.
He could have contracted
psittacosis from exposure to fowl.
He had three teeth knocked
out two weeks ago.
Infection could have
led to oral bleeding.
Not without
continuing dental pain.
Then he took
an elbow to the gut,
which caused
an esophageal tear.
Chase, CT the patient,
check for sarcoid.
Adams, sputum cultures and
serologies for psittacosis.
Taub, I'd tell you
why I think your theory
is not just wrong
but ill-conceived,
but it's more fun to prove it by
having you check the stool for blood.
Now while we wait for the
stool fairy, I'm a man down.
So if you want to drop your
pants and hit the ice.
The faster you guys
can do this, the better.
The NHL's been sniffing around,
and being in the hospitals not really
helping my marketability, so...
You have to be pretty
good to get called up.
Yeah, leading the league
in penalty minutes.
And visits to the ER, not
counting the ones you've caused.
Not a hockey fan, I gather?
I am, that's the point. Fighting
cheapens a great sport.
Oh, come on. That's like saying
passing cheapens football.
It's part of the game.
I don't cause injuries.
They're self-inflicted?
No, I prevent them.
Hake the hits, so the
smaller guys don't have to.
I thought you'd
appreciate that.
Neighbor's baby again?
I could hear it
through earplugs,
two pillows,
and three sleeping pills.
Hmm.
What is wrong with you?
I just said, "Hmm."
You're trying to figure out
some deeper significance
to my having a couple
of crappy nights.
Which one of us is analyzing
the word "hmm" here?
Fine. I'm sorry.
Apology accepted.
However, it's not the crying
that's keeping you awake.
The sound of a needy child is
stirring your paternal juices.
The sound of a needy
child at 112 decibels
has stirred my inner murderer.
Don't mess with me.
Explain the stains on your shirt.
You're lactating.
The fact that
you're the only fruit
on your family tree
is getting to you.
It's not a big deal So I'll
probably never be a clad.
It sucks. I'll lose
a little sleep, but...
You're not supposed to feel
bad when you dodge a bullet.
It's like you've
got survivor's guilt.
There are actually things
in this world
that give life
even more meaning
than soap operas
and monster trucks.
And we happen to be missing
out on at least one of them.
You remember the falconer?
Beth?
You dated two falconers?
Yes, Beth.
The night the two
of you split up,
you came around to my place,
wallowing in
self-pity and tequila.
You passed out.
She called that night. Asked
me to give you a message.
She said she was pregnant.
Which, God and Planned
Parenthood willing,
means you are the father
of an 11-year-old.
I told you the next morning.
Hypothetically.
I asked you how you'd feel
if Beth had gotten pregnant,
and you said, and I quote, "It would
be the worst mistake of my life."
And scene.
Two performances Sunday,
dark Mondays?
Just as well.
I want to kill my mother.
My Popo's on her own
and my mother always needs
me to take care of her.
Well, you could
kill Popo instead.
I have to take her shopping, to
her friends, to Atlantic City.
I love her, but every
night, every weekend...
And only if there
was some solution,
some place where
you could live.
That's not there.
My mom would freak. It would be
the ultimate sign of disrespect.
Okay. Then stay.
And maybe you'd consider
not bitching about it?
Not everyone's lucky enough
to have your independence.
Don't worry. When you lose your
family, you'll have ll, too.
He doesn't have sarcoid.
Look at that That's his spleen.
I know, but he's
gotten it supersized.
Deep vein thrombosis, caused by any one
of his many injuries or surgeries.
Leukemia's a better fit.
We have a guy who is punishing
his body on a daily basis.
Don't you think that's a more
likely cause than cancer?
No, because she doesn't
have an agenda.
Well, that was incredibly
unprofessional.
Although, it's
really Taub's fault.
If you're not prepared to
slam her into the board,
she's got no reason
not to go after you.
Might I suggest pulling her
jersey over her head first?
We should get an ultrasound
for DVT and WBC for leukemia.
You think I could have cancer?
More likely it's just a DVT.
This is my agent.
I gotta take this.
Yeah.
Give me some good news, Kenny.
I thought you said "any day".
Okay. All right.
L gotta go...
I called Beth.
I have
an 11-year-old son.
Liver failure could
alter hormone levels,
cause abnormal
breast development.
Alcoholism. We should search
his home and locker room.
Note that the person who
wants to search the home
didn't sleep in one last night.
You have the imprint of a
seatbelt buckle on your cheek.
I got in a fight
with my mother.
She hit you with a seatbelt?
It could be hemochromatosis.
Explains
the liver and the spleen,
but hemoptysis is a stretch.
What about leptospirosis?
That's a good fit.
If you ignore the fact
that he's a pro athlete
who looks like
the Incredible Hulk,
which means he's got to be on
steroids, which is a better fit.
All we really know
for sure is that
it was his evil job
that caused the problems.
Yes, I don't like him. Doesn't
mean my judgment's affected.
Maybe. Let's take a look
at the instant replay.
This is the hit that
precipitated Booby Orr's fight.
Dirty or clean?
- The hit was clean.
- Really?
The guy released the puck at
least a second before the hit.
We have a difference
of opinion. That's all.
Absolutely.
Maybe she's as biased as you.
Or maybe the entire league is.
After review, the league disciplinary
commissioner ruled the hit
illegal and dangerous, and suspended
the player for three games.
Adams and Taub, run
antibody titers for lepto.
Chase and Park, check out the
home, the locker room for booze,
steroids and
Taub's objectivity.
At least you're free.
You gonna get your own place?
If I can find a place
I can afford, so no.
If you want, you can crash at my place.
Got a spare bedroom.
That might be kind of weird.
I live in an apartment,
not a dungeon.
It's just two single
people, opposite sex.
Your bedroom door has
a lock on the inside.
Hey, if you prefer
your car, be my guest.
Scrip for ganciclovir.
If his neighbor has mono,
it could mean he has mono.
If he has mono, explains
his spleen and hemoptysis.
And it's caused by the Epstein-Barr
virus, which explains his liver.
And my moonroof leaks.
Thank you.
Why don't we just assume
that you're not the dad?
Well, either you're the dad
or she cheated on
you with your dad.
Oh!
Sand art.
I used to love this.
He's bitter, not
mentally handicapped.
Who knows what Beth
told him about you'?
At worst, you're a rapist.
At best, you're a rapist.
Maybe she said
I was a dead war hero.
Raised by a lunatic mother
and abandoned by his father.
Oh, I know, squirrel handcuffs.
You think he's
got any of those?
If you really wanted me to do
nothing with this information,
then why did you give it to me?
Because you were
pining for a kid
and you deserved to know
that you already had one.
But your paternal cravings are
more theoretical than applied.
You want vicarious immortality
more than you want
a lifelong burden.
You're assuming he's
gonna be a nightmare.
What if he's a good kid?
He's a kid. Best you can hope
for is he's a nightmare.
House, I'm not naive. I realize that
this thing could go very badly,
but the point is my son wants to
meet me, and I want to meet him.
Popo, I presume.
Hey. I let myself in.
This is...
We've met.
I thought the whole point of
this was to get away from Popo.
My dad's getting a cyst removed
and my mother had to
take him to the clinic.
Don't worry, she'll
be gone in an hour.
I'm not worried because
it's not my issue.
She seems awfully quiet.
You haven't seen her drunk.
Bobby?
I found him crying
in the fetal position.
It's not a new symptom.
He's crying because
his liver failure
threw his hormones
out of whack.
Aside from the crying, he's
actually recovering nicely.
Aside from the guy
in the book depository,
the Kennedys had
a lovely trip to Dallas.
Repetitive blows to the head
can cause chronic
traumatic encephalopathy,
the symptoms of which are
aggressive behavior and depression.
So your theory is that
his aggressive behavior
caused his aggressive behavior?
He's not depressed,
he's just bummed,
because he knows
he's a talentless moron
who's only one lost fight
away from being a barista.
I understand that can get
to a guy after a while.
If he quits being an enforcer,
it could save his life.
You don't want
to save his life.
You want to kill his career.
I moved into Chase's apartment.
He knows. He was staring
at our matching cups.
I told you
we should have split up.
We're not having sex.
With each other.
Yet.
Yes.
Yes?
I just mean no one knows the future
right now, so we don't really know...
The only conclusive test
for CTE is post-mortem.
But an MRI of his brain could
reveal white matter disintegrity,
which is the effect of CTE.
Why'? Are you trying
to sleep with her?
'Cause a simpler technique
is just to ask.
I was doing something nice. No.
That doesn't fit.
He's only had three
concussions since he was 10.
It's not enough to cause CTE.
Three reported concussions.
These guys are taught in high
school how to dupe the tests.
Guilt?
This is really insulting.
It's not guilt.
Park is a friend.
So it's guilt.
Chase convinced you to leave Mommy
and now he feels responsible.
No MRI.
Do a psych eval, if he doesn't start
weeping again, send him home.
Dr. Wilson?
Duncan?
James.
Nice to meet you.
It's nice to meet you.
Um...
How are you doing?
Good.
I got you this.
Oh.
Thank you.
Go ahead.
Okay.
It's got three
games built-in,
but you can download
more from the website.
I know.
You already have one.
I can always use a backup.
Hi. Can I start you
with something to drink?
Just water, please.
You got a GameDeck?
Way to go, Dad.
According to your psych eval,
the only thing happier
than you is Disneyland.
I'm sorry you had to see
me like that last night.
I'm just upset about being in the
hospital, I'm on some weird meds.
But they must be working, because
I'm feeling a lot better now.
Depression could be the symptom
of a serious illness, CTE.
Yeah. My aunt sends me every
article she can find on it.
Then you know
it could kill you.
In the long run,
like a lot of things.
You might be right.
And an MRI could confirm that.
I have enough evidence of head
trauma in my file already, so...
My mom said you had trouble maintaining
relationships with normal people.
She also said
you were a nice guy.
I always figured she was lying
'cause she didn't want me
to hate my deadbeat dad.
I didn't know.
I know, now.
You're a bright kid.
Thanks to you.
Thanks to my mom,
I'm also a big,
soft-hearted wuss.
I think you may have gotten
that from both of us.
I got to go, but it was
really nice meeting you.
It was nice
meeting you, Duncan.
You want to hang out again?
Absolutely.
Tonight?
Well, I... There's...
That would be great.
Okay. I'll text you.
Thank you. How'd you
talk him into it?
He agreed once I
promised him anonymity.
Mr. and Mrs. Doe liked the
name John, apparently.
Unfortunately, we just wasted his
time and proved House right.
Nothing?
What about that?
That's an artifact.
That's a density.
I know you think
I'm convincing myself,
but this brain has
been hammered for years,
meaning evidence may be
subtle, but it's there.
Meaning you
see what you want to see.
Unless, of course, Chase is an
idiot and I do have brain damage.
Patient's stroking out.
Chase.
Can you get me out of”.
Oh...
Hello?
The good news is ifs
isolated ophthalmoplegia,
which means he
didn't have a stroke.
Bad news is Taub was right.
You're still sick.
I said "right",
not "competent".
Bursts your CTE bubble. You're
gonna need a whole new theory
to keep Uncle Jesse and his
Olsen Twins on the bench.
Can we discuss my
incompetence somewhere else?
Dr. House. Could I talk
to you for a minute?
Could be neurosyphilis.
He's only 22.
And he's been on the
road since he was 14.
So he was trash even
before he was trash?
Are you curious
about what he wanted?
I assume he wanted me
off the case,
and you told him I was hit
in the head as a child,
and your mother made you
promise to take care of me.
He was doing
what he always does.
Sticking up for the little guy.
He told me to apologize to you,
or he would
excrete down my throat.
I'm paraphrasing.
So if he should ask,
I was a gentleman,
or I will excrete
down your throat.
Microscopic polyangiitis fits.
We should start
plasmapheresis immediately.
We need to run an ANCA
panel to confirm first.
Putting him on plasmapheresis
could make him bleed out.
MPA can progress quickly.
We may not have time before
it reaches his lungs.
I think you're right, thus
confirming my objectivity.
Start the treatment.
Miserable yet?
He's polite, well-adjusted,
and a straight-A student.
Which means
he doesn't need you.
So why don't you get out
while the butterfly effect
is still in the cocoon stage.
I'm making him dinner.
You don't make
an 11-year-old dinner.
You give him ajar
of peanut butter.
It'll be fine.
I could give this kid
a quinoa salad
and he would eat it
just to be nice.
'Cause he's a gutless
placater, just like his dad.
He's nice.
This is a terrible idea.
Because we like each other?
Yes. Because of the statement,
"We like each other."
You've known him 25 minutes.
All you know about him is that
he'd lie about a quinoa salad,
whatever the hell that is.
You're jealous
of an 11-year-old
because you are
an 11-year-old.
So tell me about yourself.
I mean you're smart, you're
nice, but what else?
I don't know.
I'm a kid.
Right.
What are you looking for?
Nothing.
You want peanut butter?
Do you have prosciutto?
You like prosciutto?
I'm weird.
No! No, I like it, too.
I've got some in the fridge.
How about goat cheese?
I love goat cheese.
I think that was the
best pizza I ever had.
It was the hint of Dijon.
Do you have any aunts or
uncles or grandparents?
My mom got into some stupid
fight with my grandfather.
They all kind of cut us off.
Hmm.
Are you talking
to your parents?
Yes, and they're going to be very
surprised and excited to meet you.
That's awesome.
You have
arrived at your destination,
Well...
Thanks for the pizza.
Sure. Sure. I mean, it was
great to spend time with you.
I love you, Dad.
It can't be easy
doing what you do.
I mean, do you love it?
Is it fun?
I had my own plastic surgery
practice, making lots of money.
But I wasn't happy. It wasn't
what I went to med school for.
Every winter, my dad would flood
the backyard and make a rink.
I was Lemieux, my little
brother was Gretzky.
I was good. I won the NDHA scoring
title three years in a row.
I kept getting bigger
and stronger and better.
Until I didn't.
My Juniors coach told me that if
I wanted to stay on the team,
that I'd have to use my size.
Every game, I got
less and less ice time,
until it was all fighting
and no hockey.
There's something
going on with my arms.
I can't feel them! Doctor,
I can't feel my arms.
Patient's arms
are now paralyzed.
ANCA panel was negative.
It's not MPA.
Lyme disease
could cause paralysis,
if he was hunting,
he'd be exposed to ticks.
No target rash
or cardiac involvement.
Roomies with benefits
keeping you up?
Cribbage. I played
with Park's Popo.
Is that two separate events?
Her grandmother. ALS could
explain the symptoms.
Sensory involvement
rules out ALS.
Okay, now this is interesting.
We'll get back to the
patient in a second.
Your issue is
the same as Wilson's.
Except you're haunted by the
pitter-patter of tiny skanks.
You don't feel guilty about getting
Park thrown out of her home.
You feel guilty about all the
women that you've screwed over.
My mother needs 1,000
bucks for snow tires.
Park's a friend, Popo's fun.
Paralysis has gone
from his face to his arms,
meaning it's descending, which
is the hallmark of botulism.
So it was something he ate.
How innocuous.
You've overcome your
bias by reversing it.
The only problem is that being
in love with the patient
is just as judgmental
as being in hate.
We didn't find
any contaminated...
No contaminated food,
I'm not an idiot.
But what if it's not from
ingesting, but from injecting?
He was treated for intractable muscle
spasms by the team's trainers.
Sometimes they use Botox.
We need to start the antitoxin.
The antitoxin could
cause anaphylaxis.
We need to test first
to confirm.
As if to prove my point.
Last time you said there
wasn't enough time to test
prior to a more
dangerous treatment.
It's a different situation, a different
symptom, a different diagnosis.
Different emotion.
Give him the antitoxin.
Anything?
No adverse effects.
Chase let me move in with him
to getaway from my grandmother,
then he practically let my grandmother
move in with the both of us.
He's being way more than nice.
Then which answer is it?
Chase feels guilty for
pushing you to move out'?
He didn't push me.
- Guilt about skanks?
- He loves skanks.
It's not the other option.
There are people that like me,
people who even
want to sleep with me.
Some of them are
even good looking.
That good looking?
Did you see that?
You're feeling something?
Yeah.
I could give you crap for
making me wait 11 years,
but instead I'm gonna thank you
for not making me
wait another 11.
Every little girl wants a pony
until they have
to clean up after it.
You think I'm gonna quit on this?
On an 11-year-old?
The only relationship you haven't
quit on has been with me.
Hmm. A needy,
truculent narcissist.
I think it's been the perfect
training for parenthood.
That's not even close.
This is the rest of your life.
If you screw this up,
you don't get to run away.
You get to ruin
both your lives.
This is a bigger responsibility
than any you've ever taken
on, and screwed up.
I know.
That's why I'm so
excited about it.
You're really happier doing this
than looking at boobs all day'?
Luckily, I get patients like
you every now and again
who let me
re-experience the joy.
You know the best
part of my day
is when I'm sitting
in that penalty box
after I beat someone up.
It's the only time
I know I'm safe.
Think Lemieux
ever felt that way?
I'm not going back.
To hockey?
To enforcing.
Whatever that costs.
Good for you.
Oh!
First goal for
the Pocket Rocket.
Bobby?
We need a team in here!
He's completely paralyzed and he
tested negative for botulism.
I am now accepting long shots.
Polio?
Some kids were
never vaccinated.
Unless they played sports all their
lives and had two physicals a year.
How about MLD?
TAUB; That's a bad fit.
I say that not because there's
no treatment for MLD,
but because ifs a bad fit.
His cognitive abilities
are unaffected.
Prion disease could explain the
waxing and waning symptoms.
The test for prions
is a brain biopsy.
And given his history, there's
got to be brain swelling.
We can't risk drilling
into his skull.
Pretty sure we can.
We also could keep talking until we can
find an answer we all can agree on.
What, all of us? Those of us who
love him, those who hate him?
Those who don't give
a crap about him or you?
Or I could just discuss it
on my own with Foreman.
He's not your friend.
I get it' he's a patient.
I'm not... He never
had your back.
He didn't insist that
I apologize to you.
He asked me to take
you off the case.
Biopsy his brain.
Hey, Dad.
He?'
Sorry I'm late. Got in a fight
with my mom She is such a tool.
I'm sure she means well.
She wants to open a reserve in Costa
Rica for rescued birds of prey.
But how serious is she?
From my recollection, she used
to talk about doing a lot.
Yeah, but she bought
plane tickets for Monday.
Well, Costa Rica is beautiful.
And the schools are
supposed to be great.
Oh! I'm not going. It's her
stupid dream, not mine.
Then what will you do?
Uh...
I thought maybe
I could stay with you?
Your place is only three
miles away from my school.
I can bus it every day.
And I do my own laundry.
I keep my room tidy.
Duncan, this...
This is very sudden.
I know. I'm sorry.
Please don't send me
to the jungle.
If it's okay with your
mother, it's okay with me.
Take me off the case.
I've obviously completely
lost my objectivity.
I'm not helping.
I'm not even neutral.
Agreed.
So why shouldn't
I take you off all my cases?
Because you were right.
I hate bullies.
You work for me.
You're not a bully.
Pretty sure I am, dickwad.
I've known a lot of bullies, people
who didn't like me because I'm short,
people who didn't like me
because I'm Jewish.
Yeah, I get it, there's a long
list of reasons not to like you.
You relentlessly mock, but it's
not for self-aggrandizement,
it's because ideas are
bigger than feelings.
At least that's what
I choose to believe.
I also thought you had the side
effect of desensitizing me.
You little hebe.
Here are some ideas for you.
You screwed up. You kept on screwing up.
Everything you said is true.
Except it doesn't mean
you walk away.
You just learn
to trust nothing.
Everything you think you feel,
everything you think you know,
you question every call,
play through every whistle.
I just had a light bulb.
Maybe.
You can trust light bulbs.
Stop.
It's not prions.
Epstein-Barr gave him mono, it also
gave him Miller Fisher syndrome.
The plasmapheresis
played through the whistle.
We gave it to him for MPA, but when
he got worse, we took him off.
When he got better, we thought
it was the antitoxin,
but it was actually the
plasmapheresis still working.
We had the right treatment,
just the wrong diagnosis.
It was my metaphor
that solved the case.
Put him back on plasmapheresis.
He'll be fine.
Nice save.
Didn't quite make up for being
a sieve the rest of the game.
Ex-girlfriend's
baby again?
His mother is moving
to Costa Rica,
he asked if he could
move in with me...
and I said yes.
Well, it's only
six or seven years.
Unless he can't
get into college,
in which case it's more a
matter of your life expectancy.
I said yes, knowing I'm not
remotely ready for that,
knowing he's not ready to be
separated from his mother.
This isn't the act of
a mature, rational adult.
I can't do this, House.
You were right.
I have an idea that can make
this entire problem go away.
Yes, I really want to hear your
clever late-term abortion joke.
You were right about everything.
This is life.
It's real.
It doesn't just go away.
None of that is true.
He?'
Duncan.
Actually, it's Wendel, one "L".
If you're gonna get pissy,
remember, it was House's idea.
You're an actor?
Five commercials, and a
recurring on Days of our Lives.
You were regretting not having
kids, so I gave you one.
Thereby rendering you regret-free.
It's a priceless gift.
Get out.
Well, it's not priceless.
He charges SAG minimum...
Get out!
Chillax, Dad.
Can you do an Australian accent?
I just got the call.
Three-year deal,
2.1 million.
What about the flooded backyard
and pretending to be Lemieux'?
That's why I took it.
After all I did to get here,
half a dream is
better than nothing.
Maybe my new coach will see
what my Juniors coach didn't.
That'd be nice.
I'm not sleeping with you.
That's a shame.
This is about Popo.
She's not sleeping
with me either, right?
You were jealous
of me, my family.
Maybe you've got too much
and I've got too little.
I might sleep
with you after all.
The woman that I called,
that was really Beth?
Found her on Facebook.
How much did she charge?
Nothing. She's still
pissed at you.
Can you pass the bacon?
I thought you liked prosciutto.
Nobody likes prosciutto.