Pressure.
I need pressure.
Give me sutures...
We need an Epi.
Alert trauma.
Let the record show
that we are officially
convening
a disciplinary hearing
regarding the events on February
3rd, 2012, in patient room 209.
Dr. House, this recording will
be transcribed and published
along with all supporting
documentation and rulings.
Do you have any questions
before we get started?
Yeah.
Who the hell are you?
I'm Walter Cofield. Chief of
Neurology, Mercy Hospital.
I'll be deciding
your fate today.
Cofield.
You were the Residency Director at
Hopkins before you moved to Mercy.
Which means it's safe to assume
that you trained Foreman.
Which means it's also safe to
assume that he trusts you.
This hearing isn't
about me, Dr. House.
I know you'd like
to make it about me
because then it
wouldn't be about you.
It's interesting that he picked the
old mentor to judge the new one.
Interesting' but not relevant.
The facts of this case,
on the other hand... The
facts are in the file.
If you have trouble reading my
handwriting, give me a call.
I'm going back to work.
If I just consider the file, the
facts aren't in your favor.
The facts say
you should be suspended.
Which, from what I understand,
would mean a revocation
of your parole.
The patient was a 32-year-old
high school chemistry teacher.
He collapsed while out jogging.
He was paralyzed in
all four extremities
despite the fact
that the scans...
show no sign of stroke
or structural lesions.
Did you put out
an APB for a car
with a man-shaped
dent in the grill?
No broken bones,
no signs of trauma.
Transverse myelitis.
Boring.
No enhancement on the MRI.
I just don't know what to do.
Please, you have to
help me solve this thing.
A little poetic license.
What are you doing?
Taking my vic-amins.
Those are Vicodin?
Did you have surgery recently?
About a decade ago.
My leg is no good
at judging time.
Were you taking Vicodin
during this case?
Uh...
Yes.
And during about nine
years' previous cases.
My process is proven.
Good things usually happen.
Bad things sometimes happen.
And when bad things happen, we
should figure out what went wrong
so we can learn from it
and correct it.
So we can assign blame.
Instead of recognizing that
bad things sometimes happen.
It was nobody's fault.
And then what happened?
Those who can, do.
Those who can't, teach.
Those who can't teach,
teach gym.
And those who can't move their arms
or legs teach us to laugh at others.
House actually presented
the case in that way?
Or are you just trying
to make him look bad?
Why would I be trying
Could be your
not-so-subtle way
of implying
this was House's fault.
Given what's happened,
it's understandable
that your opinion would
color your testimony.
But I just want to know
what you said, what you did
and what you were
thinking at the time.
I don't think it was his fault.
Just tell me
your initial theory.
I thought the patient
had a liver problem.
Hepatic encephalopathy
explained why he passed out,
why he couldn't move his limbs.
But that's not the idea
House went with?
He thought Taub's idea
was stupid.
And what about your idea?
He thought that
was stupid, too.
No. I meant,
what was it?
Oh. I thought the patient had
normal pressure hydrocephalus.
And why did House think
that was stupid?
Oh, come on.
Unless you're an idiot, you know
why I thought Park was an idiot.
The patient had low opening
pressure on his LP.
That's what I said.
No, you idiot.
The patient had low opening
pressure on his LP.
Try unsquinting your eyes and
reading the labs next time.
Are you intentionally trying
to get me to dislike you?
That wasn't me.
The chair squeaked.
You're testifying
for the record
that you actually used the
phrasing, "unsquint your eyes"?
This is not the place to
exorcise your guilt,
I just want to know exactly...
I actually used the phrasing
"unsquint your eyes."
He's hypokalemic,
could indicate a problem with
his heart, which would...
EKG was normal.
But, Chase,
a doctor who
actually takes the time
to read the lab reports,
has a point.
The guy's potassium is off.
Could be thyrotoxic paralysis.
Stan him on steroids, PTU,
and beta blockers.
Mmm-hmm.
And how did these orange smudges
get on the patient file?
Seriously?
That's your follow up?
I eat a lot of Cheetos,
I forget to wash my hands.
Is my snacking really
relevant to this case?
Might be, if these were
actually Cheetos stains.
What are they?
Seriously, House?
You're blaming me?
You used Adams' shampoo.
I didn't do ii.
It was a harmless prank.
My team is made up of
Type A personalities.
They need somebody to break the
tension every once in a while.
So this was a team
building exercise?
Is that what he called it?
It's what he implied.
House prefers
chaos over cohesion.
He believes that disagreement and
mistrust lead to better ideas.
He's not wrong.
As opposed to being right?
So you treated with steroids.
And then what happened?
They worked.
Our patient woke up.
Bill?
Can you hear me?
Yeah.
I'm thirsty.
That's normal. You've been
in a coma for several hours.
Can you tell me your name?
Bill. Bill Koppelman.
Can you tell me
what happened to me?
We're treating you for
an overactive thyroid.
We think that's why you
passed out and couldn't move.
Can you wiggle
your fingers for me?
Is he going to be okay?
Excuse me, but only family
members are allowed.
It's okay.
They're my students.
Everyone back at school
is so worried about you.
Is he sick because
of the explosion?
What explosion?
A chemistry demonstration he was
doing for his class went wrong.
Then why was it not already
in the patient history'?
Because the patient
was unconscious.
But I'm assuming Dr. House
spoke to the wife.
The wife didn't know
about the explosion.
And I was the one
who questioned her.
So if there was an
oversight, it was mine.
Does Dr. House not attach
importance to patient histories?
No. He thinks
they're crucial.
He just doesn't think being in the
same room as the patient is crucial.
House thinks avoiding patients
allows him to stay as
objective as possible.
He's not wrong.
That sounds like a very diplomatic
way of saying he's lazy.
That's also true.
Either way, I'm covered.
If you want an accurate
patient history,
don't ever talk to the patient.
Everybody lies.
Except me.
To you.
Would never do that.
Okay. Say you're right.
If you had actually been in the
room questioning the patient,
you could read body language,
you could ask
follow up questions,
and warn him of the
cost of lying to you.
Don't forget thumbscrews.
Can you dispute the possibility
that had you visited the patient
sooner, maybe talked to the wife,
been directed to
one of the students,
that this case might have
ended very differently?
It wasn't exactly an explosion.
It was a controlled reaction
that went a little haywire.
It was, too, an explosion.
Simon Harris filmed the whole
thing on his camera phone
and posted it on YouTube.
It got, like,
over 75,000 hits already.
Looks like you've
gone viral, hon.
He had a loss of consciousness,
temporary paralysis,
but when I was told that the
patient coughed up blood,
things really started
to get interesting.
Your patient was doubled over
in pain and coughing up blood.
And you found that interesting?
Why, is that bad?
It's interesting.
I do this demonstration
every year.
But I usually have a student
aide help me set it up.
Apparently this year he added
extra hydrofluoric acid,
which is why it exploded.
The student aide was just
trying to make a viral video,
not hurt anyone.
Ended up doing both.
So we figured the patient
inhaled the extra large dose
of hydrofluoric acid, and...
burned his lungs, which
is why he coughed up blood.
If only burnt lungs explained
the passing out and paralysis.
The explosion does.
Check out the video again.
He smacked his head
against the wall.
If that caused swelling
in his brainstem
that would have led to the eventual
loss of consciousness and paralysis.
So we discussed it
a little longer
and House decided to
treat with heparin.
I wouldn't mind
a couple more details.
It was aerosolized heparin.
You skipped over
the actual DDX,
and now you're
averting your eyes.
I'm growing more and more
curious by the moment.
He smacked his head
against the wall.
If that caused swelling
in his brainstem
that would have led to the eventual
loss of consciousness and paralysis.
Nobody move.
Ugh!
He had on a what?
Gas mask.
The stink bomb was Chase's.
He was getting revenge
for the orange hair
and rigged it
in House's office.
But House found it.
Mmm-hmm.
You can leave when
I have an answer.
Might help if
we knew the question.
How do we treat chemical
burns inside the lungs?
Maybe we can use a bronchoalveolar
lavage to wash them outwith water.
Sorry, my fault,
I should have clarified.
How do we treat chemical
burns inside the lungs
without killing the patient?
Silver sulfadiazine works
well on chemical burns.
Burn cream would drown
him faster than water.
Well?
Aerosolized heparin.
Me like?
But that's only experimental,
it's never actually
been used before.
Not true.
It's been used in sheep.
Uh-huh.
The guy was
going downhill fast.
We needed a treatment
that was a slope changer.
So you busted out the
sulphur dioxide stink bomb?
It was a team
building exercise.
No, it was manipulation.
You were pressuring your team into
coming up with unsafe medical ideas
just to get out of that room.
You say pressure,
I say inspire.
The usual, safe ideas were not going to work.
Aerosolized heparin might.
And everyone else just
went along with this?
No. I told House I thought
it was a mistake.
And those were
your exact words?
I think I might
have said "insane."
You thought it was insane
and yet you let it happen.
No, I...
If you disagree with Dr. House
on patient safety, Doctor,
it is your duty to speak up.
Otherwise,
you're equally lo blame.
I did speak up.
I tried.
And you failed.
And that's why I went
to Dr. Foreman.
The heparin could
cause the patient
to bleed into his lungs
even faster.
It is crazy.
But House doesn't do crazy
just for crazy's sake.
If he thinks this is the only
way to help the patient...
You did not tell me
you were involved in this case
when you asked me to do this.
I wasn't.
The heparin decision didn't have
anything to do with the outcome.
If signing off on everything
House does is a pattern,
it affects
the way House behaves,
it affects the way House's team
reacts to the way House behaves.
House
is brilliant.
I give him the benefit of
the doubt most of the time,
because I've seen
what he can do.
Getting House out of prison
is the biggest decision you've
made as Dean of Medicine, right?
And if he's suspended as a
result of this hearing,
he violates his parole
and he goes back.
And that probably leaves you
as former Dean of Medicine.
I suppose so.
You didn't choose me
to oversee this
because you thought
I could be objective,
you chose me because you
thought I'd have your back.
And I'd think twice about making a
decision that would get you fired.
Eric,
I'm sorry.
But if your
get-House-out-of-jail-free
experiment blows up
in your face,
it's not my job to
get you out of it.
After you'd
administered the heparin,
I see there was a discharge
order in the chart.
Yet the patient never left.
House ordered
a therapeutic bath first,
to wash off any residual
chemicals from the blast
but we wound up
finding something.
You have a bit of a rash.
Can you raise both your arms?
We just need to
see how far it goes.
You told me
I was gonna be okay.
And now there's still
something wrong with me.
It probably doesn't mean anything,
but we want to make sure.
Of course you do.
I gotta get out
of here. Okay?
Just relax.
Please just let me
get out of here.
It'll just take a minute.
We need to get a good
look at the rash.
The rash? That was nothing. Just some
irritation from lying in bed all day.
The problem was
the patient's brain.
He freaked out.
I gotta get out of here.
I gotta get out of here! Easy.
"Freak out" is a little strong.
In my opinion at the time, it was the
rash that was going to kill him.
Invasive strep.
Reasonable theory,
supported by the evidence.
The evidence pointed
to psychosis.
We caused it by giving him
steroids when he first came in.
What'd you think?
I thought Park and Adams
were both right.
But that their conclusions
were both wrong.
The neuro symptoms and the rash
were both signs of
an underlying disease.
Together with the lung,
it added up to Wegener's.
How does Dr. House handle it
when three smart doctors
come up with three different,
but equally valid ideas?
I run a diagnostic trial.
Start the patient
on high dose steroids.
Multiple birds, single stone.
If Taub is right, then he
can walk out of here cured.
If Adams is right, he will spike
a fever, get hypotensive,
we can treat it and he can
walk out of here cured.
If Park is right and he goes
all Cuckoo's Nest on us,
we can cross
"brain" off the list...
diagnose him, and he can
walk out of here cured.
Are you trying to
make this easy for me?
By your own admission, if you
give the patient steroids,
two of the three outcomes
could make him worse.
What's making the patient worse
was not having a diagnosis.
This was the fastest way
to get it.
It was the perfect
diagnostic moment.
In light of what happened,
do you still think it was the
perfect diagnostic moment?
Yes.
My theory accounted for
all the medical outcomes.
It did not account for the
disobedience of my own team.
What are you doing?
I think you're right
about the strep.
Can't hurt to biopsy the
rash while we're waiting.
Thanks.
At the time, it seemed
like a good idea.
I know this is hard.
But please tell me
exactly what happened next.
Draw up a little anesthetic.
Two cc's Lidocaine.
Get away from me!
Bill, you're in a hospital.
Calm down!
Code Grey!
So your position is that your
team's disobedience caused this?
That's not what I said.
You said you didn't
anticipate their defiance.
You implied that all would
have been fine otherwise.
So who do you blame?
Dr. Adams or Dr. Chase?
Or both?
I don't blame either one.
So who do you blame,
Dr. House?
Code Grey!
Get Haloperidol.
Got ii.
Oh, my God, Chase!
Prep the OR! Get a gurney.
Start an IV!
Come on.
Bleeder's gotta be in here.
Got it!
Which artery?
It's his heart.
Fortunately, only the knife tip
reached the cardiac muscle.
Made a laceration
in the left ventricle
about the size of
the tip of my index finger.
At that moment,
he could only stay alive
as long as my finger
plugged the hole.
Hmm.
It could've been me
on the floor.
It should have been me.
It was my theory.
I held the needle in front of the
patient that set off his paranoia.
If you're looking
for someone to blame,
blame me.
Please continue.
Getting some ectopy.
Coming through! CHI:
Good carotid pulse.
- Regular?
- No.
Got a PVC.
Gotta move it, people.
My diagnostic test worked.
It proved that the patient had
a steroid induced psychosis.
That's what you took away
from this situation?
The brain was not a symptom
of an underlying disease.
Your colleague was stabbed.
Are you telling me
you didn't care'?
How bad is it?
Bad.
Patch.
Ready.
I can't take my finger out
he'll bleed.
I don't think he can take it.
Oxygenation's 100 percent.
He's as ready as he's gonna be.
We gotta go for it.
On my count.
One, two,
three.
Suture.
Got it.
BP is stable.
Patch is holding.
What was his heart rate?
He doesn't have one.
He's on bypass.
Not Chase, the patient.
You're DDX'ing?
Park, come with me.
Taub's got this.
My friend is here because
you didn't listen to me.
I did listen to you.
Chase didn't listen to me.
At this point, being here
makes you feel better,
you're not helping
Chase or our patient.
Fine.
So he just walked out?
There really was
nothing for him to do.
It speaks to
a certain callousness
on Dr. House's part
don't you think?
Who cares if House was callous?
Are you going to
punish callousness?
But you agree that empathy is a
useful quality for doctors'?
House is not the problem.
Your friend got stabbed.
He may die from those wounds.
If you had been in that room,
maybe that could have been you.
I wouldn't have
been in the room.
Implicitly, you just said
that Chase was at fault.
We all knew a psychotic episode
was one of the three
possible outcomes.
And Chase brought
a scalpel in there.
He endangered Dr. Adams,
he endangered himself,
and he endangered the patient.
Thank you.
Lungs, rash, and now
excessive RR variability.
Go.
It's a hospital. There are lots of
doctors that can take care of him.
And your thinking is
that only you guys
are qualified to sit in
this room, doing nothing?
If you're motivated by caring,
just bear in mind he's a
dedicated chemistry teacher
with a pretty wife and adoring
students and a baby on the way.
She's not pregnant.
Would it make a difference?
Because I could knock her up.
Autonomic dysregulation...
Shut up.
Can you guys keep it down?
You made it, bud.
You're in the PACU.
You've been in surgery. The
anesthesia's just wearing off.
Did I have an epidural?
No.
Because I can't feel my legs.
Dr. Chase?
Robert?
Yeah.
I'm Walter Cofield.
I'm a neurologist over at...
I know who you are.
Good.
You think you're up for answering
a couple of questions?
Well, it's not like I can
get up and run away.
Wasn't my best joke.
I'm smiling because
for the last 12 hours
I've been picturing you
with orange hair.
I dyed it back.
Were you angry
with Dr. House?
It was a prank,
it wasn't uncommon.
So I've heard.
That doesn't mean
you couldn't get angry.
Might actually contribute
to that reaction.
Can I ask why that matters?
Are you trying to prove
that I was distracted,
that my judgment
was compromised?
Who do you think was at fault
for what happened
to you, Dr. Chase?
Again, why does it matter?
You're a smart doctor.
You know what happened here
better than anyone
and you've worked with
Dr. House longer than anyone.
And I suspect that you've spent
every minute since
this has happened
trying to answer
that very question.
I don't think it
was anyone's fault.
I was angry
but I wasn't distracted.
And I think if there's any
chance I'm gonna walk again
it's because
Dr. House is a genius.
What about warmth? Can you
feel the sheets on your skin?
I just said
I don't feel anything.
Objectivity, House.
What about
posttraumatic syringomyelia?
A syrinx formed in
the subarachnoid space,
blocking the flow of
cerebrospinal fluid.
That'd mean
the damage was permanent.
No.
Forget the nerves.
House, if ifs total
paralysis he must have...
Not necessarily.
Think arteries.
Blood flow to his spinal
column is cut off.
It's a clot in
the radicular artery.
That could be fixable.
Prep a room for an embolectomy
and let's get
that thing out of there
before it does any more damage.
And if it's not a clot?
Then you can ask Foreman if hospital
insurance covers ramp-vans.
You're through the aorta.
There.
Sensory level is at L5, it
must be the descending branch.
Can I see the monitor?
Stop there.
Shoot the dye.
There it is. TAUB:
Don't get too excited.
We still gotta get it out, still
could have done permanent damage.
Patient does not have
autonomic dysregulation.
There's blood in his urine bag.
Kidneys are failing.
House, not now.
Gotta be now.
Foreman's transferring our
guy to Princeton General
as soon as
there's a bed available.
Says the doctors here can no longer
be objective since the stabbing.
In the middle of a procedure that
could basically save your life,
House is actually trying
to drag people away?
How do you work
with a guy like that?
He wasn't trying to
pull anybody away.
Everyone had already refused
to work on that case.
He knew the answer.
He wanted to check on me.
But he needed an excuse.
Otherwise he could
be accused of caring.
So your testimony is that
Dr. House's
complete lack of concern
is evidence of
his deep concern?
Did you just do that?
What?
Wiggle your toes.
Do you feel that?
Congratulations.
It was the clot.
Short occlusion time
of the artery,
when the swelling goes down,
you should gain back at
least some of the function.
One more thing. Sorry.
You knew that your patient was
at risk for a psychotic break
when you brought a scalpel
within his reach.
Why did you ignore that risk?
I thought I was right
about the rash.
I would do it again.
I thought so.
That's it?
"I thought so"?
What the hell does that mean?
You brazenly defied your boss.
Now that happened
either because Dr. House
has established that
that's okay in his world.
Or his prank war
distracted you.
Or House makes medicine a game
and you just wanted
to beat him.
Whatever the reason,
it boils down to the fact
that you may never walk again
because House created an atmosphere
that promotes recklessness.
This will be our last
round of questions.
I've spoken
with Dr. Chase.
You know he regained movement?
No.
Are you really this indifferent
to the fact that
Dr. Chase is hurt?
Are we going off the record
because this is irrelevant
or are you going to hit me?
Why don't you go tell
the guy you're sorry...
I didn't do anything wrong.
It's not an admission of guilt.
He's your friend
and he's not well.
He's a co-worker.
Co-worker whom you've known for
almost 10 years who nearly died.
And who's still scared
he may not walk.
Are you going to have me
fired for bad manners?
I'm just trying
to understand you.
Why a man in your position,
with your abilities,
is incapable of shaking the
impulse to act like an ass.
Could we go back on the record
and get this over with?
Put the Vicodin away,
Dr. House.
My leg hurts.
Is that supposed to be funny?
Two explosions.
We're not done here.
Hey! Hold on!
Close it up.
Take him out of there.
Dr. Foreman said
you'd try this.
Said to tell you he's
no longer your patient.
Hey!
Wait.
I have to get to my car.
I want to be...
Your husband has a tumor
in his lymph nodes.
You've been wrong every time.
Not this time.
The explosion in the classroom
caused the cancer cells
to break open.
It's called
tumor Iysis syndrome.
His body was flooded with an excess
of phosphates, potassium, acids,
all kinds of cancerous junk.
That explains the paralysis, the
bleeding, the heart and kidney issues.
Everything.
What about the psychotic break?
Turns out we caused that
This is treatable.
Okay?
You have to tell the new doctors
he needs total body radiation
and plasmapheresis.
Move your cane, please.
Where's Cofield?
He said you walked out.
I'm walking back.
I'm not done testifying.
Apparently you were. Said he'd
have his decision tomorrow.
This case is a fiasco.
I didn't sleep last night.
Dr. House is
obviously brilliant.
Well, I think
we've heard enough.
But Dr. House is
also a fiasco.
If I were to exonerate him,
condone his completely reckless,
immature, almost misanthropic behavior,
I would essentially
be sending a message
to all the other doctors
in this hospital
that it's okay to act that way, and...
Sorry.
- We're in the middle of something.
- I know.
I came to speak
with Dr. House,
and when they told me
he was in here
I thought
I should say something.
I mean,
he wasn't the nicest
doctor I've ever met.
Well, I think
we've heard enough.
But he was right.
They found the tumor.
They are removing it, and they
are starting plasmapheresis.
They expect a full recovery.
He saved my husbands life.
Well, I guess that's it.
Thanks again.
As I was saying,
Dr. House's process is
dangerous and inappropriate.
But he is effective.
I've decided that I would be
doing this hospital a disservice
if I did anything to
change that process.
Congratulations,
Dr. House.
This unfortunate stabbing incident
is officially nobody's fault.
Coward.
Excuse me?
You've got like
20 pages of notes there.
You were expecting to bore us
for at least half an hour.
You've got
my parole form in here.
You were going to
send me back to prison.
House, stop.
Good things usually happen,
bad things sometimes happen.
The fact that
that would-be widow
came in just in time to sob all
over your soft, mushy heart,
and the fact that her
husband is going to live,
does not change whether or
not I did the right thing.
How'd you get the firing
wire into the Vicodin bottle
without me noticing?
Why'd I even have to?
What was the point
of the orange hair?
Your hair smelled like Adams'.
Since there's no way you're
doing her without me knowing,
it means you were
just doing her shampoo.
Which means you were out late
drinking with some new girl
or because there is
no new girl.
You were trying to make up time
by showering at the hospital,
but you were too lazy
to buy your own shampoo.
So I found a way to let
you know to not be late.
You couldn't just ask me
to stop being late?
What fun would that be?
None of this is fun, House.
They decided that
your being stabbed
was nobody's fault.
They're wrong.
I'm sorry.
Anything else?
I'm kind of busy.
No. That was it.
I've got it.