You have to lift up
the sign so he can see it.
Evan.
Hey, buddy.
Aren't you excited
to see Uncle Brant?
No.
No?
I think you are.
I think something else
is making you upset.
You know I'm leaving soon.
And it's okay to be
upset about that.
But, hey, do you
remember what I told you
when we were watching
wrestling on Saturday night?
Yeah.
That you and Uncle Brant
are like the Reaper Brothers.
That's right.
And Uncle Brant has been
in the ring a whole year.
Now it's time
for Daddy to tag in.
And while I'm away, I need
you in your uncle's corner,
making sure he keeps
you and your mom safe.
Can you help me with that?
Good.
Now let's get ready
with that sign.
Now.
Okay.
Brant, what happened?
Captain, please step aside.
Sir, this is my brother.
What's going on?
PFC Macklin has been
charged with treason.
No, sir, there's
gotta be some mistake.
I'm sorry.
Brant!
Brant! Brant!
We got visual
contact with that feed.
Possible hostile elements,
request permission to engage.
Stand by for orders.
Confirming multiple RPGs...
Army apparently thought they
were clearing an insurgent hideout.
After this was leaked on
Saturday, the AP investigated.
Confirms
authorization. Engaging.
Thirty-four civilian
casualties. Six kids.
There'll be MPs stationed at every
entrance to the second floor,
as well as outside
his patient room.
No. Don't do that.
Every time there's people in uniform in
the cafeteria, they get served first.
Make sure your IDs
are clearly visible.
I'll speak with the cafeteria staff
about showing more disrespect.
20-year-old male. Generalized
tonic clonic seizures.
Army docs scanned for
structural abnormalities.
EEG was normal, so was...
Do you need me
to sign for this?
Let me know
if you need anything.
Like a transfer.
Typhus?
Patient has no hair.
Probably means no lice.
Leishmaniasis?
No fever. Why couldn't they take
care of him at a military hospital?
I think because they
wanted to annoy you.
Any other conscientious
objectors?
So I'm the only one who has
a problem with someone
whose duty is to protect
our country blowing...
Blowing the whistle is honorable,
precisely because it's not dutiful.
I'm sorry, you said "blowing." Maybe you
were going somewhere else with that?
He's a coward.
He risked his freedom.
He anonymously downloaded a
computer file from a secure page
and uploaded it
to an unsecure page.
Not exactly storming
Omaha Beach.
EEG was normal because he was
faking it to avoid going to prison.
Let's treat him
with not-medicine.
Give those back.
Come on.
You got 28.
You can share.
Somethings going on with House.
He just seemed off.
Didn't even notice that I walked
out of the room with this.
You began to suspect he was off
when he didn't notice the mug you
stole to see if he was off'?
What else didn't he notice that
you don't want us to notice?
Those are the same clothes
you wore yesterday.
And you got very defensive when
House took your birth control.
Who was he?
Or better yet, she?
Do I need to explain the
physiology behind birth control?
Attention deficit in a man
who has no attention deficits
has to be symptomatic
of something.
You're right. I'm thinking
either massive brain tumor,
or his soap got canceled
and he's distracted.
Could be dietary, Ref sum.
Or maybe he thinks you just have more
than one non-descript, white blouse.
Or serotonin syndrome?
I'm not saying
he's definitely sick,
I'm just saying
we should look into it.
No, we shouldn't.
If you believe House is sick,
it's only because that's what
he wants you to believe.
Let's go.
We think the long flight home
allowed clots to form in your leg.
Take this pill.
If you feel any numbness in
your leg after a few minutes,
it means we're right.
You should get comfortable because
you're gonna be here for a while.
While we wait,
can you tell me why?
It was the right thing to do.
There are reports that insurgents are
using your video to recruit new members.
Making the voting public aware of
what's really happening on the ground
will help bring our
troops home faster.
My brother's grunt
means he disagrees.
I think you're being naive.
And I know you took an oath.
If you want to influence
policy, run for office.
Dad raised us to believe that
exposing the truth is honorable.
Hayes likes to
follow the rules.
Yeah, because that's what
Dad taught us was honorable.
You were 10 when he died,
you can't possibly have any...
If Dad always believed in
blindly following the rules,
how do you explain Tora Bora?
My dad was commanding
a Special Forces unit.
He lost communication with his
men, they were assumed dead.
He was ordered to abandon them and
focus on the primary mission.
He disobeyed that order, went and found
his men, still alive and fighting.
He saved their lives.
Did he die in service?
If it was something genetic,
it could help us.
No, it won't help.
It was a one-car accident.
That's the Army's
official story.
My brother's naive
on this and...
I can't feel my leg.
I'll get the discharge papers.
I have a blood clot.
No you don't.
We gave you a placebo
to see if you'd fake another
symptom to delay going to prison.
Wait, wait, wait. Wait a second.
He's not faking.
Because that's not the
way your dad raised him?
Yes.
My stomach hurts, too.
What's going on?
He's not faking.
Just because he's
got abdominal bruising
doesn't mean he wasn't
faking the numbness.
He's not contesting
the treason charges.
If his code of honor
is that strong,
he's not going to
bother faking symptoms.
Pleading guilty isn't
honorable, it's just stupid.
A distal esophageal rupture can lead
to compartment syndrome in his thigh.
Explains both symptoms.
No pain when he swallows.
What is honor?
Dying for your country?
Getting straight A's?
Killing your daughter because she
had the audacity to get raped'?
Ruptured triple-A?
Doesn't explain the seizures.
Pancreatitis? Gallstones
obstructing his pancreatic duct.
People define honor with whatever
makes them feel honorable.
It's a circle going nowhere.
Which I guess is
what circles do.
We'll ultrasound his belly
and look for the obstruction.
Need your signature
on this order.
The Army's leaning on Foreman to
make sure this is done by the book.
Didn't need an order
for his last treatment.
His last treatment
wasn't a treatment.
Forge it.
I will. From now on.
But I need the original,
so I know what to forge.
We were having coffee
when the dizziness started.
Business meeting?
Date. Our first.
We met at the
Ninety Eight Cent Store.
We were reaching
for the same tube of cheese.
Huh!
I'm sorry.
Yeah.
I need to talk to you.
Just about done.
Good news. Based on her
thrifty shopping habits
and taste for artificial dairy,
she's clearly
not a gold digger.
Bad news.
Based on his
Rhinotillexomania, he is.
A compulsive addiction
to nose-picking.
A small out on the inside
of the left nostril
led to an infection
in the cavernous sinus.
It was very nice
meeting you, Mel.
It's not true.
Gloria, wait.
I can change.
My PPTH contract
House signed it six months ago.
He signed this today.
His hands are unsteady.
Given his Vicodin abuse, I think
he has hepatic encephalopathy.
He's been
forgetful, inattentive...
Dominika's been trying
out new knish recipes.
One of them didn't
agree with him.
A little sleep deprivation could account
for his forgetfulness and inattention.
He loads up on caffeine,
that explains a jittery hand.
Maybe.
But if I'm right,
his liver's in decline.
It's curable, but if he doesn't get
treatment, it could actually be fatal.
This happens all the time.
One of the symptoms
of working for House,
you start seeing
zebras everywhere.
There's nothing wrong with him.
House.
Shh! I'm with a patient.
Sleep study.
You drugged him?
Well, I didn't say
the study was voluntary.
I think you're sick.
What? Because I'm sleeping in
the clinic, like I always do?
Slow reaction time.
Because I just woke up from sleeping
in the clinic, like I always do.
You're forgetful.
Sorry, what did you say?
You forgot that we were
supposed to have lunch.
I didn't forget. I was
sleeping in the clinic...
I'd like to run some tests.
For what?
Where is this coming from?
Hepatic encephalopathy.
I've watched you destroy your
body with Vicodin for years.
I'm surprised your
liver's lasted this long.
I'll do the examination myself.
While having you juggle
my jewels sounds interesting,
there's no such thing
as friends with benefits.
It always gets weird.
Your friends out there are
getting a little handsy.
Get enough death threats, eventually
they start taking them seriously.
A convoy was hit
outside of Kunar Province.
Eight American
soldiers were killed.
Army spokesperson's claiming that it's
revenge for the attack that I made public.
Better me take
the blame than them.
You don't think
you're to blame at all?
And you do?
Like everyone else.
A strike like that would take
more than three days to plan.
So the next one
might be your fault?
Lateral view looks good.
If you have such a negative opinion
of the Army, why did you enlist?
I needed to find out what
really happened to my dad.
There were two redacted pages
in his service record.
Going into intelligence was the quickest
way lo up my security clearance.
Then why would you
leak that video?
Part of my job was to grab a
cup of tea with the locals.
The face-time is
supposed to make them
more likely to trust us
with sensitive information,
but they became my friends.
If there was another attack, civilian
casualties, and I had done nothing...
Your spleen. It's enlarged. We should
do a biopsy and look for any...
He's got urinary bleeding.
Not just urinary.
- I'll call the blood bank.
- What's happening to him?
His spleen must be
sequestering platelets.
He's bleeding loo fast to
wait for a platelet infusion.
We need to squeeze his spleen
to release the ones he's got.
Tell the OR we're on our way.
- Pressure's dropping.
- Almost there.
BP's 70 over 40,
and he's hypovolemic.
Pressure's rising.
And he's starting to clot.
Good news is we
can control the bleeding.
Bad news is,
bleeding's not the problem.
Unless spleens are
supposed to be lumpy.
He's clotting but CT
confirmed splenic nodules.
Dr. Taub has an
interesting theory.
No, I don't.
You're forfeiting?
If you can't play
the game and work...
Extramedullary hematopoiesis.
No history of anemia.
She's right. You're an idiot.
Try again.
Where I come from, this
is called "cheating."
Where's that?
Stickford-Upon-Anus?
TB.
PPD was negative.
Could be Bruce...
Don't interrupt
Dr. Taub.
Brucellosis.
You just took out
a family of four.
They were clearly
armed insurgents,
and anyone who claims
or proves otherwise
is a traitor.
No rash or back pain.
You defend the patient for
being a whistle-blower,
then attack him for being
an honorable whistle-blower,
now you defend him for being a
maligned, honorable whistle-blower?
Adjectives matter. Hate
nurses, love naughty nurses.
Taub, pitch again.
I've pitched like five...
It's your turn.
Lymphoma?
If cancer caused his seizures,
we would have seen cerebral
masses on his head CT.
TAUB; Yes!
Taub, pitch again. Now!
The nodules in his
spleen were granulomas.
He's got sarcoidosis!
Someone tell him he's wrong.
Sorry, House. Sarcoid does
explain the seizures.
And the bruises.
Say "bye-bye," House.
Yes! Yes!
Sarcoidosis it is.
Treat it with steroids.
Then come right back here,
'cause I'm not gonna rest until I've made
orphans of all your virtual children.
House never loses.
Seriously'? Me beating House
is medically significant?
It could be.
Reduced fine motor control. Add
that to inattention and liver flap.
It does make sense.
We have to talk to Foreman.
No, we don't.
First of all, because I can
beat him in that game.
And second, even if you are right,
there's no reason to believe
that House's medical
judgment is impaired.
So we should wait until he kills
someone for confirmation?
Do you really think it's a coincidence
that we're treating a whistle-blower
and now talking about
blowing the whistle on House?
You're right.
Playing dumb.
A messy signature.
Losing a video game.
It's way too
complicated to fake.
No. I won't take it.
Without this injection, you
could have a fatal arrhythmia.
Tell Major Mathewson that I'm
not taking any more treatment
until they give me a live
television interview.
You can't really think
they'll agree to that?
People need to know the tape's
not the reason for that attack.
They need to know
why I did this.
The people who think you're a traitor
will still think you're a traitor,
and the people who think you're a
hero will still think you're a hero.
The truth makes a difference.
If Dad were here, he'd be
begging for you not to do this.
If Dad were here,
he'd be proud of me.
The conspiracy theorists are gonna
go nuts if the patient dies.
I told him that, and he told me
that option is still less damaging
than giving the kid
a national platform.
So, what do we do now?
You explain to your brother
that he overplayed his hand.
Well, that won't
make any difference.
The idiot thinks he's
doing the right thing.
What if we convince
a court that his refusal
is part of an underlying
psychiatric disorder?
They assign a conservator,
we do what we want.
Fraud? Great.
Narcissistic
personality disorder.
Both the leaking of the tape
and the refusal of treatment
indicate that he has
no fear of consequences.
So instead of defrauding
the court, you'll waste their time?
No way a judge classifies a personality
disorder as a mental illness.
If a decorated
military officer,
who happened to be the patient's
brother, corroborates, they might.
So you want me to sign a piece of
paper that says my brother is crazy
for doing what
he thinks is right?
I want you to save his life. His
heart could go at any time.
He's a fool,
but he's not crazy.
The patient is refusing
treatment because of honor,
and his brother is refusing to be
his conservator because of honor.
Good, Taub's cured the patient.
I had to go to the bathroom.
Bathroom's that way.
You just ran in from that way.
That one's been out
of order for two days.
I had to go up
to the third floor.
I'm not lying.
It's out of order.
I believe you.
I'm going to fix it.
We could treat if he doesn't
know he's being treated.
Lace his sponge bath?
Would take too long
to reach his bloodstream.
What if we aerosolize
steroids and blast the room?
Speaking of which.
It'd be too hard to get the
prednisone concentrations right.
No one fixes anything unless
they have a compelling reason.
And if we're going to treat,
we have to give him
a compelling reason.
Something that he wants
more than an interview.
Fire in the hole!
A signed order
from Major Mathewson.
They've agreed to declassify
the redacted pages
from your father's
service record.
In two days, you'll
have all your answers.
But the only way you'll live long enough to
get the truth is by accepting treatment.
I don't trust the Army
to follow through on this.
But you trust me.
I'll make sure
those pages get here.
Okay.
Selfishness is apparently
honorable now.
He wanted to create change, instead
he's just satisfying his own curiosity.
He's getting the truth.
Most he could hope for.
I need to take a dump.
Specifically, House's dump.
You set this up?
All it took was showing up two
minutes late and a $2 sign.
Bile deposits are irregular.
House's liver is failing.
Cognitive impairment will
get progressively worse.
What's going on?
My foot.
It's killing me.
It's completely cyanotic.
This isn't sarcoidosis.
Cholesterol embolization?
Are you even going to acknowledge
what we just told you'?
That you pilfered
my poo-poo?
Yeah, I was thinking it would
be less awkward for all of us
if we could just pretend
that never happened.
It's not an embolization. No
instrumentation inside the arteries.
Thank you for
getting us back to...
And if we start you on treatment
now, get you off Vicodin...
What's the opposite of "thank you"?
Pretty sure it ends in "you".
I know my body.
I'm fine.
Methemoglobinemia.
Army tests for G6PD deficiency.
If you're not sick, then our tests
accurate 99.5% of the time,
yielded a false positive,
three separate times.
The odds of that are
one in eight million.
The test is accurate.
The diagnosis isn't.
The sample was obviously
contaminated by other foods
interacting with
my liver enzymes.
Now, can we talk
about the sick patient?
His clot dissolved. That could
have caused the vasospasm.
And DIC could have been caused
by Bernard Soulier Syndrome.
And you're sick and you have
to do something about it.
If we got a patient file with the
same symptoms you're exhibiting...
And the symptoms
I'm not exhibiting?
Jaundice, ascites,
fetor hepaticus.
We can't tell if your breath stinks
because you've been popping mints
like they're Vicodin.
And you would still
diagnose hepatic encephalopathy.
I know that because four doctors you
trained have unanimously diagnosed you
with hepatic encephalopathy.
Park's right. Treat the
patient with heparin.
We'll have a stronger argument if
we go to Foreman as a united front.
We'll have a stronger argument
if we have an argument.
If House is sick, it's his
business, not Foreman's.
Foreman's business is to make sure his
doctors are able to do their jobs.
That lives aren't put at risk.
Telling Foreman
will put lives at risk.
We tell Foreman, House either agrees
to treatment or gets suspended.
Which means House
gets suspended.
And considering House at 90%
is better than any other doctor
at this hospital at 100%
that means our patients
get a lower standard of care.
House could be at 90%, he could be at 60%.
We don't know.
And until we do, there's no reason to
do anything more than what we've done.
Blurry vision, headache,
bit of nausea and dizziness.
I am completely baffled.
I only had eight beers.
Sophomore class pong
tournament's in a week.
I'm working on my tolerance.
Hop on one foot and sing
the iCarly theme song.
Like you don't know it.
Damn it, man, can't you
see I'm doctoring'?
If you want to talk to me' you can
buy me a sandwich in an hour.
Or I can just hover here
until you're done.
Heard enough. Just never could
figure out the "breathe air" part.
Next year, stick to whiskey.
Or at least stay away
from week-old green beers.
A lot less likely to contain
tartrazine-laced green food dyes
for which you apparently
have an intolerance.
Once you break the seal, should be
out of your system in 48 hours.
What are my choices here? If I tell
you I'm fine, you won't believe me.
I've scheduled
a liver function test.
If I ignore you, then you'll
just ignore my ignoring.
Which is rude, frankly.
Depending on the results, we'll
customize a treatment plan.
If I tell you I think I'm
sick and I need your help
and we need to setup a time to talk
about it, you'll just assume I'm lying.
Again, rude.
Also hurtful.
Why is it that you can find the
smallest thing wrong with anyone else,
but when it comes to you...
I really don't have
a choice here, do I?
No. You don't.
I'm on the list He's not.
You can't ignore me forever.
Well, if you're right it's
not gonna be all that long.
Do it slow.
Who are you?
Well, considering the only
people allowed in this room
are your doctors
and your family,
I'm your long-lost
cousin Ralph.
So glad to finally meet you.
Are you going to check on me?
It's gonna be at least two hours until
we can tell if the heparin's working.
Then what are you doing here?
My father taught me
that it's dishonorable to interrupt
someone while they're reading.
Honor is not a punch line.
Get out of my room.
So, was it worth it?
Best case, you spend the rest
of your life in Leavenworth.
Worst case' you spend the
rest of your life here.
Justice for 34 deaths outweighs
anything the Army can do to me.
They got justice?
Do they know that?
What if only 10 people
had died? Four?
Even one civilian death is...
What if they had just maimed a few guys.
Would that have been worth it?
My job was to log that tape,
get all the details
in the official record.
After the 10th time
of watching it,
I stopped trying
to convince myself
that the shovel could have
been mistaken for a gun
because all I could see
were the victims' faces.
All I was doing was trying to read that
kid's lips to make out his last words.
I couldn't sleep.
Couldn't eat.
Think I like the cue ball look?
My hair turned
gray in three days.
My body was telling me
I had to do whatever I could
to make sure that something
like this never happened again.
Your hair turned
gray in three days?
Loss of hair color indicates an autoimmune
condition, likely Graves disease.
Hyperthyroidism leads to
a hypercoagulable state
which causes thrombosis.
Start him on
anti-thyroids.
You want to reject
our current diagnosis
because he had
a few gray hairs,
panicked and shaved his head?
I want to reject our current diagnosis
because I think we're wrong
and treating for
wrong diagnoses
can result in side
effects, like death.
Even if he did fully go gray, stress
seems Way more likely than Graves.
I haven't read any journal
articles proving that veterans
have a higher incidence
of depigmentation.
But, of course, that could be the
hepatic encephalopathy talking.
Our treatment for Bernard
Soulier hasn't had“.
So you all want to just
ignore the new symptom?
It's not Graves because
it's not a symptom at all.
And the anti-thyroids
you want
could reduce his blood pressure
and his ability to breathe,
which could result in
side effects, like death.
Small soda.
Graves it is. Start
him on anti-thyroids.
I know we disagree
with House all the time,
but before I could say,
"Okay, he's a genius."
Now?
Maybe he's just really smart.
We're not gonna give
him the anti-thyroids.
Feeling okay?
Any better?
Pretty good.
He did just ask
me for a blanket.
You're cold?
A little.
For how long?
It's really nothing.
Maybe an hour or two.
He's at 104.
It's not Bernard Soulier.
Bold move.
You've gone from speculating that
I'm sick, to acting like I'm dead.
We acted like we don't
trust your judgment,
because we don't
trust your judgment.
Why don't you start by
not trusting your own?
We did more blood work.
It's not Graves either.
Talk to you for a minute?
Anything you have to say to
me, you can say to them.
It's only fair, considering
anything they say to me,
they also say to you.
Jiggle your pockets.
Who's got the silver coins?
Until you receive
a clean bill of health,
I'll be authorizing
all treatment orders.
I would say that that was an
incredibly stupid mistake.
But apparently I'd have to clear
that opinion through Foreman first.
White count is high,
so all the infections we ruled out
when he came in are back on the table.
Legionnaires'?
Unlikely without pneumonia.
Taub?
Loyalty issues in
his personal life
make sense if they cross over
into his professional one.
I was hoping we could get a
diagnosis before the witch-hunt.
The patient's infection is an
inherently less interesting puzzle
than the stab wound in my back.
Fine. I told Foreman.
Can we move on now?
What about dengue?
Patient isn't in enough pain.
Nope!
I don't mean about dengue,
I have no idea.
Taub's only confessing 'cause he
wants us to focus on the patient.
I told Foreman.
I did.
The next person
to confess is fired.
Or Spartacus.
For clarification,
no one's getting fired.
Who else has a pitch?
And then there's Park?
The only one who
didn't confess.
And the same cowardice,
that makes someone unable to move
out of Mommy and Daddy's home,
might also make
someone a tattletale.
You threatened to fire
the next person who...
And it's malaria.
No, it's not.
The Army issues
anti-malaria medication.
And has done for 10 years.
That's the equivalent
of 5,000 generations
of the Afghan mosquito,
Anopheles gambiae.
It's plenty long enough
to develop a resistance.
Anopheles, by the way,
ifs Greek for "useless".
Cover for intra-abdominal sepsis
and treat with antimalarials.
And was I also right
that it was a stupid idea?
We believe you have malaria.
These pills...
I don't want any medication.
My dad's file
should've been here.
Brant, I told you. I looked into it.
There's just a delay.
I believe that's what
the Army's saying.
I don't believe it's true.
If they're not going to keep
their end of the bargain,
neither am I.
So, we got groped for nothing?
If he doesn't
want to stay alive...
Hold on.
Is it too late to
become his conservator?
I know what I said before.
Right now, I don't care.
Of course not. We'll get
the paperwork drawn up.
He changed his mind?
Why?
His brother's dying. He needs
a more substantial reason?
His brother was dying the last time
we asked him to be the conservator.
So instead of pushing the issue
with the Army to get that file,
he just decided to
give up on his code?
Apparently.
So, where do I sign?
We don't need you to.
The Army gave the file
to you yesterday.
Major Mathewson had another
copy sent over to us.
Uh... You know, there's a reason I
didn't want that file released.
I know. I read it.
I'm going to treat
my patient now.
I was right.
Wasn't I?
How did he die?
What did they cover up?
They didn't cover up anything.
I did.
Dad died in that car accident
because he was drunk.
Killed a pedestrian, too.
What are you... I...
He drank, Brant, a lot.
You were too young to see it.
I had some of Dad's buddies
take care of his files.
It's the only time
I ever broke the rules.
I'm sorry.
Can I begin treatment?
Fever hasn't broken.
White count is still up,
renal function is declining.
So, he has
all the signs of malaria,
except the antimalarials
aren't curing him.
Gonorrhea? If it got
into his heart...
We did an echo. His valves look good.
What about...
You bastard.
You were faking.
Yesterday, House stole candy
by putting it into a cup.
The cup was too small, so his solution
was to remove some of the candy.
But the obviously logical thing
was to just get a bigger cup
which he did today
because he's no longer faking.
He couldn't have faked ii.
We tested your...
I took St. John's Wort to alter the way
my liver metabolized acetaminophen.
Then some N-acetylcysteine
just to finish it off.
You tortured them to torture me
just to see who you could trust?
I did it to save lives.
God, I wish I could
rationalize that one.
And now you're gonna brilliantly
deduce which one of us is the rat?
What makes you think
I haven't already?
To be continued. I need to
brilliantly cure a patient.
No hair usually means no lice.
What we didn't account for
was that it wasn't your hair.
Tea was not the only thing that your
Afghani neighbors shared with you.
I'm sure they were generous enough
to let you sit on their furniture
which was infested
with rat lice.
You have typhus.
Caused the vasculitis and
explains all your other symptoms.
But here's where
it gets interesting.
One of those symptoms, a lawyer
might argue, was leaking the tape.
There are psychiatric issues
associated with typhus.
And if you change your mind, plead
not guilty, you've got a case.
I'd be undermining everything
I've been trying to do.
You did what you
thought you had to do.
Going to jail proves nothing.
It proves I still
have my honor.
You're not doing
this for honor,
you're doing this
to please your father.
And the pathetic thing is, is that the man
you're trying to please never existed.
Traitor.
You've been avoiding
me for two days.
Because when I stranded you
behind the barricades,
you went straight to Foreman.
I've been avoiding you
because you're an ass.
I've been an ass my whole life.
I can't get rid of you.
You can get rid of me now.
Just turn and limp away.
Hun!
Your whiny righteousness
has the stench of sincerity.
Fine. I'll have to
punish my whole team,
so one of them
will step forward.
Makes sense.
Damn. Now I'm gonna
have to punish my whole team
so one of them
will step forward.
You just said that
Yeah, but I meant it this time.
First time, I was
just testing you.
Either you were gonna genuinely
confess or falsely confess'
or actually...
His name's Li'l Chase.
He's a rat.
You're a rat.
Get it?
Taub confessed to telling
Foreman to protect the patient.
Adams confessed
to protect Taub.
Your confession
was just piling on.
There was no rational reason
for you to have done ii.
And my punishment
will be nothing.
You wanted me to tell Foreman.
Your ability to solve puzzles is the
only thing that matters to you.
And you're smart enough to know even
you'll lose your edge at some point.
You want to make sure
someone's there when you do.
If that were true,
why are Li'l Chase's
little cousins
scurrying through your apartment
floorboards right now?