[MADDOX] Load up! Now!
[SOLDIERS GRUNTING]
Your Majesty, we found this man
riding through the woods.
[NECKLACE RATTLING]
Sibeth?
Kofun?
Is that really you?
What are you...
What are you doing here? What is this?
[WITCHFINDER] Kneel for your queen, witch.
- She's not my queen.
- [SIBETH GASPS]
[GRUNTING]
Poor Kofun.
Always and forever a step behind.
Though in fairness, I must thank you
for freeing me from my sister's clutches.
You're working with Trivantes.
You're insane.
They're gonna destroy Pennsa.
No, I'm going to destroy Pennsa.
[SHOUTS]
[PANTING, GRUNTING]
[COUGHING]
Kofun, don't make me wonder
whether my fondness for you
might be a character flaw.
You're gonna kill thousands.
Maghra should've thought of that
before her little coup.
Tormada, are we ready?
[TORMADA] We are, my queen.
Sibeth, please don't do this.
Do it.
[GRUNTS]
[TORMADA] On my mark!
Hold on, Kofun.
You won't want to miss this.
Move him.
[FINGERS SNAPPING]
[WALKING STICK BELL JINGLING]
[MAGHRA] Why are you troubling yourself
with the burial of traitors?
There is no one else
to say the final prayers for them.
I trained them.
I fought with them.
I never imagined this.
They tried to kill us.
They did what they believed was right.
They've lived their entire life
in the service of an ideal.
We were the ones to change the rules.
[KISSES]
Let's go.
[MAGHRA] How go your preparations?
It's somewhat difficult to prepare
for an enemy we don't know
with weapons we don't understand.
But the army is assembled.
Did you believe what Shiloh said
about Sibeth allying herself
with the Trivantians?
Witchfinders don't lie.
And I put nothing past your sister.
What use would the Trivantians have
for Sibeth or the Witchfinders?
If Tormada is indeed leading
a rogue faction of the Trivantian army,
their numbers might not be
as large as we fear.
Which is why they might have welcomed
an alliance with her.
The numbers won't matter if those bombs
can do what Baba said they can.
[METAL CLANKING]
Armed and ready, sir.
As soon as we reach the palace,
I will order battalions out to the gates.
We'll not allow those weapons
to enter the city.
Fire!
[GRUNTS]
[MAGHRA] Shh.
[BOMBS WHIRRING]
What is it?
[GRUNTS]
[GASPING]
- We're too late.
- No.
[GASPS] Oh, my.
[VILLAGERS WAILING, SCREAMING]
- [SHARP RINGING]
- [TAMACTI JUN COUGHING]
Maghra!
Tamacti. [GRUNTS]
[TAMACTI JUN]
They've breached the walls. Come.
No, they didn't breach the walls.
The bombs came over the walls.
I heard them fly.
Wolffe.
Again!
[GRUNTS]
[BOMBS WHIRRING]
[SCREAMS]
- Haniwa! Haniwa!
- [VILLAGERS SCREAMING, CLAMORING]
- [HANIWA COUGHS, PANTING]
- [BABA VOSS GRUNTS]
Keep moving! Go!
[GRUNTS]
Maghra!
- Maghra.
- Papa! We can't find her.
- Keep moving. Okay?
- Okay.
- Wolffe!
- [HANDMAIDEN] Here!
[WOLFFE CRYING]
[SIGHS] We have to move.
- We'll be safer here.
- No. Come on.
Fire!
[DRUM BEATING]
[BOMB WHIRRING]
No! No! No!
[INHALES SHARPLY]
[GRUNTS]
Hello? Who's there?
[BABA VOSS] Relax. You're safe.
Where am I?
You are on Alkenny land.
Alkenny? One... One of the hidden tribes?
The way you say that
tells me you're not from a tribe.
No.
Where then?
The Northern Mountains.
[INHALES DEEPLY] You've come a long way.
How did I get here?
Don't you remember?
There was a... a woman.
Yes. Paris.
She found you wandering in the snow.
She brought you back to this village.
She says you were running from something.
She says maybe you haven't run far enough.
[PENNSA VILLAGERS SCREAMING, WAILING]
[GASPING, WHIMPERING]
Haniwa, what is it?
The palace is destroyed. Papa.
- Shh.
- [NO BARKING]
What do you hear?
No. No!
[HANIWA GRUNTS]
[BABA VOSS] No.
- [NO WHIMPERS]
- [BABA VOSS] Maghra!
[WOLFFE CRYING]
[HANIWA] Come, baby. Papa.
[BABA VOSS] Maghra.
[GRUNTS] Ranger, help me!
[WOLFFE CRYING]
[BOTH GROANING]
Baba Voss.
Tamacti Jun. Ranger, help him.
[GASPS] Shh. Shh.
She's still breathing. Still breathing.
Maghra.
Tormada, tell me you didn't disappoint.
My Ayuras report all direct hits,
my queen.
[GASPS, CHUCKLES]
Kofun. What did you see? Huh?
You bombed your own child.
If he is in harm's way,
it's your mother who has placed him there,
just as she's placed you here.
Fuck you.
Secure him inside my tent.
- Load up!
- Wait, wait, wait.
Let's give my sister some time
to appreciate the position she's in.
The deaths she's caused.
[TORMADA] Are you sure?
We've mapped the city,
established key coordinates.
Don't worry.
Knowing my sister,
you'll be launching more soon enough.
[NECKLACE RATTLING]
[KOFUN SCREAMS, STRAINING]
- I hear you...
- [SPLUTTERS]
...struggling against your ties.
And I can't help but feel
that that's what you've been doing
since I've known you,
struggling against these invisible ties
that bind you.
[KOFUN BREATHING HEAVILY]
You cannot get free,
but you never stop trying.
I think it's what I love most about you.
You don't love me.
You don't know anything about love.
On the contrary.
If anything, I love too much, too deeply.
That's why I allowed myself to believe
Maghra wouldn't betray me again.
If you love me, you won't kill me.
[LAUGHS]
[GRUNTS]
I'm the one who doesn't know
anything about love?
[KISSES, SIGHS, BREATHING HEAVILY]
Poor Kofun. [SNIFFS, SIGHS]
A year ago, you were an Alkenny.
A simple mountain boy.
And now, you bear witness
to the rise and fall of kingdoms.
There's so much you do not understand.
I understand that you're a murderer
and a traitor.
And what makes me any different
than your mother?
Mmm.
She rose up against the ordained queen.
Is she not a traitor?
Last time I was in Pennsa,
she hosted an execution.
Is she not a murderer?
"Traitor," "murderer," they're just words.
And their truth is dictated
by whichever side you happen to be on.
- You're on the side of the Trivantians.
- No. [CHUCKLES]
I am on the side of God.
[SIGHS] How else do you explain
I'm still alive despite my death sentence,
about to retake my throne?
Your sightless child was sent to me by God
to delay my execution
long enough to make my escape.
He's your son too,
no matter how many times you deny it.
He has served his holy purpose
and shall be remembered for it. Huh.
You're a monster.
[GRUNTS]
And you are a witch.
[KOFUN BREATHING HEAVILY]
Perhaps your mother's short reign
may have tricked you
into thinking otherwise.
But there are a hundred Witchfinders
right outside this tent
who will happily burn you alive
just to remind you who you are.
I'm just trying to remind you who you are.
And who is that?
[INHALES DEEPLY] You're Wolffe's mother.
And he needs you.
You said he was brought here to save you.
Well, maybe he's not done doing that.
He's your son.
He's your son, Sibeth.
- [RANGER GRUNTING]
- [TAMACTI JUN GROANING]
[SCREAMING]
[HANIWA] Please wake up.
Mmm. Maghra.
[HANIWA]
Oh, please wake up, please wake up.
[BABA VOSS] What is your name?
You won't tell me your name?
I don't want to lie to you.
Are you the leader of the Alkenny?
Yes.
But you're not from here.
I don't know your accent,
but it's not from the mountains.
- Are you being pursued?
- No.
You said you didn't wanna lie.
I was being pursued,
but I've been traveling for a long time,
and I left no trail.
You can't know that.
No, I can't.
Rest up.
You will leave as soon as you can walk.
That might take a bit longer
than you think.
Why is that?
I'm with child.
[WOLFFE CRYING]
[HANIWA] She's waking up.
Maghra. Maghra.
Baba.
[SIGHS] I am here with Haniwa.
[MAGHRA] Ah.
- [BABA VOSS SHUSHES]
- I'm so glad you're back.
I was so worried.
The house just... just flew apart.
I know. It's the God Thunder. The bombs.
You were not able to stop them?
No.
Wolffe!
It's okay. It's okay.
He is safe. You saved him.
Where's Kofun? Why is he not here?
We sent him ahead to warn you.
No, he's not been here.
- [HANIWA] Where is he? He could be hurt.
- We will find him.
- It's all my fault.
- [HANIWA GASPS]
[SNIFFLES]
Mama. Don't be ridiculous.
[BABA VOSS] No, you did your best
to make peace with Trivantes.
No, it's not Trivantes.
[SNIFFLES] It's Sibeth.
How could that even be?
Sibeth made an alliance
between the rebel Witchfinders
and Tormada's army.
I shielded her from execution.
I let the Witchfinders live.
I created the army
that will now destroy us.
I need to go outside. [GRUNTS]
Wait, wait. Mama. Mama.
[MAGHRA] Haniwa, what do you see?
[HANIWA] The huts are on fire.
There are dead and wounded everywhere.
People are just wandering around...
and they look terrified.
Of course they're terrified.
Fire is falling from the sky like rain.
There's no more fire falling from the sky.
[MAGHRA] For now.
Sibeth is letting us know
she's in control.
Tamacti, assemble the Royal Guard
to put out the fires,
and gather and treat the wounded.
Evacuate those who can move quickly
to Altoona
where we will regroup
and be ready to fight.
[BABA VOSS] We must find your brother.
We found Mama and Wolffe.
We'll find Kofun.
[BABA VOSS SIGHS]
Come, Mama.
Kofun! I'm sorry we haven't been
properly introduced until now.
It's been a busy time,
as I'm sure you know.
I know who you are.
[CHUCKLES] Yes, I'm sure you do.
[GROANS] And I just wanna say,
that as dire as things may feel now,
you do still have options.
Options?
Mmm. Your gifts have not always
been properly appreciated. Hmm?
Well, the...
the Payans think you're a witch,
Trivantians think you're a threat
to the republic, and... and me...
I admire you.
I understand your potential. Mmm?
[CHUCKLES] If you were to join me...
You tried to kill us.
Well, yes, but that was before.
Things have changed.
Certainly, I had no idea
I'd be allied with Queen Kane.
[CHUCKLES]
She'll kill you when she's done with you.
Exactly.
Or maybe I will kill her.
Or maybe nobody will kill anybody.
[CHUCKLES]
Every day is a new day, Kofun.
Today could be a new day for you.
Fuck you.
[CHUCKLES] Yes, of course.
Boys your age
always seem to think they know so much,
when really, they're just too stupid
to realize what they don't know.
I know my father will kill you.
Ah, like I said. Stupid.
We'll have plenty of time to educate you.
What is it?
[WITCHFINDER 1]
The queen has sent for him.
[TORMADA] What for?
[WITCHFINDER 1] Ask her yourself.
[KOFUN GRUNTS]
[SIGHS]
[WREN] Their camp's
about 100 heartbeats due east.
How many soldiers?
[WREN] I can see about 50 or so.
Where are the rest?
[DOOR CREAKS]
[SIGHS, BREATHING SHAKILY]
[WHISPERING] Hush.
[TAMACTI JUN]
There's no way out of the city.
[MAGHRA] Will they invade?
I don't think so.
If they can continue to launch bombs,
why risk soldiers?
Sibeth wants her city back.
Why would she destroy it?
[TAMACTI JUN]
She could've launched many more,
but the fact that we're still standing
means she wants the city whole.
[CLEARS THROAT] To do that,
she would have to send in her army.
If Harlan and Trovere
were able to make their case in Trivantes,
they could be on their way back now
with reinforcements.
Mama. Harlan is dead.
He died to save me.
Mama, um...
He, um, wanted me
to give something to you.
A key?
What's it for?
[HANIWA]
I don't know. He said it might help.
[BREATHING HEAVILY]
Haniwa?
[HANIWA] Kofun.
Kofun?
- You okay?
- Are you okay?
- Yeah. Ah, Papa.
- [BABA VOSS GRUNTS]
Where have you been?
Sibeth.
She captured me just outside the city.
[KISSES] She sent a message.
A message?
Yeah, she tied it.
She wants your abdication
and total surrender.
You'll walk alone to her camp,
where you will forfeit your crown
and kingdom to her.
She says if you don't go soon,
then she'll turn Pennsa
and everyone in it into ash.
[WALKING STICK BANGS]
[KOFUN SIGHS]
She doesn't just want her kingdom back.
She wants to punish me.
- You can't go.
- We're not having this argument, Haniwa.
- Of course I'm going.
- She'll kill you.
She'll kill all of us
and so many more if I don't go.
She is my sister,
and as much as I despised her,
when the moment came,
I found myself unable to kill her.
Maybe she'll have the same hesitation
about killing me.
[GROANS] You don't believe that.
[SIGHS] Ju... It doesn't matter.
I-I have to go. I can't let her just...
- [BABA VOSS] Maghra!
- [HANIWA] Mama!
[BABA VOSS GROANS, EXHALES SHARPLY,
SHUSHES]
[BABA VOSS] Paris says you will not eat.
Why am I not allowed to leave this cave?
Am I your prisoner?
The villagers...
They are suspicious of strangers.
It is not safe for you to be out there.
Well, if they don't want me here,
then I'll leave.
And where will you go?
[SIGHS] You haven't even told me
your name or where you're from.
If you want us to trust you,
you must trust us.
You can trust me.
Why would I trust you?
Well,
I'm the one who's been protecting you.
It's Maghra.
- What?
- My name is Maghra.
Maghra? What kinda name is Maghra?
What kind of a name is Baba?
[SNICKERS] That's a fair point, Maghra.
Why are you the one protecting me?
Because I was once in the same position
that you are in.
And how did you get the villagers
to trust you?
I defeated their strongest warrior.
So, I guess I have to defeat you.
[CHUCKLES] Yes.
[HANIWA] Mama?
Are you okay?
[BABA VOSS] Maghra.
Yeah, I'm fine.
We're all here.
Hmm.
I have... I have to go. [GRUNTS]
No, no, no. We can't let you go.
[MAGHRA BREATHING HEAVILY]
She will kill you where you stand,
and nothing will be gained.
And what about Pennsa?
She'll burn the entire city
just to spite me.
I c-can't let that happen.
If she's going to destroy Pennsa,
she will whether you are alive or dead.
Is there no other way
to evacuate the city?
- They have battalions at all the gates.
- So we fight our way out.
The moment they hear resistance,
the bombs will come.
The bombs will be coming either way,
but this family will not be here
when they do.
Harlan.
[BABA VOSS] What's that?
[MAGHRA] He was always
three steps ahead of everyone.
He was such an infuriating man.
He gave me no reason to trust him.
Somehow, I did.
Well, he could have saved himself,
but he came back for me.
[CHUCKLES] Maybe here?
[SIGHS]
[METAL CLANKING]
- No?
- No.
He was in love with you.
I used him.
Now he's dead.
Harlan didn't strike me as someone
who could be used if he didn't want to be.
[SIGHING]
What is it?
- Mama.
- Can you bring it?
[HIGH-PITCHED CLANG]
A sound wand?
What else is in the box?
Just this old map.
[GRUNTS]
It looks like Pennsa.
[MAGHRA] It is Pennsa, but...
something else, too.
Oh, Harlan.
Oh, you sneaky bastard.
What is it?
Tunnels. Smuggler's tunnels.
Where do they go?
Out of the city. Come on.
[TORMADA] My queen.
Tormada. Come sit with me.
[TORMADA CHUCKLES]
How go your machinations? [CHUCKLES]
By now,
our message will have been delivered.
I have every confidence
my sister will arrive shortly
to surrender.
And when she does,
all of Paya will be ours.
I think reducing Pennsa to rubble
sends a more dramatic message.
I haven't endured all that I have
to rule over rubble and corpses.
Paya will fall in line
with Maghra's surrender.
It's not Paya I'm speaking of.
Trivantes.
Don't underestimate their might.
Don't underestimate ours.
Believe me, I don't.
I do have one request.
Hmm?
- Your nephew.
- Kofun?
I wish you had asked me
before you released him.
Having lost
the rest of Jerlamarel's children,
he would have been invaluable to me.
You do realize that my arrangement
with the Witchfinders
is based on an agreement
that all sighted are witches
and must be burned?
I won't need them forever.
I have been working on adapting the system
to no longer require their sight. Hmm?
Until then, though,
the Witchfinders will just need to agree
to certain exceptions.
- The Witchfinders can be dangerous.
- So can I.
They have God on their side.
I hope you don't take offense,
but I don't believe in God.
- You don't?
- Mmm.
Oh.
[GROANS]
[GRUNTS]
Maybe you haven't met the right one yet.
[MOANS, BREATHING HEAVILY]
[GROANS]
- [WREN] Are you interpreting that right?
- [HANIWA] Yes.
All the landmarks are accounted for.
[WREN] Let me see it.
This way.
Well, according to the map,
it should be right here.
I don't see anything.
Well, maybe the map's wrong.
You didn't know Harlan.
The map isn't wrong.
[KNOCKS]
Hello?
There's nothing here.
[METAL CLANGS]
[GROANS]
[GASPS]
I'll be right back.
[BREATHES HEAVILY]
We followed the tunnel to its end.
It comes out in a small cave
in the mountains.
Just west of Pennsa.
If we move now, we can be halfway
to Altoona before they know we're gone.
And what stops them
from bringing bombs to Altoona?
Sibeth's army is still small.
We can regroup in Altoona.
Gather soldiers.
Be ready before they...
they can establish position
as they did here.
We've no time to lose.
Captain Gosset, have your men begin
rounding up the citizens immediately.
No one takes more than they can carry.
Haniwa, you and Wren direct the captain
to the entrance you found.
Kofun, Tamacti, Ranger.
Leave us for a moment.
[BABA VOSS GROANS]
Baba.
You haven't said a word.
[SIGHS SHARPLY] You are queen.
You know what's best for your people.
[GROANS]
Yes, I must take care of the kingdom.
But you are my husband.
And the father to Haniwa and Kofun.
So you must decide what is best for us.
I don't understand.
My sister hunted us for 17 years.
She didn't stop then,
and she won't stop now.
She will never stop hunting this family.
So what are you saying?
I'm saying that you were right all along.
Once we lead the people out of Pennsa,
you and I, and Kofun, and Wolffe
and Haniwa, we shall go far away.
Back up into the mountains,
or further even,
where we can be the family we once were.
Maybe with me gone,
my sister will be less inclined
to direct her wrath at the Payans.
Are you sure?
I have been a mother much longer
than I've been a queen.
And if my family coming first
means I'm a bad queen...
well, then it just proves
that I... I shouldn't be one.
I don't feel anything.
- Here.
- You mean here?
- [LAUGHS]
- Oh, there it is.
- Here. Do you feel that?
- Where? Oh, here.
- No. Still nothing.
- [LAUGHS]
I think you just like having an excuse
to put your hands on me.
- I think maybe you like my hands on you.
- Well, mmm, maybe I do.
You still feel nothing?
Maybe it's scared of me.
Mmm. Maybe it's not the baby who's scared.
What are you talking about?
Why would I be scared? [KISSES]
Because you've never had a child.
And this child, would it be mine?
Do you want it to be yours?
As much as I want you.
Then we are both yours.
- [MAGHRA SIGHS]
- [BABA VOSS] I love you. [KISSING]
[GROANS]
I love you, Baba Voss.
I love you, Maghra Voss.
[BOTH CHUCKLING]
You think it will always be like this?
You fear it will not?
I fear for my child.
[BABA VOSS SIGHS]
I swear to you that I will die
before I allow anything to happen
to you or our child.
And we will protect you.
Yes.
- Yes, you protect me. I need that.
- Yes.
- [GASPING] Oh, wait.
- What?
- [GASPS]
- [MAGHRA] You feel that?
- [BABA VOSS] There it is.
- Yeah?
- It's kicking. And again.
- [LAUGHING] Yeah.
- Oh, it's a very angry baby.
- Oh, wow. [GIGGLES]
And he has a temper like his mother.
A temper? I don't have a temper.
What are you talking about?
- No, of course you don't.
- I don't have a temper. What do you mean?
That's rich coming from you.
- [BABA VOSS] Look at that. Sassy baby.
- Uh-huh. Sassy ba...
[BABA VOSS]
Sassy, angry baby like your mother.
[BOTH CHUCKLING]
- [BABA VOSS WHISTLES]
- [NO BARKING]
[RANGER] Your dog stinks.
- [EXHALES DEEPLY]
- [BABA VOSS] Up.
No, that's me. [CHUCKLES]
Up, boy.
You should go home, my friend.
[RANGER SIGHS]
My home was blown up, thanks to you.
- [BABA VOSS] You know what I mean.
- Ah, you know what I mean.
[SIGHS]
I've avoided humanity for almost 20 years.
[INHALES SHARPLY]
And if I live through this,
the day will soon come
where I will avoid them for another 20.
[EXHALES DEEPLY]
But today is not that day.
Damn it, Ranger.
If anything happens to you,
Lu will hunt me down
and kill me in my sleep.
No. She will wake you first,
so that you feel it when it happens.
[BOTH CHUCKLING]
I made the choice to leave the mountain.
That may turn out
to have been a terrible mistake,
but, as of this moment, my blade is sharp.
My weed is good,
and the sun feels warm on my face.
So, things being what they are,
I think I will stay
and find out how the story ends.
[INHALES DEEPLY] What do you think?
- I think you smoke too much of that herb.
- [LAUGHS]
- Yeah, maybe.
- Too much.
[GROANING]
[RANGER] Or maybe you don't smoke enough.
[BOTH GROANING]
[CHATTERING]
[TAMACTI JUN]
We have rounded up every citizen.
Those not yet here are on their way.
I hear unrest in your voice.
Have you ever wondered
why we eat bison and deer, but not bear?
When you hunt bison and deer,
they run away,
and that makes them vulnerable.
If you hunt a bear,
the bear hunts you back.
As a general rule, those who flee
are the ones that get eaten.
[MAGHRA] You agreed,
we stand a better chance in Altoona?
[TAMACTI JUN] Yes,
but first we have to make it to Altoona.
Mom, I'm so sorry.
- I'm so... This is my fault.
- Kofun. Kofun.
- It's my fault. I let her go.
- I let her live.
Hey, hey, my loves. Listen to me.
[FINGERS SNAPPING] Haniwa.
You are not just my family.
You are the best that I have ever known.
I have been carrying blame on my shoulders
for the Alkenny, for Edo,
for everything that came before.
And I have been learning
from my occasionally wise friend, Ranger,
that blaming yourself
does no one any good.
You must pay attention to what lies ahead,
not behind.
- Yes.
- Is that what you would do?
- It's what a wiser man would do.
- [MAGHRA SNICKERS]
[ALL CHUCKLE]
[BABA VOSS GROANS]
Come, my loves. Let's get out of here.
- Mama.
- [MAGHRA] Mm-hmm.
This way.
[MURMURING]
[BELLA'S MOM] Come on, baby. No, no.
- We have to keep moving.
- [BELLA] I want to go home.
[BELLA'S MOM]
We can't go home. We have to keep moving.
- [BELLA] No, I don't want to.
- [BELLA'S MOM] Bella, please.
[MAGHRA] Excuse me. Is your name Bella?
- Yes.
- Oh, that's a beautiful name.
My name is Maghra.
[GASPS] My queen. [BREATHING HEAVILY]
- Are you scared, Bella?
- Yes.
I'm scared too.
But you know,
I have something that helps me.
Feel.
It is a sound wand.
And, you know,
it's not just any sound wand.
It is the queen's sound wand.
Now listen.
[METAL CLANGS, HIGH-PITCHED RINGING]
You know, I've been trying to find someone
who can hold it for me and keep it safe.
- You think you could do that?
- Yes.
[SIGHS] Good.
You bring it through the tunnel for me.
And if you get scared,
you just hit it against the wall,
and you listen to the sound.
And you remember
that you are an emissary of the queen.
All right?
[KISSES] Now, go on, brave girl.
- Maghra.
- Yes.
[BABA VOSS] My love.
You are a true queen, my love.
To your people. And to me.
[KISSING]
Come on.
[METAL CLANGS, HIGH-PITCHED RINGING]
At this rate,
we'll be underground for another day.
We go as slow as our slowest citizen.
Baba Voss, why don't you take up the rear?
Baba!
Baba?
- Where is he?
- He was just here a moment ago.
Stop!
Haniwa!
[MAGHRA] Baba?
- Where is he?
- Baba?
I don't know.
Dad!
Perhaps he's gone back
to help the stragglers.
- I'll send some scouts to find him.
- No.
He won't be there.
What do you mean? What did he tell you?
He told me nothing
because he knows I would've stopped him.
I know your father
better than I know myself, and so do you.
He's gone back.
- What?
- Why would he do that?
He can't defeat an entire army by himself.
He's gone to kill my sister.
- [KISSES]
- [WHINING]
[RANGER INHALES DEEPLY]
[SNIFFS]
You really do smoke too much.
No such thing.
Where are you headed?
I'm gonna hunt down that demon queen
and cut out her heart.
Aw, sounds like a terrible idea.
Can I come?
Sure.
Beware of wolves, Baba Voss.
We are the fucking wolves.
All right.