[LUCIEN] The Witchfinders
served you loyally
and without question
for all the years of your reign,
traveling to the farthest reaches
of the kingdom to rid the world of evil.
Then you rejected the divine doctrines,
tearing us apart
and forcing us into hiding.
Now you say you want us
to serve you once more,
as if all of that never happened?
Yes, that's right.
So I ask you now,
why the fuck would we do that?
Why not just execute you as a heretic
and be done with it?
Lucien is right.
I have caused you all pain and distress.
And for that,
you have my deepest apologies.
My sister, long believed to be dead,
was returned to me.
And in my joy,
and in my gratitude to the God Flame,
I opened my heart.
And my sister bewitched me.
She and her two witch children.
And I lost my way.
Just like you,
I have suffered dearly for it.
I've been in leg irons
for the last nine months.
They starved me. They tortured me.
They took my baby from me.
But it wasn't them.
No, they were merely instruments
of the God Flame herself.
Testing me.
Putting me through trials
to purify my heart once more,
so that I might reclaim my holy kingdom
for the righteous.
And why should we believe you now?
Why should you believe me?
Because I am your queen!
I am your queen,
ordained by God.
And no human will change that.
Not my sister, not the Trivantians.
And not you, Lucien.
It was I who declared war
on the Trivantians,
I who foretold our miraculous victory
at Greenhill Gap.
And since then, my execution
has been called for by Tamacti Jun,
by my sister and her corrupted council,
by the Trivantians.
And yet, somehow, none of them
could manage the simple task
of putting a blade to my throat,
nor could their chains hold me.
And the God Flame sent me out to find you.
You are soldiers with no country...
with no rightful claim to the crown.
One of two fates await you.
You'll either be hunted down
by my sister's army,
or become slaves to the Trivantians.
Why should you believe me?
Because I'm all you've got!
And I love you all!
I am going to take back
the throne of my father.
The God Flame has shown me the way.
And I ask you now.
No, I command you,
in her name, to fight by my side!
To reclaim our holy kingdom!
For God and for yourselves.
- My holy warriors!
- [SOLDIERS CHEERING]
- The true defenders of Paya!
- [CHEERING CONTINUES]
[FOOTSTEPS APPROACHING]
[KOFUN PANTING]
Haniwa.
[PANTING] Did you see him?
- Who?
- Harlan.
- He's out there with the rest of them.
- As a prisoner?
- I don't know, it didn't seem that way.
- Forget Harlan.
When this is over, I will deal with him.
Help me lock this door.
- [HANIWA] Okay.
- [GRUNTS]
All dead, sir.
All of them?
Who was it? Payan soldiers?
If so, none were killed here.
These are all our soldiers.
That doesn't seem likely.
Check the bombs and the children.
[MADDOX] Sir.
Set!
[SOLDIERS GRUNT]
[SMACKING CHEST]
Check the house.
- [SOLDIER] Sir!
- [SOLDIERS GRUNT]
[DOOR THUMPING]
[SOLDIER] The door is barricaded.
[CHUCKLES] Barricaded?
So we're not alone.
[CLICKING TONGUE]
Keep moving, keep moving.
Wren, I don't need you here.
Go find Haniwa.
I promised their brother
I'd keep them safe.
We don't have time to argue.
I'm staying.
Fine. You're last. Watch our backs.
[STAFF TAPPING]
[STAFF THUDS]
[MADDOX] Four more dead in the lab.
- And the bombs?
- Secure.
Huh.
So it's the children in the building?
The children didn't kill
two dozen soldiers. It's something else.
Maybe they have the children with them or...
[WHISTLES] Captain Armagon.
Tear these grounds apart.
Find those children.
[SMACKING CHEST]
- And Captain, we need them alive.
- [ARMAGON] Yes, sir.
Tormada, we came here for the bombs.
Let's take them and go.
As always, thinking too small.
Always in the moment, never ahead.
We've already lost Oloman.
Without the other sighted children,
we'll soon be out of bombs.
I didn't spend all that time developing
these explosives to lose my bomb builders.
- Charlotte.
- I hear them. How close?
Too close.
Over by the tree. Now. Go.
Come on. Get low. Get down.
Close your eyes.
[ARMAGON] You there.
We don't want to hurt the children.
Then walk away.
Kill her!
[GRUNTING, SCREAMING]
- [BLADES CLANGING]
- [GRUNTING, SCREAMING CONTINUE]
[ARMAGON GRUNTING, CHOKING]
- [GRUNTS]
- [CHOKING STOPS]
- [NONNI BREATHING HEAVILY]
- [SHEENA WHIMPERING]
Everyone okay? All heads accounted for?
[BREATHING SHAKILY] Yes.
[CHARLOTTE] Lu?
[PANTING] I'm good.
Okay. We keep moving.
Okay, come on. Always behind me.
- [SNAPPING]
- [SPEAKS INDISTINCTLY]
[TORMADA WHISTLES]
[WHISTLES]
[KNOCKING]
[TORMADA] I don't know who you are.
And frankly, I don't care.
But if you have my children in there,
then a deal can be made.
They're not your children.
[CHUCKLES] Sheva.
Look at you all grown up
and leading an insurrection.
- I'm impressed.
- Oh, fuck you!
[TORMADA] I don't wanna kill you, Sheva.
But I will if I have to.
You and your family.
Now, whoever's in there with you
may not know me, but you do.
So you know I'm coming through
these doors.
[THUMPING]
I know you better than you think, Tormada.
I know that voice.
Ranger. My old friend.
How I've missed our sessions together.
[RANGER] Yeah, I know!
That's why I gave you all those scars
to remember me by before I left.
Yes.
And I shall remember to keep you alive
long enough to regret that.
Big talk for such a little shit weasel!
His time will come. I promise you.
[TORMADA] Ranger. Are you still there?
No?
Who then am I negotiating with?
[BREATHES HEAVILY]
This is Baba Voss.
And I'm not negotiating.
Baba Voss.
Quite the band of outlaws
you've assembled, Sheva.
Oh, you've done me a great service.
Now I can kill them all at once.
Get these doors open now!
Baba Voss.
A momentary aggravation.
Brought on by your poor impulse control.
I'll admit I misjudged him.
Oh, you admit it. What a relief.
- Can I make a suggestion?
- Harlan...
You promised me he wouldn't speak.
Sheva and her family sold Baba Voss's
daughter to the Trivantians, okay?
- He has no love for them.
- [SCOFFS]
And judging by the arrows
in your soldiers,
I'd say his daughter is here with him.
And if his daughter's here,
you can bet your balls his son is too.
Give him time to understand he's trapped.
He'll give you the girl
to save his children, I guarantee it.
[TORMADA] Lord Harlan.
You might be of some use after all.
Baba Voss!
I understand you have
your children with you,
the legendary Haniwa and Kofun
of the battle of Greenhill Gap.
I don't have children, so I'm no expert,
but it seems to me you've got a habit
of putting them in harm's way.
Would you really let your children die
protecting the family
that sold your daughter to Edo?
Return Sheva and her siblings to me,
and I give you my word,
Haniwa and Kofun will live.
But if I have to come in and get them,
then everybody dies.
I'll give you some time to think about it.
[SIGHS]
I should give myself up.
It was my family that wronged you.
Let me go and make this right.
You were forced to work for that man.
I know him. You know him.
Has he done anything to make you think
that he would keep his word?
- No.
They're going to get through
that door eventually.
Yes, they will.
So let's be ready for them.
Is that a...?
[GLASS SHATTERS]
[SNIFFS, GROANS]
Son... [CLEARS THROAT] ...what is this?
- [SNIFFS]
- Ah, oil?
Uh, no, I think it's fuel.
It's like oil, but it burns faster.
And... And this one is... Argh!
Yeah, uh, it's a lamp.
[STAMMERS] How do I explain this to you?
Um, it... it brightens the dark
so we can see.
God Flame in your hand.
Uh, not quite,
but it does get really hot like fire.
So be careful.
[GRUNTS]
Barrel, grip, magazine...
[COCKS GUN]
...trigger.
Only put your finger on the trigger
when you're ready to fire.
And only point at
what you're willing to destroy.
[GLASS CRASHING, SHATTERING]
Ranger.
[GLASS SHATTERS]
I think we're good.
It's a good day for some killing.
All your talk about fighting
for no nation.
And yet here you are.
I'm not here for Pennsa, I'm here for you.
And you're not here for Pennsa either,
you're here for your family.
That's actually funny.
The fate of an entire kingdom
rests upon the shoulders
of two people
who couldn't care less about it.
[GLASS SHATTERS]
[SIGHS]
[RANGER] What is it?
- Huh?
- [SNAPPING]
I can hear your thoughts from over there.
[SIGHS] It's what Tormada said
about my children.
Oh.
You have spent your life protecting them.
Only to walk them into danger
again and again.
I've met your children.
They're no longer children.
They walk their own path now.
There comes a time when the choice
is no longer yours.
And that doesn't sit well with you.
[GROANS] No, it does not. [SIGHS]
No, it does not, because you are a man who
enjoys telling other people what to do!
Baba Voss...
we may very well die here.
Now, before we do,
there is something I must know.
How is it that I'm never able
to sneak up on you?
It's those giant balls
slamming up against your thighs.
Mmm.
Your left knee creaks every second step.
What?
It's how I can always hear you coming.
[CHUCKLES] Is that true?
Very true.
[CREAKING]
[SOLDIERS GRUNT]
- [SOLDIERS CHATTERING]
- [SOLDIER] Make a hole.
[GASPS, CHUCKLES]
[GASPING]
[CHUCKLES]
[BREATHING SHAKILY]
Shall we?
[VOMITING, PANTING]
[SPITS, COUGHS]
[GRUNTING]
[BREATHING HEAVILY]
[EXHALES SHARPLY]
Dad?
There's too many walls in there.
I just needed some fresh air.
[SIGHS DEEPLY]
Yeah, I guess Jerlamarel liked
to close himself off from the world.
It's what the ancestors did.
They thought
they were protecting themselves.
But they
were just locking themselves away.
They were afraid.
They were right to be.
Baba Voss, you're out of time.
Hand over the children.
Seems you misjudged them, Harlan.
Let's go.
- [GRUNTING]
- [BANGING]
You did all you could to save them.
I imagine it won't take very long now.
No. It's gonna take longer than you think.
[BANGING CONTINUES]
[SOLDIERS GRUNTING]
[CLANGING]
[GRUNTING CONTINUES]
No resistance.
[GLASS CRUNCHING]
[MUFFLED GASP]
[GRUNTS]
[GRUNTING]
[BLADE STABS]
[WOLF WHISTLE]
[GRUNTS]
[SOLDIERS GRUNTING]
Haniwa?
- Go, go, go, go.
- Okay.
[GLASS CRUNCHING, TINKLING]
[METAL SCRAPING]
[SOLDIER GRUNTS]
[BREATHING HEAVILY]
["WELCOME TO THE JUNGLE" PLAYING
THROUGH SPEAKERS]
[BREATHING SHAKILY]
[GRUNTS]
[SONG CONTINUES]
[GRUNTING]
[YELLS]
- How many did you get?
- You go first. How many did you get?
- Same time.
- Okay.
- Six.
- Seven. I win.
[SONG CONTINUES]
[MUSIC STOPS]
[HANIWA BREATHING SHAKILY]
- [GUNSHOTS]
- [GASPING]
[WHIMPERS, BREATHING SHAKILY]
Oh, no.
[HANIWA BREATHING SHAKILY]
Sheva.
[WHIMPERING]
[GASPING, PANTING]
[SOBS]
The ringing in your ears will stop soon.
Let's go.
[BREATHING SHAKILY]
[SHEVA] Haniwa.
The bombs?
- Ready to move.
- Follow me.
Set!
[SOLDIERS GRUNT]
[BREATHING SHAKILY]
[GRUNTS]
[GRUNTING]
- [ELECTRICAL BUZZING]
- [SOLDIERS GROANING]
[BUZZING STOPS]
[DISTANT WHISTLING]
What's happening?
You saved my life.
Now I'm gonna save yours.
- [WHIMPERS]
- Stay still. Stay quiet.
[WHISTLES]
You say... What is this?
[SHUSHES] Don't move. They're with me.
[GROANS]
- What have you done?
- I had to do this.
Guntar.
[GUNTAR] Harlan.
You're late.
[CHUCKLES] You're welcome.
Clear it up. We're moving out.
- [GRUNTS, PANTS]
- [GRUNTS]
- If you kill me, they will kill you.
- You betrayed me.
Yeah, you betrayed me first.
I offered you a new life.
Turns out I was kind of attached
to my last one.
We are going to destroy Pennsa
and everyone in it.
[BREATHING SHAKILY]
Please, Trovere. Please.
Don't make me do this.
- Trovere, please.
- [SCREAMS, GROANS]
- Oh, shit. I'm so sorry.
- [GROANING]
I'm so sorry. I'm so sorry.
I shouldn't have...
- [HARLAN BREATHING SHAKILY]
- [GASPING]
[TROVERE GROANS, BREATHES HEAVILY]
I'm so sorry.
[BREATHING HEAVILY]
You loved me, didn't you?
At least a little?
You know I did.
- [GROANING]
- You know I did. It's okay.
- You know I did.
- [GASPS]
[SHUSHES]
[DRAGGING, CLANGING]
Dad?
Dad? Dad?
Kofun. Kofun. [SIGHS]
- You're okay? Yeah?
- I'm good, Boy. You?
There were more.
There's not.
It's over.
Baba, I've checked all the dead.
Tormada's not here.
[BREATHING HEAVILY]
Fuck!
Harlan. Harlan!
Baba. Time's of the essence.
- We gotta get the... [GRUNTS]
- [GRUNTS]
[HANIWA] Papa. Let him go.
- You let this happen!
- [KOFUN] Dad!
I bought you time!
His men killed
the rest of the Trivantians.
- I don't trust you!
- I don't care!
- Where is Tormada?
- He's gone.
- [GRUNTS]
- [HARLAN] Fuck.
[SHEVA] And he took the bombs.
- Where did he go?
- Fuck! It doesn't matter where he went.
Fucking asshole. We know where he'll go.
Pennsa.
They can't be moving very quickly
if they've got those bombs with them.
- Let's go.
- [BABA VOSS] No, Kofun.
No. We are going after him.
[HARLAN]
There are numerous routes out of here.
Even if we do manage to track them,
they're gonna be well protected.
We're faster than them.
Which is why we need to get to Pennsa.
Raise the alarm. Meet them with an army.
- Harlan is right.
- What?
If we take them on again,
we will be defeated.
Look, Dad...
Kofun, you are feeling energy
from the fight.
But that will soon fade,
and your body will feel weak.
We need to rest up for a bit,
and we will move swiftly to Pennsa, okay?
I am not staying here.
You need a fresh bandage.
Okay? I can smell it. Trust me.
[SNAPPING]
Make sure they find her in her house.
Nobody needs to know she's a part of this.
Understood.
- [SIGHS]
- You're not going with them?
Nah. I figured you'd need the company.
You know,
this likely won't end well for us.
[CHUCKLES] Tell me something I don't know.
[CLICKING TONGUE]
[SWORD THUDS]
[LIQUID SLOSHING]
[BREATHING DEEPLY]
[GRUNTING]
[SIGHS, SNIFFS]
[SNIFFS]
[BREATHING HEAVILY]
- Kofun!
- Stop!
- We have to stop him.
- [KOFUN] No.
Kofun... this is our legacy.
It's Jerlamarel's legacy. It's not ours.
This is more than him. It's more than us.
This place has destroyed the lives
of everyone we've loved!
Okay? And these bombs might just be
the end of everything.
You're not burning bombs! Are you?
There are centuries of knowledge
in there, you...
- I can't let him burn it. I won't let him.
- No, no.
[GRUNTS]
- [SCREAMS, GRUNTS]
- Stop!
[BREATHES HEAVILY]
You can't stop him.
[HANIWA GASPING]
- [GUNSHOT]
- [GASPS]
[BOTH BREATHING SHAKILY]
Are you serious?
This place is all that we have left.
It will keep us safe.
Says the one holding a gun.
I can't let you take this from me.
Haniwa, it's me.
Drop the gun.
Please? Drop it.
[HANIWA GRUNTING, WHIMPERING]
Are you serious?
You're actually gonna try and shoot me?
Your own brother!
What the hell? You're gonna shoot me?
[BOTH GRUNTING]
Come here!
- [GRUNTS]
- Get over...
[BOTH GRUNTING]
- You can't do this! Stop! Stop it!
- [WHIMPERING] No! No!
[GRUNTING]
Stop! Now! It's over!
Stop, it's done. It's over!
Haniwa! Just stop it! Both of you!
We have to get out of here!
- [CRYING] What did you do?
- [BABA VOSS] Haniwa.
- Haniwa. I know. I'm sorry.
- [HANIWA CRYING]
We will die if we do not leave now.
I'm sorry.
I miss our home.
Take these children to safety
and then go there.
I will make my way back to you.
[CHUCKLES] Don't become a Payan.
[CHUCKLES] I belong to no nation.
You belong to me.
[SIGHS]
Be strong, Haniwa.
This place...
with all of its knowledge... [STAMMERS]
It was our way forward.
If I know you, you'll find another way.
But you'll come back?
Missing me already?
[CHUCKLES] No.
[CHUCKLING]
A little bit.
[SIGHS] I'll come back.
Just do your best
to stay alive until I do. Okay?
I will.
Okay.
[INHALES SHARPLY] Charlotte.
[HANIWA SOBBING]
[CHARLOTTE SIGHS]
Okay. Get out of here.
Okay! Let's get going.
Hayah, Hoveh, always behind me.
Sheva! Always behind them.
Haniwa.
Thank you for saving my family.
Guess they were my family too.
That means we're sisters.
[CHUCKLES]
I'm sorry about your home.
It's okay.
There are others.