.
- Previously on "Good Girls."
- We're gonna rob that store.
- Yes!
- Oh, dear God.
- You get to help
your little girl.
And you get to take care
of this custody.
And I get to save my family.
- Ladies and gentlemen,
this is a robbery.
Get out of the way!
[grunts]
- We got more than
the 30 grand.
- Why does a grocery store
even have
this kind of money on hand?
- Because it's hella shady!
- We didn't know you
owned the store.
- You just gonna pay me back,
is all.
And right quick, too.
With interest.
- How many chicks
have a tramp stamp
that says,
"All you need is love?"
Cops came around,
but I didn't tell them.
- What do you want?
- I just get so lonely.
- Stop, my sister is here.
No! [grunts]
- That's how you like it,
right, tough girl?
- Get off of her!
- Whoa, hey.
- Boomer.
Boomer, please.
We can get you money.
- Oh, no.
I'm turning you in.
- [screams]
[thuds]
- Oh, no!
[both screaming]
- Is he...
- No.
- Are you sure?
[Dena Deadly's
"Hello Sunshine"]
*
- Mama.
Mama.
*
Mom!
The TV's broke.
- Broken.
Uh, and no it's not.
Um...
- When's Daddy coming home?
- Just hit, uh, input twice,
and satellite, and menu.
- I need help with math.
- [sighs] Why can't I help you?
- 'Cause you can't do math.
- Papa, he-a gotta the donuts!
[children shouting]
- Yay!
- Hi, guys!
Hey, grab your bags.
Quick, quick, quick, quick.
This train's a-leaving
the station-a.
- Fun dad.
- Sad dad.
I miss my kids.
- You've been gone two nights.
*
- I miss you.
- Kenny goes to sleepaway
camp for longer.
Let's keep it together.
- What about the lawn?
- I can push a mower.
- At least let me show you
the remote.
- Input, satellite, menu.
- That's not even close.
- I'll get there.
- You got a little, uh...
On your face.
It kinda looks like blood.
- Uh, no, it's pizza.
Go.
Don't leave the kids alone.
*
- * People always
moving fast *
* And never get the
chance to stop *
* Hey hey hey
* Waiting for
the day to pass *
* And looking at the clock
tick tock *
* It never lasts
* All I need to win the day
* Is shining in
the big blue sky *
* Ooh la la
la la la la *
- Hey.
What's with the fuzz?
- We got robbed, yo.
Get woke.
- Yeah, but isn't that, like,
old news?
- They had guns, Annie.
I threw my neck out.
- Must have been really scary.
- In my job,
the key is to think of yourself
as already dead so there's
nothing left to be afraid of.
- Wow.
- Hey, have you seen Boomer?
- Why?
- The cops wanna
talk to him again,
but he never came in
for his shift.
- No, I haven't seen him.
[suspenseful music]
*
- They're looking for him.
- Do they know he's missing?
- I don't know.
- Or is it just
about the robbery?
- I don't know!
- What did you tell them?
- That you bashed his head in
with a whiskey bottle.
What do you think I told them?
- So, I got $18 in tips.
I had to sell Stan's favorite
set of cufflinks for $250.
Sara is playing her first
soccer game
in a T-shirt instead
of the team uniform.
Which gives us a
grand total of $343.
Which means we now owe
$59,657
to the violent street gang.
Please tell me you did better.
What's going on?
- There's been a development.
- What kind of development?
What am I looking at right now?
What am I even looking
at right now?
- [screams]
[grunts]
[wailing]
- He knows about the store.
- He was going to the cops.
- Does he know about the gang,
too?
- Hell no.
That's way above his pay grade.
He's like the definition
of middle management.
Oh, and he also tried
to rape me.
- What?
- That is absolutely true.
- He's a dick and a rapist.
- It was self-defense.
- Self-defense.
- Definitely.
- Yes.
- How is hogtying a man,
climbing him 12 feet
above the earth,
and hiding him in a treehouse
self-defense?
- Okay, you know what?
You weren't there.
- You're damn right,
I wasn't there.
- We are feeding him.
- Oh, good.
Well, you know.
- What else were we
supposed to do?
If he goes to the cops,
we're screwed.
- No, we're screwed
because of the gang
that is going to kill us
if we don't get
them their money.
- Okay, she's right.
First things first.
- Okay, well,
I make $9 an hour,
so just give me
a couple decades.
- Okay, who do we know?
- To rob?
- To ask for money, Annie.
- Somebody rich who would care
if I was dead?
I mean, I wish.
What?
Who?
No.
- What do you mean, "No?"
- I mean, "No."
No, no, no.
- Annie, this is life or death.
- I choose death.
Give me death!
[rock music plays]
*
Which one of these houses
is your dad's?
- How come you never remember?
- 'Cause all these cheesy-ass
houses look the same.
- It's that one.
- Oh.
*
- Oh, oh.
Hey, Nance.
[laughs]
[brakes squeaking]
[sighs]
Why is she always in scrubs?
Isn't she, like,
a facialist or something?
- Aesthetician.
- [clicks tongue]
All right.
Let's do this.
- Um, would you mind taking
your shoes off?
Uh, we're trying to keep it
cleanish in here.
Hey, how do you feel
about tacos?
We could do a little cheese,
a little pico de gallo
- Yeah, I feel good.
- Oh, yay!
Fun!
Okay, uh, I am off to work.
- Good luck saving lives.
- [laughs]
Love you.
- Love you.
- What you making?
Pico de gallo?
- Yeah.
- Um...
I have sort of a favor to ask.
- How much?
- Just, like, 60.
- All right.
- Grand.
It'll be more like
a loan this time.
I'll totally pay you back.
- What is the matter with you?
- It's not like you can't
afford it.
Look at this place.
There's orchids everywhere.
You have an in-ground pool.
- What do you need
that much money for?
- For a very good reason.
- You, uh, hire a lawyer yet?
- Do you actually think
I would ask you for money
to fight you for custody?
- Are ya?
- I wasn't,
but now that
you're accusing me of it,
maybe I should.
So, can I have the money?
- No, you freak!
- Why do you have
to be such a dick?
- Because you're insane.
I mean, you never think
anything through.
This is exactly why Nancy and I
should have custody,
because you are not stable.
- Yeah, because who cares about
real love and connection
when you can make a child
a fresh pico de gallo?
- Why do you keep saying that?
- Thank you for making me
completely humiliate myself
for no reason.
These are cold.
- They're not mine.
- Eww.
[spits]
What do we do now?
- I have no idea.
[Patti & The Emblems'
"Mixed Up, Shook Up Girl"]
* Am I crying because
I'm happy *
- What is it?
- Are you okay?
- Stay here.
- * Or am I crying because
I'm blue without you *
* Yeah yeah
[dramatic music]
*
- I've got a question for you.
The two, two,
and two meal deal,
How much is that?
- $7.95.
- Yeah, see, but if I order
two hot cakes,
two sausages, and two eggs
a la carte, it's cheaper.
*
- You get a garnish.
- Like parsley or something?
[laughing]
*
- It's an orange slice.
- You tell the owner
that ain't right?
*
Cheating people like that?
- We're gonna get
you your money.
All of it.
I swear.
- That would be great.
- We need more time to get it.
*
Thank you.
- I'll come by tomorrow.
1:00 good for you?
Your friend's house.
You can subtract the coffee.
[foreboding music]
*
- How much?
- $10 for the clubs,
$75 for the rest.
So, what'd he do?
- [sighs]
- Eesh.
Something bad.
- It's real sterling.
- $50.
You can keep the picture.
- Okay, I have to take home
at least two grand
for all of this.
- Okay.
- It was his great
grandmother's.
- How much do you hate him?
[knocking]
- Mr. Boland?
Mr. Martin is here inquiring
about the 2015 Mustang.
- Oh, okay.
- Hi.
- Hey, how you doing?
- Good, how are you?
- Everything's good.
- So, uh, what are you
driving now?
- A 2007 Celica G.T.
- Ooh, the 'Stang's
quite an upgrade.
Fully loaded.
I mean, she handles
like a dream.
- She's gorgeous.
- Yeah, right?
[laughs]
- My Celica's been good to me,
but she's pushing 100,000
miles, so...
- She's dependable.
- Sad to see her go,
but...
I think it's time to
change things up a bit.
- I thought the
exact same thing.
- I'm sorry?
- You know, you see something
shiny and new
and you just forget
about what you got.
Once you upgrade,
those memories,
they come back and they--
they haunt you.
You know like, uh,
road trip with the kids.
- Oh, I don't have kids.
- The fun stuff you did in
the backseat in high school.
- I haven't had it that long,
so...
- The crazy thing is,
you thought you were the one
sick of her,
and now you'd do anything
to get her back.
- You--you do sell cars here,
right?
- Don't give up on your Celica.
- Maybe...
Maybe if we test drove it--
- You'll regret it.
- Yeah, uh, okay.
[cheering]
- Come on, baby.
Let's go, let's hustle!
- Pace yourself!
Don't be a hero!
- Run, baby!
Get the ball!
- You want some water?
Time out!
Water break!
- [groaning]
She needs water.
- Come on, girls.
Get back in the game.
- Excuse me?
Can we keep it together please?
- She shouldn't overdo it.
- She's doing great.
She's fine.
Look at her.
- Yeah, I see.
And what about when we can't
afford that damn truck anymore?
What happens then?
- Cops get real good insurance.
- You're not a cop yet.
- Yeah, I will be.
- Yeah, in six months, babe.
- Okay.
Okay, look.
I know you're not used to this.
- Used to what?
- Neither am I.
I mean, we haven't been here
in a long time.
- What are you talking about?
- This.
Right here, right now.
It's what winning feels like,
babe.
Our girl's strong enough
to run and play in the sunshine
for the first time in years.
I don't know about you,
but I'm gonna drink
in this moment.
- Fine, drink up.
- Oh, I'm gonna need a little
bit more than that.
- Excuse me?
- I'm gonna need you to say it.
- You're crazy.
- Say it with me.
We are winning.
- We're winning.
- Yeah, I'm sure you can do
a lot better than that.
- We are winning.
- Mean it.
Come on, baby.
- We're winning.
- Yes,
that's what I'm talking about!
- We're winning!
- Yes!
Come on, baby!
Let's go!
We're winning, baby!
We are winning!
Let's go!
- No, we're not!
- I'm sorry, baby.
I know.
I know, just stay focused,
baby!
Stay focused.
- We are winning.
- Get back inside, coach.
My bad.
Stay in the game, baby.
Stay in the game.
[melancholy music]
*
- That's $13.
- You know what?
This is some bull right here.
Them coming at us with guns,
dropping by my job,
uh-uh.
We have families.
We have children.
We have lives.
And we gotta end this now.
- Great.
How?
- The way I see it,
we got two issues
we need to take care of.
One is your boy
up in that tree house.
- Excuse me,
he's not my boy.
- And the money.
- Yeah, so two birds,
one stone.
Y'all are already getting
charged for kidnapping.
We might as well ransom
his ass, too.
.
- [slurping]
[grunts]
Just let me go already.
- Yeah, so you can run
to the cops?
- It's not like you're
gonna kill me.
- And how do you know?
- 'Cause you don't
have the guts.
You're not killers.
You're just a dumb
checkout girl.
And you're, what,
a housewife?
Thought you'd pull a fast one?
Hmm?
Make a quick buck?
Now you guys are freaking out
because you are in
way over your head.
- Just shut up.
- Only reason I'm up here
is 'cause you don't know
what to do with me.
- Just shut up!
- You have no idea.
'Cause girls like you,
you never think things through.
- No, he's right.
You do do this.
I mean, you've done this
your whole life.
I mean,
you make these big messes,
and then you just expect
everyone else to clean it up.
And then you just ignore it.
For hours.
Hours become days,
and days become weeks.
- Yes, and weeks sometimes
turn into months.
You're so right.
I do do that.
Mmm.
Fatal flaw.
- You can't leave me
here forever.
- Oh, we wouldn't mean to.
- No, right, but like you said,
we don't have the guts
to kill you.
And it's just we're in
so far over our heads,
I feel like it's gonna take us
a really, really long time
to figure out what
to do with you.
- And by then,
the animals
or just Michigan winter
would probably
would probably just take care
of it for us.
*
- I'm just a dumb
checkout girl.
- And I'm just
an idiot housewife.
- His grandma's loaded.
- And she doesn't trust banks,
so she keeps all of her cash
at home like Scrooge McDuck.
- Where should we
have her bring it?
- Well, they always do the drop
in a park in "Law & Order,"
so how about Beeman?
- All right, check out this app
I downloaded onto his phone.
[beeps]
- We have your grandson.
Deliver $60,000 to Beeman
Park by 5 p.m., or he's dead.
- Is that Sean Connery?
- No, it's just Scottish Man.
Here.
- Sounds hot.
- What about...
- [high-pitched voice]
We have your grandson.
Deliver $60,000--
- No, no.
- She wouldn't get that.
- Okay, uh, let's see here.
- [robot voice]
We have your grandson.
Deliver $60,000 to Beeman
Park by 5 p.m., or he's dead.
- That's good.
- Yeah?
- I think that's good.
- Yeah.
- All right.
Whew, okay.
[phone trilling]
- You've reached
Marion Petersen.
I'm not home right now.
Please leave a message.
- Try later.
[The Girls' "Psycho"]
- You've reached
Marion Petersen.
- * Baby
- You've reached
Marion Petersen.
I'm not home right--
*
- You've reached Marion--
- [groans]
- I'm not home--
- Marion, where you at?
- [sighs]
- * I wish I was dead
- I mean,
if she's out for the night...
*
- Everyone has to use
their own toothbrush.
And no one goes
in the backyard tonight.
We just sprayed for bugs,
and it's covered
in very toxic chemicals.
I won't be late.
I just have a thing with
my sister and a friend.
- Oh, a girls night.
- Yeah.
[Haiku Hands' "Not About You"]
- * I'm gonna tear up
the lexicon *
* With a hexagon and
my sexy thong on *
* No matter where your
head is gone *
* Or where you're from,
I'ma take you on *
* It's not about you
- Ugh, of course.
It's a security door.
We don't have a code.
- All right,
will you just be cool?
- I hate it when you say that.
- This is so much easier
than the grocery store.
She's not even home.
- Okay, here we go.
Here we go.
- * It's not about you
* Shut up
It's not about me either *
* I am my sister's keeper
* Chill
* It's not about you
* Shut up
It's not about me either *
* It's us verse
the grim reaper *
* Chill chill chill
* You look like a tortoise
Your issues are enormous *
* In my eyes you're flawless
I'm gonna share my cake *
* Whoo
* It's time to drop
- You're gonna rake through
with the tumblers.
- Go back to the part with
the second pin thingie.
- I'm trying.
- Stop flipping it around.
Just hold it one...
- What is taking so long?
- It's buffering.
- That unlimited data plan
sounds real nice
right about now, doesn't it?
- Can I help you?
- Marion!
You're up and about!
That's great!
We were told that you
would be bedridden
and to just let ourselves in.
- Who are you?
- We're the volunteers.
Medicare automatically
enrolls you
to receive a number
of services.
Tidying up, meal prep,
companionship,
whatever you need.
Should we come back
another time?
Or is this a bad time?
- Well, I suppose not.
- You are an incredible liar.
- Right?
- Thank you.
- * It's not about you
* Shut up
* It's not about you
.
[calm music]
*
- Got any family in town,
Marion?
- My husband passed last year.
- I'm so sorry.
- Such is life.
We had 40 years.
Five children.
Sixteen grandchildren.
- Wow, that must keep you busy.
- Every one of them moved away.
Can you believe that?
They're just too into
their own lives.
Except Leslie.
He's my little boy.
[laughs]
Oh, and this is his fiancee.
Isn't she pretty?
- Very.
Jessica Alba?
- I know what you're thinking,
but she's only half.
How about some of this
no-calorie lemonade?
- Marion,
where's your restroom?
- Oh.
[chain pulling]
- [grunts]
- [screams]
[chugging]
- [screaming]
[Toto's "Africa"]
- * It's gonna take a lot
to take me away from you *
- Help me!
- * There's nothing that
a hundred men or more *
* Could ever do
* I bless the rains
down in Africa *
* Gonna take some time to do
the things we never had *
* Ooh
*
* It's gonna take a lot
to drag me away from you *
* There's nothing that
a hundred men or more *
* Could ever do...
[unsettling music]
*
[cell phone buzzes]
- Are the kids okay?
- Yeah, they're fine.
[indistinct chatter]
- No, it's input, satellite,
some--
You know what?
Tell them there is no TV.
It's too late.
- Okay, but the kids are--
- No, what--what--
Wait, wait.
What's that noise?
- No, that noise.
Where's that coming from?
[vacuum whirring]
- Be sure that you really get
back in that corner, now.
[vacuum whirring]
- You gonna make the white girl
clean something?
Or does she just get to eat?
- Mmm, Doug looks
so skinny here.
Oy, Gloria.
Are you ever not pregnant?
[laughs]
Right here, hand me the--
- We've gotta go.
Now.
- Sorry, Marion.
You didn't take it?
- I told you,
Dean is in my backyard.
I can't do this.
- No, we're doing it.
Stop.
- Why didn't you
take the money?
- I couldn't do it.
- You couldn't rob the sweet
old racist lady?
- She had this life.
She had this full life
that she loved.
Come on, we're robbing
lonely old people?
This is who we are now?
- What we are is screwed
because you choked.
- Beth!
We needed that money!
- I know.
I'm sorry.
I gotta go.
- Okay, yeah, we'll just
talk about this tomorrow
when we're all dead!
[sighs]
- I told you not
to mow the lawn.
- Well, good thing I did,
'cause guess what
I found back there?
- What?
- Moles.
Those tiny little rat thingies
that build tunnels.
We got them, like,
really bad.
- No, I have them.
I have the moles.
- Okay.
- In my backyard.
In my house that I
paid the mortgage for,
and am perfectly capable of
handling all the aspects of.
Including the lawn.
And the remote control.
And--
- What happened to your ring?
- I took it off.
- For how long?
- I don't know.
- Oh.
You can throw chewed-up
bubble gum
into the mole hole and...
They'll choke and die.
- That's terrible.
- I know.
- Dean?
Thank you.
- It's the middle
of the night.
- I'm making lasagna.
- In the middle of the night?
- You have to reheat at 350,
okay?
- What, do you plan
on going somewhere?
- Where would I be going?
- You tell me.
You don't wanna act like
you're not gonna be around
to feed us no more.
- Oh.
An island sounds good.
Island.
With one of those huts, mmm.
Where you could see the ocean
through the floor.
- Hmm, yeah.
- [laughs]
I might come.
- I'm sorry,
it's my imaginary island.
- An island for what?
- I mean,
you can make conjugal visits.
- [laughs]
[kisses]
[sighs]
Hey.
[stammers]
You'd tell me if something
was going on, right?
- Baby...
- Yes?
- I'm just making lasagna.
[kisses]
- Why don't you come on
back to bed?
And bring some of that
sauce with you.
[both laughing]
[somber music]
*
- Where were you?
- Oh, honey, it's so late.
Why aren't you in bed?
- I woke up,
and you were gone.
- Where was Kristen?
- She's always sexting
her boyfriend.
*
- It's scary when you wake up
and I'm gone, huh?
*
Well, there's something you
need to know about mommies.
Sometimes they go away.
But guess what?
- What?
- They always come back.
No matter what.
Okay?
*
Come on.
Did Kristen teach you
that word?
Sexting?
- Mm-hmm.
*
- Well, I'm glad
I gave her a raise.
*
- Um, she sleeps with
a nightlight.
- What?
- Sadie.
She sleeps with a nightlight,
okay?
- She's 11 years old.
- Yes, I know that.
That's why you just turn it on
and you walk out of the room
so you don't embarrass her.
- What time is it?
- And she doesn't like
to swallow pills,
so you have to make sure
that you get her
the gummy vitamins, okay?
- Wha--what are you doing here?
- And she's gonna need to start
wearing a bra soon,
so don't get her anything
too girly.
Just get her something like
tank tops or something
so that she can
have them layered.
- Annie, Annie, Annie,
Annie, Annie.
- I'm not gonna fight you
for custody.
- Seriously?
Why--why not?
- Because I'm dealing
with some stuff.
And...
I just can't.
And she's a kid,
you know.
- Uh-huh.
- So don't make her take off
her shoes in her own house.
.
- How much is there?
- Same as yesterday.
- Costa Rica?
- Bugs.
- We cannot run.
We have families.
- All right.
China.
- Earthquakes.
- That's your big issue
with China?
- You have a better problem
- [scoffs] Language barrier,
human rights violations,
communistic rule.
- We're staying here,
and we are facing this.
- Air pollution.
Swine flu.
I mean--
- They don't have Indian food.
I need to go someplace
where they have Indian food.
- India?
- God, no.
- Who keeps IM'ing you?
- Oh, I put Hans up on ebay.
- Who's Hans?
- The little drummer boy
I stole from Boomer's granny.
- Annie, that is an heirloom.
- Who's she gonna
pass it down to?
Alba?
Or her only one quarter Mexican
grandchildren?
[beeping]
- Holy mother.
- What?
- Hans is up to eight g's.
- Shut the front door.
- Did you take anything else?
- You're short.
- No, we're not.
- Yeah, you are.
- Actually...
We're over.
See, these are super
rare collectables.
- Treasures.
- Yes, sister, you are correct.
That's a better word for these.
Because these super
rare treasures
go for 10 to 15 g's on ebay.
How much leg work is there,
right?
But the truth is,
it's very little.
Because we have done the lion's
share of the work for you.
Ruby?
- These are the usernames
and passwords
for our ebay accounts.
Plus auction tips to maximize
your profits.
- You want me
to sell your dolls?
- Tell him about Hans.
- Ooh, our little drummer boy.
The pride of Hamburg.
[laughs]
You see, Hans here is one
of only 12 in the entire--
[shatters]
all: [screaming]
11 in the world.
- This some kind
of joke to you?
I'm done playing with you guys.
[shattering]
- [screams]
What are they doing?
- Making it look like
a home invasion.
- So they can kill us?
- Please don't do this!
- Wait, please, wait!
We can get you the money,
I swear!
Please!
- We have families!
- Please!
- We have kids!
[both crying and screaming]
- Please, don't!
[crying]
[suspenseful music]
*
- You're an idiot.
- [crying] Beth!
*
- What, are you gonna
blow our brains out
all over the room?
'Cause that's how it works,
right?
Someone shorts you,
and they get tossed out
like trash?
And no one cares,
and no one even notices.
Your problem this time is
that's not us.
We're normal people.
*
We pay our taxes and...
We take our kids
to P.F. Chang's,
and we take orange slices
to soccer games.
*
And when bad things happen
to good people,
everyone else goes crazy.
It's all over the news.
And there are all these
hashtags and movements.
Because if it could
happen to us,
it could happen to anyone.
So if you wanna invite
all that attention
over a few grand,
then you're not the smart
businessman you think you are.
Now, roll the dice.
Tell him to pull the trigger.
*
See what happens.
- Please, please.
*
Oh, my God.
[heavy breathing]
- [crying]
Sweet Jesus.
[creaking]
[kicking]
This was my favorite
sangria bowl.
- Well, it could have
been your face.
- L'chaim.
To life.
- Dude.
[kicking]
- Hey, it looks like
we got a survivor.
[kicking]
[grunting]
[laughs]
[grunts]
- Split three ways,
it's two weeks plus overtime.
- [grunts]
[tense music]
.
- Would you go faster?
- I'm going the speed limit.
- Are you joking?
- I'm not gonna get a ticket.
- Why, you don't wanna mar
your perfect record
of armed robbery
and kidnapping?
- I mean, he couldn't have
gone that far.
His hands are tied.
- I don't know.
I mean, remember that
Gulf War vet
on our block growing up?
He ran marathons with both his
arms blown off.
- How is that helpful?
- You brought it up!
Damn, that was amazing, though.
- I mean, can we just
find this guy?
- Yes, I'm trying!
- Then what?
We shove him back up
in the treehouse?
Like Rapunzel?
- Oh, there he is!
- Where does he think
he's going?
- Oy, this is hard to watch.
- Oh, okay.
- Oof.
- All right,
I got this.
- Wait, what are you gonna do?
- I got this.
- [groans]
[crying, panting]
- [scoffs]
Okay.
- Wait, what are you doing?
What are you doing?
What are you--
- She's gonna cut
his penis off.
- No, no, no, no, no, no.
- She's gonna cut
his penis off!
- There we go.
- [screams]
What--
- Yikes.
- [groaning]
- Mmm-hmm.
Oh!
[camera shutter clicks]
- What are you doing?
- Texing a picture
of your penis.
- Why are you doing that?
- Actually, you're doing it.
It's your phone.
- And there.
Sent.
To my daughter.
Who is 11.
- No, no, no, no, no, no, no!
- Oh, yeah.
- Wait, why?
- Well, because now,
if you go to the cops,
so will I.
Have a nice night.
- Wait, wait!
No!
- I don't get it.
What did she do?
[cell phone rings]
- Oh.
Oh, hell no.
- [giggles]
- Really?
- [laughs]
- You're a sick,
sick woman.
- It's true.
- Will someone tell me
what happened?
- I mean, it was either you
or my 11-year-old.
You know?
- Hostage peen.
- [laughs]
- Can we go?
- Told you I had it.
[Monarchs'
"Come On and Move Me"]
- * Stepped into the garden
after midnight *
* For a taste
of some white light *
* Like I had had before
*
* Talked to the master
at the prayer gate *
* Sat at his feet
and his stone cape *
* And tried to breathe
his theme *
* I was ready to move
I was ready to move *
* Come on come on
and move me *
*
* We met and shared a bottle
at the J.Clyde *
* I liked his mind
I liked his sweet smile *
* And things were fresh
and new *
*
* That summer night he led me
to the river *
* After the swim
I sat and shivered *
* I waited for the kiss
* I was ready to move
I was ready to move *
* Come on come on
and move me *
- Feeling good,
feeling strong.
I'm taking requests.
- Minions!
- TV on.
Streaming box on.
Input one.
Two.
Arrow up, arrow left.
Select.
all: Yay!
- [laughs]
- Where's your brother?
- Outside.
*
- ...And gave one
half to Kyle.
Kyle kept eight of the Jujubes
and gave the last ten to Kim.
How many Jujubes did Jen
take from Sam?
- 36.
You know how many she'd have
taken if Sam had a gun, though?
- How?
- Zero.
- Whoa.
- Kenny, go inside.
- I don't wanna.
- Now.
- But your friend's helping me.
- Stop with the homework
and go inside and watch TV.
Now.
- Listen to Mama, Kenny.
- You know you should really
get him a tutor, right?
- You want the rest
of the money?
We'll get it.
- No, let's forget all that.
- Then why are you here?
[Santigold's
"Disparate Youth"]
- I keep thinking
about what you said.
About being a basic bitch
and whatnot.
- That's not exactly
what I said.
- Maybe there's something
you could help me out with.
*
- What's that?
- You ladies got passports?
- * Don't look ahead
There's stormy weather *
*
* Another roadblock
in our way *
*
* But if we go
we go together *
*
* Oh we said our dreams
will carry us *
* And if we don't fly
we will run *
* Now we push right past
to find out *
* Or either win what
they have lost *