.
- Previously
on "Good Girls"...
- I don't know what you've
gotten me involved in
but it's something super shady.
- What do you want?
- She's blackmailing us.
- To the tune of $10,000.
- We're gonna be shutting
things down for a while.
- How long?
- I don't know.
- What about us?
- I guess we go legit
for a while.
- Welcome to Dandy Donuts.
What can I get for you?
- I would suggest
that we put Sara
on a list for a transplant.
- Who the hell are you?
- I'm a friend
of your friend's.
- What's that?
- It's that fool we arrested.
He's ours now.
- They have him.
The FBI, and he's talking.
He is talking to them.
- We have to tell Rio.
- If we tell him,
he'll kill him.
- It's that kid or us.
- Tag, you're it!
- Tag!
[soft music]
- So, we're murderers now?
- Yeah, straight up execution
is what it is.
- Cold-blooded killing
of a man.
- His name is Eddy.
He likes his mom,
vintage watches,
and Mexican food.
What, I'm just trying to,
like, humanize him before we--
- We're not killing anyone.
- What do you call it then?
- We're just telling
a gangbanger
that his boy's been flipped
by the cops.
- Yeah, and you know
they're not
going to couples therapy
to work it out.
- The second we open
our mouths--
- You just want to sit here
and let him tell the FBI
all about us?
We're looking at 20 or more,
and I'm not doing that.
[children chattering]
- [laughing] You're it.
[children laughing]
- Let me just say...
It's one thing
to wash fake cash
or rob a grocery store.
But there is a line here,
and if you cross it,
you can't come back.
- Then we don't come back.
- Have yourself a Dandy day.
- Thanks. You too.
- Welcome to Dandy Donuts.
What can I do for you
on this Dandy day?
- [muffled chatter]
- Two decafs
and a glaze please!
- Stepping it up.
- Yeah, thanks.
- You know, I think you're
ready for the night shift.
It pays an extra
75 cents an hour.
- I have two kids, so.
Can I please get
a large coffee and a glaze?
Come on, pep in
your step, folks!
- Okay, okay.
Here you go.
- Dude, this is a promotion.
[cell phone dings]
- [sighs]
[gasps]
- What!
Oh, my God! Oh, my God!
- So I take that as a yes?
- [yells excitedly]
- La-ding!
- [gasps]
- [laughs] Bing, I upgraded.
Okay? It's got
the three-day battery,
so it's not gonna
short out on you.
You're not gonna drop
any phone calls unless
you put that thing in
the toilet bowl or something.
- Do not do that.
- Please don't do that.
- What do I get?
- A hug.
- And you get a very
important job, little money,
because you need to make sure
that your sister
has got this phone, okay?
Because we have
to be able to be reached
by the hospital day or night.
- Can I get Instagram on this?
- Forget Instagram, baby doll.
You got a big ass
healthy kidney coming!
- Top of the list!
♪ New kidney, new kidney
- ♪ Top of the list, top, top
- ♪ New kidney, ah, ah
♪ New kidney, hey, hey,
hey, hey, hey ♪
- Can I go do my homework?
- Oh, my God, I love you.
You're such a nerd.
Yes, go ahead.
- Go ahead, baby.
- Uh-uh-uh!
- Yeah, but see,
what's going on here?
- Okay. Okay.
- [sighs]
- I mean...
- I know!
- It's happening.
- It's all happening, babe.
- So if this call comes--
- When
the call comes baby, when.
- How are we gonna pay for it?
- Insurance is gonna
cover some.
- It's gonna be
almost 100 Gs out of pocket.
- Hm.
[suck teeth, sighs]
I know.
[sighs loudly]
Have you heard
from corporate yet?
- What?
- No, I'm just saying
it'd be real good if, you know,
you got your business
started back up.
- Yeah.
It would.
- [sighs]
Oh!
Oh, God, I'm sorry.
I'm sorry, sorry!
[door shuts]
- What are you
even doing here?
- What are you even doing here?
- I live here.
- I mean, kinda.
- It's--it's my house.
- How long are you gonna stay?
- Look, just stop, please.
- Sadie is with Greg.
- Oh.
Well, sorry...
That's sucks.
I didn't know.
- Yeah.
And Bethie said I could
stay here until I feel better.
- That's great.
- Mm-hmm.
- Mi casa, su casa.
- Gracias, hermano.
- So how you feeling right now?
- [inhales deeply]
Not so good, Deansie.
[whispers] Settle in.
- Hm.
- Uh-oh.
What happened?
- Oh, nothing, just get some
- We're just having a chat
- quality time together--
- We've got to go.
We've got that thing
- Bye.
- Y'all ready to be back
in business or what?
- What do you have in mind?
- Just need you to go pick up
a truck for me.
- In Canada?
- No.
Right here.
Parked in a garage
off I-75.
- What's in it?
- Yeah, you ain't got
to worry about that.
Just go get it,
and we're good to go.
I thought y'all would be
more excited than this.
But, hey, if you don't need
to get back to work then--
- Oh, we do. We do.
- There's something we need
to talk about though.
- Yeah, uh, none
of us drive stick.
I mean, everything's automatic,
so I just never learned.
I don't know
about you guys, but...
You know what?
It'll be fine.
It's not an 18-wheeler so
problem raised, problem solved.
- Problem not solved though
because there's
the other problem.
- Which is a
much bigger problem.
- Are you bitches trying
to do this or not?
- Hey, we got 99 problems but
this bitch ain't one, okay?
So we're in like Flynn.
Where the keys at?
[upbeat music]
♪
- We're gonna get
pinched the second
we pull that thing
out of that garage.
- Now look who's down
with the lingo.
- There's no way that kid
didn't tell the FBI
about a truckload full
of God knows what.
- And Sara
will literally be
bumped off the list
if we don't get the money.
- Wait, seriously?
- You have to pay up front
before the surgery.
- What?
You can't like finance it
or something?
- It's a kidney,
not a refrigerator.
- All right, this is it.
Up here on the left.
- ♪ We gonna do this
♪ Like, like we do this
♪ Ain't nobody else
can do this ♪
♪ Like us,
like us ♪
♪ Like I can do this
♪ Like, like we do this
♪ Ain't nobody else
can do this... ♪
- There it is.
- I mean, I don't see any cops.
- Yeah but that doesn't mean
they're not around.
[sighs]
- What do you think it's in?
The next shipment of fake cash?
- Bodies.
Dozens maybe.
[snickers] Could be hundreds
if they're chopped up.
- Just give me the keys.
- Now?
- We got to get back
in business.
- Oh, dude, don't do it.
Seriously.
- It's my family.
- Wait, wait, wait.
Wait, wait.
Maybe we should ask Stan first.
- We?
- Well, you.
- You want me to
ask my cop husband
if his cop friends
have their eye on a truck
that's potentially filled
with dead bodies.
- Well, I would be
a little bit more subtle,
but that's your call.
- [sighs]
- You okay?
- I mean, just add it
to the list of things
I'm not okay with.
Like taking orders
from grown men
who go by the names of Bullet,
Demon, and Mr. Cisco.
- [gasps] Which one
is Mr. Cisco?
Ew!
- [laughing] You are making
those names up.
- I am not!
I saw the one
with the skull tattoo
call the one
with the grill "Mr. Cisco."
Now, whether that's
a God given name or a nickname
I don't know,
but he answers to it.
- I am truly disturbed.
- Yeah, well get in line.
- Mr. Cisco
is the one to watch.
Mark my words.
[engine turns over]
Nothing but trouble.
- Let's go.
- Please.
.
- Ma'am, did you find
everything okay today?
Where do you guys
hide the baby formula?
Hi, by the way.
[chuckles]
- Uh, it's in aisle six
with the diapers.
- Duh, obvs--hey,
honey, aisle six.
Will you go get some
baby formula?
Okay, but nothing
organic or expensive.
[to baby] A few pesticides
never hurt anybody.
Did they? No, they didn't.
[baby cooing]
Oh, my God, this is so
random, but--
- Can I have this?
- No, no candy.
Um, do you know anything
about hot water heaters?
- They keep your water hot.
- Right, until they get
old and rusty.
[laughing] Right?
- Call the plumber.
- I did, believe me, but the
whole thing cost me 8,000 bucks
plus another 1,500
to dry the carpets.
- We just gave you $10,000.
- What about this?
- One, okay?
- I know.
And I feel so sick about this,
but what am I gonna do?
You know, I got
to feed my kids, right?
- Oh, hell no.
- Oh, come on. I just need
to get through to next month.
- I need a restock
at register three.
Restock at register three.
- So you don't have like
a house account or--
- No.
- Um, how about a
"You Gave Me Counterfeit
Money to Spend" account?
Do you have one of those?
Or a, um, what are
those things called?
Um, an "I Can Still Call
The Cops on You" account.
Maybe? No?
All right, well just put
the whole thing
on the "I'm What's Keeping
You Out of Jail" account.
We'll just--we'll just
call it a day.
Sound good?
[cash register beeps]
You're the best.
Thank you so much.
Don't forget the candy bar.
- I got it. I found it.
- Thanks, honey.
Okay, I said not
organic though.
Eh, it's fine.
It's on sale.
Oh, and I brought
my own bags, so,
you know, that's good
for the environment.
Oh, hey, you.
- Hey.
- How are you?
- Good, how are you?
- Can I hug you at work?
Is that allowed?
- Yeah, that's fine here.
- This is my brood.
Guys, please stay
in the store at least.
- Kids are down.
- Good.
What you got there?
Uh, what is that?
- Leftovers.
- From when?
- Nelly concert, 2003.
- Babe.
I am an officer of the law.
- Off duty.
- I shouldn't even
be seeing that.
- ♪ It's getting hot in here
- Oh, my God.
- ♪ So hot, so take off
♪ All your clothes
- Put that away.
- ♪ I am getting so hot
- Nah, see.
- ♪ I want to take
♪ My clothes off
- You need to stop playing.
You need to stop playing.
- You remember that show?
- ♪ I was like
♪ Good gracious,
ass is bodacious ♪
- ♪ Ooh
- ♪ Flirtatious
♪ Trying to make faces
- ♪ Ooh
- [laughs]
What's going on with you?
- I don't know.
I just, you know,
finally seeing some light
in this damn tunnel.
- [sighs] Yeah.
- Haven't we earned
at least one night off?
[sniffs]
- [sniffs, exhales]
Kids are down?
- For the count.
- ♪ You're with a winner
so baby you can't lose ♪
- I can't.
- ♪ I got a secret
♪ Can't leave Cancun
- [shushing]
- It's solid--I mean,
it's solid pine.
And I countersunk the screws.
And these are for paint
or modge-podge or whatever.
What do you think?
- It's really, really nice.
- It's rustic on purpose.
I left it unvarnished
in case you want to, you know,
decoupage or whatever.
- If a bug has six legs it's--
- Disgusting.
- You hate it.
- No, I don't.
I don't.
The woodworking is top notch.
I just think maybe I'm not as
into crafting as I used to be.
- Oh.
Well, it's not only for that.
It's for your stash.
You could put like 1/2 million
bucks in there easy.
That way you don't have to hide
it in the dog food container.
- I don't have a stash anymore.
- Yeah, but you're going to.
Right? Soon.
- I love it.
- You do?
Yes!
- Hey, Kenny, you want
to know a fun bug fact?
- Mm-hmm.
- The girl praying mantis
eats the boy
after they have sex.
- What?
- Oh yeah.
She just bites his weeny
little head right off.
He's so obviously trying
to get back in your pants.
- Please.
- He's using your bathroom.
- He lives here.
- Ugh. Since when?
[water running]
- Since he got cancer.
- Really lucked out
on that one.
[water shuts off]
- Yeah, that's what they call
cancer patients,
the lucky ones.
- You are making
a giant mistake.
- You just slept with your ex.
- Dude, he cheated on you
and almost left you
and your family homeless.
- In the middle
of a custody battle, no less.
- I'm sorry,
but do you remember
what he bought
that little skank?
- Of course I do.
- I'm gonna need you to say it.
- Underwear.
- Nah.
That was not underwear,
baby girl.
That was
bedazzled vagina floss.
Okay? And it was horrible
and humiliating.
And you're starting to forget.
- No, I'm not.
- Then you're starting
to forgive him
which is way worse.
- Let me worry about it.
It's my marriage.
- You can't do both.
- Both what?
- You can't be
this sweet little wifey,
and then also this like
badass criminal boss lady.
- I sound like Carmen Sandiego.
- You should be so cool.
- Can we just go to bed?
- Aw, man, all your drama
made me have to poop.
- Oh, my God.
You have got to go home.
[Nelly's "Hot in Herre"]
♪
♪ Want a little bit
of, ah, ah ♪
♪ And a little bit
♪
- Babe.
- Yeah?
- Can you turn it off now?
- Why? I thought you loved it.
- 'Cause if I listen
to it one more time,
I'm gonna need to dance.
- Yeah?
- And I am no condition...
- [laughs]
- To get my groove
on right now.
- No?
- [laughing] No.
- But it's hot in "herre."
Oh, my God.
- [laughs]
- Okay.
[music shuts off]
Hey, you still pack
little money's lunches
with those cheese puffs
in there?
- I like where your head's at.
- He gonna be mad though.
- You could take him.
He's tiny.
- [chuckles]
He is.
- He's so small.
[both laughing]
- Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh,
but I could also
get the cookie dough
out the fridge, too, though.
- Do it, do it, do it, do it.
- What. Yes.
- Do it. Okay.
- I'm a genius.
Okay.
- [chuckling]
[cell phone ringing]
- What's up?
- I forgot.
- You called me.
- I forgot what I was supposed
to ask Stan.
- Huh?
- Literally.
What am I supposed
to be asking?
- Dude, are you faded?
- I mean, yeah, he gets chatty
when he smokes, so...
- [laughing] Well played.
- So what am I supposed
to be asking?
- If the kid told the cops
about a truck.
- Right.
- Okay.
- I mean, can you just do it?
- What? No.
- I can put you on speaker.
- Trust me.
That would be super weird.
- It doesn't seem that weird.
- Just slip it in there.
You know, real cas'.
No big deal.
- Okay, okay.
Okay.
- [chuckles]
[footsteps approaching]
- Hey, babe.
So that gangster kid
that you all flipped,
did he say something
about a truck or something?
- A'ight so
we sit this kid down, right.
And before we can even start,
my man's acting like
he's about to get
water-boarded
or something like that.
Starts singing like a bird.
- For real?
- Yes.
Talking about places,
time, faces.
- Stop.
- Names.
- Trucks?
- What?
All kinds of stuff.
.
- Tyler.
You got a sec?
- Oh, I'm technically on break
for three more minutes.
- Well, I don't think
you're gonna want
to wait to hear this.
- Am I getting a Segway?
- No. No, this is not
about a pursuit vehicle.
- Um.
Is it about the hamburger meat?
- I'm making you employee
of the month.
- Seriously?
- Yeah.
Well, not this month,
but I'm putting you
on the fast track.
- Thank you, Mr. Petersen.
- Eh, come on.
Call me Leslie.
- Yes, sir, Leslie.
- Rolls right off the tongue.
- Uh-huh.
- [exhales] Hey, you know, um,
I saw you were
helping a lady out
at Annie's register
the other day.
You know, you gave her a hug?
- Oh, she initiated contact.
Plus I know her.
- Oh, it's okay.
No, I was just wondering
did you, um,
meet her on the job?
- No, not this job.
Mary Pat's from my side job.
- Mm?
- Yeah.
- Oh, what's the side job?
You know, it doesn't matter.
[clears throat]
I mean, the only reason
I was asking was
because Ms. Mary Pat left
her club card behind.
So I just didn't want her
to miss out on any
Twofer Tuesday deals.
- That's really nice of you.
- Hey, um,
you wouldn't have her number,
would you?
- No--but I do follow her
on Instagram.
She mainly posts stuff
about church and her kids.
It's pretty boring.
Hey, so, for employee
of the month,
is there gonna be like
a ceremony?
See you, Leslie.
[chuckles]
- How sure are you?
- Pretty sure.
- No, that's not enough.
I need, like, a percentage.
- 97%.
- Mm.
Almost as accurate as the pill.
- More.
- No, the pill's 99.9%.
- You can't be .1% knocked up.
- Uh-uh, that's if you
take it perfect.
For most people, it's like 91%.
- For you it was zero.
- Okay.
- Look, I'm never
gonna remember
every single thing
that Stan said.
But I think we should
just go for it.
- All right, here's the test.
Do you remember
that you called me?
- Yes.
- Do you remember
that you were so high
you forgot why you got high?
Mm-hmm.
- Look, I'm pretty sure
the cops don't know
anything about a truck.
- All right. [sighs]
Who's gonna drive?
- Let's draw straws?
- I always lose at that.
- So the straws?
- What about
rock paper scissors?
- We can't do that
with three people.
- Why not?
- Basic math.
[French pop music]
♪
- Everybody okay?
- No smokies on my tail.
- Yeah, I'm good.
- You guys, that was so sick.
They should totally make
a movie about us.
- Eh, no thanks.
- Wait, why not?
- Because I'd have to be
the wisecracking
black getaway driver
with one line who dies
five minutes in.
- Eh, true, true.
I'd be the Pacino.
- Oh, you'd so be
the Joe Pesci.
- What?
- Total Pesci.
- Because I'm short?
- It's like a whole Pesci vibe
with you.
- [scoffs] All right,
you know what? Forget it.
The movie's off.
- Guys.
- Pesci vibe.
- What?
- There's a cop behind me.
- Okay.
Okay. Just relax.
- Yeah, that's easy
for you to say.
You're not the one hauling
a truckload
of life sentences here.
- Make a turn.
- Yeah.
Lose that sucker.
- Don't lose him.
Just go slow and chill.
See if he follows.
- Okay.
Okay.
[tense music]
♪
[blinker clicking]
- What's up?
- He's still there.
- Just keep it together.
We got you.
We're here.
- You guys have to help
Dean with the kids.
He can't do it alone.
- Will you stop?
- And I don't want him
marrying a bimbo.
- Oh, he's 100%
gonna marry a bimbo.
- No bimbos around my kids.
- All right, no bimbos.
- Monday's pizza day.
The kids don't need lunch.
Dance Tuesday.
Same as the math tutor.
The dentist appointments
are on the refrigerator.
Trash and recycling
goes out Wednesday.
[police siren whooping]
- What's that?
What's happening?
[sirens wailing]
- Beth? Beth.
Say something.
What's going on?
- I'll write it all down,
but he'll need a village.
[radio chatter]
I got to go.
[phone beeps]
Is there a problem, officer?
- Driver's license
and registration.
- Just give me a minute.
I hope I wasn't speeding.
I've been rushing
around like crazy all day.
- Why's that?
- Um.
Little bit of
a domestic situation.
Not a good guy, you know?
Had to get out of there
as quickly as possible.
#TimeIsUp, am I right?
It's one of those.
- This your truck?
- I borrowed it.
From a friend who's helping me
with the domestic thing.
Am I in trouble here?
- First off, you're driving
without a license plate.
- My friend's a little bit
of a mess too.
- What's her name again?
- Sorry?
- The friend who loaned
you the truck?
- Oh, it's more
of a friend of a friend.
- I need you to get
out of the car.
You got a key to this lock?
[keys jingle]
- It must be one of these.
[jingling lock]
That's weird.
- #TimesUp.
♪
.
All: ♪ Praise him, praise him
♪ Ever in joyful song
- Praise him, indeed.
Amen.
- [whispers] Amen.
- Okay, fellowship
with your neighbors.
See you all next time.
[indistinct chatter]
- Hey! Give me five!
- He's alive!
- [giggles]
- Give me ten!
- He rose again!
[both chuckle]
- You'll like it here.
People are cool,
the choir's strong--
- Most importantly,
how are the donuts?
- Oh, always fresh,
always sprinkled.
- Oh, sold.
[both laugh]
- Well, it was really nice
to meet you, Leslie, and...
you know, you have
a really good voice.
- Oh.
- [chuckles]
[clears throat]
- Uh, would you ever want to...
grab a coffee
or something, ever?
- I can't.
- Oh yeah, no, totally.
I get it, I get it.
- It's not you--
- No, no, no, that's fine.
You don't have to.
I get it totally. All right.
- No, I--it's not--
- Sorry for bothering you.
Have a great night.
- [shouting] My husband's dead.
He passed away six months ago.
Do you think you could come
back closer
so I don't have
to shout about it?
- Oh, yeah.
Sorry.
- [chuckles awkwardly]
Um...
So it's not that
I don't want to go.
I do. I know I should
get back out there.
But I am, you know...
It would just be downhill
from here, so.
- How did he pass?
- Heart attack.
He was, um,
playing water guns
with the kids.
My son thinks that he killed
him 'cause he shot him
in the chest
with a Super Soaker
right before he actually died.
- Oh.
- Told you it was downhill
from here.
- No, no. That...
That was a good story.
- [laughs] Well,
if that's what you're into,
there's more
where that came from.
- Hey, it takes a lot
to scare me off, okay?
- [laughing] Okay, 2001,
summer of the shark.
And guess who gets her period?
- Ew.
- No, that's not
a true--that was a joke.
That was a bad joke.
Sorry.
- Oh.
No, that was funny.
No, you're funny.
[chuckles]
- Well, if that's
what you're into,
there's more where
that came from.
[both chuckle]
- I just got pulled over.
- So?
- So I barely talked myself
out of being arrested.
- For driving an empty truck?
- Why didn't you do it
yourself?
Why did you need us to bring
you an empty truck?
- I had a kid.
The Feds turned him.
- So this is a test?
- Needed to know if he talked.
I guess he didn't.
- And now we're back
in business.
- You're catching on.
Give me the keys.
- I have a family.
I have children.
- Yeah, you love
telling me that, huh?
- If you think you can
use me like a worm
on a hook so that
you don't get caught--
- I ain't got time to hold
your hand through this.
Give me the keys.
That family you're always
talking about?
Go home to 'em.
What me and you had is done.
Over.
- You can't just fire us.
- You think I need you?
Ain't nothing but
a damn charity case to me.
- We need the money.
- And I need more
of your bitch-ass drama
like I need a hole in my head.
Go home.
[tense resonating music]
- What do you mean,
you had a kid?
What happened to him?
What's that you're always
saying about your rotten eggs
and how you have
to handle 'em?
- Go home.
♪
- I don't see how you're
gonna let me do that.
Is it gonna be you?
Or do I come home one day
and your boys are
in my kitchen?
- Elizabeth.
Go home.
[door opens]
- Chimney fell on
an old lady in Wixom,
fatal car accident
on Southfield Freeway
hm, drowning?
What kind of nut job goes
swimming this time of year?
- You're kind of asking for it.
- Ugh.
I don't see anything
about a dead gang kid.
- You're sure
he's coming for us?
- We know too much now.
He'd be an idiot not to.
- I mean, homie has made
this threat before.
- I'm telling you,
it's different.
We're no good to him now.
- He said the actual words?
- He just looked at me funny.
- Sadie just did a project
on Great Whites.
They have these inky black eyes
that turn white
right before they kill you.
Was it funny like that or...?
- Okay, glass half-full.
He's just upset,
and when he calms down
he realizes we're good earners.
- What's half-empty?
- Getting put
in a wood chipper.
- I feel like he's
more creative than that.
Probably drop us
in molten steel
or feed us to pigs.
- Everything's a joke to you?
- I just deal with it
in my own way, okay?
- What do we do?
- Why are you looking at me?
- Because, you know,
last time this happened
you were all like,
"Yeah, just try to hurt us.
We eat at PF Chang's, bitch."
Can't you...
.
- You feel really strongly
about this.
- "I've Got The Joy" just
sounds better
on electric guitar.
I mean, no offense
to Leonore's organ playing.
- [chuckles] Jeff used
to play it on guitar.
- Oh yeah?
- Yeah.
He was also really
into hard rock.
Like he knew every Creed song
by heart.
You know?
- [chuckles]
- I was doing so good.
- You made it the whole night.
- Yeah, till now.
- Well, you're home
so it doesn't count.
- [chuckles]
I had fun tonight.
- You're easy to have fun with.
[chuckles]
- Do you know why
that is, I think?
♪ I've got the joy, joy, joy,
down in my heart ♪
- Where?
- ♪ Down in my heart
[both laugh]
- With a little electric riff,
it would sound so good.
- It would be so good.
- [laughs]
Uh--
- Should I put on some tea?
- I, um...
- Oh, I don't mean to--
I mean, if you have
an early morning or something.
Like, no pressure, if you...
- I guess I could.
- Okay.
I can, if you're--
- Oh, yeah.
- Thanks.
[both chuckle]
Honey?
- Yes, dear?
[both laugh]
[Hundred Waters' "Blanket Me"]
♪
♪ Shame on you
♪ Shame on me
♪ Blindly blame you
♪
♪ When truly
you're my blanket ♪
♪ You're my skin
♪ You're everything within
♪ You're my guardian,
I'm your sail ♪
♪ A boat in your harbor
♪ Gone under,
capsized and sinking ♪
♪ Blanket me, blanket me,
blanket me ♪
♪ Blanket me,
blanket me, blanket me ♪
♪ Blanket me, blanket me,
♪ Blanket me, blanket me
♪ Blanket me,
blanket me ♪
♪ Blanket me, blanket me,
♪ Blanket me,
blanket me, blanket me ♪
♪ Blanket me, blanket me
♪
♪ I'm sinking,
well, blanket me ♪
- Hey.
It's mom.
Um.
Your windows dark,
so I figure you're asleep.
Um...
I just wanted
to tell you that I
love you so much.
You are so awesome.
And you're really funny.
And you're really kind.
And you're also really cool,
which is rare for a kid.
And it's great for me 'cause it
really ups my cool factor--
[phone beeps]
- If you're satisfied
with your message, press one.
If you would like
to re-record--
[button beeps]
- Hey.
It's me. Um.
It's late so you're probably
sleeping, but, um...
I just wanted you to know that
I think you are the best.
You are so smart.
And you're really funny.
And you're really...
polite oddly.
Which I don't know
where you get that from
because neither me
or your dad is--
[phone beeps]
- If you're satisfied
with your message, press one.
If you would like--
[button beeps]
- Hey, baby, it's mom.
Um.
I think you're asleep
but I just
in case I get cut off I wanted
to say that--
[phone beep]
- If you're satisfied
with your message,
- Dude, come on!
- press one.
[button beeps, door closes]
- Uh. Great.
- If you're satisfied
with your message, press--
[button beeps]
- Hey, um, it's me.
I love you.
Okay, bye.
- What are you doing?
- What?
I just miss my kid.
- You just called her 11 times.
- Well, I miss her a lot
so sue me.
- What is going on with you?
If you'll just tell me--
- Yeah, don't you think
you have your hands full
what, with the IVF.
- Maybe I can help you.
- And everything else.
- Just stop talking.
What is up?
- All right,
you want to know what's up?
- Yeah, I do.
- Well I want to know what's up
with those PJs.
I mean, really, you look like
you're in a Dickens novel.
- [chuckles]
- Who's coming for you tonight?
Is it the ghost
of Christmas present
or the ghost of Christmas past?
- Actually I want to know
what's up with this car.
- Mm.
- 'Cause I don't think
a homeless person
would even sleep in here.
- Hm, well, joke's on you.
'Cause a lot of homeless people
have slept in here.
- Oh, is that right?
- I mean, maybe not a lot
but, you know, a fair amount.
- Sort of like a selective few
homeless people.
- Yeah, I kind of have like
a lottery system going.
- Oh.
- Mm-hmm.
[both laugh]
Why are you trying
to help me?
- You're the mother
of my child.
- Is that all...
I am to you?
- Come on.
You're not really gonna
make me say it, are you?
- Do you and Nance
have matching sets?
Or is this a bespoke number?
- Take care of yourself, Annie.
[gentle guitar music]
♪
- [sighs]
- What would it take
for you to walk out on me?
- Mm. Become a Packer fan.
- I'm serious.
- So am I.
You become a cheesehead,
and you're gonna have to
find yourself
a new man.
- Stan.
- Hm?
- Put down the book.
- [clears throat]
- I don't always
do the right thing.
- So what?
I mean, who does?
And, uh,
I think I know you pretty well.
- But what if you didn't?
- Baby, you want to tell me
what we're talking about here?
[cell phone rings]
- [sniffles]
- Hello?
Yeah, this--okay.
Okay.
Um.
- What?
- [exhales sharply]
So, um, a girl just...
a girl in Madison just got hit
by a drunk driver
and her family
is getting ready to take her
off life support.
- Is she...
- She's a perfect match.
- [breathing heavily]
[children chatter, laughter]
- How'd you sleep?
- I didn't.
- You guys.
Maybe we should turn
ourselves in.
- You want to go to the cops?
- I know, I know.
- Now you want
to go to the cops?
- We'll go to jail, Annie.
- Well, it's better than
waiting to be murdered
in some gnarly way
that I haven't
even thought of yet.
- We got the call.
What if it goes
to someone else?
[indistinct chatter]
- All those fairy tales
they told us
when we were little girls?
[Kate Pierson's
"Throw Down the Roses"]
The morals were always,
if you're good
and if you follow the rules,
if you don't lie
and you don't cheat,
if you're good,
you'll get good things.
♪
And if you're a dick,
you get punished.
But what if the people
who made up those stories
are the dicks?
- Are you following her?
- Mm, mas o menos.
- What if the bad people
made all that up
so the good people
never get anything good?
- And now I'm lost.
- What's the takeaway?
- It doesn't matter
what we've done,
we're the good guys.
He's the criminal here.
He's the one who should
be in jail. Not us.
- That's what
I'm talking about.
- Right?
- Hell to the yeah right.
- Then let's put him there.
♪
- ♪ I don't need a wristband
to tell me who I am ♪
♪ No need to clap your hands
♪ I don't need a microphone
to tell you ♪
♪ I'm better off
being on my own ♪
♪ And you hit the last note
and that is all she wrote ♪
♪ I don't stick around
♪ I won't wait around
♪ For the ending
♪ Another curtain closes
♪ We already know
♪ There's an end to the show
♪ We're making
♪ I'm throwing down
♪ The roses
[harmonizing]
♪
♪ I'm throwing down
the roses ♪
♪
♪ I'm throwing down
the roses ♪