- Previously
on "Good Girls"...
- Who the hell are you?
- I'm a friend of your friends.
- Give me your car keys.
- Downstairs on the counter.
- I've never worked
so hard for so little.
I say we get out.
- We just need
some extra hands.
- You want to bring
other people into this now?
- So what's a secret shopper?
- Nancy and I are...
suing you for custody.
- I got cola, tina, molly, oxy,
K, addys, and fat bags of herb.
- I started a business.
- Okay.
- I didn't want to tell you
because I was afraid I'd fail.
I didn't fail.
I'm crushing it.
- Dangerous people
took advantage of you.
- They didn't take
advantage of me.
It was a choice.
I wanted to.
- Ah!
Where did this come from?
[upbeat hip-hop music]
♪
- Okay.
Are you a drug lord?
Are you running
a prostitution ring?
- [chuckles]
Don't you wish.
- What is going on?
I mean, 'cause I have
a right to know.
- Remember when you were
screwing your secretary
and lost everything that we had
and I was completely
in the dark?
- Yes.
- So this is kind of like that.
Oh, don't forget that I need
you out of the house tonight.
- Book club?
- Book club.
- What am I supposed
to do with the kids?
- I don't know.
Take 'em to the movies.
- ♪ Hey, hey, hey, hey
- What the hell.
Take 'em to Disneyland.
- ♪ Every morning,
I feel so summertime ♪
♪ My haters got to work
like overtime ♪
♪ Hey, baby, don't act no...
- Who are these people,
Daddy?
- ♪ Just like a drum
- Uh, Mommy's friends.
- What are they doing here?
[laughter]
- Book club.
Come on. Let's go.
Go, go, go.
Come on.
Hi.
- Hi.
- Hi, hi.
- Excuse me.
- Hi.
- Hi, man.
Hi.
Hi, everyone, hi.
- [distorted] ♪ Ain't
no friend of mine ♪
- Heaven,
you're on five to close.
- Copy that.
- Hey, have you seen Annie?
- Uh, no, she called in
sick again.
- She hasn't been in
in two weeks.
Hey.
Is she gonna quit?
- I don't know.
- Well, what did she say?
- That she was sick.
- Well, what kind of sick,
Heaven?
There's cold.
There's flu.
There's diarrheal--
- Ew. I don't know.
- All extremely different
virus pathologies.
What did she tell you?
- Just that she was sick.
- You know what, you tell me
when you hear from her.
I want to know
when she's coming in.
- Okay. Great.
- Smile.
- [inhales] Okay.
- 'Kay, people!
So listen up.
D.N.R.
What does it mean?
[chuckling] Okay,
I can see we're all
taking
a little evening nap here.
Hey, Beth, let's get
some more coffee in here,
and you know what,
throw in some espresso shots
for the bitches
in the front row.
D...N...R.
What is it?
- Do Not Resuscitate?
- Yes.
But the thing is, Tyler,
that's for when you're dead.
That's for when
you've given up.
Are you giving up, Tyler?
- No.
- Is anyone else here
giving up?
[all murmuring "No"]
No? Excellent.
Then let's go ahead and pull
our heads out of our asses
and, oh, my God, Heather!
I'm not gonna say it again.
Get the hell off your phone.
D. Do your surveys.
The more you buy and return,
the more money
you're gonna make.
N. Never buy and return
from the same store.
That one should pretty much
be a duh at this point.
Which leaves us with R.
Any guesses?
- Um, recycle
your shopping bags?
[affirmative chatter]
- [clears throat]
Are we trying
to save the planet?
- Um, no.
- Are we at
a Greenpeace meeting?
- Uh, no.
- What are we here for,
Mary Pat?
- To make money.
- [raises voice] And what
is an essential component
of making money
when you're a secret shopper?
Reee...
all: Reee...
- Really do your surveys?
- Receipts!
[all gasping]
Save your receipts!
Come on!
Say it with me people!
Receipts, receipts,
receipts, receipts!
[all chanting "Receipts"]
- Man, they trashed my house.
- Mm. It was that
bloody Ruth woman.
She sucked down
like 17 eggrolls.
I saw her do it.
- Maybe I should stop
serving food.
- No, it's good.
It keeps them hyped up.
Hey, speaking of which.
- Here we go.
- I think we should
up the ante, you know?
Maybe offer a little
sales incentive next month.
- What? Like a flatware set?
- Actually I was thinking more
like a trip to Cancun.
- What?
- I mean, why not?
- Because we don't have
money to burn,
and we have to be smart
about this.
- [scoffs]
- We have a six-month plan.
- Dawg, the way this operation
is blowing up,
we're gonna be in the black
a lot sooner than that.
- She is not wrong.
- [gasps] I'm sorry,
could you...
Could you say that
one more time
but slowly with feeling?
- We got a lot of shoppers.
We are rolling deep now.
- How much did we clear
this week?
- [exhales]
[buttons clicking]
You guys...
Shoppers be shoppin'.
- Yo, make with
the info already.
- How much?
- Come on.
[upbeat percussive music]
- We just got it in.
14-karat, emerald cut,
white gold.
- It's so beautiful.
- It would look
stunning on you.
With that skin.
- How much?
- $1,100.
- ♪ Everybody's starting
a shakedown, baby ♪
- Come on.
Just try it on.
- I'm 11.
They're gonna laugh.
- No, no.
Excuse me, sir.
Hi. What can you tell us about
this incredible suit here?
- Are we looking to buy
a gift for Daddy or...
- Actually Daddy
couldn't pull this off.
We're looking
for my daughter.
- [chuckles] I'm not sure
something like this
would really work on her.
♪
We do have a kids' department.
- Mm.
Honey, I'm sorry.
Could you just--could you
hang on to these for me?
My purse just won't close.
- It's just stunning.
- Thank you.
- If you want to give
your husband my card,
I'm happy to set it aside.
- My husband can't afford this.
♪
- Well...
- ♪ Ah
- 36 short?
- Let's start with 34.
Something with no break
and a tight inseam.
- ♪ Ah
- "GQ" says the clean
look's still in.
♪
- [whispers] Hey.
- And we finish it
with our pistachio foam,
which Chef has infused
with local flavors
from his favorite
Peruvian coastal village.
We then flash caramelize it
using a refracted laser.
[electronic music]
- What?
- Oh, okay.
- Enjoy.
♪
- Is that a...
- Uh-huh.
- It's a grape.
- Mm, it sure is.
- I mean...
that grape has been places.
- It's better
traveled than me.
- That grape
has seen things.
[both chuckling]
But, and this is
the true test...
- Mm.
- Has this grape...
ever arrested anybody?
- [scoffs]
Come on now.
Come on, it was just an assist.
Okay? Small time drug bust.
- Did you get to put
on the cuffs?
- [slurps]
[licks lips]
Uh, maybe.
[both laugh]
- Well, in that case,
you get the bigger half,
Mr. Officer.
- Oh, no, no, no,
please, please.
I'm still full
from the heirloom carrot
on a bed of micro-greens
foraged by gnomes.
- [laughs] We're gonna need
to get some pizza after this.
- Please.
You know what, though?
It feels good to treat
ourselves for once.
- Right?
- Yeah.
Hey, are we good
to spend like this?
I mean, I know you
got the new gig--
- You know what else I got?
- Hmm?
- I have a new theory
on money.
- Tell me.
- It's like a boomerang.
If you throw it out there,
it's gonna come back.
- That's gangster.
- To your first arrest.
[glasses clink]
- Well, it's about time.
- Eddy, right?
Jim Turner.
People call me Jimmy.
It's nice to meet you.
Let's see what's going on here.
Oof. Third strike, huh?
Well, that blows.
- Whatever.
- Possession, armed robbery.
Damn, son.
You fell in with a rough crowd,
as my mama would say.
- You think I'm gonna snitch?
Or tell you anything
about anybody?
- It's okay.
Let's go.
- Where?
- Home.
You're on my way.
I'll drop you off.
- You ain't gonna charge me
with anything?
- No offense, but no one
really cares about you,
so if you're not talking,
might as well free up the room.
You mind if we grab
a bite on the way?
I haven't eaten.
What's that shawarma place
your boys all hang out at?
Aman's?
- Amir's.
- Yeah, I could eat
that fried eggplant all day.
We'll grab a booth
by the window,
do some people watching.
We watch them.
They watch us.
You, uh--you on Instagram?
- Nah.
[camera shutter clicks]
- Now you are.
- What's your problem, man?
- Oh, me? No problem,
but you might have one
coming home
smelling like cop coffee.
- Do you want to get me
killed or something?
- See, now,
that's up to you, son.
Should we go?
- [sighs]
- And something
was dumped on my lap,
and I don't want this to be
happening right now.
- Oh, she's gonna do it.
- No.
No! No!
- Oh, no, she's doing it.
- I can't.
[both gasp]
I cannot!
- I don't want to be
the one to have
to tell you this
because it's not my--
- Please don't let it
be about Tom.
- It's about Tom.
[both scream]
- No!
- Just don't--get away
from me right now.
- Oh, Countess,
you knew he was a playa.
- Dude, you are
on a reality show!
- Oh, you can't turn
those cameras off.
[women groan]
- Coming up...
- [sighs]
- I would've vied for her.
- Okay, you guys.
I did something.
- What?
- What does that mean?
- What did you do?
- Tell me there is not another
man up in that treehouse.
- Wait here.
[Gin Wigmore's "In My Way"]
- I don't like that look
in her eye.
- Mm.
- Tension's killing me.
I'm getting more Bugles.
- Ooh, wine me please.
- Yeah, yeah, yeah.
- Thank you.
- ♪ I will fight
♪ And decide
♪ All for you
♪ My reflection said to draw
- I want you guys
to be honest.
Kind of love it,
but...
maybe it's over the top.
- ♪ To have you
♪ To hold you
♪ I want to keep you within
♪ Feel the touch
of your skin ♪
♪ I want to have you
♪ Forever in my way
♪ Ah
- Not over the top
at all.
♪
[chuckles softly]
What is that?
Is that...
Is that emerald cut?
- Please put down the gun.
- How much of my money
did that set you back?
- This isn't your money.
- Oh, see, but it is.
- What are you doing?
I thought we were past this.
- Me too.
But you bitches just keep
stealing from me.
and I ain't gonna notice?
- No, it's not possible.
We have a system.
- Ah, me too.
- No, we know what is real
and we know what is fake.
- Oh, me too.
And you tried to rip me off
a hundred Gs?
- What?
both: No.
- I swear to God
we would never do that.
- Maybe it was
one of the women.
[downbeat rock music]
Maybe one of them
didn't wash the money
and just turned in her surveys
and didn't go shopping.
- What women?
♪
- We couldn't wash
the cash fast enough,
so we had to outsource.
- You shared my business
with other people?
- None of them actually
knows anything.
- They're just women who think
they'll literally shopping.
- Which one of your
lady friends screwed me.
- How could we know?
- I'm gonna need a name.
♪
- Why?
- To handle it.
♪
- Listen,
there could be...
any one
of 30 people who--
- And you're gonna
give me a name.
♪
Or I'm just gonna pick one
at the next PTA mixer.
♪
[gun clicks]
- [exhales]
- You can't tell
from these surveys.
These all look
totally legit.
- I mean, it could be
any of 'em.
- It's not like it would take
a criminal mastermind,
just somebody smart
but, like, lazy.
It wasn't me.
- Oh, well, we got
to figure it out
before he "handles" it.
- What's with the air quotes?
- I think it's pretty clear
what he meant "handle" it.
- Again, with the air quotes.
- He's not gonna
take it up with HR.
He's gonna cap a bitch!
- That's not
gonna happen, okay?
Not if we handle it ourselves.
- [gasps]
- That is not with air quotes.
- [exhales]
- What if we send everyone
to the same store?
Just in one day,
we give them a small drop
to spend so we don't
raise flags.
- What does that do?
- Well, then we can sit
and watch and see who
doesn't show up to shop.
- Like a stakeout.
- Well, that's kind of
more for cops.
- Yeah, and we're watching
to see who doesn't show, so...
- Oh, sorry, so like the very
definition of a stakeout.
- Do you always
have to label it?
- Or be down with the lingo.
- It gets to be a bit much.
- Wow. You guys just cannot
give it to me, can you?
That's sad.
Unbelievable.
- Hey, babe.
- Yeah?
- Can you make sure Harry
brushes his teeth, please?
- Oh, he's good.
- He's not good.
He's six.
And he has dog breath.
What's all this sunshine?
What you got back there?
- I don't know.
Why don't you pick
a hand and find out?
- Stan, I have to get
these kids ready for bed.
I have to prep
for a crazy day tomorrow.
- Well, then you need
to come on.
- Oh, my God, really?
- [laughing]
What?
Glass seats
behind the net, baby.
[clicks tongue]
- What'd they cost?
- Who cares what they cost?
You always wanted seats
behind the glass, right?
Glass seats.
- What I want and what we
can afford are very different.
- [sighs]
Now wait a minute.
I thought we were living
a little bit here.
- Yeah, a little,
not like Jay and Bey.
- What? Nah.
I'm sending the boomerang out,
remember?
- Yeah, and I'm trying
to keep it from
taking our heads off.
Look, I may have gotten
a little ahead of myself.
This business, it's just...
We're gonna need to pump
the breaks a little bit.
- Just one hockey game.
- How much were they?
Stan.
- [stammers] Huh?
- Stanley Lamont Hill!
[hip-hop music]
[indistinct chatter]
- Annie Bananey.
Welcome back.
How you feeling?
- Better.
- Are these gonna be necessary?
You look like
you know the drill.
- I'm sorry, Officer.
What am I being arrested for?
- Trafficking a class one
controlled substance.
- Wait, what?
- Well, they'll explain
everything to you
down at the station, okay?
- Wow.
You vile little weasel.
You planted something on me?
- Okay, that's it.
- Unbelievable.
Even for you, that's low!
[cuffs click]
I didn't think
you had it in you.
Wow. That's cool,
you little dick.
'Cause you know
what I'm gonna do?
I'm gonna rip that
wormy little mustache
right off your face
and that ugly ass
nut duster too
and I'm gonna cram 'em where
the sun don't shine, buddy.
That's right! It's on now.
You have no idea the pain
that I'm gonna bring upon
your house!
You are over,
you little punk ass bitch!
- [scoffs]
Guys, that's not
Fine and Frugal behavior, okay?
Back to work.
♪
Clean up aisle ten.
Seriously?
- I'm sorry.
I didn't get your message
until this morning.
- [sighs]
I had to sleep on the floor.
It was like friggin' Oz
in there.
- Who's with Sadie?
- She's at a sleepover,
thank God.
Hey, Beth!
Seriously?
- I couldn't get a babysitter.
Dean's at the oncologist.
What did you want me to do?
- I don't know.
Maybe not make them watch
Auntie do a perp walk?
- Oh, don't get mad at me.
I'm not the one
who got arrested.
- Yes, thank you.
I'm aware.
- For drugs, no less.
- They weren't mine.
- Said everyone
ever busted for drugs.
- I'm telling you
I was set up, okay?
- Like the cinnamon
schnapps at prom?
- Why would you even
throw that in my face?
That's not relevant.
- Because I am still
bailing you out.
- I'm telling you
they were not mine.
[voice breaking]
Boomer set me up.
- What?
- I'm gonna lose Sadie.
You know it's true.
There's no judge in the world
that would let me
keep her after
a felony drug charge.
[sobs]
- I'm gonna help you
with this.
We are gonna figure
this out together, okay?
- This is really bad.
- Together, okay?
- Okay.
Okay.
[inhales and exhales]
Hey, guys!
Auntie has a funny story.
The lawyer thinks that it would
make me look more responsible
if you stayed with Dad
and Nancy for a little while.
Baby, please don't be sad.
Please. I promise
I'm gonna fix this.
- Can we just...
sit here a little?
- Of course, baby.
- [sighs]
- Honey, you got
to get a lawyer.
- I have a custody one.
- You need a criminal one.
- Yeah.
- [groans]
I'm gonna have a whole
legal team, O.J. style.
- Yeah, and fight it.
- That little grocery store
turd is going down.
- I just want my kid back,
you know?
[indistinct chatter,
shopping cart rattling]
- Yo, bogie, eleven o'clock.
- Is that--
- Brooke, red glasses.
- Okay, how many more?
- 28.
- Settle in.
[mellow pop music]
♪
- How many more now?
- I'm not telling you.
- Why not?
- 'Cause it's the same answer
as it was five minutes ago.
- [groans] This is
the worst stakeout ever.
- At least you don't have
somebody's nasty ass feet
in your face.
- [groans]
- I'm gonna die of natural
causes in this minivan.
- You might just
go quicker.
- Just find out
who it is, okay?
- Okay.
If we had to sacrifice
someone to the gang...
♪
I nominate that lady Heather.
[slurping]
- Are you for real
right now?
- I'm talking like
gun to the head had to.
- Annie.
- She is always on her phone.
- And that's a reason
to kill her?
- It's like, "Chill, bitch,
nobody's posted
on Instagram in the
last three seconds, 'kay?"
- Oh, my God.
- I'm just saying
back pocket.
♪
- [sighs]
Should we wake her up?
- No.
I'm enjoying the quiet.
[sighs]
- Check it.
Closing time and one name left.
So what now?
- We handle it.
[engine turns over]
- I'm so sorry about the mess.
If I'd known my bosses were
coming by, I would've...
[chuckles]
I don't know.
Hey, boys, can you
keep it down, okay?
I can't even hear
myself think.
[chuckles]
- Okay, Mom.
- Uh, what can I get you guys
to--to drink?
- We're fine.
- I'm okay.
- Do you have any lemonade?
- Uh...
I--I have water.
[softly] No.
- That's perfect.
- It's great.
- Okay.
- I love water.
- [straining]
[refrigerator door closes]
[chuckles] Okay.
Um, you know, can you just--
- Oh. Okay.
- Can you--thank you.
I'm sorry,
I just haven't, um,
you know, really gotten used
to doing, like, everything
all by myself, you know,
since Jeff passed.
[sighs]
- Oh, we didn't know.
- Yeah, he had a heart attack,
um, six months ago.
- God, that's--that's terrible.
- We're so sorry.
- And I'm so thankful
for your shopping club.
You know, I feel like
I finally have a shot at--
at getting my head
above water, you know?
[indistinct chatter on TV]
- [exhales sharply]
I'm just gonna rip off
the Band-Aid here.
Uh...
we know
what you've been doing.
- I don't understand.
- [sighs]
You've been turning in the same
cash, and it's--it's okay.
You know, you obviously
have a lot on your plate,
and you're not in trouble.
But unfortunately
we do have to let you go.
- He's very cute.
- I'm so embarrassed.
- Oh, please don't be.
- You know, I ran out of time,
and I really needed the money.
- No judgement here.
- Uh-uh.
[baby cooing]
- Oh, my God.
[sighs]
[baby crying]
- We'll just, um,
let ourselves out.
- You take care, okay?
- Good night.
[baby crying]
- Wait, what...
What did you...
What did you mean when you
said that I turned in
the same cash?
- What?
- I mean, how would you know
that I turned in
the exact same cash?
Like...
- Well, obviously,
we don't know that,
but we know from your survey
that you weren't
actually doing the shopping.
- But that's not what
she said, though.
- Well, that's what I meant.
- But it's not what you said.
I mean, do you guys check
serial numbers or something?
No.
No, that would--
that'd be crazy.
- Girl, it is never easy
to be let go.
- Mm.
- Trust me, I know.
I've been there.
- And we would have kept you on
but it was corporate's call.
- Right.
You know, um, come to think
of it, if I am being fired,
it seems like I should probably
hear that from corporate.
Right?
Not you guys.
So what, um--
what's their number?
- They're closed.
- Yeah.
- I mean, it's,
what, time...
- Come to think of it,
what's their name?
- Okay, I know--
I know you're upset.
- No, I'm not upset.
But you know
who I think might be
is the Better Business Bureau.
- Just hold on a minute.
- No, no, no, no.
Let her do it.
We don't have
anything to hide.
Go ahead.
- I don't know what you've
gotten me involved in...
but it's something super shady.
[tense percussive music]
I'm calling the police.
♪
[line trilling]
- Ashfield police.
- Put down the phone.
♪
- Hello.
Hello, this is
the Ashfield Police.
Do you have an emergency?
♪
- What do you want?
- Elena. Carpool or something.
- [groans]
- Wow.
- Yeah.
- I mean, we could
let Rio "handle" it.
I'm just saying, I don't
want to, but, you know,
it would solve
the problem cleanly.
- She's a single mother.
- With a dead husband.
She's probably
drowning in debt.
- Oh, my God, you guys,
it's not like
she's this great person.
She's blackmailing us.
I mean, that's illegal.
- So is washing
counterfeit money.
- And robbing
a grocery store.
- And crossing the border
with counterfeit money.
- Okay! Okay.
- [groans]
I mean, I hate to be
the one to say I told you so--
- Then how about you don't?
- But did I not tell you
this was a bad idea.
We never, ever should have
brought other people into this.
- The system works.
- Uh, clearly it doesn't.
- Someone found the one flaw.
- And is extorting us
to the tune of $10,000.
- Okay, I know it would be
really nice and neat
to just make it my fault--
- We were out.
We were done with the gang.
We were done with all of it.
- Are you serious?
- And then we went back
and asked for more.
- Because we needed the money
and you got on board
real quick.
- And now you're rolling
like some evil mastermind.
- Don't you call her evil!
- With your six-month plan
and your secret shoppers
luring them in like
some crazy Pied Piper.
- Don't you call her crazy!
- Okay, pause!
You call her out
all the time.
- We are blood!
- Okay, thank you.
But...
- Okay.
I see.
Okay.
I mean, I'm just the one
that held your hand
when you went through the hell
of signing your divorce papers,
but whatever.
'Cause I'm not blood.
You know what?
Do what you want.
Pay her, don't pay her.
Just leave me
the hell out of it.
- Wait.
Where are you going?
- Home.
To my family.
My blood.
- You can't just bail
when things get bad.
- Things got bad the second we
took down that grocery store.
[car door thuds shut,
engine turns over]
[solemn music]
♪
[knocking at door]
[knocking continues]
- Beth, are you decent?
- Yeah.
♪
[water running]
- Are you okay?
- Yeah.
♪
- I...
I heard the water running
for like the last hour,
and I--I got worried.
- Yeah, I couldn't sleep
and then I...
couldn't shower, so...
[water running]
- D-do you mind if I
turn off the shower?
Just our water--water bill
is gonna be insane.
- God, no, of course.
I'm sorry.
[water shuts off]
- [exhales]
Ca--can I ask you
one thing?
- Okay.
- Are you doing it for us?
I mean the kids.
I mean, are you doing this
for the kids?
- Yes.
[light music]
- That's all I need to know.
♪
[door creaking open]
- [chuckles]
Nice.
- [crunching]
I'm having a "me" night.
- Mm.
- What is it?
- Uh, Sadie forgot some jeans.
- Mm, with the patches?
- Yeah.
[door thuds]
What's with all the Post-its?
- Oh, uh, Sadie gets scared
that I'll forget stuff,
so she writes them
down on Post-its.
- Like the rent?
- [scoffs] Please.
I would never forget that.
Because I have the Post-it.
- She worries
about you too much.
- It's just like
our shtick, okay?
- Yeah, but she
doesn't know that
because she's only 11.
- You know what, Greg?
I have had a really tough week,
so if there's any way
you could spare me
the judgement.
- How did you get
picked up for pills?
- [chuckles]
Here we go.
- They weren't yours, right?
I mean, if it had been
peppermint schnapps,
then you wouldn't really
have a defense, but--
- Actually, I'm partial
to cinnamon.
- Ah, right, yes.
It's all coming back to me now.
- So do you want
something to eat or...
- Uh, what do you got?
- Cheese and crackers.
- Oh.
- Mm-hmm.
both: Okay.
- What if...
they were combined, hmm?
- Is this your dinner?
- Hey.
They're not just
for breakfast anymore.
Mm-hmm.
You want, like, a glass of wine
or something with that?
- It's so grown-up.
You have wine?
- Mm...
Nah, just playing.
Only vodka.
- Room temp?
- Hey, you know me so well.
This is...clean-ish.
[clears throat]
- Classy.
- You can be a real dick,
you know that?
- So can you.
[clink]
- Oh, my God.
What did you buy this time?
- Pick a hand and find out.
- Seriously?
We're doing this again?
- Not if you don't pick a hand.
Pick another one.
- Stan.
- All right.
- Where'd you get that?
- I put our tickets up for sale
on StubHub, and your man here
made a tiny profit.
- Thank you.
- You're welcome.
You were starting to get
a little crazy.
- I'm not crazy.
- [imitating her] Gonna spend
money now, don't spend money.
- I just worry.
- Well, I worry too,
but we don't have to live
like the sky's always falling.
- The sky is always falling.
Look at Sara.
- But she's healthy now,
isn't she?
- Yeah, but what about
in two weeks
when she stops taking
her meds again?
- [exhales]
- It's like every time
I look down,
it's pieces of sky.
- Let's just take it
as it comes.
- I feel like the damn sky's
out to get us.
[gentle music]
- Baby.
- Yeah?
- [whispers] I got you.
♪
- Oh, my God!
- Right?
- No, stop!
- I know!
- [laughing] Oh, no.
He remembers
his little friend.
- Wait, wait, wait, are you
laughing or are you crying?
- I can't tell.
I actually can't.
I have tears in my eyes,
but--
No, it's over?
- Yeah.
- How am I gonna know
what happens?
- Oh, wait.
Um...
he tears his throat out.
- [laughing] Shut up.
- [groans]
- Oh, no.
- Aw, man.
Party's over.
- What?
Wait, I have the Fruit Roll-Ups
or some old raisins
in there I think.
- Mm, no.
I should probably go home.
- [sighs]
Yeah, I mean, who's watching
Sadie right now?
- Oh, Sadie's in bed.
Nancy's in bed.
Everybody's accounted for.
I'm like supes responsible.
[clicks tongue]
Mm.
- You look so sleepy.
Are you sleeping
any better these days?
- Nah.
[relaxed music]
- Mm, Greggles.
- [chuckles]
Some things never change, huh?
- Mm-hmm.
[gasps]
♪
Have you seen the one
with the chimp and the frog?
♪
- No.
- It's gonna blow your mind.
- [vocalizing]
♪
- I know, I know.
- Oh.
Oh.
- Oh, no.
- Huh?
Oh, no.
- Oh, no.
- Okay, I know.
- No, no, no, no, no, no, no.
- I know, I know.
Okay.
- [panting] Okay.
There we go, all right.
Jeans, jeans.
- What?
- Sadie's jeans.
- The jeans,
the jeans, jeans, jeans.
- [panting]
- I know.
I know, I know.
[sighs]
Oh, no.
- It's all there
and it's all real.
And it won't happen again.
- So who was it?
- You got your money.
- Yeah, I'm also
gonna need a name.
- I took care of it.
- Come on.
Just give me a name.
- Beth Boland.
- Hmm.
Now let me give you
some advice, yeah?
When you got a rotten egg
in the bunch,
it stinks up the whole lot
till you get rid of it.
- Like I said, I'm handling it.
And don't ever point a gun
at me again.
[lively music]
♪
- ♪ Gonna get,
go-gonna get ♪
♪ Gonna get, go-gonna get
♪ Gonna get,
go-gonna get ♪
- FBI appreciates the DPD
tagging in on this.
These guys are organized, but
an arrest you made this week
gave us a man on the inside.
I know a task force means
a little longer hours,
but Detroit's gonna
appreciate it big time
when we put these guys away,
so let's get started.
If you all would turn
to page four of your hymnals.
♪
[knocking]
- Open up.
[locks click]
[shivers]
What?
- We just didn't
think you'd show.
- Please.
I'm stuck with you guys.
- Good. 'Cause we need you.
- Where the hell
would I go anyway?
- I don't know, the diner
would probably take you back.
- Ugh. There's no going back.
Ever tell you guys
about the sauce?
I don't think
I've even told Stan.
You gotta swear--
- Promise.
- Ride or die.
[clicks tongue]
- So for a while, the diner was
running this Italian sub deal.
Salami with peppers and onions
and special sauce.
To save money, Tony orders
a 55-gallon barrel.
We kept it in the basement.
It was so damn hot down there.
The heat would cause
the oils to separate.
We'd use this wood canoe paddle
to stir it back together.
Eventually the paddle breaks.
And you know cheap-ass Tony,
he's not gonna buy
a new paddle.
You tell yourself
you'd never do something.
- Wasn't there a ladle
you could use or something?
- A broom even?
- Just my arm.
I had the longest.
So every day,
twirling in these sauce oils
like a conductor
for the New York Phil.
Then one morning,
I get a paper cut
opening the mail.
Whatever, I go about my day.
I'm elbow deep in sauce,
and when I pull out my arm,
my Band-Aid's gone.
- [shivering] No.
- Yeah.
I can't tell Tony.
His cheap-ass isn't gonna buy
another barrel.
- Oh, my God.
- Six months go by.
This sub deal is still a hit.
One day, a customer
comes up to Tony,
opens up his sub,
and in the middle
of those peppers and onions
is my Band-Aid.
Are you crying?
- It's just so gross, I...
[whispers] I can't.
- You never have
to go back there, okay?
- [groans]
We got you.
And, hey.
You know you're our blood.
- You know that, right?
- I love you guys.
[children yelling,
cart rattling]
Mary Pat on your two.
- Hey, get in the car.
[children chattering]
That's good.
Thank you.
Thank you, guys.
- Okay, everyone's
all buckled in.
- Thank you.
Thank you.
So much.
Wow.
Thank you so much for the help.
I really appreciate it.
- $10,000.
- Yeah, that too.
- ♪ I let a stranger
in my bed ♪
- It's all there.
- [laughs]
- ♪ 'Cause I needed
to feel wanted ♪
- So we're good now, right?
♪
- Yeah.
Yeah, we're good.
- ♪ I gotta find
another way ♪
- Till next month.
- Excuse me?
- Whoa, I thought
this was a one-time deal.
- Yeah, I--I mean, I thought
I was a secret shopper.
- ♪ Another way
- Bye.
♪
- ♪ I'm trying to be better
♪ I'm learning again
♪ But I don't know
if I'm a giver ♪
♪ I don't know
♪
♪ I got so much soul
in my body ♪
♪ But no one
keeping me honest ♪
♪ And whole days turn
into holes in my mind ♪
♪ I got high hopes,
lots of potential ♪
♪ I'm high, broke,
searching for symbols ♪
♪ And I will not let go
of what is mine ♪
♪ I'm learning to live
♪ I'm trying to be better
♪ I'm learning to give
♪ But I don't know
if I'm a giver ♪