♪ (DRAMATIC MUSIC PLAYING) ♪
(CAR DOOR CLOSES)
(FILM CREW CHATTERING
INDISTINCTLY ON RADIO)
(MUTTERING)
DRIVER: Production,
Jessica's pulling into set
in a minute.
CREW MEMBER:
(OVER RADIO) Copy that.
♪ (MUSIC CONTINUES) ♪
♪ (MUSIC ENDS ABRUPTLY) ♪
(BIRDS TWITTERING)
MIRA LEVY: Yeah, I'm walking up
to the house now, okay, Ava?
AVA LEVY: (OVER PHONE)
But I can't find my...
MIRA: There's nothing
to worry about.
No. Nothing's gonna happen
to your dolls.
AVA: I've looked everywhere.
MIRA: Honey, I promise you.
AVA: But what if
she's not in the box?
Listen,
if you put Lucy in the box,
then that's where
she still is, honey.
-(AVA SPEAKING INDISTINCTLY)
-Mm-hmm. That's why we agreed...
JONATHAN LEVY:
I apologize for the delay,
but it was a--
it was a force majeure.
MIRA: Uh-huh.
Well, Daddy's here.
JONATHAN: It means that my wife
had a really important
meeting come up
-that she couldn't cancel.
-And he and I will make sure...
-JONATHAN: But she just arrived.
-(MOVER SPEAKING
INDISTINCTLY OVER PHONE)
...all of your stuff goes safely
on the truck, okay?
My wife, she just--
she just got here,
so you guys can come any time.
-(AVA SPEAKING INDISTINCTLY)
-MOVER: Okay, but we're not
gonna be there...
Okay. I'm going upstairs
right now. Right now.
-Wait, wait, wait. What?
-(MOVER SPEAKING INDISTINCTLY)
MIRA: Yeah.
I'm gonna check on your dolls.
JONATHAN: But first of all,
it's the afternoon.
It's not evening right now.
-All right. But I--
-Yes, I'm going--
No, not your--
not your new room.
Your old room, sweetheart.
-JONATHAN: Right. Well,
what are the evening rates?
-Okay. Oh, sw--
Ava, this is so good.
You did such a good job.
There's no way anyone
is ever gonna mix this up,
I promise.
JONATHAN: I'm totally happy
to compensate you for
the delay, but...
No. You know what?
I've got her in my hand.
I'm gonna put this box
in my car,
so it's not even gonna go
in the truck, okay?
-JONATHAN: No, no, no, not
tomorrow. It has to be today.
-(AVA SPEAKING INDISTINCTLY)
MIRA: I know, sweetheart,
but I promise you that--
If you just-- Are you there?
Ava?
-Honey?
-JONATHAN: Fine,
but I can't go tomorrow.
-VERONICA: Hey, Mira.
-Oh, hey, Veronica.
-(VERONICA TALKING INDISTINCTLY)
-Yeah, no. She's really angry.
JONATHAN:
No, I'll have cash for you
when you get here, okay?
It's good she's expressing it.
I mean, it's healthy,
but it's just,
-I didn't...
-Yeah. Yeah. That's good.
Six o'clock is fine, but please
no later than that, all right?
-VERONICA: Do you know
when you'll be done?
-I think I'll be done at 8:00?
JONATHAN: Yeah. All right.
See you soon. Thank you.
All right.
Thank you for everything. Bye.
(SIGHS) Hey.
JONATHAN: Everything okay?
Yeah. It's just
this fixation on her things.
I mean, it's normal.
Her therapist warned us
about it.
I just didn't realize
it would be this intense.
Yeah. You know,
I'm sure she's gonna feel
so much better once everything's
unpacked, and...
Mm-hmm. You don't think
I could find an Advil by chance?
I've got such a crazy headache.
JONATHAN: Um, I don't know.
Let me see, maybe...
MIRA: (SIGHING) Oh, God.
Maybe in the bathroom?
JONATHAN: Is Tylenol okay?
Uh, it'll have to be.
Okay. Here you go. Here.
-Thanks.
-You got a migraine?
I don't know yet.
It started in the middle
of my meeting with Ackerman.
JONATHAN: Hmm.
Well, Ackerman's a migraine
personified.
I don't know about that,
you know?
I think it's the stress of
having to leave in the middle.
We weren't exactly finished.
JONATHAN: Uh, yeah. Sorry.
Couldn't cancel the movers.
Okay. But I'm still
just a little unclear
why it had to be today.
Why? Because we agreed
to vacate on the 20th.
But why did we agree
to vacate on the 20th?
Because I'm leaving on a flight
the day after tomorrow.
Yeah, but you're only gone
for a week.
Well, nine days, actually.
Okay. So what's
the big deal, honey?
-What is it?
-Okay, okay, okay.
Let's just
get through this, okay?
Okay. Let's go downstairs.
Well, shouldn't we just
start here since we're already--
MIRA: No, we can do it later.
Okay.
But wait, wasn't it
just supposed to be a week?
I mean, how many lectures
are you doing? Just two, no?
Um, well, two in Berlin,
and then there's
the panel in Vienna.
-I showed you the itinerary.
-Right. Yeah. I just--
I better get used to you
traveling so much.
Well, it's not-- it's only
my second trip this year.
Yeah. Uh,
where are the documents?
-There.
-Okay.
It's just this last paper
really took off, you know.
-Yeah, it's great.
-JONATHAN: Yeah, it's crazy.
Yeah. Okay.
JONATHAN: Okay, yeah, so...
-(SIGHS)
-JONATHAN: There you go.
So here is the list
of items right here.
MIRA: Mm-hmm.
And here's
the settlement itself.
MIRA: Right.
Uh, which is exactly
what we agreed to with Jason.
Remember, he sent us the memo?
He emailed it to us last week?
Right? Okay?
And the only difference
is the amount we got
for the house, split in two,
minus the broker's fee.
In the last draft, it was blank.
Okay.
Uh, what is--
What am I supposed to--
JONATHAN: You'll sign by
the stickers, and then
-you'll initial each page.
-Right.
-JONATHAN: Wait,
hold on, hold on.
-No, I got it.
Wait, wait. We have to
look through all the items
and make sure everything's okay.
That's why we're doing it here.
-I'm just not up for this
right now, so...
-We'll do it really quickly.
We'll just go through it
quickly, then you'll sign,
and that's it. You'll be done.
You don't even have to wait
for the movers, okay?
No, I do. I promised Ava
I would be here to put--
make sure her boxes
got on the truck.
Well, then you have to wait
anyway, right?
So come on. Let's get started.
Okay. Okay. Fine.
(SIGHS)
-So what do the colors mean?
-Yeah.
Yellow's mine.
Um, red is yours.
-Okay.
-Blue is storage.
So they'll pack everything up,
and, uh,
then they'll unload
at my place first,
then you guys,
then the storage facility.
Okay?
Will Poli be home?
Will he be able
to help you unpack?
I'm not sure.
Uh-- didn't we say said that
I was gonna get the green couch?
Uh, actually, no, we didn't.
We didn't.
You said that you didn't want
any of the living room furniture
because you got all new stuff
at the tower.
No, I'm pretty sure we talked
about the green couch specifi--
-We didn't.
-Okay.
Do you want to?
You wanna talk about it?
I mean, like formally
in the settlement?
MIRA: It's fine.
It's just furniture.
Okay.
JONATHAN:
All right. All right. All right.
Okay. There you go.
Happy to do it.
Really. Okay?
How's your headache?
You need to lie down
for a moment?
-No. I'm fine.
-Okay.
You up for doing this?
We'll just go through
the house quickly
-and just get it done?
-No.
I'm not up for it, Jonathan.
JONATHAN: But you already wanted
to make an adjustment
to the thing.
-I just think it's important...
-I know. It's okay. I trust you.
I really do.
Just-- you do it. I trust you.
(SIGHS)
Is... is something wrong?
No. It's just, um,
it's been a shitty day,
you know?
-Yeah.
-It's really--
it's a horrible ending
to just a terrible day.
JONATHAN: What's horrible?
Oh, yeah. Well, yeah. Yeah.
No, I mean, it is-- it's a--
It is surprising
how something so formal
can have such an impact, right?
I mean,
it's just a piece of paper,
-just a fucking gett.
-MIRA: A "get"?
Yeah. It's, uh,
it's Hebrew for divorce papers.
Oh, yeah.
I think I remember that.
Although "give" would be
more like it.
-(SCOFFS) Yeah.
-Give up.
It's Aramaic for deed.
-MIRA: Mm.
-It's basically papers
that when I give them to you,
we're divorced.
-And that's it?
-JONATHAN: Yeah.
Yeah. But it's like--
it's a crazy,
traumatic ceremony.
-There's three judges.
-MIRA: Mm-hmm.
And, um,
you have to have witnesses
to testify that you are
who you say you are
and I am who I say I am.
It's humiliating.
-Is it gett with two Ts?
-Yeah.
And then you have to go
into this little room,
-and there's a guy in there...
-MIRA: Uh-huh.
...writing calligraphy
on parchment.
And he's writing out the text
of the gett.
-Yeah.
-JONATHAN: And it's--
it's like a thriller,
because the tiniest mistake
and you have to start
all over again.
And then, uh, and then you go
back in to the judges...
-MIRA: Mm-hmm.
-...and the witnesses.
And then I have to hand you
the gett in front of everybody
and yell a few sentences at you,
and then you hold it up high,
and you walk around the room
with it.
And then the judge rips it
to pieces.
-And there's more.
-Jesus.
JONATHAN: (LAUGHS)
Yeah, totally.
Why does it have to be
like that?
-Isn't it brutal enough?
-Well, I think there's a--
plenty of legal reasons,
but I think it just has to be
absolute and definitive.
That's the... you know.
-They don't like any gray areas.
-Mm.
JONATHAN: You're either in
or you're out.
And if you're out...
there's no going back.
-MIRA: Right.
-There's some logic to that, no?
MIRA: So what's it say?
It's like, um...
"This is your gett, and with it,
you are divorced from me
and hereby permitted
to all men."
To all men?
Thank you very much.
JONATHAN: Yeah.
Does all men include you?
No. No.
I'm not allowed to touch you
anymore
or even be in the same room
alone with you
-from that point on.
-Hmm.
JONATHAN:
It's over. Clean break.
And like, um...
What are-- are you...
allowed to marry me again?
JONATHAN:
Am I allowed to marry you?
In principle,
but only if you haven't been
with any other men.
-We are fucked.
-JONATHAN: Yeah.
-Hey.
-Hmm?
Come here.
-(MIRA CHUCKLES)
-Come here.
(SIGHS)
So basically, this is forbidden?
(CHUCKLES) Well,
we're not divorced yet.
(MIRA CHUCKLES)
Not yet.
(MIRA MOANS)
(BREATHES HEAVILY)
(PLASTIC RUSTLING)
(MIRA GASPS)
(BOTH BREATHING HEAVILY)
(GASPS)
(BOTH MOANING)
-(JONATHAN GRUNTS)
-Oh, yeah.
Oh, my--
(GASPS)
(JONATHAN GRUNTS)
(GROANS)
(PANTING)
(JONATHAN EXHALES)
-(PANTING)
-Okay.
No.
-Just--
-No, don't.
Don't go yet. Don't go yet.
Please.
Stay here.
(PANTING)
(VOICES CHATTERING DISTANTLY)
Penny for your thoughts?
(JONATHAN CHUCKLES)
It'll cost you a lot more
than that.
Are you hungry?
Yeah.
I'm always hungry.
Let's go out.
-What?
-Yeah.
-Really?
The movers are gonna be here
in 20 minutes.
We'll go to The Grille,
all right?
Back in 20 minutes.
-I want a steak.
-(LAUGHS)
Okay. Okay. Great. Let's do it.
-Okay.
-I'm just gonna...
Sure. Do your thing.
(GRUNTS)
What?
Nothing.
I should probably... (MUTTERS)
(CHUCKLES)
JONATHAN:
Just give me a second, okay?
Mm-hmm.
JONATHAN:
I'll be right back.
♪ (GENTLE MUSIC PLAYING) ♪
Right, so...
(WATER SPLASHING)
(CHUCKLES)
♪ (MUSIC CONCLUDES) ♪
JONATHAN: Okay.
Let's get these stupid papers
signed,
and we'll go get a bite to eat.
Pay tribute to a long
and happy marriage.
(CHUCKLES)
You can go home
straight from there, yeah?
Um, I think
I'm gonna take these home
and take a minute to go over it.
JONATHAN: What do you mean?
We went over it a hundred times.
MIRA: Yeah, but you have to read
a contract before you sign it.
Uh, no. Actually, you don't,
'cause that's the exact
same document
that we approved already.
All right. So what's--
Why does it have to be today?
Mira. Come on. We agreed, today.
-We agreed we'd do it today.
-It'll be tomorrow, I promise.
-JONATHAN: No, I c--
-MIRA: What's the big deal?
JONATHAN:
I cannot do it tomorrow
-because I'm getting ready
for my trip...
-Okay.
-...and I won't have time to
go down to the courthouse.
-That's fine.
-JONATHAN: So let's do it now.
-So it-- it'll be, um,
-when you get back.
-Oh, my God. I--
-I can't believe this.
-MIRA: What?
(SIGHS)
No. Okay. Okay.
Okay, here.
Sit down right here, okay?
Right now.
-Babe, I'm not--
-JONATHAN: Just listen.
Go over it. Go over it.
Take all the time you need.
I'm gonna get out of your way.
Just for fuck's sake,
get it over with.
Why are you talking to me
like that? What is wrong?
-JONATHAN: What's wrong is...
-Yeah?
...we went over it
a hundred times!
We spent months hashing it out,
-so what is your latest whim?
-Okay. Whoa. Okay.
-Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa.
-You can't, like...
We're here. We're--
We were just having
a really good time.
-Yeah.
-And we're about to go
get something to eat.
I don't think so.
I'm not going to, okay? No.
-Jonathan. Hey.
-No. Mira. Mira.
Please, get it over with.
I don't understand
what the big deal is.
What could be more rational
than wanting to take it
and go over it quietly at home?
So...
-Mm-hmm.
-(CHUCKLES)
-Okay.
-Yeah?
Yeah. Fine.
Fine. That's okay.
Forget about it, okay?
Just take it home.
Go over it quietly with Poli.
He's nobody's sucker,
that's for sure, right?
-Just make sure, you guys
can look through it...
-Jonathan.
...that I haven't, you know,
fucked you over
in some secret clause
or something
that I've put in there.
Go ahead. Just take it.
-Don't do this.
-JONATHAN: Fucking forget it.
It's fine. I don't care.
It's fine.
I don't understand what--
We were just so close
to each other.
Yup. Exactly.
Just so you know, if we're
talking about renegotiating,
it's a two-way street,
and there's plenty of stuff
in there that I'm not
crazy about either.
I'm not saying
that I wanna renegotiate.
I'm just saying I wanna read it.
-Okay.
-Okay?
-Just saying. I'm just saying.
-MIRA: Okay.
Jesus.
By the way,
since we're talking, um,
you haven't paid your half
of Ava's dance classes,
and they're bugging me about it.
All right.
I'll pay you right now.
No. Don't pay me.
Pay them what you owe them.
Your half. That's how it works.
Right. I will pay them.
How much is it?
I don't know.
Check with them.
Okay.
It's 2,500 dollars.
-What?
-Yeah.
What?
We moved her
into the intermediate group.
That's twice a week,
ballet and jazz.
Yeah. I know it's twice a week.
It was my idea.
JONATHAN: Okay, well,
that's how much it costs.
I don't know what
you want me to tell you.
You asked me to take care of it.
You didn't think
it was a little exorbitant or...
If I can afford it,
Mira, you can afford it too.
MIRA: Okay. It's not about
whether or not I can afford it.
-It's just...
-Okay.
It's outrageous, so--
Well, I guess
if that's what it costs,
then we'll just, you know,
we'll cut her back down
-to once a week.
-Okay. That's fine. Go for it.
Tell her that she can only go
once a week
and she's gotta choose
between ballet and jazz.
I'm fine with that.
Can't-- can you tell her that?
Why should I tell her that?
MIRA: Because I can't--
You know why.
I'm-- She's furious at me.
I'm walking a delicate line
with her.
Okay. Well, you know what?
Not giving her boundaries,
that's not gonna make it
any better.
Fine. Jonathan, I know
I'm a failure as a mother,
-but that's not really helping.
-JONATHAN: You know what,
instead of acting like a martyr,
-why don't you just try...
-Oh, my God.
...having an honest
conversation with her?
-She's seven years old.
-Give me a break!
-She's not a toddler anymore.
-You know things are shitty
between her and I right now,
-and your lecture isn't helping.
-Well, you have to-- Okay.
-Will you tell her or not?
-What do you want me
to tell her?
That her mother ran away
with some guy one day
and now she has to choose
between ballet and jazz?
Wow.
I hoped I'd never hear that
again.
I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I didn't--
That was unnecessary.
I'm sorry about that.
(SIGHS)
I'm sorry.
Is that what you tell her?
Is that the story
you tell her about me?
No. No. I don't--
I don't talk to her about that.
I don't ever talk to her
about the separation.
Okay.
Why, do you talk to her
about it?
No.
JONATHAN: It's fucked up.
I mean, I don't--
like, it's hard.
Where do we even begin to...
MIRA: I know, I wish we...
We don't even know
what's going on.
We just all grow up
illiterate about it.
Maybe we should've been
more prepared for it.
It's a fact that it doesn't
always end up that way.
I mean, it doesn't even
usually end up that way.
So how do you prepare
someone for that?
I don't know.
I think we should teach kids
that, yeah, love ends.
It's, uh...
Yeah, relationships end
and people leave
and they break up
and they divorce.
-And that's just a part of life.
-JONATHAN: Yeah.
And then maybe
it just wouldn't be so painful
and, uh, you know,
all the suffering.
I think the real suffering
is the in-between.
You know, the limbo,
neither here nor there, just...
I think that's way harder
than a breakup.
That's much more traumatic
for the kids
and for the parents.
At least,
that's how it is for me.
Mira, let's get this over with,
okay?
I'll--
I promise you that if you find
something in the document,
or if there's a mistake
in the settlement,
I won't contest it.
I'll write something right now
guaranteeing you that.
All right?
I don't understand.
I mean, what--
This isn't about
the money, right?
So what is...
I got fired.
JONATHAN: What?
Or I was-- I was invited
to resign.
Anyway, it's-- it's over.
(CLEARS THROAT)
I don't understand.
What do you mean?
MIRA: That's what my meeting
with Ackerman today was about.
Oh.
MIRA: Yeah.
(SIGHS)
I mean, it was kind of obvious
something like this could happen
ever since I didn't take
the London job. I mean, I was...
You were never gonna take
the London job.
MIRA: No, that's--
Okay, that's not accurate.
-And there were various
options to that.
-Mira. No, there--
There was no option, so...
Come on. I'm not blaming you.
That's not what this is about.
It's just like, you know,
when I didn't take the job,
then...
yeah, they didn't know
what to do with me.
Couldn't relocate. I couldn't
travel because of Ava.
And, you know, going, uh,
back to running
a product management team,
it just--
it seemed like a demotion.
So they started shopping me
around the company,
to find me a position.
-Nothing clicked.
-Yeah.
So this morning, uh,
he asked me for a meeting,
which he began by saying,
"Mira, I would like to set you
free for a new adventure."
(LAUGHS) Asshole.
I'm like,
"I'm 43 and half years old.
I'm one-half of a single parent.
What kind of new adventure
do you have in mind?
I mean, tell me the truth.
Tell me that you're firing me
because I no longer live
for this company,
I'm not at your beck and call
120 percent of the time
like I used to be.
You can't ask me to,
you know, go out,
entertain the clients anymore
because I'd rather be at home
with my kid.
And you know what,
maybe the new, young,
ambitious product manager
should take them out anyway,
because she's much more fun."
I guess the weird-- I was, uh...
You know, I was sitting
across from him and, um,
I could see in his eyes,
they were just like
switched off, you know?
I was invisible to him.
I used to have all this power
over him.
I could steer him
in whatever direction
I wanted him to go,
and now I was nothing.
And then I realized
that I, um...
I've lost that power
over everything.
You know, that power that comes
from, um, being desirous.
I sat at the table and I just--
I felt so disposable
and, uh... yeah,
so I really, I felt old.
So, that's it.
Yeah, I'm, uh...
There's a hearing in two weeks.
I have a severance, there'll be
stock options, and...
But that's it. That's--
You know, it's done.
I'm really sorry
that happened to you.
(LAUGHS)
You're sorry
that happened to me?
JONATHAN: Yeah. Yeah.
Okay. You don't need
to be polite.
JONATHAN: No. No. I'm not.
I, uh--
But, uh, I, uh, it's...
MIRA: What?
You know, it's weird.
What?
JONATHAN: I'm just-- I'm--
-I'm listening to everything
that you're saying...
-Uh-huh.
...and it's just--
it's not, uh...
You're right.
If circumstances were different,
I'd be fucking losing my mind
right now.
I'd be telling you
I was gonna murder Ackerman
-and...
-MIRA: Mm-hmm.
...be going crazy
with revenge fantasies.
-MIRA: Right.
-Yeah.
And I'm listening to you
right now,
and I don't... I don't feel...
anything.
Oh, wow.
Well, congratulations.
-I'm sorry.
-MIRA: No.
I don't-- I'm not trying
to be callous. I'm not.
I know that you're going through
a really hard time right now,
-but you asked, and that's...
-Yeah.
I'm sharing how I feel.
Well, how you don't feel.
(JONATHAN GROANS)
Half an hour
after you were inside me.
-JONATHAN: Yeah. It's a--
-Yeah.
JONATHAN: That was--
That's the weird part.
(CHUCKLES) Uh-huh.
But, honestly,
even when we were having sex,
-which was great. It was.
-MIRA: Mm-hmm. Mm-hmm.
-It really was, right?
-Yeah.
JONATHAN: And-- there was a part
of me that was observing myself
from the outside, checking in
to see like how I felt,
how I was feeling.
What if this was the last time?
What if I never even
see you again?
-MIRA: Mm-hmm.
-How do I feel?
Would it be so unbearable?
And no,
I realized I could do
without it.
-You didn't feel that way?
-Mm-mm. No.
Okay, it's just like,
I think about it a lot,
-you know?
-MIRA: Mm-hmm.
Because I do--
I do think that my...
extreme dependence on you,
that that's really what ruined
everything for us beyond repair
because that paralyzed me.
Hmm.
The thought of losing you,
the fear of losing you,
because that would mean
losing everything.
So I'm just saying that,
like when we were in the middle
-of that...
-Mm-hmm.
...I realized that that fear
wasn't there anymore.
That I was free from you
at last--
Okay. I don't wanna--
I don't wanna hear anymore.
I mean, it's not really
the right time
for a therapy session.
You don't have to blurt out
-whatever pops in your head.
-Shut the fuck up.
Just shut up.
Like, what... what is this?
What is this sarcasm
and this fucking toxic shit?
Who are you to say
when the time is right
and when the time is wrong?
-Why do you get to decide that?
-While you tell me
you just fucked me
in order to prove yourself
that you don't love me anymore?
I'm trying to talk to you.
I'm trying to tell you something
about--
No. You're a fucking narcissist.
This isn't sharing.
This is you vomiting your stream
of consciousness all over me.
You don't give a fuck
how it makes me feel.
That is such bullshit.
I-- Mira, there--
I have never had an inch
of emotional space
-to share about my feelings
with you.
-Oh, my God.
If I hear one more word
of this psychobabble,
-I'm gonna scream. (LAUGHS)
-Well, go ahead, scream.
Scream. You've always been
much better at that
than actually communicating,
-than actually having
a conversation.
-MIRA: Right.
And you're surprised
they fired you?
It's a miracle they kept you
this long
-when you never learned...
-Shut up!
JONATHAN: ...how to actually
communicate.
I fucking hate you.
Wow. Okay.
I hate fucking you too,
so everything you said just...
Well, you know what,
it didn't seem like that
-a second ago, but...
-Oh, my God, you moron.
You think because you
fucked me like that one time,
-it suddenly makes you--
-Mira, just stop it.
Oh, what? Oh, sorry.
God, I said fucked.
I forgot I'm not allowed
to say that.
-What are you talking about?
-Oh, is it allowed now?
Am I allowed to say cock,
pussy, and cum,
and all those bad words
without you, you know,
running out of the room?
You are so out of touch
with my life.
It's actually really sad.
-MIRA: Oh, really?
-Yeah.
MIRA: So all of your religious
hang-ups are just like gone?
-What?
-'Cause a minute ago, you--
you sprinted to the shower after
'cause, you know, bodily fluids
gross you out.
So what's different?
It's actually none
of your business.
MIRA: But why?
We're sharing, right?
So now I'm gonna share with you
how shitty it felt
to pretend
like I wasn't a sexual person,
because for you,
I knew it would turn you off.
Feeling depraved every time
I wanted to fuck you
because for you
it was "complicated."
And I tried not to
take it personally.
I did. I said,
"Okay. It's not about me.
It's who you are.
It has to do with you,
-where you're from."
-You know what amazes me,
is that I actually
really bought it.
I believed you. I believed that
I was hopelessly screwed up.
MIRA: Right.
And I could've lived
my entire life not realizing
that everything
that you've despised me for...
Mm-hmm.
...everything that you hated
about me,
somebody else would love me
for exactly the same thing.
They would accept me
for exactly who I am.
Well, either they're lying
or they're very inexperienced.
(SCOFFS)
You're so fucking twisted.
You are the most twisted person
that I have ever known.
And not a day goes by
that I don't thank God...
-Sure.
-...that I realized
-how amazing sex can be...
-Oh, my God.
...and I didn't have
to waste my life.
You are the most asexual person
I ever met,
and you made a thousand
theories to justify it.
JONATHAN: It's true!
And you know what, it turns out
all I needed was a woman
who actually wanted me as I am.
And I had to teach you
everything about sex.
That's exactly right!
That's exactly the problem.
You taught me,
and you managed me,
and you told me how we would
do it and when would do it,
-and everything about it.
-MIRA: Oh, my God.
-That's so unreal.
-And you'd scold me.
You would scold me
like a fucking child.
You know, I think of
all the mistakes
we've made in our life.
The biggest, that we got
together in the first place.
JONATHAN: Okay. Well then,
let's fix our mistake.
Let's sign these papers so
we can get the fuck out of here.
-MIRA: Bring them to me. I will.
-Happy to.
(RAIN PATTERING)
Here you go.
(THUNDER RUMBLES)
Initial on each page.
Sign by the stickers.
Yeah, I heard--
I heard you the first time.
Great.
Stop staring at me.
I can't concentrate.
Okay. Whatever you need.
(CLEARS THROAT)
(WHISPERING) Okay.
(SIGHS)
You don't wanna sign it.
MIRA: I'm trying to skim it.
You're doing everything you can
to distract...
Mira, you've read it
a hundred times.
-You don't wanna sign it.
-Fuck off.
JONATHAN:
You don't want to get a divorce.
That's what this is about.
What I'm trying to figure out
is if you already knew that
before you got here today.
Jonathan, please.
My head's pounding. Just...
Will you just say it?
Will you just say it, please?
Say it. You don't want to.
-Just say it.
-I just can't.
I wanna come home.
(THUNDER RUMBLES)
God, don't look at me like that.
I know. I'm just--
I know what this looks like.
(SIGHS) Oh, man.
I don't, like--
MIRA: You can think
whatever you want about me.
I guess there's nothing
more pathetic
-than what I'm doing now.
-Just-- like how do you--
What-- wh-- wh-- what...
How are you not ashamed?
I've never been more ashamed
in my whole life.
JONATHAN: I don't-- like--
So...
I don't know.
So should I be expecting
another surprise call from Poli?
Does he know that you're here?
Just help me.
Help me understand
what your thinking is here.
So if I said, "Okay. Yeah.
Great. Let's forget it.
Let's get back together."
You-- what?
You'll go back home to Poli
and tell him what exactly?
There's no Poli.
We broke up two weeks ago.
It's over. And he's in Tel Aviv.
Okay.
MIRA: I haven't told Ava yet,
so please don't say anything
to her.
He's gonna come back next week
to say goodbye.
I'm gonna, um, pick her up
on Wednesday
and we'll tell her together.
Please, please don't do that
unless you're absolutely sure
that it's over, okay?
It's over.
Um, you know,
for a long time now,
we've been having these really,
uh, vicious fights.
After the last time I was here,
he gave me an ultimatum.
He said, uh,
either we're having a kid or,
um, we're breaking up.
Well, kids, plural. It was not--
it wasn't just one.
And I guess I agreed.
Eventually, I gave in
and we tried for six months,
and nothing happened.
Then we went
to Dr. Varona, and...
she said that, uh,
I should start IVF as soon as--
sooner rather than later
'cause of my age.
And, uh...
somehow I just-- I kept delaying
picking up the prescription.
And, eventually, Poli,
he was like, um...
"You don't want this.
It's not happening,
and it isn't gonna happen
because, um,
you don't wanna have my kid...
'cause you'll always see me
as the guy
who broke up your family."
And we went to counseling
and on the first session,
the, um, therapist, she--
you know, she asked me
if I thought that, um...
I could ever give up on you.
You know, if I could, um,
accept that it was over.
I didn't say anything.
And, um, I just--
was just silent.
And in the second session,
it was obvious
that the relationship was done,
but it took Poli another week
to accept that.
I don't know if you care.
And, yeah, I'm sure you think
this is probably
another manipulation.
I'm too tired to try to convince
you otherwise, so just...
-do with it what you want.
-Do with it what I want?
What-- what--
What do you expect me
to do with it?
MIRA: I don't know.
-JONATHAN: Uh-huh.
-I'm not trying to--
I'm not trying to
talk you into it,
'cause you've made yourself
pretty clear.
I'm just saying that, um...
I mean, I know it would be
different this time.
Right.
MIRA: We both have so much more
self-knowledge now and, um,
that has to make a difference,
don't you think?
No, I don't think.
MIRA: Why not?
Like how can you be so sure?
Because, Mira,
you don't want me.
You got fired and you got
dumped, and so you just...
No, I didn't--
I didn't get dumped. I just--
You're not listening to me.
I just told you what happened.
It doesn't matter.
It really doesn't matter.
But why?
Why doesn't it matter?
I'm trying to tell you
something about how I feel
and about how I felt for you
this whole time.
-Mm-hmm.
-Like, why doesn't that matter?
And I know that you feel it too.
-I know you do.
-Okay.
-And maybe the fact that
we haven't been able to...
-You don't-- you don't, like--
...extricate ourselves from each
other's lives all this time,
I mean, that means--
it means something.
You didn't absorb a single word
that I said to you before,
and I don't know
how to get it through to you
that I don't have feelings
for you anymore.
I don't. I'm sober.
I'm inoculated. That's it.
I know you're angry.
And, um...
-JONATHAN: Oh, my God
-I'm just like asking that,
you know, you just take
a second to think about it.
-And I'm not saying
it's immediately gonna...
-Mira, what the fuck?
But like maybe you--
when you're in Europe.
JONATHAN: What do you think?
You think I'm just gonna
throw away all the progress
that I made
over the last two years
just 'cause you-- I mean--
(SCOFFS)
You know--
do you wanna something?
You know that there was a period
where I started praying?
Like actually praying to God
for you to come back?
After you came over to the house
that one time and you just--
Yeah!
I was laying right over there
with Ava
waiting for her go to sleep,
so that I could talk to you,
try to convince you.
And I heard the door slam...
and I wanted to kill you
all over again.
And somehow I found myself
right here
in the middle of this kitchen,
just like with my eyes closed
swaying, praying to God...
that you would come back to me.
(LAUGHS)
So you got me to pray again.
That was unexpected.
Can I have some?
It's pineapple vodka.
It's revolting.
I don't know
who brought it here.
I can take it.
Thanks.
Can I have more?
(GAS COOKER LIGHTING)
(JONATHAN SIGHS)
-Look...
-(EXHALES)
You should be happy for me.
You really should.
That I'm finally rid
of this dybbuk, you know?
It's better that I'm over it,
for both of us.
And I know you're gonna
get through too, honestly.
-(LAUGHS) No.
-JONATHAN: Yes. I do know that.
And it can be a new chapter
for you.
You can start a whole new life.
It could be a really
exciting time for you.
Yeah.
Let me tell you one thing.
I have zero interest
in my new life. I mean, zero.
I have no curiosity about it,
and I...
I have no motivation
to start anew.
You're saying that
from where you are right now
after just getting fired
and everything that's happening.
No. It's not about now.
It's like all the time.
-JONATHAN: Yeah.
-All I want is what I--
what I used to have.
I don't want anything new.
Please. Don't. Don't. Don't.
-Why?
-Mira.
Look, you know me better than
anybody else on this planet,
so I'm not gonna try to hide
from you the fact
that I do have that urge, okay?
I have that urge to say,
"Fuck it. Let's just..."
-Yeah.
-"...tear up these papers.
Let's do it.
Let's start again," right?
I mean, I have been waiting
two years for this very moment.
-Right.
-But I have to fight it.
-We both have to fight it.
-No, we don't.
Yes, we do, because
it's never going to work.
I'm not in that place anymore,
and you're not in that place.
But, but we can find
our way back,
I think that's
what we're doing right now.
No, that's not
what we're doing.
Look, just because there's
this thing that happens
whenever we see each other,
that doesn't mean anything.
-It's a mirage.
-No, no.
And I know
that after a day passed,
after the excitement passes,
we would look at each other
and we'd think,
-"What the fuck did we do?"
-No.
We can't live
in the same house together.
-And by then it'd be too late
because we--
-(PHONE VIBRATES)
-It's not gonna happen again.
-Listen. Listen to me, please.
I've never been more sure
of anything in my life.
Just trust my instincts
for once.
-Okay? Okay?
-(PHONE VIBRATES)
-But...
-I'm sorry. Hold on.
I have to just check this
'cause I think--
I think there's, um...
Oh, fuck. The movers just--
They're running late.
And you have to call Veronica.
She's been trying to call you.
Oh.
(JONATHAN SIGHS)
MIRA: Hey, Veronica.
(VERONICA SPEAKING
INDISTINCTLY ON PHONE)
MIRA: No, no. It's ok--
It's no problem.
Just, you know, let me
talk to her. (CLEARS THROAT)
-AVA: Hi, Mommy!
-MIRA: Hey, Ava.
(AVA SPEAKING
INDISTINCTLY ON PHONE)
MIRA: Sweetheart,
if you made a mistake
with the boxes, you know,
that's easy to fix.
We can just, you know...
(AVA SPEAKING INDISTINCTLY)
But, honey, you and Daddy
can like--
you can make
that decision tomorrow
when you see the new house.
(AVA SPEAKING INDISTINCTLY)
Because, uh,
tomorrow's Wednesday, honey.
You're-- you know,
you're with me today.
(AVA SPEAKING INDISTINCTLY)
Yeah, I know you were, but, um,
Tuesday switches every week.
So, yeah, just check your chart,
okay?
I know, but, you know,
that's what we decided on, so--
-AVA: Please.
-Oh, Ava.
-VERONICA: Mira...
-Oh, hey, Veronica.
No, no, no, no. She doesn't--
if she doesn't wanna talk to me,
so that's okay.
(VERONICA SPEAKING INDISTINCTLY)
MIRA: Um, I think
maybe an hour or so.
VERONICA: Okay. Bye.
Okay. Bye.
(CRYING)
JONATHAN:
Why don't you go home, honey?
I've got everything
under control here, okay?
(SOBS)
Calm down. Get going, okay?
What about the settlement?
JONATHAN:
Forget about the settlement.
Let's just toss it.
-But wh--
-It's not important. I--
It's not worth it.
It was-- it was important, but--
to get it done today,
but, uh, not at this cost.
But why was it so important
to you?
JONATHAN: Doesn't matter now.
Just tell me. Please.
Just say it. Why?
Well, I thought that maybe
I wanted to have another kid.
(MIRA GRUNTS)
JONATHAN: Suddenly I realized
that it's the thing
that brings me the most joy
in my life.
I'm good at it.
I want Ava to have a sibling.
And I'm not willing to wait
for the love of my life
or whatever.
And in therapy,
it came up, actually,
that having another kid
was more important to me
than having another partner.
And I was having lunch
with, uh, Celia Patterson,
-from my department?
-MIRA: Mm.
Her and her girlfriend
just split up and, uh...
Well, it came up
that she was in the process
of looking for a partner,
a man, for, um...
What's it called? Um...
Elective co-parenting,
which-- yeah.
And kind of
as a joke, she was like,
"You'd be perfect.
What about you?"
So you're gonna have a kid
with Celia Patterson?
JONATHAN: I don't know. Maybe.
I mean, not necessarily her.
But it's a--
it's a cleaner situation
to go into that arrangement
officially divorced.
But I'm not gonna put
that stress on you right now.
-No.
-JONATHAN: No. I mean...
it's not really...
I'm just asking, you know?
All this thinking, you know,
you've been doing
about having a kid
with whoever...
Um...
Even occur to you
to have it with me?
With you?
(CHUCKLES)
Honestly, it never occurred
to me that you would want to.
MIRA: Why not?
-Why not?
-Yeah.
Are you punishing me
for the abortion?
JONATHAN: Mira, what? No.
What are you talking about? I--
There's nothing
that would make me believe
-that you would want to.
-But I would.
I mean, I'm not gonna--
I'm not gonna say that
we made a mistake back then.
I didn't think
we could handle it,
you know, back then.
I didn't think our marriage
could survive another kid.
I know. Joke's on me. (CHUCKLES)
But that's the truth, so...
JONATHAN: I believe you.
And we're in a different
place now.
-Yeah.
-MIRA: Yeah.
Yeah.
We're in a different place.
We're not the same people.
You know, we're not, uh,
young anymore. We're not...
You mean, I'm not young anymore?
-No. That's not what I said.
-MIRA: That's what you meant.
-JONATHAN: No. No. That's not...
-Yeah.
No, that's--
it's not about you at all, Mira.
-MIRA: Okay.
-What I'm trying to do is see
if there's a way to undo
this paradigm
where having a kid is bound
to having a romantic partner
because then maybe I'd be free
to think about...
Free to keep fucking around
and still get to have a kid?
Is that the idea? No?
'Cause it's wrapped up in
so much psychological bullshit,
I'm still trying--
I'm just trying to understand
what you're actually saying.
Is it that
your successful therapy
has turned you
into an egocentric asshole
who, you know, just does
whatever the fuck
he feels like...
-Okay. We're done.
-...and then doesn't even--
What do you mean?
Here's the tip for the movers.
MIRA: No. You're not leaving.
-JONATHAN: What's the balance?
-Come on.
JONATHAN:
They should know the route,
but if there's any problems,
just have them call me.
MIRA: Jonathan.
Otherwise,
I'm sure you can handle it.
MIRA: Okay.
Just hold on a second.
Let's talk for a minute, okay?
JONATHAN: About what?
Haven't you had enough?
I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
I'm sorry I lashed out.
I'm really strung out, okay?
JONATHAN: It's okay.
I understand.
Okay. We can't end it like this.
I mean, you can't just leave,
okay?
Jonathan, listen,
you can't drop a bomb like that
and just leave.
-Okay, we'll do it another time.
-No. No.
-We're gonna talk about it
right now. Right now.
-Mira, you need to calm down.
-Mira, let me go.
-Because this affects
all of our lives.
-It affects Ava's life.
-I'm done. I'm done, okay?
MIRA: Okay. Um, okay.
Just-- I'm not gonna let it end
like this, okay?
Please. I'm really sorry.
-I said something really nasty.
-JONATHAN: Okay. Okay.
MIRA:
I'm sorry. I didn't mean it.
I got that.
I got that, okay? Okay.
-All right. Let me go now.
-Okay. Okay.
So-- no, no, no. Just take
a second to take a breath.
-Just a breath! For a second,
just take a breath!
-You need to let me go. Stop.
Give me the key.
No. Just, you know--
like just take a second,
-just like...
-Mira...
I mean, let's talk
for a little bit.
-Like, what's your problem?
-Can you just--
-MIRA: No!
-Give me the key. Mira, stop.
MIRA: Stop.
JONATHAN: Give me the key.
MIRA: No.
-No. Stop it.
-(GROANS)
JONATHAN:
Stop. Stop it. Stop. Stop it.
(MIRA SCREAMS)
(MIRA GRUNTS, SOBS)
(JONATHAN GROANING)
Wait. Wait. (GROANS)
(GLASS CLATTERS)
(PANTING)
-(JONATHAN SPITS)
-(TAP RUNNING)
(CLEARS THROAT)
(MIRA SIGHS)
(JONATHAN GROANS)
We should have done that
a long time ago.
(CAR LOCK BEEPING)
♪ (TENSE MUSIC PLAYING) ♪
(TRUCK APPROACHING)
(MOVER SPEAKING RUSSIAN)
(MOVERS CHATTERING
INDISTINCTLY IN RUSSIAN)
♪ (TENSE MUSIC PLAYS) ♪
-(CAR ENGINE STARTS)
-(SEATBELT ALARM BEEPS)
(SEATBELT ALARM BEEPING)
(ALARM STOPS)
♪ (TENSE MUSIC CONTINUES) ♪
(BIRDS CHIRPING)
(BIRDS TWITTERING)
♪ (MUSIC CONCLUDES) ♪