Driver's phone just went off.
What? What? What happened?
They're switching the sim cards.
If you can't read their phone messages,
then you're not gonna know
when they're gonna meet. So...
We'll find another way.
Did you, or did you not,
follow the rules we gave you?
Sarah doesn't like
me changing numbers.
Sarah?
Have you been working at the tap?
Hi. Hi.
I mean, of all the places,
Braden Moore owns the tap.
You've risked the entire operation.
Four shots. Whooping
good morning. I have an appointment.
You understand how dangerous
this is, becoming an informant?
What are you doing?
Am I late?
No, no, we're early.
How are you?
I'm good.
Yeah? Yeah. I'm fine.
Are you sure?
Yeah.
Now that you're working with us,
it's better that we meet
away from the station. Ok?
Why are we meeting?
Who is this?
A person of interest. Have
you seen him at the pub?
No. Why do you wanna know?
We just need to know if you've seen him.
We think the gang might
have been in contact with him,
and that worries us.
But we really can't tell you anything else.
Ok. I will look out for him.
Yeah? Just while you're doing
your normal duties at the pub.
Don't put yourself in harm's way, ok?
Has something happened?
Er...
Do you...? Ok, the other day,
Braden and Liam, they took my phone.
They took your phone?
Did they see anything?
No. No. I always delete our messages.
You know you don't have to do this.
There must be other jobs you can do.
No, no. I have to do this.
I cannot go back to scraping that oven.
I'm ok. I know what I'm doing. Ok.
Text me any time.
All right. Go easy, yeah?
And remember that face.
Thank you.
Alison.
The password's 2-7-9-1. Help yourself.
I'm sorry.
Look, I was an idiot.
Yeah. I still am.
Yes, you were. Can I explain?
Explain what, exactly?
We've got a bit of business we
need sorting, don't we, manc?
Door closes.
Mark...
Yeah? My mum just texted me,
and she's locked herself
out, and she needs my keys.
What you standing around
for? Go and help her.
Thank you. And I'm so sorry.
No, it's ok. No worries.
Four on every floor. At least.
Shame you can't manage them.
Muffled speech hey, don't shit yourself.
I've got it covered.
And inside the vault...
Muffled speech he's done this before.
He'll need detailed specs.
He will. But for now, we've got these.
They don't hold back, do they?
First time I've seen a photo.
Worth the effort, right?
Joseph, I know you don't wanna
keep going back, but we need to.
Speak to your insider.
She mouths
muffled speech.
Phone vibrates phone
clatters phone vibrates
vibrating continues
vibrating continues.
Are you ok? Yeah.
Are you sure they didn't see you?
Yeah, I'm sure they didn't see me.
I told you not to go out
of your way to watch them.
Yeah, but you told me to look
out for the man in the photo,
and I thought they might be meeting him.
I was very clear.
Alison, it's my responsibility
to keep you safe,
and if you're not gonna play by the rules,
then this isn't gonna work.
Do you understand?
Yes. But this is what I got.
"Llama treasure plates"? Yeah.
Live subtitles do this all the time.
You get used to it.
The app works by sorting the
sounds into nearest phonetics,
so "llama treasure plates"...
Is that right, Alison? "Llama
treasure plates" could be...
Pressure. Treasure. Treasure. Pressure.
Pressure plates. Maybe
llama could be "alarm".
Alarm is good. Alarmed pressure plates.
That works. What about the
next bit? "Person lies ash waves".
Personalised.
Personalised, but "ash waves"...
Personalised. But "ash
waves", I don't know.
So, if the pressure plates
are on the floor... yeah.
Ash waves could be "pathways".
This bit's clear.
They're using weight-sensitive vaults
and dealing with
high-net-worth individuals.
They need help from an insider.
They're trying to arrange a
meeting, can you see that?
And your app thinks the meeting is at.
"Eye centre dense rude".
Any guesses for that one?
Didn't think so.
Ok, so, guys, Ben, Nia, absolutely critical
that we are at that meeting, yeah?
So all hands to the pump,
trying to decode where the hell that is.
And who is this insider
that they're meeting?
Let's try and figure
that out, yeah? Yes, sir.
Yeah.
This is way beyond anything
we could have asked for.
This is brilliant.
Thank you.
Ok.
And in the meantime, while we're
trying to figure out the location...
Keep an eye out at the tap?
Anything you can get, we appreciate.
Go on.
'Hello. This is Joe from access to work.
'I'm just calling to let you know
we've received your application,
'and the current wait
time for an assessment
'is 16 to 18 weeks, whereby
you will be assigned...'
Just give me both barrels.
Well, how do think it feels
for a woman to be alone with two men
while they're looking through her phone?
Violating, I'd imagine.
Yeah.
I'm sorry that Braden scared you.
No, he didn't.
I fucked up. No excuse.
For me.
Trust, it don't come easy.
Just... just let me explain.
Are you working with Braden?
He's involved in my new work.
I owe him. He's letting
me stay in his flat.
Ok. Good luck with that.
Please.
Just one drink.
I'm sorry.
Well, we're closed.
I have a few tinnies at mine.
You spoil me.
Don't expect much.
Yeah. Tinnie?
Yeah. Yeah.
Thank you.
To second chances?
You said you were going to explain.
So... why don't you
tell me about you, then?
What do you wanna know?
Why you don't trust people.
All right.
I know what it's like to be scared.
I haven't seen my dad for years.
But... he left a Mark.
Several, actually.
Sometimes, I think I
see him in the street.
Can hardly breathe, you know?
Getting ready to, like, run or fight.
So, where is your dad?
He fucked off when I was a kid.
And then I ended up just
pin balling between foster homes.
I've calmed down a lot since then,
but whenever I meet someone
who gives me the time of day,
I'm still like...
"What's wrong with them?"
And then I met someone like you.
Alison laughs
you know, you have beautiful eyes.
Laughs so now you're pissed.
Doesn't make it any less true.
You know, apparently,
every Iris is completely unique,
like a fingerprint.
Really?
What makes you think of this stuff?
You.
Me?
Staring at me with those big old...
Those... I'm not staring.
Yeah, you are. No. No, I'm not.
Sorry. I know it's not
because I'm that handsome.
Is that right?
Spent my entire life not being looked at.
No, I get that.
When I get a bit lost and
people say, "never mind,"
or, "I'll tell you later,"
but they never do,
that's when I feel
ignored, and I hate that.
You are, by the way.
What?
That handsome.
Phone vibrates.
You know...
It's pretty fucked up to read
someone else's messages.
So now we're even, then.
Now we're even.
I should go.
Thank you.
Distant siren wails.
Sorry...
Hi. Sorry.
Sorry about the carnage in here. Hi.
Ok, how did you find out that
they're meeting at the ice rink?
Right, I saw a text on Liam's phone.
He left it on the bar
before he went to the toilet.
Who was the text from?
An unknown number. It
wasn't stored in his phone.
And he was at the bar? Yeah.
Do you talk a lot with Liam?
Yeah, because how else
can I get close to him?
Alison, I've.
I say this from experience.
That what is exciting isn't
always what's best for you.
Yeah.
But why are they meeting at the ice rink?
Because... it's unexpected.
Music blares and because
surveillance is a nightmare.
Loud music, bad
audio, lots of movement.
Scraping, music plays
so... You need me?
Rap music plays
we're not gonna get
any audio through this.
Glitchy audio playback
yeah. They've chosen this venue
for a reason, haven't they? Yeah.
It's because this meeting is significant.
6-0-1 in position. No eyes yet.
Ok, where are we at
with the visual, 6-0-2?
6-0-2. Nothing yet.
Come on.
There. Top screen.
'6-0-1. I have a visual.
'Hulk, Cruella and hoodie
entering via north door.'
Yeah, but we're gonna
need more than that.
That's no good. Yeah.
Can we get a clearer visual?
6-0-2. We'll try.
6-0-1. On it.
What about that screen there?
We're gonna need more than that.
Yeah, we are.
Ok, can we get a clearer visual, please?
No, I can't see their
faces clearly. Can you...?
Come on, guys.
They're here.
'6-0-2. New contact with
wolf and unknown ic-4 female
'in a Navy blazer.'
Up there. Did you hear that,
Nia? Unknown ic-4 female.
Working on it. Thank you.
Fuck's sake. Ok... What's happened?
The screens have gone completely
dead our end. What's going on?
Not now. Not now, guys.
'6-0-1. Sorry, we'll reset.'
they're back on. Thank god for that. Ok.
Beep there we go.
Ok. Anything you can get on that
woman there in the Navy blazer,
anything at all. Blue jacket.
Alison, if you just focus on this one
and just tune everything else out.
Wolf said, "this is a friend of mine."
"We go a long way back."
Something, something.
"I trust her."
He says her name. Which is?
Sand... sand... I think
it's Sandra. Brilliant.
And then he said her last name.
I think it's with b or m. I don't know.
But it ended with, like, a "sh". Brilliant.
Ok, Nia, check any kind of Sandra.
All associates known to Cruella, to wolf.
Cross-check with all associates.
Anything else you can get,
anything at all, that's great.
Alison mutters.
"I've been doing this
for a very long time."
"I'm very good at it."
Yeah, well, we'll fucking
see. That's what Cruella said.
Yeah.
Package. They're talking about package.
Hoodie says they need to wait.
Yeah.
To the gram... No, no, no.
He said the exact weight.
Ok. The weight? The exact...
The exact weight. I think
he said "to the gram".
To the gram? Yes.
That'll be to get around
the weight-sensitive vault.
Maybe they need something to stand in
for whatever it is they're stealing.
Meeting... meeting over. It's breaking up.
They're breaking up now. Yeah.
Chandra.
How do you spell it? C-h-a-n-d-r-a.
Ok. Ok. I think we've got an ID
on the woman in the Navy blazer.
She's chandra bakshi. Yes!
That's it. Chandra
bakshi. She is the insider.
She works on the
transport team of a billionaire
by the name of Amir joshi.
Amir joshi? So he's the target.
He's head of one of the
wealthiest families in India,
and he's just arrived in the UK.
Whatever the gang is stealing,
Amir joshi has brought it with him.
Sir. What have we got?
Ben, Amir joshi, we know
him? Yes. We know him, sir.
We know this guy? Ok. And
he just touched down in London
for a quarterly meeting with his investors.
He arrived on the 7th of
September. On the 7th? Yes.
Which was the opening of the
window for the gang's robbery.
Ok, so let's get a full
profile on Amir joshi.
I wanna know his
business, his associates,
which security companies he uses.
Find out which vault he uses in Mayfair.
Do we notify him or his team?
No. We already know
he's got one insider,
so there may well be others,
but let's just hang
back for the time being,
until we get more information. Very good.
I got it? You got it.
Thanks to you. This is great.
Thank you.
It's good.
Let's go. Thanks, Alison.
Alison, I'll walk you out.
Just through there.
Problem?
Yeah. It's about Alison.
She did very well today.
She's good. She's really
good, there's no doubt.
But that's... That's what worries me.
'She's invested.' 'Meaning?'
'well, this is a bit beyond
the call of duty for a civvy.'
before Alison, we were pissing
in the wind. You know that.
Now we have a case,
no? It's that simple.
But is it simple? Yeah.
Because it's our duty
to protect her. Protect!
It is. Would you be saying that
if our source wasn't deaf?
I don't know. Yeah, I think... Yeah?
Yeah, I would. I would.
'Alison, she's smart, she's capable.
'I just... we know Braden is
in contact with a gun runner.'
I have got a bad feeling about it.
Ok. So, fine, so we keep
a close eye on her, right?
But we need this.
Right? We really need this. Understand?
Yeah. Course, guv.
You make pub friends fast.
Well, I'm new here.
Can't be too discriminating.
Charming.
How about I take you on a
proper date tomorrow night?
I mean, no pressure, just if you want to.
Course. I would like that.
I'll find somewhere, let you
know and text you the plan.
See you later. See you later.
Hey, what can I get for you?
Hiya. Can I get a pint of
Bobby's biscuit, please?
Yeah. Thanks.
That'll be 6.99.
Card machine beeps
thank you.
What are you looking at?
What?
You've got customers.
Almost done.
'So, tell me, what exactly did you see?'
the man in the photo
gave a bag to Braden.
And then Braden gave
it to Mark to store it.
And then he looked really scared.
I think they used the word "guns".
What, you think, but you're not sure?
But "gun" is a difficult word.
It could be fun, it
could be gun, it... right.
But I think it is "gun".
Ok. And the bag, is it in the pub now?
It could be.
Could be. But you're not sure?
Ok, all right, I'm sorry
to press you on this.
It's just if there is a weapon,
we legally can't ignore it.
But they will know that
someone has told you.
We will sort it, ok, Alison?
I just... You need to
stay away from the tap.
Just stay away for the day
and, I don't know, go and see a friend.
Do something normal. Ok?
Ok. Ok.
'We think this is the likeliest target.'
very subtle. Where'd
you get the images?
Auctioneers. Joshi's been in
touch with the top three in London.
He's obviously looking to sell.
A weapon, when we're this
close, is all we need, isn't it?
But we can't ignore the intel.
Yeah. If it was a gun.
We move in now, they
shut the whole plan down.
We blow our cover for
nothing. Yeah, agree.
We need to play it carefully.
Time we did a drug check on the tap.
Afternoon.
What are you doing here?
I'm visiting my favourite employee.
Should my ears be burning?
Well.
I can't say the conversation
has been flowing,
but she makes a stern cuppa, your mum.
Clicks his tongue
dad legged it, has he?
How do you know he's not gonna
walk through that door at any moment?
He chuckles there's
no man at this house.
I am made up that Liam
is getting his leg over.
But I don't like you.
I don't trust you.
So stay out of the way
when working at my pub.
Thanks again, mrs Brooks!
No wonder your dad left.
Would drive me up the
wall, living with you lot.
Ds Sara burns. How are you?
Good, yeah.
Sara clears her throat
we have a search warrant issued
under the misuse of drugs act.
What's going on here?
It's an illegal substance
check, sir. What?
It's a standard check. A dealer
was caught in the alleyway outside.
Go. Thanks.
I swear to fucking
god, this is not me, bray.
Course not. You wouldn't be that thick.
Not with your family to think about.
Can I come in?
You didn't turn up.
I waited an hour for you.
I thought before, we
had a real connection.
After everything I told you...
Well, not everything is about you.
You don't know anything about my life.
Why do you think I asked you out?
I want to. I want to know everything.
Well, we're getting evicted. You
didn't know about that, did you?
Shit.
I... I'm sorry.
You're involved in something illegal?
Just don't lie to me.
It's not what you think.
What is it, then?
I can't.
Do you hurt people?
No. That's not who I am.
Then who are you?
I will tell you. But I need more time.
Please.
You can't throw this away
before it's had a chance to...
That's exactly why I'm doing it.
Knock on door.
All right, bray? Mind if I come in?
Course not.
What you doing?
What is that?
Something I'm very glad I
decided not to keep at the pub.
If it's what I think it is, I
don't want it in my flat.
This ain't your flat.
When did you put it there? Last night.
I've got keys. Come and go as I please.
Helen told me no guns.
Well, take a look.
I don't need to look.
I'm just getting you through the tech.
Those are nothing to do with me.
You're in this now, and I'm
gonna tell you how we do things.
I don't know you. I
don't fucking trust you.
This is how it's gonna be.
Ok? Ok.
Good.
Alison, you all right? Is Ashleigh here?
Ashleigh? Training
day today. Can I help?
Well, you said I must tell you... Yeah.
If I have contact with anybody
that you're investigating.
I did say that. Yeah, yeah.
Well, wolf... Yeah?
Joseph, he's trying to evict me.
Joseph holhurst.
He's been on our radar a few years.
He has a history of
starting up companies,
getting them into debt and
then declaring them bankrupt.
Then moving on, starting
up another company.
Now he's landed at Hollis & byrne.
What, he's allowed to do
that? Well, life's unfair, isn't it?
Life is unfair.
But we know he's involved in a robbery.
And he gets to kick me and
my mum out of our home?
It's upsetting, I get it. It's upsetting.
But the thing about
Joseph is he's careful.
Switched on. He knows how to
appear to be on the right side of the law.
The gang's last robbery was a jeweller's.
Jewellery store.
Jewellery. Yeah, yeah.
Jewellery store, three years ago.
Innocent man, member of the
public, got shot at close range.
Wife couldn't even identify him.
The jeweller took a round
of bullets through the back
while running for the alarm.
Still works at the place,
behind the counter,
but from a wheelchair.
These are the people
we're dealing with, Alison.
Now, we managed to get
Helen's husband, Alfie red man...
Not a nice man. We got him
sent down for manslaughter,
which ain't great, but believe me, I tried.
And the rest of the gang got away with it.
I know Braden Moore
pulled one of those triggers.
And he's got another gun.
All of their hands are bloody.
And the only way we're
gonna get them put behind bars
is if we catch them in the act.
That way, we get Joseph
on a conspiracy charge,
we get Braden, we get
the whole sorry lot of them.
But that takes Patience, hard graft,
and you've gotta keep a cool head.
Ashleigh thinks you're too, involved.
The information that you're
giving us is very helpful.
But you're not police. And
this shouldn't be your fight.
It'd only raise suspicions
if you just disappear straight after
they'd done spot-checks in the pub.
Best thing you could do right now
is go down there and
hand in your notice.
'But how would you catch them?'
I don't think I could live with
myself if Braden hurts someone.
You're hard-working, I see
that, and you're determined.
But I know this is a lot to ask of you.
Ashleigh says you have doubts.
I can do this. I know that.
Your help makes it much
more likely that we'll catch them.
'But it would mean spending
more time with Braden and Liam.'
'i can try and keep my distance.'
you're sure?
'Yeah, I'm... I'm sure.'
ok.
Hi.
Sorry. I know you said...
Mark told me you had a shift,
and I didn't wanna leave it like that.
I'm sorry about last night.
You don't need someone
like me in your life,
not with everything you've got going on.
I meant what I said.
I would never hurt anyone.
I know you wouldn't.
I'd better go in.
Alison...
Welcome to the hawthorne estate hotel,
mr and mrs standford.
Never been tempted to
bend the rules a little bit?
Are you watching them?
Think they'd even notice
if they lost something?
Now, your throb-on for that girl
is starving your brain of oxygen.
I swear to you, no-one will be hurt.
Subtitles by accessibility@itv.Com