Liam has invited me away.
Overnight? A day trip.
Never been tempted to
bend the rules a little bit?
Liam has a really nice smile,
but it doesn't mean he's not a criminal.
'Liam was watching
some people in the hotel.
'Yeah, I'm pretty sure it's the joshis.'
he hacked into the hotel's cctv.
Let's hope he's not watching you.
So, you saw Liam watching
Amir and his daughter reshmi?
Yeah, Liam asked me to lip-read them.
I saw them talking about bidding.
I think they were talking
about the necklace.
We're gonna take it from an
ultra-secure vault in London.
I need you to keep it
secret until we're done.
Kettle boiling.
Engine turns off.
Knock on door, vacuum whirring
'waterfall' by the stone
roses vacuum stops
James! Good to see you.
Good song. God. Sorry. I'll turn it down.
Don't turn it down on my account.
Volume decreases.
I remember going to
watch these at the astoria.
Must've been, what, 15 years ago?
Charlie was desperate to go.
Was he? I said we couldn't afford it.
We had a bust-up
about it. James chuckles
by the time he'd convinced
me it was possibly the best thing
we could do with our
money, it was sold out.
Thanks for... being here.
But the anniversary's not until next week.
'Yeah, I know. I know. It's just...
'Charlie's been on my mind
a lot recently, you know?'
I know it must be hard.
And if... look, if me coming
round is a bad reminder, then...
It isn't. I appreciate it.
Ok. Really.
Ok.
She chuckles softly funny.
Charlie would've liked you.
But if he was still here, we
wouldn't have met, would we?
You made sure Alfie
red man went to prison.
Not for nearly long enough.
And Helen and Braden
are still out there. Just...
Feel like I'm missing something.
Phone buzzes.
Keypad clacking.
Can he do that?
Yeah, he says he can't
afford maintenance payments.
I'm sorry, I'm, er
I'm gonna have to go. I'll call you back.
Thanks.
Phone thuds.
I'm sorry you're still
struggling with the divorce.
Thanks.
Not gonna lie... Makes me a bit nervous.
What, you joining the club?
No. Look, this legal stuff... is hell.
But it's nothing compared to
being in a marriage that isn't working.
Ok, Nia? Ok, ok, ok. Nia.
Ok, team.
I've just got off the phone to
my contact in hat ton garden.
He's ex-cop turned private security.
He has heard whispers that
the jewels are being shown
tomorrow at a private
view for a potential buyer.
So maybe, I don't know...
Maybe the gang are thinking
of hitting at a moment of weaker security
while the jewels are
in transit, I don't know.
Braden's gun is still unaccounted for.
Shit, Braden's gun is
still unaccounted for.
So I need to phone the cps
and get them to agree
to a conspiracy charge.
Do you think we have enough evidence?
We've got the gang discussing
details of vault security.
And a sighting of the
vault's security plans.
Yeah, but that's from Alison, so...
Also need to tell the cps of Alison's.
Association with Liam Barlow, don't I?
Which they're really not gonna like.
I mean, they're really not gonna like that.
Do we have a location
for Amir joshi right now?
The joshi family are back in London.
Amir joshi is going to be
at a meeting for investors,
according to the times' business page.
Ok. I mean, it's too
risky to wait, isn't it?
It's just way too risky. Ok. So, I need to.
I need to call the cps
and set up a meeting.
Ok. If we get the nod,
we need to be ready to go.
So let's get a current location
for every member of this gang.
Ok.
Ok, that'll do. Cheers.
You... you got here fast.
Dad, were you dealing?
Just a little bit of weed.
Look, look... You ok? Y-Your text, it...
He sighs softly.
That's great. Yeah, thank
you. Thanks. Cheers.
Sir? Yeah.
The met finally got back to me.
They said someone
snitched on Danny Heath.
That's why he was convicted.
Yeah.
Liam, presumably. But why?
I mean, we should be on top
of this by now, shouldn't we?
Why did Liam take Alison to the hotel?
And how does cloning the joshis'
devices get them into the vault?
I mean, maybe we're getting complacent.
We don't look complacent to me.
Well, we didn't last time, either.
Screwdriver clicking.
Phone buzzes.
Yeah.
Hey, are you ok?
There's something
that you need to know.
What? What is it?
Ok, Liam told me everything.
He showed me photos of the necklace.
They're gonna hit the vault,
maybe even tonight. What?
'When did he tell you this?'
'last night.'
'wait, why are you just telling us now?'
'because... Liam trusts me.'
and I didn't expect to like
him when I first started this.
'Alison. Alison, this is important.
'Did Liam say how they
were gonna get into the vault?'
'n-no, he didn't say.'
Liam sighs I can't let him
go ahead with the robbery.
They're not gonna.
We're gonna stop 'em, ok?
But, listen, you cannot see Liam again.
Ok? He's dangerous.
Ok. Ok?
Ok.
Yeah. Yeah, no, I got it. I got it.
Yeah, I'll be in touch.
Cps have agreed to a conspiracy charge.
The information from Alison
actually tipped the balance.
I mean, they don't want her
anywhere near a court, obviously,
but, er... they have advised
that we should bring in
Helen, Braden and Liam.
Ok, so we just have
to stick the landing now.
Just gotta stick the landing. Ben? Yeah?
How're we doing on
locating our suspects?
We've traced their vehicles.
They were all outside their residences,
but so far, we've not got eyes
on Helen, Braden or Liam. Ok.
Seems unlikely that
they're all having a lie-in, no?
So let's pull cctv images
from around their homes
for the last 12 hours and get on 'em.
Wait, wait, wait.
So, sorry, Alison said they
could be hitting the vault
as soon as tonight.
But if they've already
gone to ground, then...
The gang could be hitting
the vault before tonight.
Yeah. Fuck. Ok. We
should get down there, fast.
Ben? Yeah?
Can you get onto the met
and get them to send
an armed response unit?
If they are making an
attempt on the vault,
I don't wanna take any chances, yeah?
Door opens.
You ok? Yeah.
I just... Liam sighs
I've just got to go out for a bit.
Where you going?
We're leaving in a hour.
Just gotta pick summat
up. A bit of kit for back-up.
But we've been planning this for weeks.
I'll be back in time. Don't worry.
Footsteps recede door opens, closes
Braden inhales sharply.
Thanks for meeting me here.
Did you think about what I said?
Please...
Don't do this.
If you stop, we could walk away.
We could be together. Maybe
we can move away from here.
We could be anything we
wanna be and be happy.
It's too late.
Look, if Braden's gonna
walk into that vault with a gun,
people will die.
So if you care enough about
me to come away with you,
then, please, just don't do this.
You don't understand.
I can't walk away from this.
I can't.
But.
I thought the Liam that I
know won't let anybody get hurt.
If you walk into that vault, you're
gonna get caught. I know that.
How do you know that? Scoffs.
I'm just worried. No.
You said that you know
that I'm gonna get caught.
What do you know?
No, no, I don't know anything. I.
I told you things last night.
I put it all on the line for you.
I need to know...
Can I trust you?
Yeah. You can t-trust me.
Inhales sharply.
You should go.
Ben?
I've located Helen and Joseph.
They took a taxi from Joseph's office,
and looks like they're headed to a
Hollis and byrne residence meeting.
Yep. They're giving
themselves cast-iron alibis.
They were never gonna get
their hands dirty, were they?
Ok. Tell uniform not to take
them out of their sights. Yeah.
We need to find Braden and Liam. Yeah.
Hello. Thank you.
- Sergeant.
- Sir.
You spoken to them? No
sign of any disturbance.
But the duty manager isn't
keen on sharing information.
Not keen? I'll see about that.
Can I have a look?
We're gonna take it from an
ultra-secure vault in London.
'You have to trust me.'
Ringing tone er, sorry.
One... one second.
Yeah. Could we get mr joshi
out of that meeting, please?
It's very important that we speak to him.
Yep. I'll hold.
Croesus vaults' clientele
value our discretion.
You must understand
the level of security risk
involved in high-value items.
I do understand. I do
understand the security risk.
That's why I'm here.
Anything?
I'm being bounced between assistants.
Ashleigh sighs.
I have got credible information
that a gang of very organised criminals
are planning a hit on this vault today.
Now, do you wanna be
the one to tell your client
that you ignored my warning?
Give me a minute.
Keyboard clacking.
According to our system,
mr joshi's vault was
emptied earlier today.
The contents were moved
at the owner's request.
Moved where?
They didn't... They
don't share a destination.
I-I wouldn't expect them to.
Yep, we'll be in touch as
soon as we know anything.
Amir joshi thinks the
jewels are still here.
Yeah, well, as this nice gentleman
has finally admitted, they're not.
Miss joshi sent the courier.
We verified the request.
The... that's the Van.
Sorry, did you say
miss joshi sent the Van?
Fuck. The daughter. Fuck.
No, no. Just got here now.
Yeah. Nia?
Yeah, yeah. Give us two seconds, sir.
Ok. Hold on.
Ok, you're good.
The Van that has just left
with the contents of the
vault, its registration is
Lima-foxtrot-five,
seven-foxtrot-Sierra-kilo.
'I need a trace on that Van, Ben.'
yeah, we're just loading the anpr now.
I have the Van on the
a2, heading out of London.
It pings at a camera on
the a2 and then nothing.
Reshmi joshi ordered
the jewels to be moved.
Now, her dad doesn't know
where she's taken them,
but it seems likely the gang do.
Excuse me?
My phone is completely dead,
and I really need to text my mum.
Please can I borrow your phone? Is it...?
Sure.
Thank you so much. Thank you.
Thank you so much.
'Has it gone off the a-road?'
yeah. Several b-roads
heading out in each direction.
'None of them have traffic cameras.'
phone buzzes it's Alison.
She's texting me from different numbers.
She says the robbery's at
the hawthorne estate hotel.
That's where she was with Liam.
Hawthorne estate hotel. Ben,
is that where they're heading?
'Alison says the robbery is there,
but we don't have confirmation.'
er, yeah. Yeah, that makes
sense, given where we lost the Van.
It's about an hour away, at least.
Ben, could you head down there,
take a look, with extreme caution?
'We don't know if we can trust Alison,
'and we don't know
what we're walking into.
'I'll get an armed response there
'as back-up as soon as I can.' Yes, sir.
Hey. You ready? Shit, sorry.
I meant to text you. Ok.
Er, we can do dinner later?
Sorry. Crazy day.
Ok. Call me when you're
done. I don't mind what time.
Sure.
Park at the back.
Camera shutter clicks lovely.
Five minutes.
Ok. I think we'll do a few more here.
Then we can get you in the
black beaded couture on the stairs.
Not making any promises,
but I think that could
just get us the cover.
But that dress needs the necklace.
They'll be here any minute.
Navi sighs
ok. So... good.
Chuckles softly
rolled out the red carpet.
That's the courier.
Let's do it.
Exhales.
Yeah.
Computer beeps, chirps.
Hotel security approaching.
'Keep walking.
'Told you.'
Unlocking now.
Go on through.
Necklace has changed
hands. Two bodyguards.
They're nearly up.
And look at what I've done here.
Now, the necklace...
Where do you want it?
Just on the table over there.
Yeah, I see it. It's gonna
come down here. And
I would love for the... Yes.
Joshis are in position.
The necklace is on the table.
One cpo outside the
suite, another inside.
Back straight, smile wide,
and whatever you do...
Do not be yourself.
'Just open the door.'
Good afternoon, sir.
Compliments of the house.
Champagne and macarons.
Good luck with her. Yes, sir.
Room service coming up.
Perhaps the master bedroom?
Who's that?
Champagne and macarons, madam.
Compliments of the hotel. Reshmi scoffs
shall I send him away?
What flavour?
Pistachio, ma'am.
Stick 'em in there.
Maybe later. Reshmi chuckles.
Ready?
Now.
Alarm ringing faintly
alarm blaring really?
Come in?
You need to leave, now.
Cpos, you're hearing that, right?
Get reshmi out, leave the
necklace upstairs for the courier.
Suite doors will lock behind you, anyway.
The courier has a key card. He's
coming up to protect the package.
Phone ringing Roger that, chandra.
Reshmi scoffs yes?
'Good afternoon, madam.
It's the management.'
is this a drill? I'm afraid not.
Please evacuate immediately.
I apologise for any
inconvenience caused.
Alarm continues
what on earth is going on?
Phone chimes god.
Problem? Alison.
She's... she's at the
hotel. For fuck's sake.
Tell her to leave. She
needs to stay out of this.
Phone buzzes.
Listen to me.
There's a robbery that is happening now.
No, madam. This is a fire alarm.
It's a robbery. They're using the cctv.
My god! What is going
on? Let's keep moving.
Reshmi coughs.
Wait outside, please.
No, no, no!
They want everyone to get out
so they can take the necklace.
They're clear. They're clear.
Alarm blaring
'switch the necklaces.'
Keep moving, madam.
Wait. I need my necklace.
You have to go back and get it.
Chandra said it was safest in the room.
I don't give a fuck what she said!
I'm telling you to go back and get it.
I'm not leaving without it.
Bag secure. Coming down.
Fuck! The cpo is coming back.
Hide! What?!
I'm in the suite.
I'm not waiting for him.
It's full of smoke.
Computer chirping we've got a problem.
I can't open the door to the linen room.
'My remote access isn't
working.' Well, get it working.
'The fire alarm must
have triggered something.'
we haven't got time for this.
'You can't go down the main
stairs, the joshis are there.
'If they check the replica,
they'll suspect you.' What?!
You can't get caught
with the jewels on you.
You're gonna have to dump them.
There's a laundry chute on
the other side of the staircase.
'Put them in there, and we'll
collect them at the bottom.
'Put the jewels in the laundry chute!'
Ok, it's done.
Now get in here and get me out!
Heavy breathing.
I'm going in. I've gotta go!
Sir, thank you. Do you
know the way to go?
If you wouldn't mind, thank you so much.
Liam, where are you?
I can't stay here, can I?
Muffled chatter, guests clamouring.
I'm coming! Coming.
Just... just wait, I'm coming.
Alison! Alison!
Liam...
Alarm ringing.
Man coughs, handbrake clicks fuck.
Thank you so much for your Patience.
Guests clamouring yeah,
I'm really sorry, madam.
Phone buzzes Ben?
Something's going on at
the hotel. They're evacuating.
Ok, we've just got a text from Alison.
She said she's at the
hotel. Can you see her?
No. 'We need to know she's safe.'
'she might be inside. I'll check.'
armed response are on their way, Ben.
They're six minutes off, ok?
No, no, no. I'll take
a look. I'll be careful.
Stop this before it's too late,
ok? The police is on their way.
Funny you're here, too.
Look, they've got guns.
And Braden's got a gun, too.
Which is why you need to
get out before you fuck this up!
Ok, let's go.
Sighs screw this.
Braden! Stop!
Police!
Alison yelps, supressed gunshots argh!
Alison whimpers can you get off me?!
Liam grunts, Ben groans.
Alison whimpers, sobs.
Ben, Ben! Just stay... stay with me.
Stay with me. Ben gasping
Alison sobbing please!
Can you call the ambulance?
Don't just stand there, do something!
Please.
Ben groaning I'm sorry. I'm sorry, Alison.
I-I'm sorry.
Ben... sorry, sorry, sorry, sorry.
Just hold on, all right?
Ringing fades sound muted.
Gunshot.
Ben gasps groans in
pain high-pitched ringing
door slams I'm sorry. I'm
sorry, Alison. I-I'm sorry.
Alison sobbing Ben. Ben, Ben! Help...
Low hum of conversation.
'As this interview is under caution,
'we've provided a bsl interpreter.
'It's very important
that you understand us.'
DC lawford was shot.
One of Amir joshi's
bodyguards was killed.
I was there. I saw it.
You'll appreciate why it's
important for us to understand...
Do you want to tell us how
you came to be at the hotel?
He sighs softly.
I-I went there to try and stop the robbery.
Right.
And how long have you known
that the robbery was
gonna be at the hotel?
I didn't know. I... I guessed.
You guessed?
I mean...
You can see why I might have
difficulty believing that, yeah?
I mean, you stayed at the
hawthorne hotel with Liam...
Two days ago.
I mean, you stayed
in the exact same suite
that the robbery took place in.
I texted Ashleigh.
I told you it was gonna be at the hotel.
And a couple of hours before,
you told me it was at the vault.
But... You gave me false information,
which meant we
couldn't stop the robbery.
I didn't give you false information.
You see, DC lawford is in surgery.
He's having a bullet
removed from his abdomen.
So I need to understand, quickly.
Why you changed your story.
Did you get cold feet?
Did you and Liam fall out? What was it?
No, no. Liam told me that
it was gonna be at the vault.
That's what he said. Right.
Why would he say that if it wasn't true?
Liam found out I was working with you.
And I think he was listening
into our conversations
through my hearing aids.
Through your hearing aids?
Sorry, is that even...
Is that even possible?
What... what... What makes
you think he hacked you?
Well, he was asking
me about my hearing aids
and how... How they worked, you know?
And I found out my hearing
aids were paired up to my phone.
And I didn't set that up.
Ok. So... you think that Liam
used you to misdirect us?
Yeah, I think...
And you were never
tempted to help him?
Yeah, I was...
At times, I was tempted by him.
But that's because he
knew I was struggling.
But... I couldn't do it.
Because the more I
learnt being with you guys,
the more I realised that people
really do get hurt. And
I really didn't want that
to happen to anyone.
I really didn't.
Do you know where Liam is now?
What he's...? He's not...?
Did you not arrest him at the hotel?
Braden escaped in the Van.
Antony's in custody,
but he's saying nothing.
We didn't find Liam at the hotel.
We didn't find the jewels, either.
But here's what we do know.
Someone shut down the hotel cctv.
Right before DC lawford got shot.
I think that was Liam.
I think... Liam always
intended to escape on his own.
He planned it.
So he tricked...
He tricked the gang, and
then he used me to do it.
Sniffles.
DC lawford put himself
on the line for the job.
Let's make sure that wasn't for nothing.
Let's put all our efforts into
finding Braden and Liam.
We're not gonna let
them walk away this time.
So, everything that I did
and all the risks that I took,
they were for nothing?
Should've listened to you about Alison.
She was over-involved.
Officers yelling
'you don't feel so clever now, do you?'
'what have you done?'
subtitles by accessibility@itv.Com