[in Yiddish]
Next week, after your wedding,
God willing, you'll begin
a new life with your husband.
I'm here to teach you how to be a wife.
The physical relationship
between husband and wife is holy.
Its purpose is to create a family.
And family is everything.
But...
how does it work?
[woman] It's basic physics.
The man is the giver,
the woman is the receiver.
Understand?
So he must be on top
and she must be on the bottom.
You should have marital relations
every Friday night,
if you are clean.
Clean?
Each month, when you bleed,
you'll sleep apart from your husband,
and don't go to the mikvah.
After you finish bleeding,
inspect yourself twice a day
with one of these cloths.
[in English] When the cloths...
[in Yiddish]
...have been clean for seven days,
you can return to your husband's bed,
after you've been to the mikvah.
But...
that means we only share a bed
for half the month.
[in English]
Absence makes the heart grow fonder.
[in Yiddish] You'll see.
God made it this way
to keep the relationship fresh.
And it's your duty to uphold God's wishes.
That's why we need to guarantee
that your wedding night will be a success.
Right?
Husband and wife
fit together like pieces in a puzzle.
Understand?
No.
You have a hole inside you,
leading to a hallway,
leading to a little door,
opening to a womb, the source of all life.
When the man enters the hallway with his...
No!
I don't have that hole.
What?
There must be something wrong with me.
Nothing is wrong with you.
Go to the bathroom and look, Esty.
There are two holes.
One for pee and the other...
You'll see.
- Now?
- Yes, go!
[sighs]
[gasps]
[suspenseful music playing]
MIKVAH
[in English] Hello!
[woman in Yiddish] Good day.
[in Yiddish] I am Esther Schwartz.
Ah, the bride!
Here is your robe.
And here are the rules.
Use the left door!
Ring the bell when you're ready.
[sighs]
That was quick, dear.
Come here!
Let me see.
There can be nothing
between the water and your skin.
Good!
Now you are ready, dear!
[woman] Kosher.
"Blessed are You, God.
King of the universe.
Who sanctified us with His commandments.
And commanded us to immerse ourselves."
Amen.
[clattering]
[bucket clattering]
[cleaner humming outside]
- [door opening]
- [cleaner continues humming]
[cleaner gasps]
[in Polish] What the heck...
What are you doing here?
[in German]
No one's allowed to sleep here.
[in Polish] Don't you know that?
[in German] I'm going to report you!
[in English] See you later.
[cleaner in German]
Wait! I found a girl down there!
She slept there overnight!
[teacher] Wait a minute!
And you are?
[in English] I'm Esther Shapiro.
I'm... I'm sorry.
You can't sleep in there.
It was just one night, I promise.
- Okay.
- I won't do it again.
[teacher] Where did you come from?
New York.
- Why don't you pack your things now?
- I don't have any things. I'll go now.
[teacher] Wait!
[sighs] Come with me.
[Yanky in Yiddish] We've landed, Mommy!
Yes. I've got all my luggage.
Yes. The sun is shining.
I'll call you later.
What did you bring your shtreimel for?
So everyone can admire how Jewish we look?
Just put on a yellow star, why don't you!
We brought shtreimels to Europe
when we came with Daddy!
This isn't Antwerp, Yanky.
This isn't even London. This is Berlin.
The capital of Germany!
Germany! Look around.
What if we're still here on the sabbath?
[Moishe] We'll be gone by the sabbath.
[Yanky] Are we going
straight to her mom's house?
[Moishe] No.
POTSDAMER PLATZ STATION
[in English] I would love to play music
like your students.
I've never seen a concert like that.
They don't have concerts in New York?
Bands at weddings and bar mitzvahs, maybe.
And my piano teacher
used to play for me sometimes.
You play the piano?
- Yes.
- [teacher] Seriously?
What's in this sandwich?
Ham.
I'm sorry.
[teacher] Are you all right?
I thought the ham would make me sick.
- It didn't.
- [teacher chuckles]
Are you relieved?
Where I come from, there are many rules.
In music, often, you have
to break the rules to make a masterpiece.
Half of Bach's sonatas
don't follow the official rules of Bach.
[Esty chuckles]
I wish I could afford to study here.
We have a special training program
at our conservatory
for students from...
difficult circumstances.
Difficult circumstances?
War zones, for example.
Does Williamsburg count as a war zone?
I don't know.
You tell me.
What would I have to do?
You have to fill out an application form.
That's it?
[teacher laughs] No.
Then you have to audition live
in front of a panel of experts.
Are you prepared to do that?
Yes.
[notification music plays
over cell phone]
[in Yiddish] Does the rabbi know
you have a smartphone?
I have a kosher phone for personal use.
I need the smartphone for business.
The rabbi gives me special dispensation.
It has all the functions?
- Internet?
- Of course.
So,
you can look up anything?
I guess so.
Anything in the whole world?
[Moishe] I guess so.
- Can you look up a person?
- What?
Ask if it knows where my wife is.
I mean it!
Say it.
[in English] "Where is Esty?"
Where is Esty, telephone?
[Moishe chuckles]
[in Yiddish] You're crazy, Yanky.
[Moishe laughs]
[women chattering indistinctly]
[in German]
Welcome. Checking in, fellows?
- Moses Lefkovitch.
- [in English] Lefkovitch. Right.
May I have your credit card, please?
[in Yiddish] You've got cash, right?
Uh... yes.
[in English] First time in Berlin?
- [Moishe] No.
- [Yanky] Yes.
It's always a great pleasure to host
guests from Israel here in Germany!
Shalom!
Israel?
[in Yiddish] Zionists!
[in English] We're from New York.
The United States of America.
Did someone leave a package for me?
[male clerk] Yes. Here it is.
[Yanky recites prayer]
[both recite prayer]
[Moishe in English] So...
[in Yiddish] I brought enough
instant ramen to last us a week.
Otherwise we'll just eat fruit and nuts.
And Coca-Cola, of course.
You're sure it's kosher in Germany?
Everywhere.
[in English] Yankees or Mets?
Yankees.
[Yanky sighs]
[notification music plays
over cell phone]
[in Yiddish] What if Esty's in danger?
Of course she is in danger, Yanky!
That's why we're here.
I have to make a call.
[door opens and closes]
[Moishe in English] Igor!
Igor... Yeah, thank you very much.
[Moishe continues speaking indistinctly]
[melancholic music playing]
[woman in English] Yep...
[in German] Sosena, do you have a minute?
A new applicant.
What can I do for you?
[in English] I'm Esther Shapiro.
I would like to apply
for the special training program.
[Sosena] Did you fill out
an online application?
- I don't see anything.
- I... filled out a paper application.
Professor Hafez
told me to bring it to this office.
He didn't tell you
to send an audition tape first?
[Esty] No.
- Piano.
- [Esty] Mm-hmm.
But do you understand that this program is
meant to be for highly talented students
from extraordinary circumstances?
My circumstances are extraordinary.
Just read my application.
Please. It's all in here.
There's no address.
I don't actually
have an address yet, but...
Wait.
IMMIGRATION OFFICE
So you can receive post at this address?
Okay. Then we'll be in touch
about the audition.
Thank you.
Thank you so much.
And, um, Esther?
[Esty] Hmm?
Our acceptance rate is only eight percent.
Please don't get your hopes up.
[door buzzer sounds]
[Leah in German] Hello?
- Hello, who's there?
- [in English] Hello?
[Leah in German] Hello, is someone there?
[in English] This is Jacob Shapiro.
I'm Esther Shapiro's husband.
[door buzzer sounds]
[Yanky in Yiddish] She let me in.
That's good. Right?
[Moishe] It's something.
[in English] I'm Jacob.
I know who you are, Yanky.
I was at your wedding.
Really?
So is she here?
Esty?
- No.
- [in Yiddish] Do me a favor, lady.
[in English] English.
We speak English in my house.
And you are?
[in German] I'm his cousin, Moishe.
- [in English] Why did you come to Germany?
- [Moishe in Yiddish] Enough with this!
- [in German] Because Esty is here.
- [woman] Leah! Who is it?
[in Yiddish] If she's not here,
where else would she go?
[Leah in English] What happened, Yanky?
Things must be bad
for to you to believe she'd run this far.
- Are they bad? Tell me the truth.
- [in Yiddish] No, you tell us the truth!
[in English] This is not your world.
You can't threaten me here.
- [woman] Who are you?
- Nobody. They were leaving.
- I need to talk to Esty.
- [Leah] I told you.
I have no idea where Esty is.
[Leah breathes heavily]
[dog barking in distance]
[footsteps retreating]
[woman] Leah,
we have to call the police.
- No. No police.
- [woman] This isn't Williamsburg.
Nina, she isn't missing.
She's 19 years old.
I have to wait for her to come to us.
The younger one is her husband,
by the way.
He doesn't know that chasing her
will only make her run further.
[Esty praying in Yiddish]
[celestial music playing]
[chattering]
[children laughing]
What's keeping you?
I'm just a bit nervous.
Grandma.
To see you married is my greatest joy.
[Esty continues praying]
[men singing in Yiddish]
[men continue singing]
[man recites Yiddish prayer]
[Mordecai recites Yiddish prayer]
[men singing in Yiddish]
[breathing shakily]
[men singing]
[in Yiddish]
You are betrothed to me with this ring
according to the laws of Moses and Israel.
[rabbi recites Yiddish prayer]
[men chanting]
- [Esty gasps]
- [guests] Mazel tov!
[upbeat wedding music playing]
[Malka laughing]
[Karim speaking Arabic]
- [in English] Hi.
- Hi.
[Karim speaking Arabic]
- [in English] Go in. I'll be right there.
- [Esty] Okay.
[Karim speaking Arabic]
[chattering]
[Dasia] Esty?
[Robert in English] Yeah.
- Do you think she has cancer?
- [Dasia] I wondered that, too.
[Ahmed] When she took off the wig,
she looked totally fine.
She doesn't have cancer, come on.
She's ultraorthodox.
- [male student] Ultraorthodox, what?
- [laughs] Jewish!
- [male student] Really?
- Yeah.
I didn't know there was such a thing.
They're, like, the lunatic fringe.
They don't even get proper education.
The men just study the Torah
and the women are baby machines.
- [male student] Really?
- I'm not a baby machine.
[Karim in German] Good morning!
[in English] Have a chair.
Esther here is a pianist from New York
who has applied
to our special training program.
She'll be sitting in
on our coaching session today.
So, you have an audience.
Be on your toes, hmm?
Esther, if you have any questions
about life in the program,
you can ask anyone here after class.
Thank you.
[Karim]
So let's start from the top this time.
[classical music playing]
Okay.
You are playing in a chamber music
orchestra here, people.
Hmm?
You are no longer separate individuals.
You are one symbiotic being. One organism.
Feel each other's movement.
Anticipate each other's breaths. Okay?
Try again.
[classical music playing]
[Karim speaking indistinctly]
Dasia,
where are you today?
Stay with us, please.
Read the music.
Who heard that?
Hmm?
- I played the wrong bowings.
- [Karim] That's right.
Overthinking.
Okay. From the top, everyone, again.
[classical music playing]
[chattering]
[Esty] Dasia.
Are you okay?
You play so well.
No, honestly,
everything Professor Hafez said is true.
[cell phone buzzes]
I need to go to the hospital.
Hospital?
My uncle's a doctor. He asked me
to do a teatime concert for his patients.
Hopefully, his patients
won't notice my rhythm is off.
I am sure they will love it.
My family is so proud I'm a musician.
But it's...
so much pressure sometimes.
My family just cares
that I'm a good wife and mother.
Echt?
Stimmt.
[both giggle]
Not bad. [laughs]
You still haven't been to a dinner party.
Let's say tonight.
- What?
- A dinner party.
Really?
[cell phone buzzes]
I... I have to run now,
but come to the dorms at eight. I'll cook.
[in Yiddish] You have seven minutes
to do whatever you want.
Don't worry, it's a mirror.
They can't see in.
This is for you!
My mother picked them out.
I hope you like them.
Thank you so much!
[chattering next door]
What if...
[Esty] I'm so...
What?
Hungry.
[upbeat wedding music playing]
[man singing]
[men singing]
[Esty speaking indistinctly]
Wait...
[in English] I'm asking you
to leave right now. Let's go.
Please. After you. Let's go.
[laughter]
[trumpet blowing]
[in German] Are you looking for someone?
[in English] Do you know Dasia?
[in German] Dasia?
I guess she's in the kitchen.
[in English] In the kitchen.
[in German] Thanks.
[trumpet playing in distance]
[pop music playing]
- [woman in English] Hello.
- Hi.
[Dasia] Yeah, it's so nice.
[chattering]
- [Ahmed] Hey, hey.
- [laughs]
Esty!
- [Esty] Hi.
- [Yael] Hi, Esty!
- [Dasia] I'm glad you came.
- [student] Didn't know you were coming.
I have to take care of the cauliflower.
[Ahmed] Welcome.
- This is my boyfriend, Mike.
- [Mike] Hi.
- [Ahmed] This is Esty.
- [Mike] Nice to meet you.
- Hi.
- You can just... put your stuff there.
[Esty breathes nervously]
How can I help?
Well, you could try and rescue
Robert's attempt at a salad.
- [laughter]
- [Robert] Oh...
[scoffs] Ha-ha, ha-ha.
- [Ahmed] Are you any good with dressing?
- I'm okay.
I cook a lot at home.
[Robert] There you go, ma'am.
So what do you cook at home?
Everything.
Soups, kugel, cholent, goulash, cakes...
[Ahmed] Chol...?
Kugel? What's...
- [laughter]
- What's that?
- It's like... Kugel is...
- [Esty] You know it?
[Yael] Yeah.
Kugel is, like, a cake made of noodles.
- And it's, like, sweet and spicy and...
- It's hard to explain.
- It's just normal Jewish food.
- Jewish food, yeah! [laughs]
[laughs] Yes.
Yeah, I learned everything from my babby.
What's a babby?
[Esty laughs]
It's my grandmother.
She raised me.
Robert was raised
by his grandparents, too.
- Yeah.
- Oh... They also live in Berlin?
Er, no. They did...
Passed away.
I'm sorry.
You escaped, didn't you?
You make it sound like I was in prison.
Weren't you?
No.
But I left, without telling anyone
where I was going.
Why did you leave?
- This is not a job interview, okay?
- [Esty] It's okay.
God expected too much of me.
Now I need to find my own path.
Well, I'll drink to that.
[Yael] Definitely, yeah.
Wine, yeah.
- [in German] Prost.
- [in English] You have a glass?
Yeah. To Esty.
- [Dasia] To Esty.
- [in Hebrew] L'chaim.
- [Robert in English] Yeah.
- [all in Hebrew] L'chaim.
- [Mike in German] Prost!
- [Yael in English] If you don't mind...
[in Yiddish] ♪ The holy rabbi
Will perform the mitzvah ♪
♪ Of dancing before the bride ♪
♪ May the merit of his holy forebears ♪
♪ Bring blessings
Upon the bride and groom ♪
♪ And all will dance quickly in our days ♪
♪ Toward our righteous Messiah ♪
[man singing]
[men singing]
- [man yelling]
- [guests gasping]
- [guests chattering]
- [Mordecai singing]
[chattering]
[Mordecai continues singing]
[man] ♪ The groom will now dance
With his pious bride ♪
♪ For the sake of the holy union of God
And His Shechina ♪
♪ How does one dance before the bride? ♪
♪ May they build an everlasting home ♪
♪ And all will dance quickly in our days ♪
♪ Toward our righteous Messiah ♪
[man continues singing]
[men singing]
[Esty praying]
[Esty whimpers]
[Esty panting]
[chattering]
[chattering and laughter]
[woman singing]
[in Yiddish] Now what do we do?
Call all the hospitals?
The US embassy?
US embassy?
Patience, Yanky.
Leah Mandelbaum is lying.
Didn't you notice?
No, I didn't notice that.
Actually, she seemed pretty nice.
[Moishe] Nice means nothing!
We'll get the truth out of her yet.
Blessed are You, Creator of this fruit!
How? Beat her up like a gangster?
No, it's better to scare her.
With a gun?
What gun?
[laughs loudly] Beat that.
[laughs]
[casino game playing over cell phone]
So what's the plan now?
- Give me 20 bucks.
- What?
No, 100 would be better.
What? What for?
Didn't you bring any money of your own?
We're here to find your wife, not mine.
[Yanky] Yes.
Exactly!
How are we going to find my wife?
Hundred bucks. Come on. Please!
Whatever.
[chattering in German]
[Robert in English]
Erm, Esty? I have a question.
Why Berlin?
I mean, New York has, like, the best
music schools in the world, right?
I had to get as far away as possible
from my community.
Why?
I just didn't fit in there.
[Ahmed] I hear you, Esty.
I mean,
imagine being a gay kid in Nigeria.
[Mike] A gay kid with a cello.
[laughter]
With a fucking cello.
[Esty laughs]
But look at you now.
All of you.
I really hope to get that scholarship.
Then let's hear you.
What?
It's good practice and you heard us.
We play in front of each other
all the time.
- Like, all the time.
- [Dasia]...time.
Really, too much. It's too much.
[Ahmed]
Basically, every Saturday, we play.
[laughter]
Okay.
- [Yael] Yay! Woo!
- [Mike] Very good!
[melancholic music playing]
- That was beautiful, Esther.
- [Yael] Stop it.
That won't help her.
- Yael, come on.
- She's not a child.
That was nice.
Really, that was nice.
Nice enough to entertain the boys
at a few bar mitzvahs, maybe.
But you'll never make it
into the conservatory.
Was that really necessary?
What? I'm just being honest!
Which is what she deserves.
Maybe she's musical,
but she's not a pianist.
[Yael scoffs]
Every one of us here has been practicing
our instruments every fucking day
since we were children.
Look, an ear for music
might be a God-given gift,
and there are singers
who are born with beautiful voices,
but no one comes out of Brooklyn
after a few lessons on the piano
all ready to play the Philharmonie!
You clearly have a knack for music.
And things might have been different
for you in different circumstances.
But you'll never catch up.
Not on the piano, not ever. I'm sorry.
Where's the bathroom?
It's down the hall to the right.
Army general Yael Roubeni
at your service, right?
[Robert] Esty.
Esty!
[melancholic music playing]
[telephone ringing]
[in Yiddish] Hello?
Grandma?
Grandma, it's me. Esty.
[Esty cries] I'm so far away, Grandma.
I miss you so much.
I don't know what to do...
Hello?
Grandma?
[melancholic music playing]