Bajalo. Get him down!
What have you got
against chickens?
One got choked last
night, thanks to you.
33-year-old male
with haemoptysis, fever.
We can't even talk about it?
If you can't apologize, we
can't talk. And puncture wounds.
I'm not apologizing for
doing the right thing.
Lying to me was
not the right thing.
Puncture wounds are
from a crucifixion.
I lied to save
my patient's life.
I didn't lie to you,
I lied to my boss.
Either of those
arguments working yet?
Guess that means I don't have
to go to the wedding on Saturday.
The hospital's
chairman of the board?
I'm not gonna stand him
up and neither are you.
I loathe weddings and their
seven levels of hypocrisy.
But you do seem awfully hissy,
and there's an outside chance
I can get you drunk and score.
So as long as you don't
take it as an admission of guilt,
sure, count me in.
Bit too much honesty?
You're also going to the
rehearsal dinner Friday night.
Dressy casual.
House-keeping.
Either you're crazy or you're
atoning for something naughty.
And you're crazy.
He's a doctor.
I'm not atoning for anything.
That answers that, thanks.
My Marisa was diagnosed with terminal
brain cancer, stage IV glioblastoma.
When the doctors said
she had two months to live,
that's when I made my bargain.
With your health
insurance carrier?
With God.
Oh!
I told him I would nail myself to a
cross every year he kept her alive.
So how did that negotiation go?
You lowballed with ear
piercing and God countered?
Three weeks later, she was
cancer-free. That was four years ago.
Pontius Pilate,
misunderstood oncologist.
Yeah. My ex-wife
thinks I'm crazy, too.
She moved out the
first time I did this.
At least your daughter
has one viable role model.
- You don't believe in
God? - I did.
Then I grew my curly hairs.
So how do you think I was cured?
Maybe you were
misdiagnosed in the first place.
You have your answer,
Doctors. We have ours.
Causal determinism, we are
hardwired to need answers.
The caveman who heard
a rustle in the bushes
and checked out
to see what it was
lived longer than the guy who
assumed it was just a breeze.
The problem is,
when we don't find a logical
answer, we settle for a stupid one.
Ritual is what happens
when we run out of rational.
If you're done mocking him,
we need to prep for an LP.
Good. Another hole in him
should really make God's day.
Why are you late?
Your next dental
appointment isn't until January
and you just saw
your GP eight days ago.
Think stage IV glioblastoma
in an eight-year-old
can disappear in three weeks?
Had a flat tire.
Your patient has cancer?
Your tires have got less
than 5,000 miles on them.
No, and neither does
my patient's daughter.
I hit a piece of rebar
near a construction site.
In three weeks?
It's highly unlikely.
There's no construction site
between here and your home.
I agree, I think it was
a misdiagnosed cyst.
But there is one between
here and my dry cleaner.
It could be a misdiagnosis or it
could be spontaneous remission, but...
Why would I lie about this?
I don't know yet.
But you would've dropped off
your tie, it's got a mustard stain.
I was buying an engagement ring.
I'm gonna propose
to Sam at the wedding.
That is the second stupidest
thing I've heard today.
And I'm surprised
how close you came.
You didn't need to
buy her a new ring.
Isn't the first one good
for all-you-can-marry?
I assume you haven't
apologized to Cuddy yet.
Your stupidity
demands equal time.
Nothing to apologize for.
Pretend to apologize.
You want me to lie?
There's a lovely symmetry to it.
A lie got you into it,
a lie gets you out of it.
Everybody lies.
I'm sure Cuddy...
Just need to give her a chance.
Yeah, that must've
been what I meant.
Have you seen the bride-to-be?
Gorgeous woman half
his age. He's a lucky guy.
Yeah.
For a while.
My father's 19 years
older than my mother
and they've been happily
married for 32 years.
I'm guessing your dad
wasn't on the Forbes 400
and your mom didn't
look like a swimsuit model.
Sorry, that didn't
come out right.
My father was the classics chair at
Columbia and my mother was his student.
His gorgeous student.
What's it mean when somebody
takes their cell phone into the bathroom
when they're taking a shower?
Means they don't want you to
check their calls, e-mails or texts.
If we're talking
about your wife,
it means the chickens
are coming home to roost.
Taub has been known to dabble.
Used to be.
Maybe it's just a habit. I do that
with my cell phone and I live alone.
She has a meeting
today at 1:30, at a hotel.
I'm gonna go with
the chicken thing.
Negative for toxocara,
bacteroides, ascaris, everything.
So what looks like an infection
but doesn't test like one?
Animals.
I'm sure your wife's
just seeing a dude.
Patient works for Morgan
Timber Works, card's in the file.
"Specializing in stables,
barns and stalls."
He works around animals.
Rhodococcus equi.
Unless this guy's
sleeping in the manger.
Or has a history of open wounds.
We think you have rhodococcus
equi, a horse infection.
It's pretty rare in humans but
easily treatable with antibiotics.
Does it make your
teeth fall out?
No.
Then again, maybe we were wrong.
Fever, coughing up blood,
coughing up teeth.
Either God sweetened the deal
with a no-flossing clause, or...
Radiation sickness.
Yeah, maybe the carpenter
builds microwave ovens.
Kaposi sarcoma?
No skin lesions.
Heavy metal poisoning fits,
canned tuna, sushi, lead paint.
Heavy metal it is. Do a home
search and a peripheral smear.
I can't. I have a
personal errand to run.
Trying to catch
your wife cheating?
Why would you say that?
Missing mojo, posture
slumped, expression defeated,
you didn't try to back up your
theory. And Chase told me.
Go, find your mojo.
Shopkeeper,
I need a patient file.
Ask records.
Not one of our patients',
my patient's daughter.
Ask your patient.
He thinks I only want
it to debunk his faith.
And why would he think that?
Because he's strangely
perceptive for an idiot.
And I'm going to violate patient
privacy laws just to keep you happy?
You keep me happy, I return
the favor. Think of it as tat for tit.
When we're at work, we need
to focus on our work thoughts.
Why are you wearing that?
It's my dressy casual.
What do you think?
You look like Wilson.
It looks weird.
But you knew I'd think that,
which makes me wonder
why you look disappointed.
If you prick me, do I not bleed?
You knew I wouldn't like it but
you thought I would say I did.
That's what this is about. You're
trying to trap me into lying to you.
You sure?
That sounds so juvenile.
You're okay with burglary now?
I asked his permission.
The reason we
don't ask permission
is we're afraid the patient
is going to hide something.
But our patient
hasn't been home,
lives alone,
doesn't have any help,
and has no motive
to hide anything.
You ask for his key, too?
Oh! Doesn't have one.
And now we know why.
You think he's crazy?
Crucifixion's pretty convincing
evidence. Lead paint?
Place is too new.
He believes in a higher
power that can affect his life,
like most people on the planet.
True. On the other hand,
crucified himself.
No canned tuna and I don't
think we have to worry about sushi.
No computer, no television,
no music. What does he do?
He reads. Prayer has
been proven to aid recovery.
Only if the person knows
they're being prayed for.
Means there's no
objective effect.
So faith comes from within.
Not exactly a newsflash.
I guess worry is
good for the waistline.
It's not worry, it's starvation.
His tooth didn't fall out because
of heavy metal poisoning,
it fell out because
of malnutrition.
He does have rhodococcus equi.
Taub was right.
He just didn't know why.
- It's locked!
- I'm busy.
I'll wait.
I really am busy.
Cuddy got me
the daughter's file.
Well, not Cuddy, exactly.
Her signature.
Well, not exactly her signature.
Another lie?
Thought you could
take a look at it for me.
Maybe you hadn't heard,
I'm kind of busy.
With what?
Sudoku.
What do you think?
I'm the head of oncology
in a major hospital.
And yet these files are
not from this hospital.
These are from
Where-My-Fiancée-Works Memorial.
Sam's boss is doing a
clinical review of all of her files,
and she just wanted to make sure
everything's in order
before he starts on Monday.
Which explains why Sam
is too busy to look at my file.
If I don't help her, she can't
go to the wedding, and...
We fell in love at
her cousin's wedding,
which is why I want to
propose to her at a wedding.
And now, you have 60
seconds to berate me for that
and for helping my
girlfriend with her homework.
You don't want to
propose at a wedding.
Emotions running high,
people on edge.
You want to try somewhere like
a Buddhist temple or an aquarium,
or a Buddhist aquarium.
That only took 10 seconds.
You can spend the rest
of the time on my file.
Rachel?
Hey. How long
before you're home?
Not long.
Hey. Hey.
Uh...
Yeah, you left your laptop on.
I saw you today, at the hotel.
Were you checking up on me?
Yes.
Satisfied?
Good.
That's it?
You said you're
satisfied, that's enough.
You're not wondering
why it started,
that makes me think you
don't want to talk about this,
which makes me think...
You're being paranoid.
You took your cell phone
with you into the bathroom
when you took
a shower this morning.
I made a new friend, online.
In a support group.
A guy?
Yes.
Support group for what?
For people with
unfaithful spouses.
Why didn't you tell us
you were starving yourself?
Well, I wasn't trying to.
I'm on a tight budget and
it seemed like an okay diet.
You seem to be feeling better.
Not really,
my legs are killing me.
How bad is the pain?
On a scale of one to 10,
10 being the worst.
Nine and a half.
Then why are you smiling?
I'm not smiling.
Leg pain
and pseudo bulbar affect.
He's feeling one emotion while
unknowingly expressing another one.
Classic neurohecatia.
Two days of anticholinergics
and you'll be walking out of here.
Really?
No. I just made that up to see
your reaction. Diagnostic test.
This is awesome.
33-year-old carpenter
presenting narcissism,
delusions of grandeur
and hallucinations.
He hasn't had hallucinations.
I'm not talking about him, I'm talking
about him, with a capital O-M-G.
You want us to do a
differential diagnosis on Jesus?
Hears voices, thinks he's the
son of God, probably schizophrenic.
I think you offended him.
You're saying the patient's religious
extremism could be a symptom?
A neuro disorder could
explain all his delusions.
Get an MRI of his brain.
Let's see if we can find God.
Heard you got the daughter's
file. Patient change his mind?
I forged your signature.
Thank you for your honesty.
Think of it as a present.
See, somebody is about to
turn the big 4-5 in several months,
and somebody else wants
to make a very big deal of it.
4-3.
4-3. Are you sure?
Very.
How could I make such a
mistake? In reading your HR file.
Oh, no, wait, I didn't.
And boom goes the dynamite!
Scores are tied. We are even-Steven.
You're right, I did lie.
To HR, not to you.
When I first applied for the VP
admin job, I was 29 years old.
I knew I'd be taken more
seriously if I were in my early 30s,
so I added two years to my age.
You lied to make yourself older?
Are you lying
about being a woman?
Even if you can trap me,
do you think I'll suddenly
embrace the value of lying?
My point is you already have.
I just need to prove it.
Chickens aren't roosting.
She's just got a friend.
A guy she met in an online
support group for cheating spouses.
I've heard of that group.
It's called Irony.
You think she's
cheating on her spouse
with someone from a
cheating spouse support group?
Sounds like the perfect place
to hit on vulnerable women.
Look. Multiple
dense lesions.
It looks like MS.
How did we miss MS?
It was hiding behind
the malnutrition.
MS. attacks the immune
system. No system, no symptoms.
And now we're feeding him
so they're both back.
How are you feeling?
Terrible.
Obviously.
Where are your friends? Still
casting lots for your clothes?
All I ask is that
they pray for me.
Always sacrificing,
very inspirational.
The lesions are in
your temporal lobes.
When those areas
get messed with,
people have strange experiences.
Like hauntings, alien
abductions, past lives...
Deals with God?
You didn't come to
see if I was better,
you came to see if your medicine
has turned me into an atheist.
I'd settle for agnostic.
Faith is not a disease.
No, of course not.
On the other hand, it is
communicable and it kills a lot of people.
I can't move my arm.
You feel that?
Your friends are not
praying hard enough.
It's not MS.
Paralysis is a symptom of MS,
so are leg pain and
pseudo bulbar affect.
He's getting worse on
the prednisone. It's not MS.
The MRI was clear,
he has lesions.
It could be an AVM,
cerebral infarction.
Let's put it to the vote.
Vest or cummerbund?
Cummerbund.
You know me,
I can't say no to any of
you guys. You're all correct.
He has MS. But not the
friendly Mr. Rogers MS.
This is the
weird-guy-in-the-panel-van kind.
Marburg MS?
What did I just say?
He'll be dead in two to
three days, at the most.
That's unless we can
get someone to nail
themselves to a cross
as soon as possible.
Or stem cell treatment.
That's an experimental
treatment.
That's had promising
results with
demyelinating diseases.
It's our best shot.
It would be if it wasn't
embryonic stem cell treatment.
Our patient's right of the pope,
he's never gonna
consent to that.
I know that, you know that,
but he doesn't know that.
But now she knows that,
he's gonna know that.
Way to go.
Confirm Marburg. Then see if
he's a fair-weather flagellator.
You looking smashing,
Miss Moneypenny.
Cummerbund?
Very foolish, Mr. Bond.
The daughter's case checks out.
Stereotactic biopsy confirmed
stage IV glioblastoma multiforme.
It doesn't respond to chemo
but they gave it to her anyway
as a Hail Mary and just got lucky.
So either God intervened,
which is a lazy explanation,
or we just don't know why,
which is no explanation.
Sometimes there is no explanation.
And I'm just fine with that.
Which annoys me to no end.
I need that file,
that chair and that desk.
Your woman is fudging the facts.
Five of those cases,
the stated doses
don't explain
the radiation damage.
Sensitivities vary.
Not that much.
Yeah. That's
what I thought.
I asked her
point-blank about this.
She said the dosages
were accurate,
and that she had
done nothing wrong.
Because morally she didn't.
All five patients were terminal,
she exceeded the dosing
protocols to try to save their life.
You'd have done the same.
She's a sap and
she's perfect for you.
I hate rehearsal dinners almost
as much as I hate weddings.
The only reason
anyone gets married
is because Homo erectus females
needed protection from
predators while breastfeeding.
And the only reason these
two are getting married
is to throw an obnoxious gala to
make the rest of us feel unworthy.
Even though we know in two years
the lawyers are gonna be
fighting over the Bentleys.
That'd make a lovely toast.
She's got looks, he's got money.
One of them is bound to run out.
I give it 19 months.
That's very specific.
No fault divorce in
New Jersey requires
couples to live at
least 18 months apart.
I'm actually only
giving it a few weeks.
I thought I was supposed
to be the dark one.
Not today.
Yeah.
You're gonna have to go stag.
My patient is refusing treatment.
And you care?
No, but it's an excuse
you can't argue with.
Accepting this treatment
is an insult to God.
I can't expect him
to keep our deal.
You already broke it.
Your blood test shows you
were loaded with ibuprofen.
Taking painkillers
breaks my deal?
The point is to suffer
like your savior did, right?
Well, he didn't take myrrh,
the Tylenol of ancient Rome.
And his nails went through
his wrists, not through his palms.
Palms are for sissies.
And what about the 39 lashes,
and the beatings and
the crown of thorns?
What you go through is closer to
a bad manicure than a crucifixion.
It's not about
showing God my pain,
it's about showing him my faith.
If he asks me to die for
my daughter, I'll do it gladly.
Don't make this
about your daughter.
You're just worried that we'll find
a cure that will cost you your faith,
and you'll be
like the rest of us.
Alone and afraid? You're
right. I don't want that.
You're smiling.
Does that mean that you're
comfortable with your choice
or that you're afraid?
Because this may
be your only hope.
You can prescribe a lot of
things but hope isn't one of them.
Sticking by your convictions
and damning the consequences.
You two have a lot in common.
You're both idiots.
All convictions
equally ridiculous?
Just when they're applied
indiscriminately to all circumstances.
He needs to see his daughter.
He needs to see
Inherit the Wind.
And tell her he's dying because God
doesn't want him to take his medicine.
Honesty's not all bad.
Get her in here.
You don't have to die. Not
if you take the medicine.
The treatment
violates God's laws.
He doesn't want me to take it.
But God doesn't want you to die.
He doesn't want anyone
to die. He's all about love.
I know this is
coming from your mother.
This is coming from me.
I'm the one who
almost died, I know what it's like.
You're my daddy, you can't die.
I wish I didn't have to.
You don't have to, Daddy.
Just take the medicine.
You always tell me to
take the medicine. Please.
One day, you're
going to understand.
No, I'm not.
I'm never going
to understand that.
If God could do this,
I hate God.
I just spotted a couple of hot
girls by the chocolate fountain.
Weren't you just
upstairs with...
It wouldn't have happened
if not for you, buddy.
Someone had to distract
the sober friend.
I'm not here to be your wingman.
I'll be your wingman this time.
I didn't come here
to get laid either.
Then don't.
Talking to beautiful women
isn't nearly as much fun
as watching Taub not
talking to his wife.
I went through your e-mails.
There's nothing in
there that's inappropriate.
We're friends, Chris.
But you tell him things
that you've never told me.
I tell him things I can't
tell you, that's the point.
Not things about me, about you.
About your new job,
about coloring your hair,
about how you felt
when your mother died.
I want to know those things.
He's easy to talk to.
He's open and honest.
He makes me feel safe.
Sounds like you love him.
I'm not having an affair.
He lives in Oregon. I've never
met him. I probably never will.
You are having an affair,
an emotional one.
Are you equating what
I'm doing with what you did?
I've done terrible
things to you.
And I deserve all
of this and more.
But you can't pretend that
what you're doing isn't hurtful.
Someone looks lovely tonight.
Thank you.
I meant me.
But someone else
looks simply stunning.
That was you.
And the blonde at the bar.
Just to be clear, this whole
little act isn't gonna work.
I need an apology, not flattery.
It's not an act.
It's the wedding.
You hate weddings.
I thought I did. Then I
realized I've never been to one.
Never?
Turns out they're kind of fun.
Well, I can't complain about
my boss. He's right here.
You're his boss?
Only Mondays through Fridays.
On the weekends, he's my bro.
This round's on the bro?
Um...
I'm sorry about your daughter.
I never meant to hurt her.
You just thought
she'd change my mind.
I was surprised she didn't.
So was I.
I didn't tell you the truth.
When I said I'm
not afraid to die.
But you're going
straight to heaven, so...
That's what I believe.
But I'm human.
So you know you may be wrong.
How could you do
what you just did?
That's why we have beliefs, so
we can still see the right thing to do
when we're blinded
with doubt and fear.
Our beliefs define us. If
we lose them, who are we?
Look, I'm sorry. I didn't
mean for it to go that way.
You think I'm being
selfish but I'm not.
He makes me feel better
about me and about us.
Well, that is hard to believe
because all I feel
right now is betrayed.
I never wanted that.
Good.
Because just like you asked
me to stop my behavior,
I'm asking you to stop this.
No?
I'm not gonna lie to you.
Is this revenge?
I don't know.
But I do know that it's
something I need right now.
What would you wear?
I'm a sucker for the white gown.
Traditionally for young,
first-time brides.
Well, I may not be
young but I'd be first-time.
That is a lie.
You were married before.
In 1987, for six days.
Your knowledge of New Jersey
divorce law made me suspicious,
so I looked it up.
So this was all your trap?
Trap's primitive,
I prefer inveiglement.
Anyway, the point is, I lied to
you, you lied to me, I forgive you.
Well played.
You're tired, aren't
you? All those files.
No, no, I was thinking...
I mean, if those two even have
the slightest chance of making it,
then we have to be a sure thing.
And we've already
made all our mistakes.
And...
I've come to realize
that I love you
even more than I thought I did.
Sam, will you marry me again?
Wow. I don't even
know what to say.
I have a suggestion.
Where did this even
come from? When did you...
You just came to realize?
What made you love me even more?
Everything you've done, your
work, your sense of morality.
The five cases.
I not only agree with
what you did, I admire it.
I didn't do anything.
You already asked me
about the files and
I told you the truth.
I know, and I get it.
You don't believe me.
I believe that you
are a wonderful person.
Who lies and cheats.
No, Sam.
Listen, I'm on your side.
I can't believe this.
What? Sam. Sam,
don't do this.
So how many do you think?
At least three.
Hat-trick Chase.
See? Life of the bachelor.
All of the sex, none of the guilt.
It's not over, okay? I
just really miscalculated.
I thought she'd forgiven
me for everything
but all those hurt feelings,
they never really went away.
That makes a lot more sense.
Ignore him, he just got an idea.
I have one more test to run.
Uh, I hate weddings.
Won't be long now.
You'll be staring down the
yawning void before you know it.
You came from a
wedding to tell me that?
No, I came from a
wedding to run a PET scan.
Thought you'd given up on me.
I have. PET scan
was for your daughter.
I was wrong about her.
She did have glioblastoma.
And she still does.
Cancer never went away.
Yes, it did. They
tested her every year.
With a CT scan
which misses all the tiny little
tumors that a PET scan doesn't.
You made a mistake. She
does not have cancer anymore.
I ran it twice, no mistake.
Looks like God broke your deal.
I'm sorry.
But I'm also right.
You're a bastard.
Do whatever you want to me.
Good call.
Surprised you've got enough
strength to come to work today.
Thirty-six hours is long
enough for me to recover.
And not nearly long enough
for this guy to be getting better.
House wanted us checking
every 12 hours anyway.
Sorry I took off on you.
Twice.
First one was my bad.
Second one I had no choice.
It was a threesome.
They're overrated.
He's bluffing.
Get House.
Got something to show you.
Your daughter's PET scan.
It's clean.
She's fine.
My bad.
Got her mixed up
with Marion Silver.
Marisa Silva.
That's believable, right?
Anyhow, good news for
you, bad news for Mr. Silver.
You tricked me. God
didn't break our deal, I did.
You led me into
temptation and I followed.
And God will
punish you for that.
He has to.
'Cause if he didn't,
it'd make you wonder,
wouldn't it?
He will.
Well, that's why I'm
so confused by this.
This is your MRI. Shows
incremental improvement.
You're getting better.
I double-checked
the name on this one.
But it's not all good news.
This patient is screwed.
Technical term is
dead as a doornail.
Who is that?
God.
You broke your deal with him
but your daughter's fine
and you're getting better.
Nothing bad happened.
Which can only mean one thing,
there is no God.
'Course, if your daughter
gets hit by a meteorite today,
I would have some
serious egg on my face.
You're smiling. I assume
that means you're miserable.
It means I'm happy.
This doesn't mean
God doesn't exist,
it just means
he's truly merciful.
My beautiful Marisa was right,
God is all about love.
Punishment is proof of God and
no punishment is proof of God.
Ingenious argument.
Faith isn't an argument.
I'd like to see my daughter.
Everyone else knew?
Everyone I could trust.
So, yes.
If you had told me,
he'd be dead by now.
So why do I still
want to tell the truth?
Either you're naive, or you have
scruples. I'm not sure which is worse.
This is insane.
We can't work like this.
I can.
Sam?
Sorry, I was hoping to be
done before you got home.
We had a fight.
We had one fight.
And I admitted I was wrong.
We can talk about it,
we can get over it.
This is about trust.
I never lied to
you about anything.
I know,
and I always trusted you.
I...
Maybe we could
talk to a counselor.
You said that helped
after our divorce.
It did, and I think
I changed a lot.
And I haven't.
This is my fault?
I know where this is going.
And I don't want
to go there again.
You're quitting, Sam.
You're quitting again.
So I guess you haven't
changed that much.
Good work today.
Don't even think your
patient's gonna sue.
Looks like everybody's happy.
I've been an idiot.
I got this argument
stuck in my head.
If everybody lies, then trust is
not only unfounded and pointless,
it's fictional.
But trust is not an argument
that can be won or lost.
Maybe I just have to suspend
my cynicism and believe.
Maybe it's time
I took a leap of faith.
I'm sorry.
I won't lie to you again.
Thank you.
Sam left me.
What a moron.
Too soon. I'm still
in love with her.
I meant you.
Do you have a drink?
Or drinks?
Cuddy's coming over.
Does she know you're here?
I apologized to her.
Good for you.
Not really, I lied.
I just took your advice.
Too bad you didn't.
Good for you.