Hey.
So, uh...
What did you want?
It's too late now.
Too late for what?
I'll tell you later. Come
on, the bell just rang.
We've still got time.
I'm ready.
Oh.
You sure?
Yeah.
Why now all of a sudden?
What, you don't want to anymore?
Yeah, I do.
I'm just wondering
what changed your mind.
You did.
Now?
If you want.
Excuse me.
You two need to come with me.
Take a seat.
But we didn't...
You know you're not
supposed to be back there.
We weren't doing anything.
That's not what it
looked like to me.
Principal Fields will be back
as soon as the assembly's over.
Ms. Washburn, please. If I
get one more referral, my mom...
Bench.
Who put sand in her vagina?
Hey, kids.
How you boys doing?
Uh, can we help you?
I certainly hope so.
You know what this is?
A laptop?
A password-protected laptop
that I need you nerds to hack into.
No insecticides
or toxic cleaners.
Check the bathroom.
Who are you?
Your roommate's doctor.
You remember your
roommate, don't you?
I thought he just
had bronchitis.
That's what the morons at the
Rutgers student medical center thought,
which may be part of the
reason he just coughed up a lung.
What do you mean,
"He coughed up a lung"?
He coughed,
after which the respiratory
organ which resided in his chest
resided in his mouth.
Actually, his hand. Well,
his mouth, then his hand.
Bathroom's clean.
What's in this?
Just soda.
Mind if I have some?
You want my drink?
You got a problem with that?
Uh, yeah. Actually, I do.
You barge into our room,
start looking through our
personal private stuff,
demand I hack into a computer,
I think I can safely
assume doesn't belong...
I'm sorry. Did I break your
concentration? Please, continue.
You were talking
about personal privacy.
What, you're finished?
Well, allow me to retort.
Wait a second. You're
saying this actually happened?
Absolutely.
You're lying.
Interesting theory.
Can you prove it?
Doctors don't carry guns,
they don't shoot people,
and they definitely don't
search patients' homes.
Plus I've seen Pulp Fiction,
the movie you're
totally ripping off.
Huh.
Wait, uh, was it Timmy Morgan?
I have no idea.
It had to be him. He's, like,
totally obsessed with old movies.
Pulp Fiction is not
an old movie. What...
So you're here to talk to the
principal about something Timmy did?
I got no problem with Timmy,
and even if I did,
I ain't no snitch.
Then why are you here?
To dig myself out of a hole.
Instead I dug a bigger one.
What did you do?
What happened to your eye?
It's none of your business.
Actually, it's none
of yours. I'm a doctor.
It's a few days old, so
it's not why you're here.
Unless you two got busted
for some sort of revenge plot,
but then you'd look angry
instead of ashamed.
I'm not ashamed.
Interesting.
You defensively insist
that you're not ashamed,
which, of course, means you are
ashamed, and yet you're the victim.
You want to know how
she got the black eye?
Tell us why you're here first.
Anyone ever tell you
you're annoying?
Yes. All
the time.
But he's right. You
wanna know, you first.
I didn't kill anybody.
I have to be here, so I figured
I'd punch up the stakes
in the first act.
But we did and almost always
do search the patient's home.
And if we tell them first,
then they could hide
something that we need to know
in order to figure out
what's wrong with them.
Why would they hide something
that could be killing them?
Because they are morons.
They're
all morons and everybody lies.
Wait. If everybody lies, then
that means you're lying right now.
I didn't say everybody
always lies, Aristotle.
And on that note, unless
there are any questions...
Good.
Oh, Dr. Hourani.
Before you finish, maybe you
could describe what you actually do.
You know, like if someone
comes in for a routine physical.
You want routine?
Please.
It just feels kind of numb.
You do a lot of bicycle riding?
No.
How long have you been married?
Twelve years next month.
And you have six kids.
You don't think it could have
anything to do with that, do you?
Probably.
How often do you
use your vibrator?
Excuse me?
Your battery-operated Brad Pitt.
After giving
the gift of life to six
8-pound 4-ounce wrecking balls,
I think I can safely assume
it's an industrial
strength model.
Dr. Hourani!
Please.
You wanted routine.
Am I done?
Maybe we should just move on.
No problem.
I meant with your typical day.
I assume you see
more than one patient.
Nope.
Okay.
Then I guess we move on
to our next guest...
Wait, if you only
see one patient,
what do you do
the rest of the day?
Dr. Hourani?
Just in time for lunch.
If by "lunch" you mean a
"conference call with the board,"
and by "just in time"
you mean "20 minutes late."
I meant sex.
Fine, lunch.
How about we start
with a small tossed salad?
As of this morning,
I'm on a diet.
Meaning?
I told you, I'm busy.
No, you told me you were
supposed to be busy 20 minutes ago.
But you were obviously able
to put them off then,
there's no reason you
can't put them off now.
How about I wanted
to then and now I don't?
Get your finger off my phone.
We obviously have
something we need to discuss.
Now is not a good time.
If you're mad
because you don't
feel you're getting
the necessary amount
of affection,
all you have to do is ask.
Seriously, not now.
If memory serves,
I enjoyed a healthy Sunday
brunch, SO your insinuation...
Ow! What is
your problem?
You! You are my problem.
You are the most selfish,
self-centered son of a bitch
on the face of the planet.
And I'm sick of it.
I'm just done.
I can't deal with you anymore.
So that's what a typical
doctor does on a typical day.
Any questions?
What's a vibrator?
Why was your girlfriend so mad?
It doesn't matter.
Well, obviously it matters.
I mean, if she's
your girlfriend,
you should care how she feels.
I mean it doesn't matter
to the story.
It's the most important
part of the story.
It's the only thing
that does matter.
You don't kiss her enough.
Is that the problem?
Absolutely not.
Which, by your definition,
means it is.
We kiss plenty.
Your turn.
Then what's the problem?
What's the problem?
Excuse me, when exactly
will the Commandant be back?
Shouldn't be much longer, sir.
Well...
So now you're not gonna
talk. That's real mature.
All right, fine. We got busted
for kissing behind the school.
Now you know why we're here,
so tell us why you're here.
The deal was
about the black eye.
And we didn't kiss.
So you're just
making him beg, huh?
I didn't have you
pegged as a tease.
I'm not a tease.
The available evidence
suggests otherwise.
I'm not a tease.
Prove it.
By telling me your story.
You're a pathetic loser jerk,
and I wouldn't kiss you if I had brain
cancer and your lips were the cure.
Whoa.
She actually said that?
Well, yeah, that was,
like, two days ago...
It doesn't matter.
I clearly didn't lead him
along or anything like that,
which proves
I'm not a tease, so...
Why is your girlfriend
mad at you?
I'm getting a kind of bossy
vibe. I take it you're into that.
Don't answer.
Your turn.
What seems to
be the problem, sir?
I'm having more difficulty
breathing, and some pain in my chest.
You're new, aren't you?
Yeah. I just moved
from Chicago.
Chicago's awesome.
What part are you from?
We need to get a chest CT.
Excuse me,
I'm the senior team member,
which means we don't need
anything unless I say we need it.
Do you want to have an affair?
You want to have a threesome?
You can't talk to her like
that. I'm telling Cuddy.
We need a chest CT.
Get it yourself.
Isn't that like
sexual harassment?
Not if you're good-looking.
Excuse me?
You said the one guy
was short with a big nose.
I guess it's not the
only thing that's big.
What does that mean?
It means he's lying.
Again.
'Cause you can't
handle the truth!
That's so easy.
A Few Good Men.
Okay, I give up. I think we
should move on to our next guest.
Mr. Dryden
works for one of the largest
advertising agencies
in New York City.
Boring.
Can we at least hear what
happened to the patient?
Yeah, please.
If Dr. Hourani
promises to...
Patient's dead.
The floor's yours, Don.
Dave.
He's not dead. You said
earlier he was still in the hospital.
What's wrong with him?
He's got a cough.
You said he coughed up a lung.
What about the laptop?
Who cares about the laptop?
Yeah, and he already said he
was lying about that, you moron.
Gabe, we do not use
that word here. He did.
Yeah, and I was talking
about people like you.
Ooh.
Dr. Hourani, please.
Could you just finish,
quickly, SO we can move on?
I don't know what's wrong.
He was stable for a while
and then all of a sudden...
Bronchial infection
must be from a drug resistant strain.
02 sats are plummeting.
We need to get him
on a bronchodilator
before he goes into
respiratory arrest.
Need suction.
Sit him up.
Start blow-by oxygen.
What is that?
I think this is...
It's his lung.
That actually happened?
Yes, it really happened.
I take cases that other
doctors fail to diagnose,
which is why I only
take one at a time.
My current patient
is a college student.
He's actually in
the hospital right now.
And, yes, he really did cough up
a large portion of
dead lung tissue.
How's that even possible?
That's what she said.
No, she did literally say that.
How's that even possible?
Primary squamous carcinoma could
cause lung tissue to
basically disintegrate.
It's not cancer.
FOB was normal.
It's not infection either.
Broad spectrum antibiotics
haven't had any effect.
Who password-protects
a computer they keep
in a locked desk
in a locked office?
Someone who works with
someone who thinks it's okay
to break into
other people's homes.
An amoebic
liver abscess could rupture
through the diaphragm
into the thorax.
Not when his liver
function tests are all normal.
His dorm mates are
computer science majors.
If they're fabricating chips
they could be working with
all kinds of
different toxic solvents.
We need to search the dorm.
We?
While we're out, do a thorascopic
lung biopsy and c-ANCA
because it's sarcoidosis.
But if you think it's
sarcoidosis, why are you...
So you really did force his
roommate to hack into the laptop?
Why would I lie?
But whose laptop is it?
It's your girlfriend's,
isn't it?
She's not my girlfriend.
I'm just interested in
her because she's a client
and she sleeps
above her covers...
Four feet above her covers.
What?
Ghostbusters.
So that's why she's so mad?
You looked through her computer?
No, that part happened
after she got mad.
First she got mad. Then I
stole her computer to fix things.
And then we got the case.
Wait, so you tried to fix your
relationship by stealing her computer?
Well, when you say it
like that...
Yes.
Looks like you're the moron.
Ooh.
Can also get three sets
of golf clubs in here.
No way.
You didn't get her laptop by
blowing down the door of her office.
That's from
Thunderbolt and Lightfoot.
Just seeing if you're
still paying attention.
It was actually more subtle.
The Thomas Crown Affair.
The Steve McQueen version.
Just tell us the truth already.
Excuse me,
but there are others here
who would like
a chance to speak.
Go right ahead.
No!
The audience is always right.
It wasn't me.
Ma'am, are you okay?
Can you hear me?
Ooh.
What's that smell?
Smells like a gas leak.
Call Dr. Cuddy!
You poisoned
a room full of patients
So you could steal
your girlfriend's laptop?
I didn't poison anybody.
I spilled some hydrogen
sulphide and ammonia on the floor,
thinking the stench would
clear the place out.
But instead of breathing
through his nose,
some idiot decided
to hold his breath.
He passes out
and before I know it,
the place is
a perfect storm
of mass hysteria.
Although it worked out
just as well.
They're morons.
Agreed.
No, not the patients, the kids.
It doesn't matter how you
stole it, what matters is why.
You know, you're starting
to remind me of someone.
I didn't ask how you
stole it, I asked why.
Isn't it obvious?
You think you can tell
why she's mad by reading
budget spreadsheets
and per Diem schedules?
I know why she's mad,
what I need to know is
how to make her un-mad.
Step one is gaining access
to the journal on her laptop
where she records her
inner most thoughts,
instead of just
watching porn with me.
Oh, grow up.
If porn was bad, why would
there be SO many nuns in it?
Why is she mad?
I was myself,
which, by the way, she's
supposed to love unconditionally.
I didn't do anything.
We had a great weekend.
Went to a blues club, we
watched Cinderfella on DVD.
And?
It doesn't matter. She's being
unreasonable and I have to fix it.
I need to know what's really
important to her. I need something big.
Because?
We're past that.
Have you tried
childhood pet names?
I don't know her pets.
She's never mentioned a pet?
Yeah, but I wasn't listening.
She's not mad because I don't
remember a dead dog's name.
Her first dog was Ronaldo.
R-O or R-E-Y?
I didn't ask, try both.
Just got a case from the ER.
Rutgers student came in with
what looked like acute bronchitis.
But there's nothing in his
blood or sputum cultures.
Don't you think
it's time you people
stop looking to the white man
to solve all your problems?
His O2 sats are in the toilet.
If we don't figure out
what's attacking his...
So figure it out!
I'm busy.
That can't be true.
Why not?
'Cause if he was dying...
I mean, you're a doctor.
Patients die every day. Not
all of them are interesting.
You still haven't
answered either question.
She was mad because
she's genetically programmed
to make a big deal out
of every little thing.
So she's mad
'cause she's a girl?
And now she's mad
because she's programmed
to make a big deal out
of every little thing.
Actually, she's not like that.
Why are you sticking up for her?
She said you were a pathetic
jerk and she hates you.
That was a long time ago.
It was two days ago.
And it wasn't even true then.
How do you know?
Because I know how you think.
Really?
Really.
And no peck on the cheek.
It has to be on the lips.
Winning a bet to
force her to kiss you
actually cuts
against your theory
that you know how she thinks.
I wasn't forcing her to do
anything that she didn't want to do.
You hoping for a career
in the NBA or the NFL?
The bet let her do
what she wanted to do,
while still being able
to act like she didn't,
so her friends
wouldn't get all, like,
calling her a slut or something.
Not that it's slutty or
anything, it's just a kiss.
Not even close to true.
I just couldn't
believe I'd lose.
Ah, now we're getting somewhere.
No, we're not.
Oh, I thought we were.
No, you thought we weren't
and that's exactly what you want
because you don't want to
tell us why was she mad at you!
You tell us you don't
want to do your job
because you're too busy trying
to break into your girlfriend's laptop
to figure out a way to
make her not mad at you
but you don't tell us
why she was mad at you.
It's stupid.
Talk.
I'm out of here.
Unless...
Rachel's gonna be up soon.
You never know.
Yes, I do.
Could you take the
garbage out before you go?
I would, but...
Oh, come on.
It's not a lot.
The pain's always worst
first thing in the morning.
Mommy!
You used her toothbrush.
That's so gross.
What's the big deal?
It's not like she had a problem
with swapping spit
the night before.
Maybe it's not the swapping
spit that bothers her,
but the fact that
you don't listen to her.
Had she warned you not to do it?
Oh, I listen to her.
But you just said before
that you didn't.
No, I said I didn't
remember what she said...
No, you said
you don't listen to her.
I listen to her.
Okay? Believe me,
I listen.
It's my toothbrush
and it's not just once,
and it's not like I'd even care,
but you totally destroy it.
You're supposed
to brush with it,
not gnaw on it
like a rawhide bone.
I think Ms. Four-Cavities'
time would be better spent
copying Mr. No-Cavities
instead of complaining about him.
And given what
I'd just been doing,
I thought you wouldn't
want me going out to dinner
without a good brush
and a floss.
Would you please just use
the toothbrush I bought you?
Would you please just shut
up and watch the movie?
I said, please.
Why would you have to brush
your teeth before you go to dinner?
You don't wanna know. Yet.
You're gross and dumb.
You listen to what she says
just so you can tell her
how wrong she is.
You are clueless and naive.
I have to tell her that she's
wrong because no one else will.
She's the boss,
which means she's
surrounded by morons
who are either afraid of her,
or they want to kiss up
to her, or they want to
kiss her.
But not you.
I already kissed her,
and I respect her enough
not to treat her like
some tender blossom
who needs to be coddled.
Makes sense to me.
That's what you think you did?
Yeah, totally.
You?
No, I didn't punch her.
Oh, my God.
You're a moron.
I didn't mean to.
The stick had
a wicked heel curve.
Did I mention, you're a moron?
Hey, you just said
that it's wrong
to treat your girlfriend
like she's weaker than you.
I'm not talking
about trying to score,
I'm talking about shooting high.
Tennis shoes on a wooden floor?
She obviously can't butterfly
and cover the low corners.
Your turn. The laptop.
I must be in the midst of
a complex partial seizure
'cause I know you are
not sitting at my desk.
Sorry, I ran out
of lotion in mine.
Get the hell out of here. Can't.
This is the only place left that
Cuddy will never look for me,
and I still haven't
found what I'm looking for.
I can tell you what you're about
to find. It's my foot in your ass.
I don't think you got
enough lotion for that.
How'd you even get in here?
The door was locked.
Well, either I can
walk through walls, or...
We have lift off.
Is that Cuddy's journal?
No, it's a freelance piece
I'm writing for Teen Vogue.
Let me see that.
Sorry, gotta go.
Key.
Oh.
I gotta give you
one thing, Hourani.
Your wife, she's
beautiful. I mean, wow.
Thank you.
House!
Walt.
I thought you
were Dr. Hourani.
Yeah.
So that's why you're here?
Well, that was stupid.
I know.
Mr. Stupid Head
at your service.
Where are you now?
In the principal's office.
House, we don't
have time for games.
The PET scan was negative
for sarcoidosis.
Great. Means the
treatment's already working.
It would if we'd actually started
the treatment, but we didn't.
Why the hell not?
Because it's not sarcoidosis.
If you were here,
you would know that.
He's dying.
What's left of his lung
has collapsed and FNA
of the mediastinal...
I don't care about the FNA.
What I care about is how
he responds to the treatment.
House...
Just do it.
Sarcoidosis is
a diagnosis of exclusion,
which means that the cowards who
spend their time excluding what it isn't
usually cause their
patients to die from what it is.
I don't get it. Why would
you lie about your name?
Who cares?
What did she write
in her journal?
Thank you!
That is exactly my point. Why
does no one ever believe me?
What?
Just because he's dying
doesn't make it interesting.
You cheated on her, didn't you?
No, I didn't cheat on her.
It's obviously more than
just you used her toothbrush
and wouldn't take
the garbage out.
No, actually,
it was exactly that.
I just need some time alone.
Because I used your toothbrush?
And you wouldn't
take out the garbage.
That's insane.
You know that, right?
You do whatever you want.
Always.
I said I was sorry.
I was still half asleep.
I wasn't paying attention.
And you're always right.
And I don't mean you
always think you're right.
But you are
actually always right.
Because that's all that matters.
That doesn't even make sense.
What? You want me
to be wrong?
I want you to care about
more than just what
you want, what you think.
You need me, House.
And you may even love me,
but you don't care about me.
And I deserve someone who does.
That's what I said!
You don't listen to her.
You didn't say that.
Yes, I did.
Well, I wasn't listening then.
But you found a way
to fix things, right?
That's why you were happy
when you read her laptop.
I did.
At least I thought I did.
She recently got
the thin envelope
from her first choice preschool.
But it turns out, it was
her fake first choice
because she was
convinced she couldn't
get her kid into
her actual first choice
without a substantial donation
or an inside connection.
If it's Brye Park,
I'm afraid she's right.
Wait, that's our school.
What other school
would he be talking about?
Just finish the story.
You know, I gotta tell you,
there's bossy,
which can be sexy,
and then there's bitchy...
Finish the story.
You obviously know this
because you're on the school board,
which puts you on the inside
and being the CEO here
obviously connects you to Cuddy.
Well, if we're so connected,
why isn't she the one asking?
Because she thinks it's wrong
to use connections to
cut in line. I don't.
I might be able to help.
Fantastic.
But I could use a favor as well.
Where are you?
I needed to take care
of something.
It's not a foreign body.
You must've missed it.
If we do any more imaging,
we're gonna have to add
radiation poisoning to the DDX.
I meant the sarcoidosis.
The biopsy and c-ANCA
were both negative.
We're gonna have to
do a pneumonectomy.
No sign of drug
or alcohol abuse.
He's not a smoker, coal miner
or a potter. It's sarcoidosis.
Start him on corticosteroids
and methotrexate.
If it's a drug resistant bug
and we give him steroids...
He'll die, which from the sound of
it, wouldn't be much worse than...
You moron.
But you have to show him
your ID and your insurance stuff.
You can't just
give him a fake name.
You don't have to do anything.
Last time I checked,
this was still America.
'Course that was 10 years ago.
But you're gonna pay him, right?
I mean, it was your fault.
A yellow light
does not mean stop.
At the most, 20% my fault.
Since the insurance
companies automatically
put 100% of the fault
on the rear-ender,
my little lie was
actually an effort
to achieve an outcome
closer to the truth.
And it would've worked, too,
if it weren't for
those meddling kids.
I am Dr. Hourani.
Then why did you say the
other doctor was Hourani?
It's a common name.
It's like Smith in Lebanon.
Let me see your ID.
I told you. I left it
in my other pants.
Really? "Cause it looks
like it's still in this pair.
Get your hands off me.
Give me your ID.
Hey!
Will you stop...
Give me your ID.
Gentlemen, please.
- Kids, stay calm.
- Give me your ID!
Stop! Stop this right
now! Stay in your seats.
Stay calm, you guys.
Stay in your seats.
Gentlemen, please, this
is not the time or place.
Is there a problem
in here, Ms. Corwin?
Why don't you just take off?
It's not like the principal
can call your parents.
No, but the principal
can call the police.
Or the guy he's
doing the favor for.
His girlfriend's
obviously gonna find out.
He's screwed.
I'd bolt.
No, you wouldn't.
Yeah, I would.
How do you know?
What's wrong?
I guess... I don't
wanna do it like this.
Sorry for shooting
the puck so hard
and tricking you in the bet.
You didn't trick me.
Yeah, I did.
I gave Madison a Red
Dead Revolver cheat code
so she'd hit your foot
with the rope.
I knew you couldn't beat me.
You're right.
It's just...
I really like you and I'm
pretty sure you like me, too,
but I don't want to
play any more games.
When you want... I
mean, if you ever want to,
just tell me you're
ready, and, you know...
Sorry.
Well done.
He's not always a jerk.
And neither are you.
She obviously likes you.
Just stop using her toothbrush
and stop playing games.
She'll still like you.
She's bossy,
but she's usually right.
Thank you. FIELDS: Dr. House,
can I ask you a question?
Are you insane or just stupid?
Is there a third option?
Actually,
I don't think there is.
I'm sorry,
I just wasn't thinking.
I mean, I was,
but only about myself.
That's apparently the way I am.
Usually. Not always.
I need to
convince someone of that.
And you think you can do
that by getting someone to
pull strings to get her
daughter into our preschool?
I spoke to Sanford Wells.
You can call the police, you can
turn me in for lying at the accident.
I'm sure Mr. Dryden has
already taken care of that.
Let her daughter in.
She's a great kid and
Dr. Cuddy's a great mom.
They'll fit in perfectly here.
And how exactly does admitting her
daughter prove how unselfish you are?
Seems like you're still
doing it to help yourself,
not anyone else.
I don't know.
I just know that
I need to do something.
I need her in my life.
You know what it's like
to actually need someone?
Yes.
I do.
But I also know what it's
like to have responsibilities.
Maybe it's time you grew up.
Dr. House? Is there
anything you'd like to say?
Can I be excused?
It's just food.
Something small enough
to go down the wrong pipe,
but too big to be washed out
by the bronchial lavage.
Wouldn't show up on a CT.
But would cause the COPD and wouldn't
respond to steroids or antibiotics.
Prep him for exploratory
surgery and start the betting.
Betting?
I got 100 bucks
that says it's a pea.
I'm busy.
I know.
I just want to say
that I'm sorry.
Shouldn't you be saying
that to Sanford Wells?
A fifth grade career day? You
really thought you could pull that off?
I figured, how hard could it be?
And I wanted to prove to you
that I do care about your needs.
And Rachel's.
I do.
Is that why you
also stole my computer?
Yes, it is.
And then threw it in the trash?
I did not throw it, I placed it,
knowing that
the janitor would find it,
and know it was yours, and
return it to you unharmed.
I'm a moron.
But that doesn't mean I don't care
about you, I don't think about you,
I don't want you to be happy.
I was wrong, you were
right. I can do better.
Just give me a chance.
What were you? An
astronaut or a bull fighter?
I was myself.
For the most part.
I know you're still upset,
so I'll leave you to deal
with it however you want.
House.
You want to come over
for dinner tonight?
I'd love to.