Cranial nerves.
On old Olympus' towering tops, a
friendly Viking grew vines and hops.
Olfactory, optic, oculomotor...
vagus, accessory.
Causes of edema.
Alive. Allergic...
Differential for
swollen scrotum.
Theaters, English spelling.
Torsion,
hernia...
Epididymal cyst.
S... Syphilis.
Enough with the drilling.
We're third year, no more exams.
You don't have to
face House every day.
And after today, neither do you.
Here's to no more
coming home in tears.
It's kind of like coming to the
end of an extreme roller coaster,
even with the terror,
nausea and whiplash,
I'm a little sad that it's over.
Let's go.
You got your procedure log?
Oh, I'm not quite done, I still
have one more lumbar puncture.
It's due today.
Unless you wanna blow off
becoming a doctor and get another PhD.
I know. I'm gonna get it done.
I thought you'd have that thing
finished, like, six months ago.
I've been busy.
Oh, come on, Cruz. Let me
do this. I need it for my log.
Wait, you aren't done yet?
I've been busy.
What's in it for me?
The satisfaction that comes
from helping out a classmate?
How about cash?
Have you talked to House?
It's 6:00 a.m. He won't
be in for a few hours.
I keep a roll of
quarters in the car.
I just turned in my log,
and guess what I saw?
There's an opening
in the diagnostics department.
House wants an intern?
He's never had one before.
You got to figure.
He doesn't want an intern,
he wants you.
Uh, you must be Dr. Thirteen.
Remy Hadley. Nice to meet you.
You're back!
Hi.
What the hell happened to you?
Why did you lie
about going to Rome?
You'd lie too if you bottomed
out and ended up in drug rehab.
Thank you, House,
for respecting my privacy.
What a perfect
reminder that I'm back.
I didn't even know
you had a problem.
Loved ones are
always the last to know.
Loved ones and robotic,
estranged ex-boyfriends.
Our patient is Kendall Pearson,
16-year-old aspiring pirate.
She's that Canadian
kid who's trying to be
the youngest person
to sail around the world.
She collapsed yesterday
during a practice run.
Luckily for us,
cameras were there.
Her corporate sponsors want us
to check that she's seaworthy
before the clock strikes,
"You're too old to set a record."
Gives us three days.
You've still
only got one, right?
Uh, last day as a student.
Could be simple dehydration.
She told the Coast
Guard she had felt dizzy.
Pulse and BP were normal
at the time of the rescue.
It's not dehydration.
What about your internship,
did you sign up this morning?
Actually, I'm still deciding.
Maybe she had a seizure and
that's what caused her collapse.
Coast Guard reports there's
no sign of head trauma.
What about her back?
Look, right before the collapse,
she hit the small of
her back on the railing.
Damage to the adrenal glands
caused adrenal insufficiencies,
which caused the collapse.
Nice.
Blood draws every 15 minutes
for four hours, to track her cortisol.
Masters, there's no hurry.
There's no wrong choices.
At least, that's what they tell
people who make crappy choices.
What's with the sudden
interest in her future?
You know, a blacksmith
who spends this much time
hammering out a new
blade from raw Jell-O,
he gets curious about
who ends up wielding it.
No reason to be curious unless
you're interested in wielding it yourself.
You want her to intern here.
And you're considering this?
Before I make my decision,
I still have one
more LP I need to get,
so, I'd like to go to the ER.
Thirteen, why don't you take
Masters to do the blood draws.
You can remind her about
all the perks of working for me.
Behind the deck, port side.
If her adrenal hormone levels are
consistently low, we'll replace them.
You'll be ready
to launch Thursday.
Great.
Inside cabin, facing the bow.
Sorry, K, I need to borrow Mom.
The sponsors?
No, Couric's
people kicking up a fuss
about
rescheduling the interview.
Uh, I can take over.
Ceiling of the galley.
Right.
The last time I was on a boat
was my freshman mixer in college.
I didn't so much mix as hurl.
Too much to drink?
No, I was 13.
And in college?
Yeah, I know. Weird.
I was thinking cool.
We'll be back for the next
blood draw in 15 minutes.
Unless,
of course, you'd like to stay
and continue bonding
over your lost childhoods.
Listen, I have a ton of prep
work to do to be ready to launch.
Is there any way we
can speed the tests up?
Mmm, I'm afraid not.
Unless you're up for
getting on a treadmill.
We could stress her body,
see if her adrenals respond.
It would only take half an hour.
Hmm.
It's about an LP.
Go. I'll handle this.
Um, Dr. Cuddy, can I come by your
office later? I'd love to get some advice.
Uh, I'm in meetings
all afternoon.
Try me tomorrow.
Tomorrow...
This is my last day
as a medical student,
so I've got this
decision to make,
probably the biggest
decision of my career,
which means maybe the
biggest decision of my life.
Although,
I guess, if I get married...
House has opened
up an internship.
You do realize, if you take it,
he'll probably end
up firing you again.
He's always hired me back.
And he'll continue mocking and
insulting you whatever chance he gets.
It's certainly toughened me up.
You're trying to get me
to say good things about him.
No.
I'm trying to make you make your
own decision and leave me alone.
Working with House is great
and it sucks, often simultaneously.
Most people can't
work in that environment.
Question is, can you?
Thanks, Dr. Cuddy.
You paged me down here
and now you're doing my LP?
Got bored waiting.
It's been two minutes.
This is your 11th.
Fourteenth.
Listen, your roommate, is she
hooking up with that resident?
I gotta find House.
Rehab?
It's a great cover story.
Now, I can't ever drink
around those guys again,
thus eliminating my
main bond with Chase.
Save the attitude
for someone who didn't
just get you your
medical license back.
Price you pay.
There's
a chicken in your office.
No, there isn't.
You lied about rehab?
Oh, great.
Relax.
She's completely honest but
also completely boring. Watch this.
Don't tell anyone.
Of course not.
You did an LP?
Why didn't you page me?
Oh, I'm sorry.
Did you want to do one of
those? You should've spoken up.
You want the job or not?
Um... I...
After careful consideration,
I have decided to accept
your offer for an internship.
Great.
My department has a
slightly different procedure log.
Uh, you forged the last one.
I only did nine LPs.
Do you know how to do an LP?
Of course.
Do you know how to do nine LPs
and say it was 107
It's time to grow up.
Turn that in, the job is yours.
Stop staring blankly and go.
No doubt something horrible
has just happened to our patient.
Her hand turned
completely blue during the treadmill test.
We put her on vasodilators,
restored enough blood flow
so she won't lose any fingers.
Rules out adrenal insufficiency.
Where's House?
He said to meet him here.
His chicken's gone.
Probably on the balcony.
You knew he had a chicken?
- How come...
- Down here!
Loss of consciousness
plus she's slowly turning blue.
Have we ruled out magical gum?
Low cardiac
output can cause both.
Patient possibly
has cardiomyopathy,
possibly caused by
mercury poisoning
from all the tuna
fish she eats at sea.
Uh, why are you putting
chicken footprints on the floor?
That clever bastard Wilson
got hold of an Australorp.
Hello.
The quietest and
calmest of all the chickens.
Damn him!
Mercury poisoning is out. Red
blood cells have normal morphology.
Raynaud's. Vasospasm in
the ulnar artery would explain the hand.
But not the loss
of consciousness.
Cerebral
vasospasm explains both.
Cerebral vasospasm makes sense.
Take Thirteen, give the patient
a calcium channel
blocker infusion
in the basilar artery.
Masters.
Thought you were
gonna turn that in.
I'm a bit busy with my patient.
You're not busy now.
Masters.
Still haven't
turned in your log?
Still haven't gotten my 10th LP.
I was thinking. Maybe you
should take House's internship.
First you act like
it's the equivalent
of volunteering to
be water-boarded,
and now you're supporting it?
You're weird.
You make paper airplanes for fun
and hang them from the ceiling.
You have a membership
to the Einstein Museum
and an overbearing obsession
with facial symmetry.
It indicates
freedom from disease.
We're
biologically programmed to...
Point is,
you rub people the wrong way.
But House is okay with
your lack of bedside manner,
he's okay with your willingness
to argue any point, with anyone,
even if they outrank you,
he's okay with your
peculiar fashion sense.
It's peculiar?
House doesn't think
you're weird, which is weird.
But good weird.
Is that a chicken?
I think it's an Australorp.
I'm gonna go
check on my patient.
Can someone please explain to me
what House and Wilson
are doing with those chickens?
They have a bet
to see who can keep
a chicken in
the hospital the longest
without getting
busted by security.
Advancing past
the vertebral artery.
And why are they doing this?
The place they bought them
only had one pig.
I'm glad you're gonna be
sticking around after today.
Really? You want me to stay?
It's good to add a different
perspective to the department.
Someone who still remembers
there are rules other than House's.
If I don't play by House's
rules, he won't let me in.
Find a way around them.
I'd have to lie to him,
which is still lying.
Lying about a lie, that's
practically telling the truth.
Catheter is in. Start the
calcium channel blocker drip.
Means I need another LP.
Luckily, I know where you
can get one. You good here?
Let's go.
Decent stick, very smooth.
Sounds like you've
had a few of these.
Suppose that comes
with the territory.
I have Huntington's. No need to
get hushed and solemn about it.
Why are you lying about rehab?
Because the real
reason I was gone
is not something
I want to share.
Couldn't you just say that?
Should be enough
for Foreman and the others.
How long have you worked here?
House's people have
personalities that range from nosy
to "Pardon me while I
do this cavity search."
Do you think there's room for
someone who does things differently?
No.
Not unless House decides
that's what he wants.
During catheter removal, I
got a good look at her cerebral midline.
Her pineal gland is calcified.
Case closed.
We'll start her on hormone
therapy and ship her out.
I handed in my log.
On your way to do that,
did you happen to stop
and give Thirteen an LP?
Thirteen's stiff gait,
small pupils,
and the raging headache
she's hiding gave you away.
Yes, and I still broke a rule.
My rule.
I told you to defy the
Man, not this man.
Why is it so wrong that
I don't like to cheat?
Can we go?
No.
Not liking it is fine,
not doing what you don't like
makes you an eight-year-old
and wastes your potential.
You want me to be like
you, it's not gonna happen.
That's the last thing I want,
'cause then neither one
of us would be exceptional.
You think I'm exceptional?
Not anymore.
I can do my job
without compromising.
No, you can't. 'Cause
I'm not gonna let you.
Internship's gone.
It's time for Masters
to say goodbye.
Enjoy being a surgeon.
You'll be fine.
Surgery.
Anatomy.
The branches off
the subclavian artery.
VITamin C and D. VIT.
VITamin. V, vertebral,
I, internal carotid.
Internal thoracic.
T, thyrocervical,
C, costocervical...
Martha M. Masters.
That's me!
I'm gonna be a surgeon.
Next!
Welcome to your
surgical internship at PP TH.
The senior residents
stand behind you.
We'll all get to know
each other soon enough.
Grab a donut and get to work.
We're out of donuts.
Then get to work.
Little oozing.
- Isolated the left subclavian.
- Suction.
You gotta do better
than that. Can't see a thing.
Push calcium chloride.
It will supercharge the platelets
and increase the clotting.
Two amps of calcium chloride.
Tell the blood bank to send up
three units of packed red cells.
The field is clear.
Nice.
Generally speaking,
pledges aren't supposed to
talk unless asked a question.
That's because,
generally speaking,
pledges don't
have anything to say.
Um... "KP."
Is that patient Kendall Pearson?
I thought she was discharged.
Mmm. It's a House case.
I never know what
that guy is up to.
I want you to scrub
in on my lung harvest.
But it's my first day.
Yes, I know. I was there. Be
scrubbed and ready in 15 minutes.
What happened? Last I
heard, you were going home.
Kendall collapsed
in the parking lot.
They're doing something
called a sympathectomy.
She must have had
a hypertensive crisis
caused by neural
overstimulation of her kidneys,
so they're cutting the nerves.
It's like cutting the
gas line to an engine.
Yeah. Sounds like
what Dr. Taub said.
Said it's basic
surgery but... It is.
You should still be on pace
for a launch in 36 hours.
Her mom's packing the boat now.
I'm supposed to
pick up some dry ice.
But...
Nothing you can do for her here.
Um...
We're just trying to help our
daughter reach her dream.
She's different.
So, you have to be different.
I'll make sure she's okay.
Thanks.
You can see the full
lobular structure of the left lung.
Bifurcate innominate artery.
I've never seen one of those before.
Hold this, Masters.
Rib spreaders.
You guys okay if I pull a circulating
nurse? We got a train wreck in OR 10.
You got it.
Proximal end attached.
Can someone
take the retractors for me?
Not really.
I have to use the bathroom.
I know you're a
rookie, but you gotta be kidding.
- I'm not.
- It can wait.
I'm gonna have an accident.
Next one in line, grab it.
What's wrong?
Hypotension.
Low cardiac output.
Float the Swan.
Don't you have your own surgery?
I took a break.
I told them I had to pee.
You lied.
Small one but
it's a gateway lie.
I care about the patient.
Another lie.
You care about
being exceptional.
I told her dad I was
gonna take care of her.
A third lie. Welcome
to the slippery slope.
RA is 8.
Equalization of pressures.
I think she has
restrictive pericarditis.
Add that to a
calcified pineal gland...
When is a calcified pineal
gland not a calcified pineal gland?
I realize technically
it's never, but...
When it's a granuloma.
It's Wegener's. We
should start her on steroids.
But she had a high CK.
Wegener's wouldn't explain that...
Dehydration does.
Yes. But the calcified
pineal could be sarcoidosis.
You had me at,
"I had to pee."
But Thirteen's right. Start her on
three-fold immunosuppressants.
Masters, you want
to fight me on this,
fill out a consult form
SO you can stick around.
Welcome back.
I'm not back!
I'll just be
staying for this case.
You got really good
at this lying thing.
Hope it was one hell of a whiz.
I ran into Dr. House.
He requested a surgical
consult for his patient.
House never asks for a consult.
Something about this case,
he needed a little more help.
First day of your
surgical internship,
you want to be loaned out
to another department.
Interesting career move.
Drop the form by my office.
Don't stay away too long. I'm already
well on my way to forgetting you.
How about I take both you
lovely ladies out for a drink?
I'd love to except I
think you're a cretin.
And the last time she was
at a bar was ballet class.
I didn't take...
Oh.
That's funny.
I'm gonna stay and run a few
extra tests on House's patient.
This one lab value
doesn't make sense to me.
You're back with House? Mmm.
Just this one case.
I'm not staying.
I would kill for a
chance to work with him,
like, literally skin you and
wear you as a disguise.
You want yours extra
crispy or original recipe?
Chickens!
You ever get sick from poultry?
Um... A few months ago,
from this pheasant-in-a-can
my dad got me as a joke.
You think that's why I'm sick?
I think that can was chock-full of a
bacteria called salmonella enteritis.
Likes to hang out in the bones.
Let me know if any of
this is tender or painful.
This bacteria thing,
is this good news or bad?
Well, if I'm right, that means
all you'll need are antibiotics
and you'll be, well, shipshape.
Sorry, couldn't resist.
Did you always know
that sailing was it for you,
that it was the right thing?
Didn't even start till I was 10.
And at first, I was not a fan.
Certainly there's plenty
not to like about sailing.
But now that
you're so into it...
Oh, no, there's still plenty
of things I hate about it.
I hate being wet,
I hate being cold,
I hate eating nothing
but freeze-dried food.
That's quite the endorsement.
Sailing is amazing
but it doesn't mean
I love every second on the boat.
Doing what you love means
dealing with things you don't.
If there were nothing to
overcome, it might not be that...
Ow!
Salmonella
enteritis is a nice catch.
Thanks. Starting
on the soft tissue windows.
Once this case is over,
you going back to surgery?
That's the plan.
I think that's a mistake.
I think you should
go back to surgery.
I just said I was.
No, you said it was your plan.
Which means House might be right
and you might be
lying to yourself.
Would it be so terrible?
You chose House over surgery.
And my time here
changed me in ways
that not everyone in my life
thought was for the better.
No masses.
Moving on to bone windows.
Are those people right?
I think when you do change,
it's not so simple to go back.
There.
In the humerus.
Doesn't look like an infection.
That's because it
looks like cancer.
You have a lymphoid sarcoma.
A cancer in the bone in your arm.
Am I going to be okay?
It's a treatable cancer.
But part of that treatment
involves amputating your arm.
I'm sorry.
There's nothing else?
Um...
We can do chemo and
radiation, after the amputation.
I don't mean after,
I mean, instead of.
If I leave soon, I still have
time to break the record.
Honey, you can't be serious.
I feel fine.
Last night, they thought
it was an infection.
We know it's cancer. We
ran the biopsy three times.
You don't know how fast...
Postponing the surgery
could increase the likelihood
that the cancer will spread.
Kendall, you need to think
about what the doctor's saying.
I'm thinking about this sail,
like I have since I was 10.
Don't take this away from me.
It's just a month, I can
take extra precautions.
I'll Skype you every day. And I
can fly back if something goes wrong.
She'll be risking her life.
I think we need to
discuss this as a family.
You're considering this?
Your daughter's condition...
Thank you, Dr. Masters.
She's not budging.
She wants to launch tomorrow.
She's a minor. You sign the
consent form, we can do the surgery.
Amputation can
be an emotional...
She's talked my wife
into agreeing with her.
One parent's
signature is enough.
She needs you to be a parent.
You're asking me
to blow up my family.
I'm asking you
to save your family.
On her first solo
Atlantic crossing,
she scheduled a court date to
become an emancipated minor.
She'll do it again.
And she'll win.
She's gonna do what she's
gonna do with or without me.
I'd rather have it be with.
I'm stuck.
No, you're not.
Case is over.
You're back to surgery.
Fetch!
Who's a good boy?
Good boy.
No one will stop Kendall's
sail. You need to step in.
Sign on the door says
I'm a diagnostician.
Cool diagnosis
means I'm finished.
She could die.
Pretty sure the law
of the land states
that everyone has
the right to be an idiot.
I think it's
the second amendment.
Fetch!
Bring it here.
Good boy.
Who's a good boy?
You are constantly
railing against hypocrisy,
forcing people
to face the truth.
This time, nothing?
Yeah, because
they've faced the truth.
And made a decision that will in
all likelihood Kill their daughter.
I'm fine with that.
I wanted a diagnosis, I got it.
What do you want?
I don't want her to die.
Break the rules.
I can't.
So coloring inside the
lines is more important to you
than saving this girl's life.
I was wrong about one thing.
You are not exceptional.
And fetch!
Oh, ho, ho!
Who's the good boy?
Good boy.
Dr. Wilson?
I'd like to get your advice
about a cancer patient.
Kendall Pearson?
Oncology rounds.
Everyone's talking about it.
Ow!
Are you okay?
Yeah. My back's acting up.
Oh.
Um... So...
What would you do?
I would keep trying to
convince her to have the surgery.
And if she kept saying no?
I would just keep...
Mmm... Keep... Keep trying.
I know there's
a chicken under there.
Oh, thank God.
He already pecked through
one pair of my loafers.
So, that's all you'd do?
That's all you can do.
Is it?
Isn't that House's chicken?
Disgusting beasts. I don't know
why I ever agreed to this bet.
So call it off.
And lose $20?
Listen.
House was in the exact
same situation Kendall's in.
He needed surgery
but he didn't want it.
Once he was in
a medically-induced coma,
his girlfriend signed the
consent form as his proxy.
They went ahead with
the surgery against his will.
Probably saved his life.
So, she did the right thing?
Depends on who you ask.
Fetch!
No! No!
Excuse me!
Who's responsible
for this chicken?
Does anyone know
who owns the chicken?
That bird belongs
to Dr. Gregory House.
You need to do the surgery.
I will.
Now.
We've been through this.
I'm leaving today.
It's a stupid record.
It's not about the record.
I used to race
against other people.
I could have the slowest
boat in the fleet and I'd win.
So it's about being
better than everyone else?
It has nothing to do
with anybody, except me.
The other racers
would think I was crazy.
I'd set off on some tacking
angle that made no sense to them
because they couldn't
see what I saw.
I could sense the changes in the
wind before they even happened.
At the top of the game,
you play by different rules.
Medicine's gonna
burn a little bit.
Bradycardic arrest.
Third-degree heart block.
Likely
a paraneoplastic syndrome.
Need to get her to the OR for a
pacemaker and plasmapheresis.
What's going on?
The cancer is causing
her heart to slow down.
We have to get her
to the OR and treat her.
This is what
I was worried about.
If this had happened at
sea, she would be dead.
Oh, my God!
We need you to
sign the consent form,
authorize us
to amputate her arm.
Subclavian access established.
- Temporary pacer ready.
- Don't need it.
Push calcium chloride.
It'll fix the heart block.
Bradycardia was me.
You did this?
Her parents signed
the consent form.
Amputate her arm.
What happened?
You had a cardiac episode that
required us to bring you into the OR.
That crisis resolved, but...
What did you do?
During the surgery, we found
cancer in a lymph node in your neck.
So you cut off my arm?
The cancer was already
spreading. It had to be done.
I told you I didn't want this.
If we had waited until after the
sail was over, you would have died.
That record,
that was everything.
It wasn't everything.
You have a life, a future...
You weren't supposed
to do this! How could you?
Because we love you.
I hate you.
I hate both of you.
Okay.
My arm...
My arm!
Dr. Masters.
Thank you.
Someone has got
their pouty face on.
I did things no doctor
in their right mind would do.
Good.
I manipulated,
lied, forged, stole.
I don't want to know the
specifics. I might be called to testify.
I broke the rules because
I believed I was right.
You were right.
Then why don't I
feel good or satisfied?
Instead I just feel
like throwing up.
And you're following me to ask
how I break the rules and
maintain my rosy demeanor?
I didn't do it to be happy.
I just thought I would be.
Well, you can't
always get what you want.
To the victor, the spoils.
Your bird recover okay?
Physically, yes.
Emotionally,
it was a long night.
Next week, ferrets?
House.
I can't do it.
I'm leaving.
Surgery?
I don't know what I'm gonna do
but I do know I don't want to be here.
Nothing will ever
be simple again.
I'm fine with that.
Oh!