What's the difference
between a sea lion and a seal?
What's that, baby?
What's the difference
between a sea lion and a seal?
Seals tell the truth, but a
sea lion is always lying?
A sea lion has ears.
Yeah, that's right.
I forgot.
I'll show you when
we get to the zoo.
Can we have pizza tonight?
I'm not gonna be here, Daisy.
I'm going back on
the road, remember?
You've only been
here for two days.
I'll be back in
three weeks this time.
Somebody help her!
She's having a seizure!
There's a lady down there.
Daddy, come back! Daddy!
Hey, lady. Hey, lady, are
you okay? Come on. Come on.
Hey, wake up!
Come on, get up! Hey...
Come on.
Help me!
Somebody help me!
Come on!
Hurry! Hurry up!
Daddy!
Move the train!
Hey, man, are you okay?
Yeah, I think so.
She's epileptic.
Come on, let's get you up.
You all right?
Here we go.
Hey, sweetie, I'm okay.
Daddy?
I found this case in the ER.
White male, mid-30s, loss of
consciousness, abnormal EKG,
and he's the subway hero.
Your enthusiasm is impressive.
Wish I could say the same
about your presentation.
Everybody knows you lead with
your most interesting symptom.
You're right, EKG is more
interesting than loss of consciousness.
So I think we should do...
God! She's still talking,
make it stop.
House's world view doesn't
include random acts of self-sacrifice.
He's gonna count heroism as a
symptom until proven otherwise.
The guy did a wonderful thing.
Can't we just take
that at face value?
You are adorable.
Heroism does exist.
What about the guy who
landed the plane in the Hudson?
News flash, that guy
was already on the plane.
For all we know he would have
killed everyone else on board
if it increased his chances.
Faced with almost certain death,
a normal person rides the pine.
What about firefighters?
The guys who undergo
months of training
to deny their own instincts
for self-preservation?
And the patient
isn't a firefighter.
He plays a bass in a band.
So humanity is apathetic
and self-serving?
Yeah.
I was mugged once. When I
saw the gun, my legs went out.
I always thought
it was "fight or flight,"
didn't know it was
"fight or flight or faint."
Laugh all you want, the other
100 people stayed on that platform.
That's a normal
response to danger.
The coward has spoken. Our
patient's problem is neurological.
Sympathetic stimulation.
Stress to the brain triggers
a response in the heart.
Go forth and look for masses
in Clark Kent's limbic system.
Seems like you're
getting a bit of attention.
Everyone keeps going out
of their way, asking me if I need anything.
It's kind of nice.
So what happened out there?
I don't really remember.
It's just images, like flashes.
I kind of went on autopilot.
My memory doesn't go back into
real time until I was in the ambulance.
I read that's pretty common for
people in life-or-death situations.
- Jack.
- Honey.
This is my wife Eva.
Are you okay?
Yeah, I'm fine.
They're just doing some tests.
How's Daisy?
She's not so good, actually.
She watched her father
jump in front of a train.
She's still shaking,
she can't stop crying.
Why would you do that to her?
He saved a woman's life.
He could have died.
Did you even think
about your family?
I need your advice.
Dinner with your
mom on Thursday...
It's my birthday.
I know.
I'm definitely coming.
Wilson's got tickets to the
Hong Kong Film Festival.
Ever since his break-up
he's been a mess.
I haven't been able to
tell him that I'm not going.
So maybe if you
happen to see him,
you can mention how
important this is.
You should go.
What? I can't.
It's your birthday.
It's fine. It's sweet that
you care about your friend.
And frankly, as you will
find out sooner or later,
my mother is a handful.
Go.
I need your advice.
This film festival...
I have had these
tickets for two months.
Yeah, I know.
I'm definitely coming.
Okay.
But Thursday is Cuddy's birthday
and her mom's coming down.
It's a whole dinner thing.
And I thought,
maybe if you see her,
you could mention how
upset you've been...
You have to go.
Your girlfriend's birthday?
It's not even a question.
She has one every year.
How often do you break
up with the love of your life?
Okay, for you, it's more
often than most, but still...
I'm a big boy,
I think I'll survive.
I will definitely
make this up to you.
Hey.
Am I imagining things,
or did I see a billboard with your
face on it on my way home tonight?
Was my whole face there?
'Cause I just saw the nose.
I thought you
said they were taking a picture
of a bunch of doctors together.
They did. I have no idea
how it ended up just me.
Well, you are pretty cute.
You're flirting with me?
Don't see anyone
else in the room.
What?
I don't know.
Things have been a
little tense around here
since that whole
online-boyfriend thing.
Phil's not my boyfriend. I'm
not the one with the problem.
No, you're the one with
feelings for someone else.
You're still my husband,
I still love you,
and I want things
to be okay between us.
Also, you're a famous
model now. That's pretty cool.
Sexy, even.
So I advance through
the carotid bifurcation?
Are you asking?
Yes, I'm asking.
I've only read how to do it, but
practice is different than theory.
Just tell me how to do it.
You're gonna inject dye just
past the takeoff of the optic artery.
Now?
His BP's going up, the
procedure's stressing his body.
What do I do?
Hold on a minute.
Just give him a chance
to regain equilibrium.
BP's up, heart rate's 180.
What should I do?
Give me the catheter,
get the crash cart.
He's in cardiac arrest.
Maybe your second
time will go better.
So we finally know what Taub
would look like if he were life-size.
Can we go back
to the office now?
You kidding?
We got a differential to
run. Cardiac arrhythmia...
That poster got me laid when I got
home last night, SO do your worst.
Arrhythmia proves I was right.
Jack's problem is his
heart, not his brain.
So when you're not on a
billboard you sleep with nurses,
but when you are you
sleep with your wife.
I think you got that backwards.
That's my elbow in the corner.
What's your wife doing later?
Huh. They chose you
and cut out Chase?
Apparently, Marketing thinks
my face is the most trustworthy.
For real?
Both of our
patient's cardiac incidents
happened after physical stress.
I'm guessing vasovagal syncope.
Buzzkill.
Vasovagal syncope would
manifest at a much younger age.
Could be drugs.
Tox screen was clean.
What about autonomic
nervous system dysfunction?
Could cause arrhythmia
and fainting.
Inappropriate? I mean
because of the Jew thing?
Autonomic nervous
system dysfunction. I like it.
Let's biopsy his
pituitary gland.
Adrenal venous sampling
makes more sense,
and it is a less
invasive procedure.
Which you don't care about because
you just want to check the pituitary
because you still think there's
something wrong with the guy's brain?
Can't fool you.
He has no other symptoms
for pituitary disease.
We can't stick
a needle in his brain
because you don't
believe in heroism.
Fine, do it your way.
You'll waste half a day, but I'm
sure he's in no hurry to get better.
The autonomic nervous system
controls involuntary actions,
like your heartbeat.
If we're right, it's
manageable, but will progress.
Do you think we could
consult with him?
I didn't know
you knew Dr. Taub.
I don't.
You saw the ads.
Look, no offense, but
you were wrong yesterday.
And they wouldn't have made
him the face of the hospital
if he weren't
really good, right?
Dr. Taub.
The patient would
like to see you.
How can I help?
I forgot, you guys talk.
Look, no offense
to either of you,
but dinner with
your mom? Come on.
I'd have to act like
a decent human being.
You know what a strain
that puts on me.
And, you,
ever since you
broke up with Sam,
you've done nothing
but mope and whine.
It's an unbelievable bummer.
And just what is SO exciting
you have to blow off
both of us to do it?
I just want to sit on my couch
in my underwear, drink scotch,
and watch The Real
Housewives of New Jersey.
By myself. I just
want one night off.
Is that so much to ask?
Yes.
You have to choose one of us.
I choose Wilson.
Good, because he's coming
to my birthday dinner.
I do not whine.
Jack's not exactly
the hero-type.
He started this band in college.
They gig around the country,
looking for their big break.
It's been 16 years.
That must be hard
on you and Daisy.
It's like I'm a single parent.
I love him so much,
but I'm at the end of my rope.
What Jack did yesterday
was so incredible,
our boss assumed his illness had
something to do with his behavior.
But if that's not the case,
there's more to
him than you think.
You think Taub
really comes across
as the most
trustworthy doctor here?
I knew it was bugging you.
They cut me out.
You're a pretty boy.
Works well with the ladies,
not so much with the patients.
No one wants an underwear
model performing their splenectomy.
I notice they weren't exactly
knocking down your door
looking for
Dr. Trustworthy.
That's 'cause I'm black.
Cortisol levels look
normal. We were wrong.
Which House will
interpret as him being right.
He's gonna make us biopsy
the pituitary gland.
You seem pretty calm for a
guy who's surrounded by racists.
80% of the Princeton
population is white.
Some are racist, some aren't.
White works with
both demographics.
So race IS your excuse,
not the fact that
you usually look like
you're about to punch
someone in the face?
We're good.
02 sats are dropping.
He's not breathing. Suction.
Sats are coming back.
Mucus plug. That's weird.
Fluid in the lungs.
Pneumonitis?
That doesn't fit
with anyone's theory.
Our tests finally
rule out the brain.
That leaves
the heart and the lungs.
Pneumonitis can be
caused by bacteria,
parasite, some kind
of obstruction...
Who was the girl on the tracks?
News story said her name's Chloe
Jefferies. Why does that matter?
'Cause there's another
reason besides being sick
that he'd risk his
life for a stranger.
She's not a stranger.
The damsel in distress
is an epileptic,
SO we assumed she was
having an epileptic seizure.
But what if she wasn't.
What if she's sick, too?
Jack is away a lot, on tour.
What happens on the road
stays on the road.
The most likely cause of
pneumonitis is infection.
Shouldn't we be getting
a sputum culture?
There's no significant elevation
in white blood cell count.
This is more like
toxic exposure.
He's got a point.
Why is your assumption
of his guilt
more valid than my
assumption of his selflessness?
Because my assumption is backed
up by millions of men, and Taub,
who've cheated on their wives.
Find the girl and the love nest.
Every hero has his Kryptonite.
Hello?
So we're breaking into
this girl's apartment
because House thinks
that two people
standing 30 feet apart on a
subway platform have to be lovers.
God, you're a drag today.
Let me guess. You're back
to fighting with the wife?
No.
We had sex again last night,
twice. And again this morning.
Oh.
Rachel hasn't wanted this
much intimacy in a long time.
I don't think it's me she's
hot for, it's this Internet guy.
She's just happy and
that's turning her on.
So she's not cheating on you
and you're getting all
the action you can handle.
I don't see the downside.
What was Jack's band called?
Suicide something.
Suicide Season.
She does know him.
Question is,
how'd they get sick?
Kryptonite.
EKG's unremarkable. Thyroid,
liver and kidney function seems fine.
You're perfectly healthy.
I wish that you would
take a second look.
I'm tired all the time
and when it's cold,
I get this weird
pain in my shoulder.
I have a pain in my leg,
you don't hear me complaining.
Except for just now.
How do doctors get this idea
you're better than everyone else?
Probably all that pulling people
back from the brink of death.
It's just a guess.
My own daughter's a doctor.
She makes a hobby of
dismissing my concerns.
She sounds smart.
Did she tell you to say that?
I've never met your daughter.
That's hard to believe, since
you're currently shtupping her.
We have a situation.
Roach bombs, where?
In Chloe's apartment.
Who's Chloe?
Look, we don't care
about your personal life,
we're not gonna
tell your wife...
I honestly have no idea
what you're talking about.
Guess who showed up
looking for Jack.
Hey.
- Hi.
- Are you okay?
The EMT said you'd gone
to another hospital.
They held me overnight
for observation,
I'm fine. I had to
come here to...
I don't know why you
did it, but thank you.
You're welcome.
I should have brought
flowers, or something.
You're like my guardian angel.
No, I'm just a guy in a band.
Maybe you've heard of
them? Suicide Season.
One of my nurses gave me the CD.
I haven't had a chance
to listen to it yet,
but I have a feeling I'm
going to be your biggest fan.
I'm gonna need you to cough.
What are you doing?
Getting a sputum culture.
They obviously don't know each
other, so it's not toxic exposure.
Just leaves my theory,
infection.
If you could just cough up a
sample, we can test for pathogens.
Sorry. Sorry. There's nothing...
There's nothing coming up.
Well, maybe I can help you.
- It hurts!
- What's the matter?
Round, equal, reactive
to light, it's not a stroke.
No, it's not my head,
it's my ears.
When I saw her
lying there I thought,
I can't just stand
here and let her die.
She has her
whole life to live.
He didn't jump because he was
sick or because he knew that girl.
Even you have to admit that now.
Yes, but that doesn't make him
a hero, it just makes him an idiot.
The only reason that
headline doesn't say
"Moron crushed
by train" is luck.
Next headline is gonna be
"Moron goes undiagnosed
"because doctors won't
talk about his ear pain."
Ear pain fits with my theory.
Jack has an infection
that spread to his mastoid.
Great, we'll
confirm that in a week
when your secret
cultures have sprouted.
Am I in trouble?
I only get mad
when you waste my time,
I couldn't care
less about yours.
But let me know when they come
back negative and I'll mock you.
- You have a better idea?
- No.
So I'm gonna pick one at
random. Acoustic neuroma?
A tumor
in the ear. Makes sense.
And if it's putting pressure on
the breathing centers in his brain,
it explains the lungs.
The lungs explain the heart.
Evoked auditory potential test.
This counts as my time.
You guys got this?
I have been going out of my way
to be nice to old Jewish
ladies for months now,
on the off chance one of
them could be your mom.
You couldn't have
mentioned she's a shiksa?
She converted when
she married my dad.
You see, now is too late.
I'm not blaming you for this.
She's the one who ambushed
you to find out what you were like
because "I never
tell her anything."
I'd have to agree
with her on that one.
Anyway, I obviously
can't come to dinner now.
Obviously?
She's crazy and she hates me.
House,
I need you to come to
that dinner for two hours,
keep your mouth shut
and behave like an adult.
Yes, you will be in hell,
but I will feel better
having you there.
That is what a relationship is.
We average our misery.
That was
unexpected.
I'm having a good day.
I finally resolved
that thing with my sister.
What thing?
We had the worst fight over whether
it's time to put Dad in that facility.
I've been sick
over it for weeks.
You never mentioned
anything about your sister.
I actually talked
a lot about it with Phil.
I should be getting back.
It's fine now.
It's no big deal.
Are you in love with him?
I've never met him.
Waves one and three
normal at 70 decibels.
It's been 37 minutes
and everything is normal.
House was wrong again,
he doesn't have a tumor.
House doesn't usually accept
"we gave up halfway" as an answer.
If I could get fluid closer
to the sources of infection,
I could get better
cultures, prove my theory.
I'm gonna set up for an ear
drainage and a thoracentesis.
I'll only be wasting my time.
She's a student.
Somebody's got to go with her.
I saved that girl.
I did that.
I'm really proud of you.
This whole thing
has made me wonder
if things could be different.
I have spent so much
time away from you.
Yeah, well.
You love your music.
But it's not just that.
I think that I have been
afraid.
That I would screw things up,
that I couldn't be the man you
and Daisy needed me to be.
But maybe I'm better than that.
Hmm?
I am going to quit the band.
I think we'd like that.
Uh-oh.
- Hey, how's the ear pain?
- It's better with the drugs,
but it still really hurts.
We are going to take some fluid
samples from your ear and your lung.
Can you get up? Lean
forward. Lean on this.
Okay, this is Lidocaine.
It'll numb you up.
Okay.
This is weird.
What's the matter?
The pain in my ear is gone.
Gone? Completely?
Yeah. When you
stuck me in the back.
What does that mean?
Okay. I'm just
cutting that for you.
Is she going to
eat anything else,
or just the cheese and crackers?
She's going through a
picky phase, it won't kill her.
You're her mother.
All I know is, when you and
your sister were growing up
you ate what we ate, NO excuses.
Would you pass the salt?
She had eggs
this morning and lots of fruit.
Ah! That explains it.
Explains what?
She was a little vilder chaiah
at the park this afternoon.
She wouldn't listen
to anything I said.
Must have been all the sugar.
Actually, the whole
sugar-makes-kids-hyperactive
thing is a myth.
It's a study.
I'm sure it's very interesting.
I didn't read any studies,
I just raised children.
It's not your fault.
How are you supposed to keep
up with what she eats all day?
You're never home.
I'm sorry, I have to get this.
Tell me you need me.
Jack doesn't have cancer.
God, that's awful.
I'll be right in.
Masters stuck him in the back
with Lidocaine and his ear pain went away.
We don't need you here,
we just need to figure out why this
guy's body thinks his ear is on his back.
'Cause his ear used
to be something else.
When you're a fetus, your
cells are close together,
when you grow, they
spread out and specialize.
Sometimes the body screws up
and they keep the old area codes,
still report to
the same pain centers.
Referred pain.
Looks and brains.
When you stuck him in the back,
you cut off communication with
the pain centers in his spinal cord.
So we just need to figure out where
the message is actually coming from.
What about his thyroid?
Hyperthyroidism would
explain all his symptoms.
Or it could be his liver.
Good.
We'll take a look at both.
For the record,
referred pain does not
rule out infection.
If it's spreading...
Were you like this when you
were working for your math degree?
If Euclid had been
a guest lecturer,
would you have been the kid
sitting in the front row going,
"Actually, you haven't proven
the Pythagorean theorem."
Hello?
All right.
Mom?
Thank you, sweetie.
So say you two got married,
would you convert to Judaism?
We haven't gotten that far, Mom.
That's actually a really
interesting question.
I'm an atheist.
Honey, half the
Jews I know are atheists.
It's about community.
House isn't that
big on community.
And why do you call him House?
The man's name is Greg. It
makes it seem like you're not serious.
I'm just trying to help
you think about the future.
You're a certain age now.
The parade of boyfriends
can't be as amusing as it was.
You need to settle down,
like your sister.
Settling down isn't all
it's cracked up to be.
Next week is Sam's birthday and I
was gonna take her to the Poconos.
That's very sad.
Perhaps not the best choice
of topic for a festive occasion.
I just don't want Rachel
growing up thinking you're a slut.
Okay. I got this.
First of all, Mom...
Oh, my God.
Did you sedate my mother?
It kicked in just in time.
She'll wake up in a couple
of hours, be good as new.
Think of it as my
birthday gift to you.
You told me to
keep my mouth shut.
This was the only
way I had a chance.
Leaving aside the
fact that House Is a sociopath,
I have to admit that
I'm honestly relieved.
Your mom is quite a handful.
What? I feel...
You've got to be
kidding me. You drug...
Sorry. I honestly
thought you'd be worse.
That was my gift to myself.
I take it Jack's
thyroid levels are normal.
Foreman is doing
a liver biopsy now.
Good.
What's up with you?
Nothing. I'm peachy.
It's hard when you feel
like you've been replaced.
We got a new puppy once,
and our old cocker spaniel
just moped for weeks.
Have you even had sex?
We're not talking about me,
we're talking about you.
No, you're talking about
puppies, and I'm not listening.
She wants to do it all the time,
but it has nothing
to do with me.
I'm just a piece of meat.
Well, she likes someone else,
and you've slept
with other people.
Uh...
Why are you still together?
I love her.
We've been together
for 22 years.
I've never loved anybody else.
I don't know how
to not be with her.
So you're never
gonna cheat again.
I don't know.
That seems kind of
selfish, doesn't it?
Foreman found diffuse
inflammation in Jack's liver.
Looks like autoimmune hepatitis.
He's starting him on steroids.
Isn't this nice?
What's this note?
Does that sound like an A?
Remember if I put
my finger like this
without this
do-hickey on it, it's an F.
Hmm?
Hmm.
Can we read a book instead?
Yes, we...
Jack? Jack!
Help him!
Come on. Come on.
Okay. Okay.
He seized three
times last night.
We got him stabilized,
but barely.
If there was nothing wrong with
his brain before, there sure is now.
Any particular reason we
need to be looking at the patient?
Yes.
Cuddy's mom is in my
office. And she looks mad.
What did you do?
Our patient also developed
a raging fever overnight.
That means Masters was right
all along. This is an infection.
Should we give you
a minute to gloat?
We still don't know
what kind of infection.
It could be bacterial, viral,
fungal. Until the cultures...
You are the worst gloater ever.
Her starting those
cultures when she did
means we're 24 hours
closer to the answer.
"We're sorry
your husband croaked,
"but at least we were 24
hours closer to the answer."
Let's narrow it down, shall we?
Four days ago the guy was
face-down in the subway.
God only knows
what's in that sludge.
Toxic fumes make him pass
out. Rat pee does the rest.
If it's leptospirosis, it's the
fastest-moving case in history.
Leptospirosis can
turn into meningitis.
I can't confirm any of this yet.
We don't have time
to choose wrong.
It fits,
and since it's the only idea
on the table, I say it's a winner.
Start him on doxycycline.
No, wait.
I'll do it.
You guys have to go back to the
office, tell me when bubbie's gone.
You a doctor?
Sure.
You're on new meds.
Go back to sleep.
Am I gonna die?
I hope not.
'Cause then I'd have
to go back to my office.
Of course, if you do kick it,
then you get to be famous for
another two, maybe three weeks.
They're saying I'm a hero.
Yeah, but, you know,
in a few days
a panda bear will give birth
to triplets and we'll all move on.
Oh, I'm sorry. You actually
believe that you are a hero.
You should get yourself
some tights and a cape
and you can run around Gotham
pulling babies out of burning buildings.
Maybe you'll keep getting lucky.
You're still the same
guy you were last week.
Hey, how long are
you gonna sit there?
Could be hours.
Hiding behind a sick guy,
that's heroic.
Look, I can explain.
Sometimes I mix
up my medication...
I don't need you
to explain anything.
I think we both know
that I owe you an apology.
Say what?
I don't even remember
going to bed last night.
I must have had
too much to drink.
I do know I can be difficult.
You were a little bitchy.
In the clinic, you were
a complete schmendrick.
But once you knew I was Lisa's
mother, you held your tongue.
That's because you love her.
I still think you're a pain in
the ass with a God complex,
and I'll kill you
if you hurt her.
But I'm glad she has you.
We don't have to hug now, do we?
What do you think?
I've got a train to catch.
I thought you were
staying till Sunday.
I'm coming down with a cold.
Every time I stay
with Lisa or her sister,
one of those rugrats
gets me sick.
Children are awful.
Did she have a rash recently?
No. What's going on?
Feverish, itchy?
No.
What's she doing here, anyway?
It's the middle of the morning.
Shouldn't she be in school?
I'm keeping her
out for a few days.
There's been
a little outbreak of-...
Chicken pox.
Sorry, but if I'd let
you finish that sentence,
that would have been
much less impressive.
Chicken pox is no
big deal for kids,
but it's a terrible, horrible, no
good, very bad deal for grownups.
You think Jack has chicken pox?
But he doesn't have blisters, he's
not itchy. And Daisy never got it.
I know. Again, that's why it's
so impressive that I figured it out.
5% of cases present
without blisters.
The kid was just a carrier.
I'm gonna start you on
anti-varicella gamma globulin,
which will save your life.
But it won't make me a hero.
How are you feeling?
Hey.
Like I'm not gonna die.
I can't wait to take you home.
The guys called.
All this press has got
us a couple new gigs.
Just a few more dates.
Three weeks tops.
But you said... I know. I know.
Three weeks isn't so bad.
It's not three weeks.
This is what he's always
done. Just one more tour.
I'm sorry.
The pathetic thing is, I let myself
believe that he could change,
he could be this other guy.
There's nothing worse
than loving someone
who's never gonna
stop disappointing you.
Culture confirmed Jack
does have chicken pox.
It just took six hours longer.
Autopsy works, too.
FYI, it turns out
your hero is a loser.
He's going back on the road.
He still risked his
life for that woman.
That was impulse.
It was easy.
Dealing with family is hard.
Wait, that's another
thing I got right.
How many does that make?
And how many for you?
I'm also kicking
your ass at gloating.
Hi.
I think we should get a divorce.
You have feelings for him,
and I can't handle that.
But it's my fault you
needed someone else.
I keep hurting you.
We love each other.
I know.
But are you happy?
No.
Then what are we doing?
You know, you turned out
remarkably close to normal,
considering the genes in play.
Thanks.
Here. In case your
mom comes back.
Happy birthday.
You are a sweet, sweet man.
You coming over?
Yes.
Oh, no, I can't.
Wilson?
It's bowling night.
He'd never
forgive me if I don't.
No, screw it, I'm coming.
No, no, no.
I am not gonna be
responsible for that.
You drugged the man,
you go bowling with him.
But my chances for sex are
considerably lower with Wilson.
Fine.
Hey. You ready?
Here's the thing...
Well, it's about me, too,
and I have my boundaries, Dina.
And they're clearly being crossed
by you and your entire family,
making hate pages... WOMAN 2:
That's not true. That has nothing to do...
We all need improvements, Dina,
and I've formed my opinion
on you.
- No, don't shush me, Dina.
- No, I will shush you
because you're not
letting me finish.