One small step for man.
One giant waste
of your monthly allowance.
Safety's disengaged.
We are go for launch in
five, four, three, two, one.
That was freaking awesome!
Whoa.
Aw, jeez, come on.
My father's gonna kill me.
Can I film that, too?
Whoa.
What?
Oh, man.
Is that guy dead?
I think so.
Get the rest of the flames out!
You gonna be okay, mister?
It smells like...
Like liquorice?
Think House is coming in today?
Maybe if we start
offering spa treatments.
He already jumped
off of a hotel balcony.
Who knows what he'll do next?
Ride some kind of
prostitute chariot to work?
First person to offer me an
interesting case gets to ride her,
single or double team.
My scooter.
Which now said out loud
sounds even more inappropriate.
Seriously? You're
bringing them to work now?
23-year-old homeless man brought
into the ER with
burn injuries and...
Let me guess.
The diagnosis was fire?
He said his burning flesh
smelt like liquorice
and the ER antiseptics
like blueberry muffins.
Cool.
Dysosmia could be anything
from an environmental factor
to an early sign of a
degenerative brain disease.
Smells like a winner.
Okay, you and Chase go check
out the park where they found him.
You two, load him up with
prednisone, give him an odor ID test.
If he's still mistaking
his body odors for candy,
problem's definitely
in his brain.
Also find out what else
he's lying about,
since I'm assuming Ferris
Bueller is not his real name.
Why?
Seriously, who is that?
They say he's a righteous dude.
And before I forget, I
want you to meet Dominika.
She's about to become a
permanent member of Team House.
Nice to be meetings you all.
Doing what exactly?
Me.
We're getting married on Friday.
Mount up.
I don't think that
two people are supposed...
Living on the edge, baby doll.
How's the arm?
Hmm?
It hurts.
Do I have to check out now?
Not until we figure out why
your sense of smell is off.
When was the first
time you noticed it?
Maybe a couple months ago.
We also need you
to tell us your real name
SO we can review
your medical records.
I didn't ask to come here.
Okay, I'm not paying
for any of this.
Don't worry, I don't think the collection
agency has an office in the park.
I don't have a medical history.
I've always been healthy.
What about those scars
and burn marks?
Lean forward.
My Dad.
We didn't exactly get
along when I was a kid.
How many times
were you hospitalized?
Never.
He was good at it.
Made sure he never did anything
that couldn't be covered
up by a sweatshirt.
I'm sorry.
No, don't be.
I'm not.
The past is the past, that's
why I don't like talking about it.
You can't ride
that thing in here.
Speaking of things,
I'm having one on Friday.
If you want to drop by,
we'd love to have you.
No pressure.
You're still standing on it.
So I am. Perhaps
you're not familiar
with the New Jersey
handicap ordinances.
Or perhaps I am.
They apply to wheelchairs and
powered scooters only. Not toys.
Have you any idea
how much this toy costs?
I don't care.
For some reason, my leg's
been hurting a lot this week.
For some reason,
I still don't care.
Fine. I'll return it.
Do I have to
walk it out of here?
Stop.
I'll make an exception,
for your leg.
But next time,
check with me first.
Congratulations
on your engagement.
I hear a strange voice.
A very soft-looking man.
Must be the Wilson.
I know we said no secrets,
but I think I need to take
this alone, honey bunny.
Okay.
Nice to be meeting you.
You're trying to
screw with Cuddy.
Yeah, it's the classic
"you dumped me
"so I'm gonna get
married a week later" ruse.
'Cause not only
is she that stupid,
but apparently I'm that stupid.
Then what? You're
openly mocking marriage?
Trying to prove
it means nothing?
It doesn't,
but you proved that
yourself years ago.
I'd love to keep guessing, but
I've got people with tumors waiting.
Why do you want us to think
that you're getting married?
Only one theory left.
I am.
Dominika needs a green card.
So you're just doing some
random stranger a favor? It's illegal.
People go to jail for
that, pay huge fines.
Have you seen me
practice medicine?
You know how much it
costs to have a live-in maid,
personal assistant, cook,
massage therapist, whore?
I do.
She's willing to work
four days a week for free.
It's gonna save me
about $33,000,
and all I have to do is say
two stupid words, "I do."
And if she doesn't
see it this way?
Ironclad pre-nup.
We go our separate ways.
Your stunned look,
I take it, is your way
of saying,
"Brilliant idea, House."
Wow.
You look different.
The prednisone has
had time to work,
so we need to give you
the odor ID test now.
Sure.
We need you to tell us
what you smell.
Oh.
Something spoiled,
maybe rotting meat?
It's baby powder.
I kind of like that one.
Peppermint?
It's extremely bad body odor.
You got to admit, that one's
kind of a good deal for me.
My backpack. Oh.
Where'd you find it?
In the park, right next
to a big pile of questions.
What kind of
drugs you shooting up?
Vitamin supplements. I've been
trying to boost my immune system.
All right, test me if
you don't believe me.
Ferris tell you
his real name yet?
Peter Johnson.
Danny Jennings.
I bought those books used.
All from the same guy?
I'm sorry, but I think I
should check out now and...
What's wrong?
Oh, my stomach...
Gastrointestinal bleeding.
Is anyone else
disturbed by this?
What?
She offered.
Danny may have lied
about his name,
but he was telling the
truth about the vials.
Tests confirm they were
vitamin A and B-12.
He also enjoys vitamin H.
Kid's a junkie.
Tox screens were
negative for drug use.
His hair wasn't.
I had it tested.
Because unlike Santa
and the Easter bunny,
homeless, non-mentally
ill 20-somethings
without drug problems
don't exist.
He was a heavy user
sometime in the last five months.
Wow, that
was incredible. Thank you.
No, thank you. I like men
with the big, strong, sexy feet.
He really puts
the Mani in the pedi.
If he has a
history of snorting heroin,
he could've caused
the dysosmia himself.
But we still need to explain
the bleeding in his GI tract.
Vitamin injections
could have caused that.
Hypervitaminosis A syndrome.
So his symptoms
aren't connected?
House, you buying this?
Not usually.
But this guy has been
sleeping on a bed of dog poop.
I wouldn't be surprised if
he's got six different symptoms
for six different reasons.
The bleed could be caused
by a GI obstruction.
Vitamin OD makes
sense and it's easier to treat.
Give him tocopherol and zinc
supplements for the excess vitamin A.
If we're right, he could
go homeless tomorrow.
And if we're wrong, his intestines
could get further distressed
while we ignore
the GI obstruction.
See what happens
when women don't have
to serve men to
stay in the country?
They get all uppity.
This is why we
invented green cards.
Go x-ray the guy's abdomen,
if it'll make
you feel all equal.
I need a favor.
I want to add my fiancee's name
to my health insurance
a few days early.
She wants to get a tooth
capped before the big day.
I'm not signing this.
I agree.
I think she looks
beautiful the way she is.
Oh, no. Wait. You're not
signing that for moral reasons?
You're declaring yourself
the sole arbiter of true love?
'Cause you covered
Taub's wife for years.
It's fraud.
She wanted me to bribe you
like they do back in the old country.
Tell her what I said.
This is America.
The land of the home,
and the free of the braves.
I just get teary-eyed every
time I hear her say that.
She brought you a gift.
Almond kulich.
I make with own hands.
It's delicious.
Almond kulich.
How do you say no to that?
You realize if I do sign this
and you don't get
legally married,
you'll lose your
insurance with our carrier.
Yes.
Fine.
It's your life.
I wish you both
the best with it.
Thank you.
North, Miss Teschmacher!
Your blood test was clean,
but your hair showed heroin use.
I've been clean
over three months now.
How'd you kick it?
I had to die first.
I OD'd back in November.
And they said I was clinically
dead for several minutes.
It was like God
gave me a second chance
to do things right this time.
You're saying God cured you?
No.
State rehab cured me.
But I should be dead,
but I'm not.
That has to mean something.
I mean, I must be here
for a reason, right?
Did you figure out the reason?
My goal is to become
a doctor one day.
I am smart.
I mean, I got a scholarship
for pre-med out of high school.
Chase?
Look.
We found 13 masses
spread across the wall of his colon,
ranging from 2 to 8 millimeters.
They can't be tumors.
Edges are too sharp and defined.
I thought they might
be parasites,
but we didn't see any movement
between X-ray exposures.
And no larvae or eggs were
observed in any of the stool samples.
Which is kind of surprising
for a homeless junkie
living in a park.
Ex-junkie. He claims he's
been clean for over three months.
And he's not planning
on staying homeless.
He's trying to
protect his health,
which is why he's been
taking vitamin supplements.
He wants to be a doctor.
He's just telling you
what you want to hear.
Once an addict,
always an addict.
Can you please not do
that in front of me?
Doubt it.
You're the main reason
I'm on the stuff.
We could be looking
at fungal masses
hanging off
the walls of his colon.
Start him on
amphotericin B tonight,
and in the morning, run a scope
up where the sun don't shine
and see if you can
find any truffles.
I think we should boycott
this wedding on principle.
I kind of have to go.
His fiancée did give me
a foot massage,
and he invited me to be
in his wedding party.
What about Chase?
He ask him?
Yeah, he's in it.
What the hell?
You just said you
weren't even going.
I still have feelings.
What's that?
That's definitely not a fungus.
You were
bleeding because you had
13 pieces of bone in
your digestive tract.
We think you have pica,
a craving for non-food items.
That's caused by
a chemical imbalance...
I didn't crave them.
I kind of volunteered
to eat them.
What, why?
There's this great Italian
restaurant I like to frequent.
And by restaurant I mean
their dumpster out back.
The cook is kind of
a friend of mine.
He challenges me to eat stuff.
Sometimes it's raw squid, or I
have to chew on a chicken bone.
But if I do it, then he
hooks me up with real food,
not just the garbage.
Great friend.
These fragments could have
perforated your colon and killed you.
You have to
promise us you'll stop.
I think there's something
wrong with my eyes.
What is it?
It's like I'm looking at you
from the bottom of a well.
If we add tunnel
vision to the dysosmia,
we can subtract the
bone-induced abdominal bleeding.
I thought the
dysosmia was from heroin.
He said he never snorted,
he just shot up,
so that wouldn't have
affected his sense of smell.
And we believe
the lying liar why?
House.
Are you even listening to us?
I'll start when you decide
what the symptoms are
and give me some theories.
If we combine the dysosmia
with the tunnel vision,
the symptoms fit for
western equine encephalitis.
But the patient doesn't.
No fever.
What the hell?
Negative reinforcement.
What about
Foster-Kennedy syndrome?
He could have a
meningioma, or plasmacytoma,
started by pressing on his olfactory
nerves, affects his sense of smell,
and now it's growing and
pressing on his optic nerve.
Good.
MRI his head and find it.
Your potential donation
could... Hey, hey.
Would have an immediate
impact on our community.
We could extend our...
Something wrong?
I just think maybe
it'll be a better idea
to have a tour of
the clinic first.
It's right this way.
We have several patients
that are children
and we find that it's important
to give them
the opportunity to play
to make the hospital
a less intimidating place.
My Dad used to
lock me in a closet
and it feels like
I can't breathe.
We need you to stay still.
Give him a break.
You want him squirming
around? We'll have to do it twice.
I want you to show
him a little respect.
You really think this kid
can turn his life around?
He believes God gave
him a second chance.
That kind of belief
can be powerful.
Masters doesn't surprise me,
he plays the fellow med student
who dreams of being a
doctor and reels her in.
But you? Falling for his
deep connection with God?
He has hope.
After all he's been through,
it kind of makes me
root for him.
We don't even know who he is,
except that he lies
about who he is.
The bit about his abusive
father is probably all made up.
And he faked the scars?
He's a punk, probably
got in a lot of fights.
And he sucked you in
using the dad story.
I don't think I'm feeling
very well. I think I'm...
He's vomiting.
Should I ask him to stay
still while he does that?
He has two dark spots
in the parietal cortex.
They're not tumors, maybe
some kind of injury or inborn defect.
Apparently,
he was clinically dead
for several seconds
when he OD'd.
The dark spots could be brain
damage from oxygen starvation.
Except it's not.
I've seen MRI imagery like that
in schizophrenics.
Three serving two.
But schizophrenia
doesn't explain
why his blood pressure
skyrocketed
and he threw up in the MRI.
Panic attack.
He's claustrophobic.
He was fine once we let him out.
The dysosmia and tunnel
vision could be hallucinations.
Except, as was already covered,
he was screened for
mental illness down in the ER.
In your head!
It's face.
On your face!
Close enough.
The ER docs missed it because he
didn't present with major symptoms yet.
We're seeing it in its infancy.
So we treat him, and then what?
He becomes just
another schizophrenic
homeless man
wandering the streets.
- We have to help him.
- I'd love to,
but I got four million
other crazy people
ahead of him on my to-do list.
Along with milk.
You two spent months trying
to figure out a way to date
and not have it affect
your working relationship.
Now you need to do the
same thing for not dating.
No, I don't.
This is serious.
Did you know that she's...
She's dying of guilt and
feels horrible for dumping me.
It's great.
Not the dumping part,
but the part where she'll
now let me do whatever I want.
So you're just trying
to punish her?
She feels bad and your only
goal is to take advantage?
That's not true.
I have plenty of goals.
One of them is a 60-inch
flat screen, right there.
You're a lot of things, House,
but you've never been a sadist.
You're pummeling an
opponent who isn't fighting back.
I already gave him
his second dose
of clozapine, you don't need...
I'll bet you 50 bucks his
favorite sport is hockey.
How could you
possibly know that?
Just a hunch.
How you feeling?
My arm kind of hurts.
I'll talk to the nurse
about upping your pain meds.
Hockey, eh?
Oh.
My nephew bought it for me.
Knows I'm a huge fan.
I hate hockey.
If this IS schizophrenia,
you're gonna need regular care.
I've found some shelters
that have
full-time medical staff
and also offer college...
My arm really hurts.
Let's have a look.
It feels like it's on fire.
We need to take a
look under the bandages.
No, no, no, not that one.
This one.
Ahoy there, me hearties,
permission to come aboard.
Danny said his left arm felt
like it was on fire last night.
We assumed it was a
schizophrenic delusion, but...
It's not.
He's on clozapine.
He'd be getting better,
not worse.
Sounds like
regional pain syndrome.
Has to be a genetic disorder.
Would you slow down?
You're gonna get us arrested.
I wouldn't worry about it.
We'll probably die first.
Don't make me take my shoe off!
We need to run his DNA. He could
have early onset of Parkinson's.
Or cortical-based
ganglionic degeneration,
or Huntington's or any one of
a dozen other genetic diseases.
If you let us out,
we can start testing.
If you're gonna test for
them all, it'll take weeks.
I'm not canceling my
honeymoon to treat this kid.
It's a fake marriage,
but a real honeymoon?
Most are.
Danny could also
have died before
we get through testing
for all the possibilities.
So we cheat.
Since it's genetic,
daddy or mommy's got it, too.
They're either sick or dead.
He doesn't know
where his mother is,
and he won't tell us
where his father is.
He's a homeless ex-junkie.
You telling me that you four
geniuses can't outwit him?
Green light!
Cuddy got it for me.
I'm now drafting a request for
studying the effects of caffeine
involving an Italian
espresso machine
and a massage chair.
Make it quick.
I found Danny's father.
Well done.
Kid said he was in a
state-sponsored rehab last November.
There's only one Danny Jennings
that was in treatment
at that time,
and he listed his father's
address as his primary next of kin.
The "Well done" was
for making it quick.
Now I'm gonna have
to take that back.
He lives about 30
minutes from the hospital.
And the reason you're continuing
to talk instead of driving there?
Chase and Masters are
already on their way.
Why didn't you ask me to
be part of your wedding?
You're genuinely upset at being
mockingly snubbed by a mock wedding?
Is it because I haven't
been here as long as them?
Or is it that you
really don't like me?
Or are you just screwing...
III...
I'll come back
when she's finished.
She is.
Oh, my God, what did
you think she was doing?
She's just installing the cable.
That's not a euphemism.
Oh, I feel sorry
for the little one.
Isn't there something we can do?
Can I help you?
We need to talk to you
about your son Danny.
Danny? Who are you?
We're his doctors.
We need to know if you
or perhaps his mother
have any family history
of genetic disease.
Why, what difference
would it make?
You may not care
about your son, but...
Is that what Danny told
you when he was in rehab?
We didn't love him?
Not why we came here.
We just want to know
if there's any
diagnosed genetic disease
in your family.
We're trying to
make your son better.
Better?
He died of a drug overdose.
We buried him three months ago.
Who are you?
What are you doing?
Test.
Who are you?
The important question is
who are you?
Danny Jennings is dead,
which means that Danny
Jennings has no pulse,
which you, on the other hand,
do.
Ergo, you are
not Danny Jennings.
Or I did the test wrong.
So why don't you cut the crap
and tell me your real name?
No.
Hiding your identity. Either
you're a criminal or a superhero.
I'm not a criminal.
Awesome. What
color is my underwear?
I'm not telling you my name.
No problem. I just
need your father's name.
Forget it.
Care to tell me why?
He's looking for me.
He supposedly
cleaned up and got sober.
And now he...
He wants to be part
of my life again,
and I can't let that happen.
You're a big boy now. You
still think he can hurt you?
You don't get it.
If I ever see my Dad again,
I'll Kill him.
What's happening to me?
Well, luckily for you, we don't
need daddy to figure that one out.
Did you find out his real name?
Cerebellar Ataxia.
That's a weird name.
Guy whiffed twice trying to
pick up a cup right in front of him.
That plus everything else...
means that we have whittled
our list of genetic diseases
all the way down to one,
early-onset Parkinson's.
After everything he's been
through, now we have to tell him,
"Hey, you have
an incurable disease
"that gets
progressively worse."
You could lie,
I'm fine with that.
But you'll probably
both feel better
if you give him Levodopa
and confirm with DNA tests.
He's gone too far.
He's taking up six handicapped
spaces with a monster truck.
It's only four, and he's gonna
get rid of it after the wedding.
And the chapel?
He's turned the chapel
into his own
personal catering hall.
Who cares? Other than a
janitor sleeping off a bender,
he's the first person
to use it in two weeks.
Appeasement is never the answer
in the face of naked aggression.
It won't be long
before his tanks
are rolling down
your Champs-Élysées.
I know what House is doing.
You, on the other hand, why do
you care? He isn't hurting anyone.
You're the first boss he's
ever had who could handle him.
Before you, he was either fired
or buried under a mountain
of malpractice suits.
He needs someone to say no.
He needs someone he'll
listen to when they say no.
If you really care about House,
you'll stop
feeling sorry for him,
and get out there and start
kicking him where he needs kicking.
I changed my mind.
You want the fish
instead of the chicken?
This room is for
patients' families,
not for doctors trying to
defraud the government.
Oh. So you've decided
to take a moral stand?
Yes.
The chapel still has
sanctity for some people.
You're right. I think
I saw Blue the janitor
passed out in one of
the pews last week.
It's Lou, and I would
have thrown him out, too.
Where are we gonna go?
We got caterers staging
everything downstairs as we speak.
We got floral arrangements,
place settings, other weddingy stuff.
It's not my problem.
I sent out the invitations.
People are coming here.
That's also not my problem.
And I want the TV back.
You should just let me die.
The world's
better off without me.
It's normal.
People feel depressed
when they get bad news
because it's bad news,
obviously.
I didn't OD by accident.
I was trying to kill myself.
Why?
Because I've done things.
Horrible things.
I've hurt people.
But when I didn't die,
I thought...
I thought God forgave me.
But he just wanted me to suffer,
and I deserve it.
No.
You don't deserve it.
I had a girlfriend in college
and I almost killed her.
I just snapped
and I started hitting her.
And if her roommate
hadn't come home...
I'm evil.
I'm just like my dad.
We're both monsters
that deserve to die.
I can't... I can't...
I feel dizzy.
I need a crash cart in here!
His heart is
dilated and failing.
And at the rate it's happening,
he'll need a new one soon,
and there's no way we'll
get him on the transplant list.
What are we missing?
Everything. We know
nothing about this kid.
Except that he's gotten
worse since we admitted him.
Why?
Most of our patients tend to
do that, unless we cure them.
Yeah, but why so fast?
He had dysosmia for
a couple of months,
never even came here
to get it treated.
He was just
a random burn victim.
We get him,
boom, he's got tunnel vision,
peripheral polyneuropathy,
Cerebellar Ataxia
and now cardiomyopathy.
What's different here than say,
living in a filthy state park?
You think cleanliness
is making him sick?
An allergic reaction?
We treated him with Vicodin,
clozapine and one IV bag of Levodopa.
His condition started
deteriorating before that.
Stop that man!
I need the meal card
for the patient in 243.
He's eating healthy
because he can.
Most of the meals
in here are vegetarian.
Adult Refsum disease.
It fits all the symptoms.
His body can't process the
phytanic acid in chlorophyll.
It's his healthy diet of green
vegetables that's killing him.
So if we change his diet...
We can save his life.
Run him through
a plasmapheresis treatment
to remove the excess
phytanic acid from his blood.
Confirm with gene testing.
Okay, I got to go get married.
They say true love
doesn't exist anymore.
Maybe it never did.
So without further ado...
Do you, Dominika
Patrova, take this man
to be your
lawfully-wedded husband?
I do.
And do you, Gregory
House, take this woman
to be your lawfully-wedded wife?
Yep.
Then by the power vested in me
by the state of New
Jersey just for today,
I now pronounce you man
and wife. You may kiss the bride.
Those of you with
cameras, please feel free
to provide legal documentation.
It's okay, I'm just
angry at myself.
Promised I wouldn't let this
get to me, and it got to me.
Just say the word, and we will
climb out that window right now.
I wouldn't give
House the satisfaction.
You see? Things are
getting back to normal.
Yeah.
Normal.
You feeling better?
So, all I have to do is eat the
right kinds of food and I'll be okay?
Basically, yeah.
It's pretty limiting and it
is for the rest of your life,
but if you follow the diet
and get checked up regularly,
you should be fine.
Thank you.
Mmm-hmm.
For not giving up on me.
You're not a bad person.
You made mistakes,
but we all do.
Maybe when you get out of here,
you can go talk to
someone, a professional.
Yeah. Yeah, some of those places
you suggested have people on staff.
You know, I think God really
does have a plan for me.
And all this?
It was just his way
of testing my resolve.
I wouldn't have
passed it without you.
See you tomorrow, Danny.
That's not my real name.
Doesn't matter.
I know this is
not real marriage,
but I really like you.
I like you, too.
I can't.
Why not?
I never sleep
with married women.
I'm going to bed.
You can take the couch.
What's going on?
Danny disappeared
without checking out.
So you called the FBI?
We didn't call
them, they just showed up.
Danny's DNA, when
we sent it to the lab for testing,
it set off alarm bells
all over the country.
Alarm bells for what?
He's linked to 13 unsolved
murders in 10 different states.
He's a serial killer
who eats his victims.
And we saved him.