Touch me. Please.
Please.
How dare you?
I'm so fucking hard.
You don't get off this elevator
until you have calmed down.
Please.
- You wanna see it?
- Yes.
Yes.
Closer?
Kiss my thigh.
Touch yourself until you come.
Oh, shit. Fuck.
Get it together, Molly.
Is the chemo port
at least fucking covered?
I touched your thigh with my face.
Is that okay?
Yeah, that's okay.
I mean, these past few months
have been weird, you know?
I mean, it's been great.
Um, but I've never done anything
like this before and, you know, I love it...
but I feel bad
that I'm not making you come.
Are you getting anything out of it?
Yeah.
The way you look at me
when I give you exactly what you want.
You look at me like you want me so much.
Uh, can I just say that
your eyes are mesmerizing?
And I know that sucks to say out loud.
I'm sorry, but they are.
Um, are you really
not gonna eat these cookies?
Because, if you don't,
I will eat all of them.
And, look, I know, you know,
that you do this with other people.
Um...
A couple days ago,
I heard a guy barking like a dog.
Oh, yeah. I just started seeing him.
He likes to be a human dog.
Well, he's very good at it.
Very loud and realistic.
So...
All right. I'm gonna do something
that neither of us want, um,
which is talk about my feelings.
I, um...
I was with somebody for years. And...
I'm just gonna dive in.
Um, she cheated on me.
Um, and then we decided
to open up the relationship.
But that just gave us an excuse
to be horrible to each other.
Plus, this guy named Pierre
entered the picture,
and we had very bad threesomes with him.
And I wound up with, um, sores on my taint
from an STD
that doctors thought was extinct.
She gave you a... a prehistoric STD?
Yeah. I mean, she was a wonderful woman.
And I wish her well.
You know, I just... I've been very lonely.
I don't mean alone,
but I've been very lonely in my life,
and, um, doing this with you
has made me feel...
not lonely.
And, look, I know I don't know you at all,
and I have a lot of questions.
I mean, the first time that you kicked me,
I had to call an ambulance,
and then you were gone
for a very long time.
And when you came back,
you were walking with a cane.
I mean, did kicking me in
my rock-hard dick permanently cripple you?
I wanna believe that's true, but...
Are you okay?
Just tell him.
I don't wanna talk about it.
Sorry. Sorry, sorry. I'm sorry.
I'm sorry. I have to take her to chemo.
I have to get the tooth removed.
What?
She's...
Just give me a second.
It's just...
It's like a magic trick.
Oh, my God. Okay.
I have to get a tooth removed.
So I can't take Molly to her next chemo.
Okay, we don't recommend
that you go alone.
Because of the exhaustion
and the chemo brain.
You know, you forget how to speak English.
Is there anyone else that can take you?
You gotta do it.
Do it for Nikki. Do it for Nikki's mouth.
Uh, my mom.
Great. Is she able to come?
Yeah. I mean, I think so.
Oh, Jesus.
I-I just have to tell her
my cancer is back.
She didn't even tell her
that she has cancer again.
It's all good. I have some literature
- on how to tell loved ones.
- Great.
And it's okay to say directly
what you need from her.
Like, I like to hold some space
for silence.
- Hold some space for silence? Very cool.
-  Yeah.
You're gonna do that?
Think that's gonna work?
Wait, what's your relationship like?
It's had its ups and downs.
The biggest down was that her boyfriend
made me give him a blow job
when I was seven, so...
Big down.
Okay.
- Wait, this is funny.
-  Uh...
His name was Mark Wallace,
and when I went back
to school in the fall,
my second grade teacher's name
was Wallace Mark.
I shit you not.
Sorry. I just gotta laugh.
You were seven years old?
Yeah. I mean, I told my mom.
And she just fell apart,
and she did go to rehab a few times.
I had to keep convincing her
that it wasn't her fault.
I got tired of doing it after 30 years, so
now sometimes we don't talk for a while.
- I'm just gonna cancel my appointment.
- Wait. No, no. It's fine.
Okay, I'm in a good place,
and she lives in Vermont
with a goat farmer,
so, you know, like,
let's just rip that Band-Aid.
Now?
Wait, wait. You're doing it right now?
Mom?
Hang on,
I'm in the coop collecting eggs,
and I gotta move the owl.
I've got a-a real hawk problem. I...
Mom, my cancer is back.
What?
It's stage four.
It's, uh...
It's in my bones. It's incurable, so...
I'm dying.
I'll come there right now.
Where are you right now? I'm coming.
Okay, guys, just shut up!
Gonzo, Jill, Toto!
Senator Peanut, stop it.
I'm holding space for silence.
I'm trying to talk to my daughter.
I've got a good boy treat.
Stay!
Oh! Down!
Stay.
Go get it!
I've never had someone
check me for ticks before.
How did you think of that?
Mmm. It just came to me in the moment.
You're incredible.
- I felt so taken care of.
- Aw.
Is there anything else
you wanna try next time?
No judgment.
Uh, actually, there is something
I've always wanted to do.
But I've never said it out loud before.
Um...
Hey.
I wasted so much time
worrying if I was normal
or if I was turned on by normal things.
There's nothing wrong with you.
Okay. I, um...
All right, here.
Uh...
I wanna be peed on.
Yeah, just let me think about it.
Hi, Gail.
- Mom, is that a dog in your car?
- I'm fostering him.
Can he stay in your apartment
while we go to the hospital?
- No. Molly's immunocompromised.
- No, I mean... Yeah. It's okay. It's fine.
Can you get his bed, his bag and...
Oh, his leg.
- Is this the bag with everything?
- Yeah.
Um, her keys are in here
in case she can't open the lock.
Sometimes she loses feeling
in her fingers.
- Yeah, yeah. I'm her mother.
- Okay.
- Here, take the dog.
- Oh, um...
- Don't forget to walk him.
- She brought a dog.
- I'll have my phone on me the whole time.
I have four foster dogs now.
The dogs, yeah.
We're back to the dogs.
Toto. Senator Peanut.
She wouldn't let me get a pet
when I was a kid.
Gonzo.
We did cat-sit for her drug dealer.
- Sweet little Jill.
- I liked that cat.
Oh, they need so much help.
One of 'em doesn't have a rectum.
That can get complicated.
What are you watching?
It's called Drunk Girl Falls off of Llama.
How are you feeling?
Yeah, great.
Yeah.
No, I-I feel good
when I'm heading into chemo.
It's just the two days after chemo
that I feel like I wanna die,
but that's convenient,
'cause that's what's happening.
I don't care what they say.
You're gonna beat this.
Should you be eating that?
You once sent me to school
with just a hot dog bun for lunch.
I read a great article about
raw cloves of garlic and cancer.
Raw garlic cures stage four cancer?
Why did you wait ten months to tell me?
I haven't told anyone.
Mentally, are you okay?
I called Steve.
What?
I wanted to know what happened
and if you were okay.
I told you I was okay.
I don't know why you had
to hear that from Steve.
He said you were on
some kind of a sex quest.
A sex quest?
Ta-da.
You were so cute.
You're still cute.
Oh, man.
Oh, look at you and Dad.
You guys look so in love.
I was.
That's just the way his face looked
when he knew he had cocaine in his pocket.
Oh, I love this one.
Oh, my God.
Uh...
That was...
He... He took that. That was the...
After the recital.
No, he didn't. I don't remember that.
I would never have
put this in here if I'd thought...
Okay, well...
Okay, fine, let's just take it out.
Is that why you're doing
what you're doing?
Having sex with strangers,
because of what happened?
Oh, this is my fault.
- I'm just trying to figure out who I am.
- This is all my fault.
Are you ever gonna forgive me?
Am I interrupting?
Hi.
-  Sheila. You came.
- Hi. Hi.
- Sorry, what is...
-  Oh.
-  Hi.
- Um...
What are you... Why? What?
I started a meal train
with your cousins who live in the city.
You mean you told...
You told... You told them?
Of course. I told the whole family
so you didn't have to worry about it.
- Do you like chilaquiles?
- No, no, no.
I'm sorry. I can't have that.
The... The pepper hurts my mouth.
- Oh. Okay.
- I don't want this. Like, whatever this...
Chemo brain. What is this called,
this thing you organized?
Toot-toot. Meal train's here.
I brought bagels. Hi, Gail.
Hi, Steve.
Hi. Hey, Molly.
All right. Try and get some rest.
Here, let me take off your shoes,
okay, baby?
Mmm.
You're so nice.
What's wrong with you?
Why are you still with me?
Oh, you're so hot!
- He is a sexy person.
- Baby, baby, let's go to bed, okay?
- Yeah. Whee!
- One, two, three. There you go.
- Nice. Okay. Lie back.
- Yeah. The wind in my sails.
- You have to sit up, he said, okay?
- Mmm.
Little bit.
- Oh, this is so nice.
- There it is. The queen.
- Where are... Yeah.
- Hey.
Is that my phone? Is it Molly?
Can you make sure if it's Molly?
I can do it. Give it to me.
Uh, no, it's not Molly.
Let's just get some sleep, okay?
Thank you. Thank you.
You have a beautiful spirit.
-  Get in there.
-  All right.
It's all good. Thank you.
It's just I didn't eat lunch.
Wow. This is a trip being back here, huh?
We spent a lot of time
in this room together.
-  We sure did.
- The first time around.
She was so strong. So brave.
She fought so hard.
Uh, you're gonna eat your scallion
cream cheese. I got a whole tub of it.
- Just for you.
-  Oh, my goodness. Thank you.
- You were so good to her. To all of us.
-  Aw.
- Oh. Thanks.
- You really were.
Yeah. Dig around in there.
There's some other little treats in there.
- When did you guys actually break up?
- Technically, we're still married.
Because, of course,
I wanted to keep her on my insurance.
I mean, I don't wanna abandon her.
But, you know, this has been
good for me too.
- I started seeing somebody.
- Did you? Wow.
Yeah. It's casual.
But, um, she's actually here.
I wasn't sure if it would be weird
to bring her in.
-  Bring her in.
- I wanna meet her.
- Really?
-  Yeah.
Molly, do you wanna meet
the woman that I'm seeing?
What? Molly?
'Cause I really...
Stop. I really want her to meet you.
It's important to me.
You're an inspiration.
Steve said you're beautiful,
but you're, like, radiant.
Maybe it's the radiation.
I don't know what's going on here,
but you're only allowed
two to three visitors.
So, who's this?
Hi, Pet.
Um...
I'm also seeing someone.
Okay.
Oh, whoa. Whoa, whoa, whoa.
-  Mmm.
-  Oh, God. Oh.
Oh, oh. Oh.
There's my good boy.
Okay. I actually need to get back to Rudy.
I'm pretty sure he's done playing tennis.
Ooh. He probably is.
Mom, don't you wanna go say hi to Rudy?
I guess.
Just call me whenever you're done
doing whatever this is you're doing.
Okay. Yeah.
It's really good seeing you, Molly.
I think we're also gonna head...
- Hey. Get away from her. Hey!
- Don't touch me.
Down, down. Come here.
Don't let those mean people scare you.
It's okay.
Yeah, it's okay.
I think I'm ready.
You all set?
Yes, please.
Oh, God. Oh, God. Oh, my God.
Oh! Oh, God.
- Oh, yes.
- Oh.
-  Fuck.
-  Whoo!
- Oh, my God! Mom!
-  What?
Mom, I said that I would call.
Is that what you...
People like that?
Yes, people like that.
You like that?
I don't know what I like, Mom.
I'm-I'm trying things.
Well, you better clean your bathtub.
Oh. I just came to get my dog.
Thank you for tonight. It was so special.
Oh.
- And I didn't know that you had cancer...
- I'm sorry.
It's okay. It's fine.
Thank you, Pet.
Really?
Do you have any idea what's in her pee?
She just had a chemo infusion.
So you've got chemo all over you now.
Is that bad for me?
- I don't know.
- I hope you didn't get it in your mouth.
- Oh, God.
- I'll google it.
Oh, my God.
- Oh, my God.
- I'll google it.
Okay. Oh, God.
- Did you... Did you swallow?
- It's closing... My throat is closing up.
-  Okay.
My throat is closing up.
- My throat is closing up.
- Well, take that stupid collar off.
- Can you get the key? Unlock it.
- Shit. I don't know... The key.
- Where's the key?
- Over there.
Yeah, I--
- Uh... Key. Key.  Okay. I got it.
-  It's itchy.
- Can you do it?
- I don't have thumbs in my suit.
Okay. I can't feel my fingertips
after chemo.
- Oh, God.
- Mom?
- Can you help?
- I'm not touching him!
- I can't breathe. I can't breathe.
- Okay.
Don't drink my daughter's pee
if you can't handle it, you freak.
Yeah.
Thank you.
For what?
Just letting me
take care of you today.
Um...
Did you give me back my phone?
I can't find it.
I just...
- I don't see it.
- Uh...
No. I have it.
- Oh.
- Yeah.
- Thanks, babe.
Why is it off?
I just wanted you
to have one day off, Nikki.
What?
Oh, my God. Noah, fuck you.
I don't get a day off.
- I don't want a day off.
- You're not sleeping.
You're on unemployment.
You don't see your friends.
- You never see me.
- Fuck you. Fuck you.
Oh, my God. Don't stand there
and act like you're a good guy.
Did you think what would happen
if she had had an emergency?
Her mom was there.
I am her family. She is my family.
Not you.
Do you wanna know the truth?
All I want to do is be with Molly.
I don't really care if I see you.
You're tired. And you're high.
No, I'm not. This is... I mean it.
The world without Molly in it
doesn't make sense. It's stupid.
You're telling me about your day,
and it's so stupid.
I'm watching my best friend die,
and you're telling me about how long
you had to wait for the fucking train?
I don't like being around you anymore.
Well, I don't like
being around you anymore either.
And that sucks 'cause you're
my favorite person in the whole world.
It's been really hard on us.
It's just been really hard, Nikki.
Am I drooling? Oh, God.
Am I drooling or am I crying?
What's happening on my face?
You're droo... I-It's both.
-  Hey.
- Hey. How's it going?
- All right.
-  Help!
- Help me! Please! Help!
-  Question.
Do you have, like, really big scissors?
Can someone help me?
Come on, please!
Who is that?
Oh, no one.
It's just my neighbor.
He's gonna cut off the collar, then go.
- I got it.
- Oh, thank God.
- Okay, I gotta go to urgent care.
- No. I really don't think you do.
Uh, thank you so much.
I-I think we're good now.
- You should stay. Have a cup of coffee.
- Mom.
Hey, maybe we can get together next week
- if I don't die. I don't know.
- Why would he die?
Because Molly peed on him
right after she had chemo.
Chemo?
Like, chemo for cancer?
Yeah.
Stage four.
Out. Out.
How dare you?
What?
How dare you tell him
anything about me?
What is the big deal about telling people?
Why does everything have to be a secret?
I'm helping you.
No, it's not helping me. It makes me feel...
like I'm...
Fuck. I forgot the word
I was trying to say.
Fucking chemo brain.
What word is this?
Weird.
Oh, rag doll.
Little scary rag doll girl?
Broken. It makes me feel like I'm broken.
Hey, and I don't...
I don't want you here, okay?
Why are you doing this to me?
I'm not doing anything to you.
I am trying to...
Fuck my brain.
Glue.
Weave a basket?
Heal. I'm trying to heal.
I want you to heal.
That's why I'm helping you.
No, you don't help me. I-I...
Maybe I let you think that you help me
because that's what I've always done.
But I have to be
the one to protect you.
I'm the one who has to make sure you don't
take drugs and try and kill yourself.
That was a very hard moment for me.
It was a hard moment for me.
I'm so sick of your guilt.
Like, every time you look at me,
you feel guilty.
I failed you.
I'm the one who left you alone
with that man.
While I was passed out down the hall
from whatever he put in my drink.
I'm the one who let him ruin you.
Stop it. I'm not ruined.
Okay? I don't blame you.
- You do blame me. You do.
- No. No. It's my fault too.
I saw him put something in your drink.
I saw him.
And I didn't say anything.
God.
You didn't know. You didn't know.
He smiled at me when he did it.
I liked that I had something
you didn't know about.
I liked that he chose me over you.
So it's not you, okay?
Well, it wasn't you.
Is that what you think?
Honey.
Honey, it wasn't you.
Well, maybe...
...we're not good for each other.
Maybe there's a way we could just
love each other but be apart.
Just...
Just, please.
I don't even care if you don't mean it.
Just tell me you forgive me, okay?
Forgive yourself.
Yeah.
What's his name?
Oh.
Ricky Mustache.
You have a meeting you can go to?
Yeah.
Okay.
I have stage four breast cancer.
And when I got hurt
and you had to call the ambulance,
um...
it was because the cancer that's in my hip
caused the bone to fracture.
Um,
I left that part out. I, uh...
It doesn't have to be awkward.
Okay.
Let's just call it.
I had fun.
No.
What? Uh...
What? So...
What's this gonna be?
We're gonna have some tragic love story,
and we walk through a park in the autumn,
and I get a leaf caught in my hair.
And you're like,
"Whoa, you have a leaf in your hair."
And then I just fucking die.
No.
No leaves in your hair.
Just...
keep kicking me in the dick.
Yeah, I could do that.
Hey.
I left Noah.
And my mouth hurts so bad.
Come here. Come here. Come here.
Oh.