- 'Previously on "Hannibal"...'
- Hannibal!
We are as close
as we are ever going to get
to catching this man.
I'm dismantling who I was
and moving it brick by brick.
It's the last stage of a transformation.
We could disappear now.
You've set some sort of trap
and you're goading Hannibal into it.
How can you be sure
he's not goading you?
I can't.
I have begun to question your actions
with regards to my attack.
I am no longer your therapist.
You are dangerous.
- Antony Dimmond.
- Boris Jakov.
I'd offer a hand, but...
It's a double-fisted kind of bash.
Do you know Roman well?
You were staring with the thinly-veiled
disdain of a man who does.
I was his TA at Cambridge.
He was insufferable even then.
Have you read his books?
They're terrible.
You know they're terrible,
you're just too polite to say.
Blink if you agree.
See.
Doesn't stop him squatting
over his keyboard
and depositing a fresh one
every six to eight months.
It takes me six to eight months
to write one line.
Why?
Poetry is hard.
Too hard for Roman.
Well, it's easier for him to slide into
academia and dissect the work of others
than it is to stand by his own words.
One can appreciate another's words
without dissecting them.
Though, on occasion,
dissection is the only thing that will do.
Bonsoir.
You really are the Devil.
Certainly seem to enjoy it.
You have a click in your hoof.
The Devil has been a yoke
on the neck of humanity
since we first began
to think and dream.
I for a much shorter time.
You admit the yoke.
Smells of candy apples and thyme.
You smoked me in thyme.
Smoked. Glazed.
Served on a sugar cane quill.
You will be falling off the bone.
Well, of course.
And with these rarified dishes
you so carefully prepare,
do we all taste different?
Everyone has their flavour.
Cannibalism was standard behaviour
among our ancestors.
The missing link was only missing
because we ate him.
This isn't cannibalism, Abel.
It's only cannibalism if we're equals.
This is only cannibalism if you eat me.
But you just feel this is
the natural order of things,
everybody gets ate.
Be he fat or be he lean.
With my last leg standing next to me,
I should still wrestle with the urges
to fight or flee.
It's called "terminal restlessness".
The body fills with adrenaline
and feels compelled to go-go-go.
"Go-go-go"?
I've already got up and gone.
This is posthumous.
You're not dead yet, Abel.
You still have to eat.
No, I don't.
At this point, there is absolutely
nothing I have to do.
But I shouldn't spoil the fairy tale,
should I?
You and your little gingerbread house.
Let it be a fairy tale, then.
Once upon a time...
Bellissima.
Grazie.
Dr Fell, I hope you translate
as well as you waltz.
Mrs Fell.
Our new appointee was confirmed
by the board after close questioning.
You've examined him
in medieval Italian,
and I will not deny
his language is...
admirable.
- Thank you.
- For a straniero.
Are you familiar with the personalities
of pre-Renaissance Florence?
I think not.
Dr Fell might hold in his hand,
in his non-Italian hand,
a note from Dante Alighieri himself.
Would he recognise it?
I think not.
Professor Sogliato, would you
do me the honour of a dance?
Of course.
Allegro mi sembrava Amor
tenendo meo core in mano,
e ne le braccia avea madonna involta
in un drappo dormendo.
Poi la svegliava, e d'esto core ardendo
lei paventosa umilmente pascea;
appreso gir lo ne vedea piangendo.
Dante's first sonnet.
It fascinated Cavalcanti. The eating
of the heart is a powerful image.
If he's such an expert on Dante,
let him lecture on Dante...
to the Studiolo.
Let him face them.
- Extempore.
- I'm happy to sing for my supper.
Professor Sogliato.
We are among the palaces
built 600 years ago
by the merchant princes,
the kingmakers
and the connivers
of Renaissance Florence.
There's connivers of modern Florence.
I've found a peace here
that I would preserve.
I've killed hardly anybody
during our residence.
You created a vacancy
at the Palazzo Capponi
by removing the former curator.
A simple process requiring
a few seconds' work on the old man
and a modest outlay
for two bags of cement.
You no longer have
ethical concerns, Hannibal.
You have aesthetical ones.
Ethics become aesthetics.
You seem more interested in making
appearances than maintaining them.
Would you?
If this is about my position
at the Palazzo,
once the path was cleared,
I won the job fairly.
On my merits.
Yes, even the most
contentious Florentines
can't resist the verse of Dante
ringing off frescoed walls.
One contentious Florentine can.
Have you given serious thought
to eating Professor Sogliato?
My killing Sogliato now
would not preserve the peace.
Your peace is without morality.
Morality doesn't exist. Only morale.
How you feel today.
How do you feel today?
I still believe I'm in conscious control
of my actions.
Given your history, that's a good day.
If you think you're about
to catch Hannibal,
it's because he wants you
to think that.
Don't fool yourself into thinking
he's not in control of what's happening.
May I get dressed?
You may.
What have you done, Hannibal?
I've taken off my person suit.
You let them see you.
I let them see enough.
How does it feel?
Being seen?
Well, you're in no position to ask,
Dr Du Maurier.
You ended our patient-psychiatrist
relationship.
I lacked the appropriate skills
to continue your therapy.
I never found you to be lacking.
I'm sorry I didn't provide you
with a suitable substitute for therapy.
Is Will Graham still alive?
Will Graham was not
a suitable substitute for therapy.
What was he?
Is this professional curiosity?
Almost entirely.
Do you trust me?
Not entirely.
Are you taking into consideration
my beliefs about your intentions?
My intentions?
Human motivation can be
little more than lucid greed.
Greed...
and blind optimism.
You're optimistic I won't kill you.
Due bottiglie di Bâtard-Montrachet
e tartufi bianchi, per favore.
Hello!
Bonjour!
Mr Jakov, isn't it?
We met in Paris a few months back.
Sorry, I didn't mean to startle you,
it's just here I was
and then there you were.
- I never forget a face.
- Antony Dimmond.
- Nice to be remembered.
- You're hard to forget.
What are you doing in Florence?
Are you working with Roman?
Dr Fell?
I heard he took an appointment
at the Capponi Library.
Yes, he's the new curator and
translator at the Palazzo Capponi.
Evidently, the last one eloped with
a woman or someone's money, or both.
That's the commonly-held belief.
- You just missed Roman.
- Did I?
Oh, I was hoping to take the piss.
Spare the piss for the time being.
If you're free, my wife and I would
love to have you for dinner.
Listen.
They prefer eating in company.
I've kept cochlear gardens
since I was a young man,
fattening snails on herbs
and vine leaves.
Like all of us, what they eat greatly
influences and enhances their flavour.
When I'm not busy eating myself,
you wish me to be eating oysters,
drinking sweet wines
and snacking on acorns.
All to make me tastier?
Oh, yes.
And you are making them tastier.
And I you.
Imagine what you must taste like.
Won't be long until someone's
taking a bite out of you.
You're becoming brighter, Abel.
Dying hasn't dulled you one bit.
The snails are certainly having
a lovely experience,
fattened on me
in a red-wine marinade.
They have no idea
they're going to be eaten.
We do.
How well do you know the Fells?
As well as anybody.
Which'd be not really.
Lydia a friend of yours?
Not really.
I'd be surprised to hear she had one.
We share a mutual detestation.
She disapproves of my disapproval.
What do you disapprove of?
Roman, mainly.
Lydia isn't quite bright enough
to see I'm just intimidated.
Roman does, of course.
How he loves to strike fear.
Dante wrote that fear is
almost as bitter as death.
Dante wasn't dead when he wrote it.
- Are you travelling alone, Antony?
- The only way I travel.
Oh...
Roman is speaking to the Studiolo Friday
on Dante. You should come.
Sounds appropriately hellish.
Are you avoiding meats?
I'm trying not to eat anything
with a central nervous system.
Oysters, acorns and Marsala.
That's what ancient Romans would feed
animals to improve their flavour.
My husband has
a very sophisticated palate.
He's very particular about how I taste.
Is it that kind of party?
It is not that kind of party.
No.
It really isn't.
Shame. You were both suddenly
so fascinating.
- Buonasera.
Buonasera.
You let him go.
What would you have me do, Bedelia?
Due bottiglie di Bâtard-Montrachet
e tartufi bianchi, per favore.
Grazie.
Bedelia.
He attacked me.
Is that your blood?
No.
You were defending yourself?
I was reckless.
This wasn't reckless violence.
It was a controlled use of force.
I know what happened.
Do you?
He was your patient
before he was mine.
He died under your care.
You were not defending yourself.
I can help you tell the version of events
you want to be told.
I can help you,
if you ask me to.
Will you help me?
In accord with my own taste
for the pre-Renaissance,
I present the case of Pietro della Vigna,
whose treachery earned him
a place in Dante's Hell.
He was disgraced and blinded
for betraying his emperor's trust.
Dante's pilgrim finds him
in the seventh level of the Inferno,
reserved for suicides.
Like Judas Iscariot, he died by hanging.
Judas and Pietro della Vigna
are linked in Dante's Inferno.
Betrayal and hanging,
then, linked since antiquity,
the image appearing
again and again in art.
This is the earliest-known depiction
of the Crucifixion,
carved on an ivory box in Gaul
about A.D. 400.
It includes the death by hanging
of Judas,
his face upturned to the branch
that suspends him.
On the doors
of the Benevento Cathedral,
we see Judas hanging
with his bowels falling out.
And here, from a 15th-century
edition of The Inferno
is Pietro della Vigna's body
hanging from a bleeding tree.
I won't belabour the parallels
with Judas Iscariot.
Betrayal, hanging, self-destruction.
"lo fei gibetto a me de le mie case."
"I make my own home be my gallows."
Mr Dimmond, welcome.
Please join us.
We were just about to discuss
the matter of chewing in Dante.
Thank you for your kind attention.
Thank you.
Would you say I secured my position,
Professor Sogliato?
The Studiolo seem satisfied.
Satisfied?
I thought the applause was
downright enthusiastic
in its soft and dusty way.
Dottore Fell is a friend of yours?
I was his TA at Cambridge.
The tales I could tell.
Please do.
What kind of friend would I be?
What kind of friend, indeed.
Dottore.
An exposition of atrocious
torture instruments
appeals to connoisseurs
of the very worst in mankind.
Now that ceaseless exposure has
calloused us to the lewd and the vulgar,
it is instructive to see
what still seems wicked to us.
What still slaps the clammy flab
of our submissive consciousness
hard enough to get our attention?
What wickedness has your attention,
Mr Dimmond?
Yours...
Dr Fell.
I have no delusions about morality.
If I did,
I would've gone to "la polizia".
I'm curious as to what fate
befell Dr Fell
to see you here in his stead.
You may have to strap me
to the breaking wheel to loosen my tongue.
You overestimate my affection
for the genuine Dr Fell.
Clearly, you found him
as distasteful as I did.
On the contrary.
We can twist ourselves into all manner
of uncomfortable positions
just to maintain appearances,
with or without a breaking wheel.
Are you here to twist me
into an uncomfortable position?
I'm here to help you untwist...
to our mutual benefit.
Observe or participate.
What?
Are you, in this very moment,
observing or participating?
Observing.
You say you're observing,
but this...
This is participation, Bedelia.
Did you know what he would do?
I would prefer you answer honestly.
- I was curious.
- You were curious what would happen.
You were curious
what Mr Dimmond would do.
What I would do.
Did you anticipate our thoughts?
Counter-thoughts?
Rationalisations?
Yes.
Is this what you expected?
That's participation.
What have you gotten yourself into,
Bedelia?
Shall I hang up your coat?
Would you rather I extended you
the same kindness as the escargot?
Eating me without my knowledge?
No.
I find knowing to be far more powerful.
Why do you think I'm allowing this?
Cos snails aren't the only creatures
who prefer eating with company.
If only that company
could be Will Graham.
I'm just fascinated to know
how you will feel when all this...
happens to you.