'Previously on "Hannibal"...'
You know and I know
it's the best way to bait him.
So I really bad-mouth
the Red Dragon in TattleCrime.
It feels like a trap to me.
'I have blasphemed against the Dragon.
There is much for you to dread.'
You orchestrated his end,
Alana.
I am the Dragon.
Get up. Stand by the bed.
Do you know where you are
in the room?
Yes.
And you know where you are
in the house?
Then you know where the front door is,
don't you?
Reba, feel on my chest.
Bring your hands up slowly...
Don't do what you're thinking!
Just feel on my chest.
Just around my throat.
You feel that?
It's a key.
Take it off over my head.
Careful.
Now...
...I'm going to see
if I can trust you.
Go to the front door, lock it.
Go ahead.
I'll wait right here.
Don't try to run.
I can catch you.
Oh, Reba.
Now lock the door,
and put the key around my neck.
Hang it around my neck.
Now let's make sure it's locked,
shall we?
Very good.
Now go on back to the bedroom.
You know the way.
Sit down.
Sit still or I can't keep Him off you.
Please try.
Put out your hand.
Feel this.
Don't grab it, feel it.
It's a shotgun.
You know what it will do.
Take your hand down.
I wish I could've trusted you.
I wanted to trust you.
You felt so good.
So did you, D.
I love it.
Please don't hurt me now.
It's all over for me.
I can't give you to Him.
You know what He will do.
No...
No, no, no...
He will bite you.
Better you go with me.
No, no, no, no...
Oh, god, no!
Oh, Reba...
...I-I can't stand to watch you burn.
No!
He shot himself in the face.
I put my hand in it.
He set fire to the house.
He shot himself.
I put my hand in it.
He was on...the floor.
I won't put you through this again,
but, er... I'd like to come back by,
just to say hi
and see how you're doing.
How could you help it,
a charmer like me?
In the end, he couldn't kill you
and he couldn't watch you die.
The people who study this kind of thing
say that he was trying to stop
because you helped him.
Probably saved some lives.
I drew a freak.
You didn't draw a freak.
You drew a man...
...with a freak on his back.
There is nothing wrong with you.
I know there's nothing wrong with me.
In making friends,
I try to be wary of people
who foster dependency
and feed on it.
I've been with a few.
The blind attract them.
Not just the blind.
Ding-dong, the Dragon's dead.
Are congratulations in order?
I didn't kill him. Suicide.
Then he wasn't as strong
as the Dragon after all.
He was trying to stop.
I was rooting for you, Will.
It's a shame.
You came all this way
and you didn't get to kill anybody.
The only consolation is Dr Chilton.
Congratulations for the job
you did on him.
I admired it enormously.
What a cunning boy you are.
Are you accusing me of something?
Does the enemy inside you
agree with the accusation?
Even a little bit?
I came back to stop the Dragon.
He's stopped.
Your family was on his itinerary.
Safe now.
You can go home again,
if there's any point.
Is there any point?
I like my life there.
It won't be the same.
You'll see it's not the same.
The unspoken knowledge
will live with you,
like unwanted company in the house.
Molly and I want it to be the same.
When life becomes
maddeningly polite...
...think about me.
Think about me, Will,
don't worry about me.
You turned yourself in,
so I would always know
where you were.
You'd only do that if I rejected you.
Goodbye.
Will...
Was it good to see me?
Good?
No.
Do you think you can sit up?
Try to sit up.
You didn't break my back.
Your face... is closed to me.
If I can see you...
...you can see me.
Oh, you think you understand,
don't you?
"I understand that blood and breath...
"...are only elements undergoing change
to fuel your Radiance."
Hannibal said those words.
To me.
I wanted to share with Lecter,
and Lecter betrayed me.
He betrayed me, too.
I would like to share.
You shared...
...with Reba.
I shared with Reba a little,
in a way that she could survive.
But you didn't change her.
I chose not to change her.
I am stronger than the Dragon now.
Hannibal Lecter is
who you need to change.
I want to meet Lecter.
How would I manage that?
The only teeth we found in the skull
were grandma's dentures.
And the upper part was made of vulcanite
instead of acrylic like they use today.
No one's made vulcanite plates
in fifty years.
Dolarhyde had a new acrylic set
just like them made to fit him.
Chinese manufacturer.
The new pair we found on the body.
Grandma's old yucky pair
we found in his mouth.
Well, not his mouth, per se.
We think it's a guy named
Arnold Lang. He's missing.
Worked at a service station
near Dolarhyde.
Found his car,
but it'd been wiped clean.
So Dolarhyde snuffs out Lang,
takes the dead body back to the house,
does his whole thing with the blind lady,
song and dance, "Will I shoot you?
"Won't I shoot you?"
"I can't stand to see you burn.
Boo-hoo!"
Then blows Lang's head away
with a twelve-gauge.
So the routine of hanging the key around
his neck was to be sure she felt the body.
So she could tell us
she certainly felt a body.
The Great Red Dragon lives.
The obvious thing is
to get him to come to us.
Bait him with something
he wants more than me.
- He'd have to be an idiot to go for it.
- I know.
Want to hear
what the best bait would be?
I'm not sure I want to.
Hannibal would be the best bait.
Why in God's name would anyone
want to meet Hannibal Lecter?
To kill him, Jack.
The Dragon could absorb him
that way, engulf him,
become more than he is.
You sound pretty sure.
I'm not sure. Who's sure?
I'm not even sure Hannibal
would draw the Dragon.
I just say that it's our best shot.
Set him up how?
We take Hannibal into federal custody.
We fake an escape.
We assign a moment to decision.
What you propose is so thoughtless...
...I find it difficult
to imagine that moment exists.
Decisions are made
of kneaded feelings.
They're more often a lump
than a sum.
However you think
you are going to manipulate
this situation to your advantage...
...think again.
There's no advantage.
It's all degrees of disadvantage.
"Who holds the Devil,
let him hold him well.
"He will hardly be caught
a second time."
I don't intend Hannibal
to be caught a second time.
Can't live with him,
can't live without him.
Is that what this is?
I guess...
...this is my Becoming.
What you are "becoming"
is pathological.
Extreme acts of cruelty require
a high degree of empathy.
You've just found religion.
Nothing more dangerous than that.
I'd pack my bags if I were you, Bedelia.
Meat's back on the menu.
You righteous, reckless,
twitchy little man.
He might as well cut all of our throats
and be done with it.
Ready or not, here he comes.
Dr Bloom.
You finally broke down
and came to visit.
Your face did not change at all
when you first looked at me.
Shock, in seeing me,
is usually... delayed.
I wanted to see you, Frederick.
I wanted to remind myself
what Hannibal is capable of.
What Hannibal is capable of.
What Will Graham is capable of.
What you are capable of.
You were the roper.
Too bad there was not enough rope
for you to hang yourself with.
Just enough... to hang me.
Who does Will Graham have you
roping now?
Hannibal.
If I had them,
I would burn the man alive.
Though...
...maybe I would rather have his skin.
I've been getting grafts.
How I would love to count Hannibal
among my donors.
You were never comfortable
in your own skin, Frederick.
You wouldn't be comfortable
in Hannibal's.
Are you?
There's a deal for you, Hannibal.
Or there could be.
A deal? With whom?
The FBI.
- Jack couldn't ask me himself?
- Jack doesn't know you as well as I do.
He thought if he asked you for help,
you would just torment him.
Quite right, too. How wise of Jack.
The Red Dragon faked his death.
Good for him.
Jack wants to fake your escape.
I release you into police custody,
and Jack uses you as bait.
Was it Will's idea?
Yes.
Yes, that worked out so well
for Frederick Chilton.
Do please tell Frederick,
if you see him,
I wish a speedy convalescence
and hope he won't be very ugly.
I've been on the phone for hours on
your behalf, and this is what you get...
Any rational society would either
kill me or give me my books.
If you cooperate in the capture
of Francis Dolarhyde,
you get your books,
your drawings, your toilet.
All privileges will be restored.
You trust Will with my well-being?
As much as I trust you with his.
You trust me with yours?
You intend to release me
into police custody.
Police are not as wise as you are.
I might escape in earnest
and come to kill you.
First chance you get, I assume.
You died in my kitchen, Alana,
when you chose to be brave.
Every moment since is borrowed.
Your wife.
Your child.
They belong to me.
You made a bargain for Will's life,
and then I spun you gold.
Hannibal has tentatively agreed
to the deal, as proposed.
What will it take to make him
less tentative?
He wants Will to ask him.
And he wants you to say "please".
I'll say "pretty please".
Well, people are going to stampede
if they think that Lecter is out.
Let them stampede.
Authenticity.
And let them believe
I helped Hannibal escape.
Authenticity?
Someone has to be close
when the Dragon comes.
And then?
We kill Dolarhyde.
And then...
...we kill Hannibal.
To the Devil his due.
I thought you said
your goodbyes.
We've one last goodbye between us.
You didn't just say goodbye,
though, did you?
That little extra bit at the end...
What was that you said?
You'd never have turned yourself in
unless I rejected you.
Yes. That extra bit.
I believe that's what they call
a "mike-drop".
You dropped the mike, Will.
But here you are having to come back
and pick it up again.
I knew you'd keep running
if I kept chasing you.
I knew you wanted me to know exactly
where I could find you when I needed to.
And you did.
I need you, Hannibal.
Ding-dong, the Dragon's not dead.
He told you he wanted to meet you.
Maybe that was a serious invitation.
After the big escape,
you send a message to the Dragon
in the personal ads,
ask him for a rendezvous.
He won't go near a mail drop.
He might be curious enough
to look at one, see if you sold him.
We chose a drop that can be
watched only from a few places
from a long way off,
and we'll stake out
the observation points.
It sounds weak to you,
even as you say it.
Secret Service has a set-up they've
never used. They'll let us have it.
You're our best shot, Hannibal.
Please.
He's not going to kill us here.
What he wants to do requires
something a little more private.
What are you doing?
You know, Will, you worry too much.
You'd be much more comfortable
if you relaxed with yourself.
Going my way?
The bluff is eroding.
There was more land
when I was here with Abigail.
More land still when I was here
with Miriam Lass.
And now you're here with me.
And the bluff is still eroding.
You and I are suspended
over the roiling Atlantic.
Soon, all this will be lost
to the sea.
You're playing games with yourself
in the dark of the moon.
It wasn't surprising that I heard
from the Great Red Dragon.
Was it surprising
when you heard from him?
Yes and no.
Do you intend to watch him kill me?
I intend to watch him change you.
My compassion for you
is inconvenient, Will.
If you're partial to beef products,
it is inconvenient to be
compassionate toward a cow.
Save yourself, kill them all?
I don't know if I can save myself.
And maybe that's just fine.
"No greater love hath man
than to lay down his life for a friend."
- He's watching us now.
- I know.
Don't run. I'll catch you.
Hello, Francis.
Hello, Dr Lecter.
I'm so happy you chose life, Francis.
Suicide is the enemy.
You were seized by a fantasy world...
...with the brilliance and freshness
and immediacy of childhood.
It took you a step beyond alone.
I'm going to film your death,
Dr Lecter.
As dying, you meld with the strength
of the Dragon.
It's a glorious and
rather discomforting idea.
Watching the film will be wonderful.
But not as wonderful
as the act itself.
♪ Oh, the skies
♪ Tumbling from your eyes
♪ So sublime
♪ The chase to end all time
♪ Seasons call and fall
♪ From grace and uniform
♪ Anatomical
♪ Metaphysical...
It really does look black
in the moonlight.
See.
This is all I ever wanted for you, Will.
For both of us.
It's beautiful.
♪ Oh, the dye
♪ A blood-red setting sun
♪ Rushing through my veins
♪ Burning up my skin
♪ I will survive, live and thrive
♪ Win this deadly game
♪ Love crime
♪ I will survive
♪ Live and thrive
♪ I will ♪