'Previously on "Hannibal"...'
You won't be coming back here
for a long time.
There's something reassuring
about you eating Dr Lecter.
It makes you the apex predator.
I am packing loads of viable sperm.
Stumbled across any viable uteruses?
Where is the polizia?
They're being bought by the same people
that bought Rinaldo Pazzi.
Is your husband still in the city?
Chiyoh has always been
very protective of me.
I've taken the liberty of giving you
something to help you relax.
Jack was the first to suggest
getting inside your head.
No!
Sono un ufficiale del FBI.
Ascoltami.
Mi chiamo Jack Crawford.
Sono un ufficiale del FBI.
Ascoltami. Ascoltami.
Ascoltami.
Commendatore Benetti.
I don't imagine you're here
to make an arrest.
No. You imagine correctly.
Take Lecter and this one.
He'll pay us double for both.
There's no price on your head,
Signor Crawford.
So, Hannibal Lecter...
Il Mostro di Firenze,
narrowly escapes the Questura.
Is that how the story goes?
Missed him by this much.
The good Doctor Lecter
is once more in the wind.
But he left one last victim.
Open him the way Lecter
opened the other one.
Open him all the way.
Arrivederci.
Wrong floor.
Would you mind coming over here
and pulling this needle out of my neck?
Where did they take them?
Did you do this?
Of course.
I appreciate it.
You're sitting at Hannibal's table.
You know him. You know Will.
I know them.
They are identically different,
Hannibal and Will.
Where did they take them?
They are most likely taking them
to the US, to Maryland.
I can even tell you the address,
once you've pulled this needle
out of my neck.
Then what?
My "then what" consists
of getting out of Florence alive,
since I'm supposed to be dead.
Which puts me in no position to stop
whatever it is you intend on starting.
Where?
Muskrat Farm, the Verger estate,
near the Susquehanna River
in northern Maryland.
Pronto.
Dimmi tutto.
Mason has what he wants.
I think it's time you get what you want.
He has Hannibal.
He has Will, too.
Your brother's a sadist.
He'll torture them
and take the time to enjoy it.
That gives us time.
There's a hush
over Muskrat Farm, Cordell.
Like the quiet of the old Sabbath.
Smells like salvation.
Gentlemen,
welcome to Muskrat Farm.
Your people might have assassinated me
in Florence, Mason.
Now where's the fun in that?
I still keep my father's knife,
ever ready to slip into a pig's back
to check the depth of the fat.
Cordell, if you would?
A little lean, I think.
Maybe we should fatten you up,
shall we?
It is more trouble to move
a semi-wild pig against its will
than it is to kidnap a man.
Pigs are harder to get hold of,
and big ones are stronger than a man.
There are the tusks to consider,
if you want to maintain
the integrity of your abdomen.
Something worth maintaining,
Mr Graham?
Tusked beasts instinctively disembowel.
At swine fairs, I've seen exotic pigs
from all over the world.
You are the best of all
that I've seen.
We are going to have
some good, funny times, Dr Lecter.
Sad news about Jack Crawford.
Appears Hannibal Lecter
killed him in Florence.
I hope there's some satisfaction in being
the final victim of the Chesapeake Ripper.
There'll certainly be some notoriety.
The faeces are flying again in Florence.
Jack Crawford is alive.
Well, that's disappointing.
He saw the snatch.
I trust you haven't betrayed
doctor-patient confidentiality, Dr Bloom.
Your trust hasn't been misplaced.
The FBI is going to catch
the first squeal on the kidnapping.
The moment Jack Crawford
set foot in Italy,
I registered complaints
with the local authorities,
the sheriff, the US Attorney's office,
that he'd been harassing me,
calling me late at night
with incoherent threats.
Of course he can't prove he didn't.
And it muddies the water.
Now you can head off a warrant.
There will be no warrant,
and there will be no warrant forthcoming.
I appreciate wanting to kill
Hannibal Lecter,
and I'm not without benefit from that.
He can't make good on his promise
to murder you if he's dead, now, can he?
But he's not dead.
Play with your food, Mason, and
you give it the opportunity to bite back.
Oh, I'm not playing, Dr Bloom.
Hannibal is.
He's always playing.
I snatched Will Graham
right out of your mouth.
You must be famished.
There is an inescapable parallel
between you and Jezebel, Mason.
Keen Bible student that you are,
you'll recall dogs ate Jezebel's face,
along with the rest of her.
If Jezebel was right
with the Risen Jesus,
the Riz would have provided her
with a new face,
as he has provided mine.
The transplant surgery
is extremely skilful,
which is why Cordell here
will be performing the face-off.
Hello.
You boys remind me of that German
cannibal who advertised for a friend,
and then ate him and his penis
before he died.
Tragedy being,
the penis was overcooked.
Go to all that trouble to eat a friend,
and you overcook his penis!
They ate it anyway.
They had to, they committed.
But they didn't enjoy it.
I'm committed to enjoying
every bite of you.
You're going to eat him
with my face?
Yes.
I got a taste for it
after you two had me eat my nose.
You must be terribly proud
that you could bring this off.
It's dangerous
to get exactly what you want.
What will you do
after you've eaten me?
You could wreck some foster homes
and torment some children.
Uh... or drink martinis
made with tears.
But where, Mason,
would the hard-core fun come from?
It's foolish to dilute
such an ecstatic time as this
with fears about the future.
Er, Cordell,
Mr Graham's looking very dry.
A little moisturiser, please.
I'm curious, what will be
the first cuts of me you'll serve?
The first course, of course,
will be your hands and feet.
Sizzling on a Promethean barbecue.
The coal is white and very hard,
it makes a clear ringing sound
when struck.
You've thought of everything.
And after that, we'll have
a little pyjama party, you and I.
You can be in shorties by then.
Cordell is going to keep you alive
for a very long time.
Well, no pyjama party for you,
Mr Graham.
We're gonna feed you to the pigs
as soon as Cordell
has removed your face
in a much more civilised fashion
than you just tried to remove his.
Mason would've preferred
to brand your face.
He fought bravely and with his own funds
against the Humane Slaughter Act,
and managed to keep
face-branding legal.
It's very important to Mason
that I have the pig's experience.
Mason has done beautiful things
with these creatures.
Very special.
Truly a visionary.
He has a wealth of information
and resources in his faceless skull.
The longer you're respectful,
the longer you'll keep your tongue.
And when I do lose my tongue?
I'll boil it and slice it very thin,
marinate it in olive oil,
garlic, parsley and vinegar.
Simple and clean. And delicious.
Have they told you the drill?
The drill is, in a few hours,
I'll come down here
and remove all you've got
below the elbows and knees.
I'll keep you going with IVs
and tourniquets until the very last.
Some things are best saved for last.
Once you're dead,
I'll prepare your loins and ribs.
Aged.
Meats are aged not only for tenderness
but mainly for flavour.
And flavours change.
Every day I'll feed Mason
some new part of you.
Don't you worry, Dr Lecter.
You will always be cooked to perfection.
I think I might feed the eel
some delicacy of Lecter.
His genitals, perhaps.
How long have you and Dr Bloom
been an item?
Not long.
Longer than that, Cordell says.
Does Dr Bloom want children?
I'm sure you've had a chance
to check under the hood by now.
How's the uterus? Intact?
Are the hips childbearing? Roomy?
Land the plane, Mason.
Oh, you've got a big surprise
coming to you, Margot.
Would it spoil anything for you
if I told you I've already found us
a surrogate?
Not for my sperm, but for your eggs.
I don't have any. You took them.
I most certainly did,
but I didn't humpty-dumpty them.
I just went and found them
a new basket.
I told you I wanted to give you
a Verger baby, our own baby.
Yours and mine.
Well... mostly yours.
Where's the surrogate, Mason?
She's resting at the moment.
She's here?
She's on the farm.
I want to see her.
First, I think you need
to prepare yourself,
psychologically, I mean.
This is going to be a very emotional
experience for you, Margot.
I have to think about appropriate timing.
Don't think too long, smiley.
Oh, that's the spirit, Margot.
Your maternal instinct's revving up.
I love it.
What are you doing here?
I'm Mason Verger's psychiatrist.
Is that part of his therapy or yours?
I think we're all working
through some issues.
I'm putting an emphasis
on self-preservation.
Jack's alive.
Good for Jack.
You helped Mason Verger find us.
I helped Mason find Hannibal.
We followed Bâtard-Montrachet
when we should've just followed you.
Almost as ugly as
what Mason wants to do to us
is the fact that he can do it
with the tacit agreement
of people sworn to uphold the law.
I was trying to get to Hannibal
before you.
I knew you couldn't stop yourself,
so I had to try.
By facilitating torture and death?
I can abide the thought
of Hannibal tortured.
Not necessarily to death.
I'd say he has it coming,
wouldn't you?
Or maybe you wouldn't.
What did you think would happen?
I thought Jack Crawford and the FBI
would come to the rescue.
But the finer details of what I thought
would happen have evolved.
Then you have to evolve, Alana.
You have to spill blood.
Either by your own hand or...
...someone else's.
Buonasera, signor.
Buonasera, Signorina Verger.
Thank you for coming, Margot.
It hasn't been that long
since I treated you.
Have you started taking the chocolate,
as Mason likes to say...
...after you fought him for so long?
Are we in therapy now?
You tell me.
Mason promised
to give something back to me.
Something that he stole.
There was a surrogate all along.
It's a Verger baby.
It's my baby.
Mason will deny you.
He will always deny you.
You know you will have to kill him.
Are you saying you'd do it for me?
I could never trust you.
No, of course not.
But you could trust me
never to deny that I did it.
It would actually be more therapeutic
for you to kill him yourself.
You'll remember
I recommended that in session.
Wait until I could get away with it,
you said.
What difference would one more
murder charge make to me?
I'm the only other suspect you've got.
You can do it when it suits you,
and I'll write a letter gloating about
how much I enjoyed killing him myself.
Buonasera.
He has a pocketknife.
I was trying to save Will from you.
But right now, you're the only one
who can save him.
Promise me you'll save him.
Please.
I promise.
And I always keep my promises, Alana.
Just cut the ropes on one arm,
give me the knife and leave.
I can do the rest.
Are you going to kill Mason?
Margot is.
Snatch some of my hair,
back from the hairline, if you don't mind.
Get some skin.
Put it in Mason's hand after he's dead.
Could I have ever understood you?
No.
Ah... Cordell told me
if I waited long enough,
he could grow me a new face
from my own cells.
But I was adamant
it was your face I wanted.
I was looking at your face
while you were watching me cut mine off
and I thought,
"Oh, that's a nice face."
You're going under now,
Mr Verger.
When you wake up, your face
will be bound and uncomfortable.
Have you accepted Jesus,
Mr Graham?
Do you have faith?
I do. I'm free.
Hallelujah.
This will immobilise your body,
but you'll feel everything.
I'm going to cut off your face
without anaesthesia, Mr Graham.
Is he alive?
There's no foetal heartbeat.
Take it out.
Take it out!
You'll be sure to let me know
if this hurts, won't you?
Cordell?
Cordell!
Hi, Mason.
What the hell's going on out there?
Where's Cordell?
Cordell's dead.
They're all dead out there.
Hannibal got away.
Well, get on the horn to Washington
and get four of those bastards
with guns up here now!
Send the helicopter.
I found your surrogate, Mason.
Your surrogate, Margot.
I promised you
I'd give you a Verger baby.
I'm taking what you promised me.
And I've got everything I need
from you now.
You can't kill me, Margot.
You'll lose everything.
"In the absence of an heir,
"the sole beneficiary is
the Southern Baptist Church."
But there is going to be
an heir, Mason.
A Verger baby.
Yours, mine...
Mostly yours.
You know what happens if we stimulate
your prostate gland with a cattle prod?
Hannibal does.
He helped us milk you.
You're dead, Dr Bloom.
No, Mason.
We all are. Didn't you know that?
But these aren't.
Will you go home?
Can you go home?
No more than you can.
- Would you watch over me?
- I will.
Not in a cage.
Some beasts shouldn't be caged.
Your obsessive and successful hunt,
whose plight was it driven by? Mine?
Yours?
Mischa's.
Did you eat her?
Yes.
But I did not kill her.
The most stable elements, Chiyoh,
appear in the middle of the periodic table,
roughly between iron and silver.
Between iron and silver.
I think that's appropriate for you.
Do we talk about teacups and time
and the rules of disorder?
The teacup's broken.
It's never going to gather itself
back together again.
Not even in your mind?
Your memory palace is building.
It's full of new things.
It shares some rooms with my own.
I've discovered you there.
Victorious.
When it comes to you and me...
...there can be no decisive victory.
We are in zero-sum game?
I miss my dogs.
I'm not gonna miss you.
I'm not going to find you.
I'm not going to look for you.
I don't want to know
where you are or what you do.
I don't want to think about you anymore.
You delight in wickedness
and then berate yourself for the delight.
You delight.
I tolerate.
I don't have your appetite.
Goodbye... Hannibal.
He's gone, Jack.
Jack.
I'm here.
You finally caught
the Chesapeake Ripper, Jack.
I didn't catch you.
You surrendered.
I want you to know exactly where I am.
And where you can always find me.
Cuff him. Put him in my car.