Post-traumatic amnesia
is caused
by a disturbing event.
Did someone hurt me?
She's hoping that being here
will jog her memory.
My doctor said that being in
a familiar setting might help.
But that isn't familiar at all.
Cadence.
- Hi.
- Cady.
Why did you forbid everyone
from talking to me
about my own fucking life?
The doctors said it was best
if you remember on your own.
Do you think that
you aren't wrecking
a perfectly good ecosystem?
- Fuck you!
- No, fuck you!
Stop!
Who's Raquel?
Gat's girlfriend.
I thought I knew you.
Forgive me for not wanting
to blow up my fucking life
just 'cause you were
in the mood to hook up.
I've been sexting
with an older guy.
I have no idea
how to do any of that stuff.
My marriage is just fine.
So was mine until it wasn't.
You're selling the Thornton?
I don't intend to discuss
the sale with your father.
I am selling my favorite piece
to alleviate
your cash flow issues.
I'm gonna wake this one up.
Mom.
Mom?
Help!
I got my love
of storytelling from Gran.
Sometimes she didn't have
time or patience
when we begged her to make up
a fairy tale on the spot.
Tell us a story.
But on good days,
she'd give in.
And she always began
the same way.
A story? OK.
All right.
All right. hush.
Once upon a time,
there was a mythical land,
where it was always summer.
Lately, I have to
make up my own stories.
So here's a fairy tale
in honor of my gran.
This mythical land
where it's always summer,
it was ruled by a brave
king and his fairy queen.
The royal subjects
love their fairy queen.
Her magic kept the sun
shining...
The seas warm,
the rose gardens flourishing.
Legend has it,
her magical heart
was made of pure yellow gold.
It would never slow
or fall or break.
She gave the king three
fairy princess daughters,
and they had more tiny heirs.
Then one day,
the queen's golden heart
stopped.
If you insist on being here,
don't disturb me when I'm...
Oh, I'm sorry, sweetheart.
I thought you were
someone else.
I can come back another time.
No, no, no, no, no, sit.
I'm happy to see you.
Bess is driving me crazy
insisting on moving up here
with the girls
to take care of me
like I'm some old man
when everyone knows that
she can't stand Cuddledown.
How are you feeling?
Clairmont is so...different.
Yeah, it's gonna be
spectacular
when the work is finished.
I've always had a fondness
for modern architecture, but...
But Gran liked
the classic style.
Let me guess,
my mom has you under orders
not to talk to me about her.
I don't take orders
from Penny.
But...
no, to dwell on the past
is a dull man's pursuit.
I've known that Gran passed.
But knowing is different
from remembering.
And I remember now.
OK. Great.
Do you have a...
a program from her funeral?
Because I can remember
the night she died now,
but I can't remember
anything about the memorial.
Look, I said no!
I don't want to
discuss that day.
You know, it was terrible.
Mirren, you know that.
Cadence.
Oh, right.
What happened to the
little blonde girls
running around this place?
They grew up.
You OK, Cady?
You look pale.
I just don't understand.
This place feels
nothing like Gran.
I hate it.
And you didn't even let us
say goodbye to old Clairmont.
You just...erased her
like she didn't exist!
Oh! How dare you!
Dad, Dad, Dad,
she didn't mean it, OK.
She is not well, remember?
Sorry.
Sorry, you know what he says
about dwelling in the past.
Hey, hey, hey.
Wait, Cady,
I like to go to her rose garden
when I miss her.
I feel her there.
She always said it was
the closest thing to heaven.
The fairy queen's sudden fall
revealed her secret
to the realm.
She had lied to the king,
to the princesses,
to all the tiny heirs
to the throne.
The queen was not
a fairy at all,
but a mere mortal.
And mortals die.
That's not champagne.
That's rose gold.
She would never wear rose gold.
Cadence, come here.
I don't...
I don't know.
- Come here, Cady.
- Mom.
This is champagne. Hmm?
It's dignified.
My mistake, Ms. Sinclair.
I'll see what we have.
And in the meantime,
your mother's effects.
What's gonna happen
with Gran's black pearls now?
Are you all gonna share them?
Uh...
your grandfather wants her
to wear them in the ground.
Oh.
I think she would
have worn a tennis necklace
with this dress,
don't you think?
She doesn't really
look like herself.
Honestly, I thought
she'd look worse.
I can't see the incision
from the autopsy.
- Mom.
- Oh.
She was in perfect health.
We had to make sure the staff
didn't poison her.
I'm joking.
It was just her time.
Go on.
You can wait in the car
while I finish up here.
I realize that was the first
dead body that you've seen.
Yep.
Hopefully the last.
It won't be.
But you'll be better
prepared next time.
That's why I brought you.
Oh, uh, your dad gets in
on the late ferry.
- Well, you should call him.
- Wait.
There's a box of his junk
in the attic.
Dad's coming?
Now?
Wha--how could he do that
to you?
He's not doing
anything to me.
Plus, it would look weird
if he didn't show.
How are you so good at this?
The guy who broke your heart is
coming to your mom's funeral,
and you're just...fine.
You never fall apart.
I wish I was like you.
Falling apart
is for other people.
We are Sinclairs.
And we manage with our
backs straight.
Like my mother always said.
Once I fix my posture?
You know,
I was younger than you are now
when we lost Rosemary.
And my mom had
excellent advice then.
She said,
go back to your routine,
and you look to the future.
You erase the person you lost
from conversation.
And if you must speak
about them,
do not show
that you feel the loss.
If you follow the rules,
eventually,
nothing can hurt you.
You just make your heart
a small target.
After all,
look where Gran's
enlarged heart got her.
♪ Sometimes when
I zone out at night ♪
♪ I forget
you're out of sight ♪
♪ Like living before
you were gone ♪
♪ So I read up
on the afterlife ♪
♪ I don't believe
in Jesus Christ ♪
♪ Just somewhere
we can all belong ♪
♪ And days move slow ♪
♪ I'm livin' in the
same black hole ♪
♪ There's flowers
on your grave ♪
- Cady.
- Hello.
So I, uh, have a migraine,
and you throw a party?
You said you missed music,
so...
Do you like what we've done
with the place?
Yeah, I think that Bess is
gonna go mental, but...
Oh, no, my mother's
not stepping foot
in Cuddledown this summer.
She thinks it's outdated,
and that our whole family
can fit into one wing
in the new Clairmont.
So Liars get squatter's rights.
Would you like
the twins' bedroom?
Yeah, my mom
won't go for that.
She, uh, checks on me
like three times a night.
I mean, you did pass out
in a rose bush
on a painkiller bender.
The gardener had to put you
on a golf cart
to get you back to Windemere.
Paulo did?
Who?
The groundskeeper.
Did you remember something?
Something happened
that triggered you
and made you sick?
Guys, maybe let's not talk
about what sent
Cady into a batshit spiral.
I actually heard my mom
tell Penny
that, um, Harris yelled at you.
They think that it's his fault
that you freaked.
Maybe.
I asked him about Tipper.
I remember everything
up until the funeral,
and then it all goes blank.
So you do remember.
Gat, it's fine, OK?
I know you and I
got in a fight,
but it's in the past.
Bringing up the funeral
really did upset Granddad.
Yeah, I'm sure it wasn't
his favorite day ever.
You know we can't tell you.
'Cause we want you
to get better.
But the whole point
of a funeral is closure, right?
How am I supposed to move on
if I don't know what happened?
Come on, guys. Just tell me.
Did something bad happen?
Is that why Granddad
is so upset?
Did I do something?
I'm sorry. I don't feel well.
OK, OK.
Gat, we agreed.
Hey, she's not asking about
the night that she got hurt,
right?
Just the funeral.
We can talk about
just the funeral.
Fine. OK.
But then that's it, OK.
No more talk of
summer '16 ever.
Can we please just have
a fun, normal summer
with weed and pickleball
and Liars being Liars?
Thank you.
- So did I...
- No, no, no.
OK, if we are
gonna be depressing,
I require salt air
and a cold beverage.
Onwards, Liars.
I'm glad you got
some memories back,
but part of me hoped
you wouldn't remember her.
What, Raquel?
It's fine.
Come on, you don't have to
do that "it's fine"
Sinclair thing with me.
Look, for a long time,
I didn't know what happened
between the time
that we kissed
and the way things are
with us now.
I didn't understand
why you didn't seem
to like me like that anymore.
But...now I know.
So you're off the hook.
It's all good.
♪ Will you be
a satanist with me? ♪
♪ Mortgage off your soul ♪
♪ To buy your dream ♪
♪ Vacation home in Florida ♪
Johnny.
I'm good.
Aren't you scared
you're going to burn?
No.
I don't believe
in sunscreen anymore.
Scientists are corrupt, and
SPF is a moneymaking scheme.
Do you have any baby oil?
Oh, my God, your skin
will literally bubble.
I'm surprisingly resilient.
Hey, Gat,
we weren't talking
when Tipper died, were we?
Oh, yes,
let's rehash that now.
It sucked.
All I wanted to do was help.
But, well,
I didn't know what to do.
To be honest,
I was kind of lost.
Aw, you didn't have to send me
a thank you note.
I got this tailored,
but I'm sure it's not
what the cool kids
are wearing to church.
It's for Cadence.
What, the suit?
The...the note.
I'm not sure
if I want to go today.
So I thought a note.
No one wants to go
to a funeral.
No, no, what I mean is, uh,
I don't think I should go.
Cady and I had a fight.
Oh, no.
Did she post an unflattering
pic of you on the 'gram?
Immediately regret
this conversation.
OK, hold on,
hold on, hold on.
Was it bad?
Yeah.
Johnny and I
aren't talking either.
What do you remember
about your dad's funeral?
No, not a lot.
I remember I lost my jacket,
so you gave me yours.
It smelled like Dad.
You know, I was so
pissed at him when he died.
Did I tell you that?
We had this big
blow-up argument,
like stupid brother shit.
And the next day, he was gone.
And I was like,
this fucker died on purpose
just so I didn't
get the last word.
So I didn't want to go
to his funeral either.
But I did,
just in case you
or your mum needed me.
And I needed your jacket.
I get it.
I love being the hero.
It's my great character flaw.
Grief is ugly.
Other people's grief
is uncomfortable,
but we show up for the people
we love just in case,
so that their memory
of the day isn't just
cold, jacketless loneliness.
It used to feel like
I belonged here.
But this summer it's like...
I don't know.
Look, I get it. I get it.
But when two families merge,
someone always feels
like an intruder.
Hell, Carrie still gets
dirty looks
from some members
of our family.
That's not the same.
They're just so...
so privileged.
Yeah.
But they're not lucky
like we are.
Nobody hugged them enough.
You think I should
apologize to Gat?
I was kind of a dick.
Yeah, you were a total dick.
And Gat was a dick to Cady.
It was like a whole
circle of dicks.
It's fine.
I am fine.
You're giving serious
Aunt Penny vibes right now.
My mom is...
great in a crisis.
Mine's been crying
in the shower.
Mine's been using my dad as
an emotional support animal.
Look at them.
I was just about
to tell him
right when Tipper's heart
went...
The shuttle's here.
It's time.
♪ All dressed up ♪
- ♪ Nowhere to go ♪
- OK, girls, come on.
♪ TV's on ♪
♪ No one's home ♪
Hey, hey.
OK, if you need a minute,
we can go on separate boats.
No one will judge you
if you're late.
Fair point.
Let's roll.
OK.
Aren't we missing someone?
Wouldn't be a funeral
if we weren't.
♪ Meal for two ♪
♪ Eat for one ♪
Wait.
♪ This place of worship ♪
I'm here.
♪ Come undone ♪
♪ Shattered frame ♪
I'm here.
♪ No photograph
to look out for ♪
♪ I'll be your gold angel ♪
♪ If you want me ♪
♪ Baby, you want me? ♪
Hey, I think
that was once my jacket.
Sam.
- Hey, Gat.
- Hey.
Wow, this tailor did
good work.
I'm surprised Penny didn't just
throw all my stuff in a bonfire
the second she arrived, though.
The groundskeeper said
she should wait
until after we get some rain,
so...
didn't think you'd be here.
Ah, I love a Sinclair party.
Canapés, the cocktails,
the condescension.
How's our girl doing?
I don't really know.
That's no good.
Hey, wish us both luck.
- Pen.
- Sam.
Good of you to come.
Hey, Cady, sweetie.
Dad.
How good of you to come.
♪ Baby, you want me? ♪♪
♪ Ave Maria ♪
Dude, stop staring.
It's creepy.
Do you think heaven's real?
Uh, sure, I guess I do.
Seems fake to me.
Yeah, I mean,
if you're picturing
picnics on clouds
and togas and shit.
No, I think it's more like,
I don't know,
your favorite people,
your favorite food,
every pet you've ever had
licking your face
when you get home.
That's basically
our regular life.
But it's not everyone's life.
Heaven is for everyone, Will.
Not everyone.
If heaven's real, so is hell.
Um...I guess.
But Gran's not there.
I promise.
What is wrong
with your dress?
It's fine.
Heya, pal.
Sorry for your loss.
Why are you here, Beaumont?
My mom knew your grandmother.
Paul Revere chapter of the DAR.
She loved her like a mother.
That makes our situation
pretty fucked, huh?
Enjoy the service.
Thank you so much.
Now I'd like to ask
Tipper's husband,
Harris Sinclair,
to come forward
and say a few words.
So what did he say?
Harris?
A eulogy. It was good.
No, I mean Tipper
and our family.
What'd he say about them?
I'm not trying to avoid
telling you the truth.
I was so focused on my parents,
I really just don't remember.
Oh, oh.
Harris did that thing
that guys do in the movies,
you know, where he pulled out
his speech,
and then he put it
back in his pocket
and he spoke from the heart.
It was slick.
But, yeah, I...
I don't remember what he said.
Gat, you don't remember
any of it?
Honestly, Cady,
I just remember watching you.
Well, I hope
someone says something
memorable at my funeral.
I'll tell you
what I don't want.
A bunch of snobby
New York "art world" types
who don't even know me
standing around a room
talking about wine.
Yeah, and fake girls
being fake sad,
worrying about their lip gloss.
A bunch of people who just
show up so they can say
they went to a Sinclair party.
Religious people talking about
stuff I don't believe in.
But in my experiences,
all funerals suck.
No one's gonna notice if I go
back to Red Gate and read.
Uh, sure, yeah, you do you.
Thank you.
That is a parasol.
- Oh.
- For the sun.
UV rays and fillers don't mix,
you know.
She thought I was a butler.
Her third husband just married
her first husband,
so she's wrong about a lot.
- Your people are very strange.
- Yeah.
How did you end up so awesome?
Crystals and manifestation,
an adventurous lover all help.
Mm. Mm-hmm.
Yeah, I'm not awesome,
but I am OK because of you
swooping in like some big hero,
saving me all the time.
God, I have to go mingle.
Yeah, I can't rescue you
from that.
But you have my steel, milady.
Cady.
I'm really gonna miss Tipper.
Thank you so much, Judy.
So good of you to come.
Thank you.
- Are you hiding?
- Yeah, are you?
Yeah, kind of.
There's this guy
from a rival tennis team here
that I really
didn't want to see.
Our island's been invaded.
For real.
The sexter's here.
What? Where?
Is he hot?
Shh.
I feel like
he's gonna want to hook up,
and I still have no idea
what I'm doing.
No, he won't want to bone
at a funeral.
Ugh, there you are.
You left me out there
with the cheaters,
my dad and Gat.
And my mother.
It's officially
a quorum of cheaters.
Technically,
Gat didn't cheat on you.
He cheated with you.
What?
And we totally hate him for it.
Listen, change of subject.
Cadence, would you expect
sex at a funeral?
I guess people find solace
in unexpected places.
Like my vagina.
The sexter is here,
and I've had no time
- to work on my flexibility.
- Shit.
- That fucking guy.
- Oh, my God, it's happening.
Mirren, hi.
Hi.
I had no idea
that you were here.
Yeah.
This is Blake Beaumont.
These are my cousins,
Cadence and Johnny.
Yeah, we've met.
My condolences
to the both of you.
Mm.
Be gentle with her, Blake.
Hey, did you just
short-circuit?
No, I'm fine.
She really loved you both
so much.
Thank you.
No fucking clue who they are.
Well, you would if you watched
that Theranos documentary.
You handled that well, though.
Always perfect Penny.
Oh, perfection is unattainable.
At least that's what
I've been told
I'm supposed to pretend
to believe.
It's really annoying,
actually.
You've been at it
since the crack of dawn.
You still don't have,
like, a hair out of place.
Oh, hardly.
I mean, the dress needed
tailoring, and I didn't...
What the fuck, Penny?
- Keep your voice down.
- What?
No, we agreed that she would
be buried in those...
We didn't agree on anything.
We just didn't have the nerve
to tell Dad
that it was very obviously
a bad idea
feeding them to the worms.
Come on.
Fine, you can wear them
today, OK,
'cause you have been great
with the logistics
and everything like that.
But I will come
and get them tomorrow.
To borrow them from me?
No, you know
that she promised them to me.
Do you have that in writing?
Dad gave them to her
when she was pregnant with me.
That is why
they are so special.
No, they are special
because she let us wear them
when she was proud of us,
a little token
so she didn't have to say
"I love you" out loud.
Don't talk about her
like that.
Give them back, please.
They don't even go
with your aesthetic,
your whole faux bohemian,
"I went to rehab
in Santa Fe" thing.
Penny, give them back.
Guys, guys, Yardley is here,
and she is still wearing
those Doc Martens.
Ugh.
You're not gonna believe
what she did.
Bess is feeling a little
ignored by her husband,
so she killed a whole bottle
of the Chablis before 3:00.
Don't drag her into this.
Look.
She took the pearls.
I will fight you.
Oh, is this a Goldschere?
Tipper was
an early supporter,
and he never forgot it.
Still sends us
a Christmas card every year.
- I assumed he was Jewish.
- Well, he is.
But he knows that she isn't.
That she...that she wasn't.
She had exquisite taste.
She did, indeed.
Oh, while we're on the subject,
the deal for the Thornton
fell through.
Saudi oil money, my ass.
But the broker said
he could find another buyer.
I'm sorry, the broker?
For Tipper's father's painting.
Oh. Yeah.
I assumed you knew
she was selling it.
We went back and forth.
You know, sell it,
archive it, donate it.
I lost track
of where we landed.
Do you mind
refreshing me on the...
Gatwick?
Hi.
Are you coming,
or are you going?
Uh, both, I guess.
I just...I just wanted to say
how great your eulogy was, sir.
Moving, really.
Everyone hung on every word.
Thank you.
You're the first person
to say so.
Is there anything at all
that I can do?
Well, since you asked,
we put Franklin and Eleanor
in the laundry so they wouldn't
disturb things.
They'll need to be
let out by now.
Don't forget
to pick up after them.
People are wearing
Italian leather.
Sure.
It's quieter here.
Not that I'm, like,
trying to get you alone
or anything because that
would be super weird.
I recognize this view from
one of your paintings, right?
Yeah, sorry, I was stalking
your Instagram all summer.
What, were you hoping
for more thirst traps
than oil landscapes?
You know what?
I think you're really talented.
But I was hunting
for one bikini pic.
But that's because I was
on a yacht with my brothers,
and I was lonely.
The thing is,
I might be a little bit more
vanilla than my texts imply.
What, do you think
I came to the funeral
to hook up with you?
Is that why you swerved me
and hid in the curtains?
I came here today
because I wanted to see you.
That's it, OK?
No agenda.
Really?
Maybe it's OK if there's
a little bit of an agenda.
No, absofuckinglutely not!
Oh, my God.
- It is mine.
- What?
You cannot call dibs
on a catamaran.
Its name is the Elizabeth.
Yes, after Eliza Hamilton.
Then I get this statue.
- Mom said.
- No, she didn't.
You don't even have a lawn.
Why do you care?
The Goldschere is promised
to the Whitney.
Well, who the fuck is Whitney?
Keep you voice down.
We have guests.
We can pick the bones tomorrow.
Oh, says the literal
grave robber.
- Oh, my God.
- Oh, yeah.
You clutch those pearls, Pen.
Bess, where are you going?
To the jewelry box
before it's looted.
Is that your mom?
Oh, my God,
this is so embarrassing.
I'm so sorry. I...
Hey, hey, no, it's OK.
It's OK.
I get it.
Funerals are hard.
Families are weird.
It's cool.
You're cool.
Wait here really quick, OK?
I'll send for you.
Yeah, I wasn't
gonna go anywhere.
Cadence, I need a favor.
I need you to distract Blake
for 12 minutes
and then send him
to Cuddledown.
Do I want to ask why?
Because that gives me
enough time to make sure
that I smell of bergamot.
And then I can put
my matching lingerie set on
and hide all of those
self-help books.
Actually, make that 17.
I should shave, right?
Is that good? You got it?
Yeah?
- Mm-hmm.
- Please, please, please.
I love you.
Thank you.
You're an angel.
You're the best!
Thank you!
You did not bang the sexter
at Gran's memorial.
Don't judge me.
And no, I didn't.
I waited in my room forever,
shaved until I was as hairless
as a Thanksgiving turkey,
and the sexter
never showed, so...
oh, dude, come on.
- Go away.
- That is so annoying.
OK, let's go in.
I think we should paint
the Cuddledown walls.
It's looking weirdly patriotic.
Wait, wait, the sexter
bailing on Mirren,
was it my fault?
Did I get distracted
and forget to tell him?
It's not your fault. OK?
You're not always the bad guy.
This whole sad martyr thing
is not the vibe.
Blake Beaumont is a dick,
and Mirren found out
the hard way.
End of story.
Can we please just stop talking
about all this funeral shit?
Jesus!
You're just making me
more curious.
Yeah, Johnny,
this one's on you.
All right, fine.
You want to know everything,
fine.
Blake was preoccupied.
It's bullshit, OK?
You're using Mirren
to get at me
at my grandmother's funeral.
- Is that how it feels?
- How does that feel?
- Familiar.
- Stop.
- Stop coming at me.
- And if I don't?
Johnny.
I'm out.
You're bleeding.
I'm still sorry
about that whole thing, Mir.
It's fine.
It's not your fault
that he was using me
to get under your skin.
So I should have known
something was up.
He was way too perfect.
Nobody's that perfect.
You good?
Do you know
if a tall, handsome guy
in a dark blue blazer
left already?
I'm gonna need a name.
Blake Beaumont.
Oh, yeah, yeah,
I took the Beaumonts
back to Tisbury,
like, an hour ago.
Any chance his mom dragged him
kicking and screaming
while he begged
to say goodbye to me?
Don't worry.
You're better off.
The kid is not worth
all the perfume you got on.
For what it's worth,
definitely isn't worth
sending your nudes to.
What?
How the hell do you know?
Oh, no, look, I just drive
the water taxi.
People talk like I'm not even
there most of the time.
That kid was not subtle
about bagging a Sinclair.
He didn't bag me.
And you really shouldn't be
spying on people
that are paying you
for your services.
It's called discretion, Ebon.
- Ah.
- What?
No, it's just very special
you know my name.
You people usually don't.
You've been driving the boat
around for three summers.
Of course I know your name.
And now I also know
you're a creepy eavesdropper
who sniffs girls in distress.
And we won't be needing
your services any longer.
We'll call the Falmouth shuttle
from now on.
Ready? All right.
Good boy. Good boy. Good boy.
Ready? Ready?
Come on, come on, come on.
Here. Right there.
Go on.
Go fetch. Yeah.
♪ I was your first kiss ♪
♪ Riverside Brisbane ♪
♪ We were so timid ♪
I was trying to cheer them up.
♪ And shy ♪
I just want to do something
that helps someone.
♪ We kept each other
dreaming ♪
Well, you can give my dad
his box of junk from the attic
and tell him to go back
to his hotel.
He hates Beechwood
just as much as you do.
- I don't hate it here, Cadence.
- Why?
We're so cold and cruel
and casually racist.
You know you're shockingly good
at this whole
icy-cold Sinclair thing?
Yeah, you sound like my dad.
Great. Perfect.
Why don't you just box me up
and pretend I was never here
just like you're doing to him?
Look, that's why I didn't
tell you about Raquel.
I didn't want to get exiled.
You might think
I'm a terrible person,
but integrity matters to me.
And I hate cheaters.
And you made me one of them.
You made me the other woman
in your love story
with someone else.
And then you tried
to tell me it was my fault
because sometimes I forget
to thank the chef
for my orange juice, Gat.
I feel really bad
about the way that I said that.
The timing was...
I'm not mad at you
for saying it.
You were right.
Of course you were right.
I'm mad because...
when I saw you
writing that letter to Raquel,
I thought you were
writing it for me.
And it was like
something changed.
It was...
and now I feel so stupid.
I know. I know.
I know I fucked up.
And I don't blame you
if you don't forgive me.
Look, I want to be
a good person.
It's just...
...it's not easy
when I'm around you.
Oh, no.
Oh, come on.
What are you doing?
Grieving.
And the lip?
Uh, grieving with flair.
Hmm.
Hey, come on.
Mmm.
Don't give me that look.
On really shitty days,
we all have an excuse
to revert back
to our 16-year-old selves
for a bit.
You don't have
enough tits to fill it!
Case in point.
You started this
with that necklace.
Dad, will you talk
some sense into them?
What is this about?
The Grande Baroque sets.
And the Goldschere.
The Whitney has four of them.
I looked it up.
Well, your timing is perfect.
Thatcher and I, we were going
through your mother's records.
You remember her?
The blonde
that we laid to rest today?
Or perhaps she's just cash flow
and a coffin to you,
because her ledger is telling
quite the story.
Ah, there, peace and quiet.
All she ever really asked for.
You know, I always thought
that I'd be the first to go.
Shipwreck during
the Transatlantic race.
Learjet crash.
I pictured Tipper
getting a call.
I knew she'd be all right
eventually.
She'd have the three of you
rallying around her
with love and support.
But all the while,
her right ventricle
was making other plans.
And just as unexpectedly,
I find myself utterly relieved
that she went first
because it breaks my heart
to think that I would have left
Tipper alone
to be as deeply
and utterly ashamed
of you all
as I am now.
Her checkbook is closed now,
but I am still here.
And I will decide what to do
with the fortune that I built.
There'll be no more handouts,
not until I see
people worth my investment.
I sent you all out in the world
with generous trusts,
resources you were expected
to implement
to become a credit
to the family.
Do any of you believe
that you've added value
to the Sinclair name?
Daddy, for the record,
I've never personally
touched my trust fund.
So good of you all to come.
So s'mores?
Ugh, no.
I have a stomachache.
I'm glad we talked.
Hey, look, I know I didn't say
any of the right things
back then.
I wanted to make things better.
I wanted to see you
happy again.
I didn't need to be happy.
Not on that day.
And I heard
what I needed to hear,
just not from you.
You miss her.
I miss her too.
It's OK to cry.
Hmm? You cry it all out. Yeah.
She's always with you,
I promise.
Eleanor, Franklin,
let's go get a treat.
Come on.
She's sweet with them.
She told me to make my heart
a small target.
Well, those Sinclair rules
work for her.
I think she really believes
they help.
You know, Cady,
you're only half Sinclair.
And us Eastmans, we...
we get pretty sad.
We get pretty fucking angry
sometimes.
You can be angry with me
if you want.
You can yell at me.
You can scream at me.
I am angry.
But mostly,
I'm just sad.
Yeah.
Cady, I'm so sorry
that I let you down,
'cause I swear
I wanted the whole world
to be perfect for you.
I just hope maybe someday,
the good moments
that you and I have
will outweigh
the bad thing that I did.
And then...
you'll forgive me maybe.
Maybe.
Let it out.
That's a good dog.
Ay, ay, ay. Thank you.
Thank you.
Cady?
Do we forgive Gat?
Yeah.
We forgive him.
Bro.
Ahh.
OK, so...
is heaven a thing
in your religion?
Kinda.
Depends on your karma, I guess.
I'd explain,
but it's complicated.
And you generally hate
learning, right, so...
That's fair.
- Yeah.
I appreciate you.
Thank you.
Mm.
If heaven is a thing, though,
Gran's there, right?
She's watching over us, waiting
for Granddad to join her?
I don't know, I hope heaven
isn't just a waiting room
full of people
spying on their grandkids.
Yeah.
Maybe she's young again.
Maybe she's partying
with dead rock stars.
Maybe she's just being
impolite and improper
just because she can.
Maybe...
maybe heaven is different
for everyone, you know?
I think my heaven is like this.
No adults, no Littles, no drama.
Just the four of us
here by the ocean,
kind of tipsy...
...in a mythical land
where it's always summer.
- To Gran.
♪ The dawn is breaking ♪
Wait, you remembered us
from the rocks?
Cadence, I thought
you didn't remember
anything about that day.
The memories came back to me
in the rose garden.
I don't understand.
Why did you make us tell you
about things you already knew?
I had to find out who was
lying to me about last summer.
And now I know.
Blake Beaumont
wasn't hooking up with Johnny
when I found him.
That's not why he bailed
on Mirren.
No, it's bullshit.
You're using Mirren to get at me
at my grandmother's funeral.
Is that what it feels like?
Don't fucking touch me!
What are you gonna do,
killer, huh?
What, are you gonna ruin my life
like you did that poor kid?
That wasn't my fault.
There's video.
You almost murdered him,
you psychopath.
Leave my fucking family alone,
or I'll almost murder you.
Stop.
Stop!
Chill.
I got what I came for.
♪ You and me in paradise ♪
It's just dumb tennis shit.
You're bleeding.
Johnny was violent again.
It was prep school
rivalry shit.
It has nothing to do
with your accident.
Then why did he lie to me?
And why did Mirren
cover for him?
I mean, you're the only one
who told me the truth today.
So today was all a test.
This morning when you said
that you weren't feeling well,
you were playing me.
You remembered all along.
I need answers.
I need to see if all the lies
lead to me
on that beach alone.
I think Johnny and Mirren
know something.
Please, Gat, will you help me
figure this out?
Please.
You know, sometimes I feel like
I would do anything for you.
Like you're
my whole reason for...
I thought you were in pain.
That's why I agreed
to talk about the funeral.
And now I just...
I feel like an idiot.
Johnny and Mirren aren't
the only ones who lied.
You lied all day.
♪ Down sometimes ♪
To me.
♪ Seem to rhyme ♪
♪ Out of the doubt
that fills my mind ♪
♪ I somehow find ♪
♪ You and I collide ♪
♪ Standing on the edge
of your shadow ♪
♪ But the truth lies
in the echoes followed ♪
♪ In the silence
where the secrets lie ♪
♪ Will I ever find out why? ♪
♪ Oh ♪
♪ I'm standing on the edge
of your shadow ♪♪