Have you ever thought
that you're not remembering
for a reason?
That your mind is
trying to protect you?
My mind wants answers.
We are grieving.
We're just not good at it.
Grieving over a loss
or the fact
that she's not around anymore
to bail you out?
Aah!
Penny is spending
twice her budget,
and Bess is skating
along the edge of zero.
That money was
for our daughters.
How long have you
been robbing them?
Get the fuck off this island.
Ed just asked me
to marry him with Nan's ring.
I'm so, so sorry.
Do you hate me?
No, I think you're hot.
They're not
mutually exclusive.
Raquel wasn't here today.
You went to go pick her up
at the Vineyard.
I went to break up with her.
Do you remember
Johnny's tennis friends
- from last year?
- Who the fuck invited them?
Have you ever done
anything bad in your life?
I mean, like really bad?
There was an incident
at Johnny's school...
They fucking deserved it!
...the kind that you
would not like associated
with the Sinclair name,
and now I do need you.
She unlocked my phone,
and she gave it
to my mother, who does that?
Just tell me
the fucking truth!
You want to know
the truth, Cadence?
Maybe everything that happened
to you is my fault.
Cady! Somebody please
get some fucking help!
- Help us! Cady!
- Hey!
- Someone get help, please!
- Cady!
Are you crazy?
Yes, I kept some secrets.
I'm sick
of the fucking victim card!
Once upon a time,
there was a mythical land
where it was always summer.
There was a princess...
a cursed princess, I think.
Or maybe it...
Oh, here it is.
There was once
a three-headed serpent.
No.
There was once a wicked witch.
Yes, a witch.
No, there was once
a cruel prince,
used to having
his every whim indulged.
I'm so sick
of fucking fairy tales.
You look pretty.
My mom made me go
to Clairmont this morning,
dressed all respectably,
to tell Harris
how much I love
Gran's jade-jewelry collection.
Did you tell him?
He gave me this hairpin,
making it clear it's a gift
for me and not my mother.
Mom says she needs to get
back on his good side.
She, like, enlisted me.
So what are you, uh...
what are you doing up here?
The weather's
gonna turn soon.
Just thinking, I guess.
Ed finally left
last night.
He's at a hotel
at the Vineyard.
It's weird being here
without him.
I feel like
a stranger at Red Gate.
Everything just...
everything feels messed up.
Almost everything.
The universe
is really huge right now.
I need something
to hold on to.
Hey, kids.
Have you seen Mirren?
She's not at Cuddledown.
I thought that...
Is that my mom's hairpin?
I told my dad yesterday
that it was my favorite.
Who said that you
could have that?
♪ I was walking El Camino... ♪
God, I hate this.
♪ While the kids sang... ♪
Ah, for fuck's sake!
Break a nail?
What are you doing?
Trying to close
the lighthouse
so the rain
doesn't ruin all my...
All right, all right,
don't break the door.
What are you doing?
I'm, uh, helping.
♪ I hope will set me free ♪
♪ I just wanna be
happy, happy... ♪
- Wow.
- Eh.
So impressive.
I must have you now.
Well, you know, some girls
like a guy who can fix things.
Just saying.
Yeah.
Some guys like to fix things
that aren't broken.
Well, some girls don't know
how to say thank you.
Seriously,
what are you doing here?
Ah, I'm working-ish.
I just dropped your grandpa's
consiglieri off for lunch.
That's Thatcher, his lawyer.
Oh, sure, sure.
No, I went to take off,
but they, uh...
they ordered a shelter
in place, so I turned around.
I tied up
to your service dock.
So...
you want to?
Do I want to what?
Shelter.
♪ Happy ♪♪
Mom, when's
Ed gonna be back?
He said he'd take me
to get the new Zelda.
Uh, I can take you
when the weather clears.
But I want Ed to take me.
- I know...
- Lay off it, Will.
They broke up.
So when's he coming back?
- He's not.
- Johnny.
So learn to entertain yourself
for five seconds,
for fuck's sake.
Johnny, will you just stop?
Wash up for lunch.
I'm washed.
Don't be smart
with me right now.
He's gone, and you won't
even tell me what happened.
Was it because of me, Mom?
- Because you seem pretty...
- Johnny, just stop.
No. No, you don't get
to just let him leave
without telling us.
I get to do
whatever I choose.
I am your mom,
and I signed up for it.
But...
But Ed didn't.
What if I spoke to him?
Okay, I'll tell him
it was my fault.
And I'm gonna tell him
what happened at school.
No, you cannot tell anyone.
Do you understand me?
If you want to help,
you can prove to Harris
that you can be an asset
to the family.
He's the one keeping the roof
over our heads right now.
And if it ever got out
what you did...
he'd never forgive
either of us.
The land value
is skyrocketing.
We're sitting
on a gold mine.
Thatcher, you say that
every year, and every year,
my parents tell you they
would never sell Beechwood.
- Your mother said that.
- Of course she did.
It's your legacy
for your grandchildren.
Mmm.
Let me know if I can get you
anything else.
- Thanks, Lydia.
- Thank you, Lydia.
Where are the little ones?
Playing a board game.
Trying to keep them entertained
in this kind of weather
is a nightmare.
Oh, I can imagine,
with all the valuables around.
Huh.
Is that ivory?
They were my favorites.
Mom actually said that they
would be perfect for Red Gate.
Hold on.
There's no way
that she said that.
- That's not how...
- They belong where they are.
I am not dead...yet.
You will want to include them
in an asset inventory,
though.
- What asset inventory?
- Thatcher and I
have been going over
the estate plan.
Um, you're changing
your will?
To account
for new circumstances.
Isn't ivory illegal,
Granddad?
I don't mean
that illegal is a bad thing.
No, you just need
to know how to get it.
Never take no for an answer.
Yeah, this little slip
of a China girl
sold those to us in Shanghai.
Um, they're illegal
for a reason, right?
Um, maybe you could auction
the statues off
and use the money
and donate it
to a wildlife conservatory
or something.
Cadence, you're not to tell me
what to do with my earnings.
Your gran loved ivory.
And, luckily, Orientals--
they care far more about money
than they do legalities.
I mean, you...
you can't say "Oriental."
Oriental?
Or "China girl."
Hmm.
Oriental...
it's an academic term.
Just ask Edward Said.
Your generation is
so damn eager to be offended.
It's true.
Outrage addiction.
It's an epidemic.
I blame TikTok.
You could have had my back.
You know what he said
was wrong.
I didn't say it.
I didn't fucking say it, okay?
Also, it's not like
he's racist, okay?
He's just old.
You just need to stay
on his good side.
If he says the kids these days
are a bunch of woke freaks,
then there's no harm
in nodding and smiling.
Maybe this isn't
about Granddad.
You've been acting
like a jerk all summer...
picking fights, acting shady.
- Me acting shady?
- Yeah.
You two are acting shady.
Dude, don't yell at her.
What are you guys,
like, together now?
Cute.
Boys, the storm
is getting close.
Make sure
the boats are secured.
Yes, sir.
Can I help you
find something, Dad?
No flashlight batteries.
Oh.
Got them
from the service building
as soon as I saw
the forecast.
Mom always used to, so...
I was hoping to talk to you
about something important.
Brody and I...
Hey, Mom,
have you seen Will?
Um...No, no, no, no, no!
Do not get mud on Gran's rugs.
We need him.
Stormy weather is perfect
for summoning the ghosts
of the whaling captain's widow.
Well, I think
he's at Red Gate.
So go, go, go.
Go.
I presume
you claimed the rugs
in your sisters' battle
for heirlooms?
Well, I...
I do love them, but...
Anyway...
Listen, Daddy,
Brody needs to pay back
his clients
if he's going to stay
out of trouble.
What he's trying to stay out of
is federal prison.
What do you think
about all of us moving
into the Boston house
in the fall?
No, no, no, no.
I don't like noise.
It's so big,
and without Mom...
Dad.
Dad, look at me!
I didn't know
what was going on.
I had nothing
to do with it.
I don't know
which is worse,
the idea that I raised
a criminal or an absolute fool.
You loved him, too, Dad.
Because I trusted
your judgment!
Carrie, Penny, no,
but you I had faith in.
I...I was mistaken.
Penny.
Oh, uh, don't mind me.
I'm just going to give the dogs
their thunder pills
and put them
in the laundry room
so they don't pee
on that beautiful rug.
Cadence was entirely
out of line today...
in front of company.
I don't know what she's
reading, but I will...
Oh, she was just
trying to impress Gat.
Maybe you've been
too distracted
to notice them getting
all cozy this summer, Pen.
This is an interesting
spot for a studio.
I used to paint
in my grandmother's study,
but now it just feels
kind of weird.
I want to submit one
to the Sound's Edge Gallery.
That's where my grandmother
used to take me all the time
when I was little.
It's my favorite
one on the Vineyard.
Hmm. That's cool.
Hey, don't touch.
My medium
takes weeks to dry.
So should we just, um, take
our clothes off?
Oh, look at this.
This is the, uh...this is
the view from the ferry, right?
You know I'm not, like, trying
to go on a date or anything.
Yeah, it's pretty.
So, if you're gonna be here,
you might as well make
yourself useful.
All right,
I'm not a sex object.
- I need to be wooed.
- Oh.
Now shush.
I'm looking at art.
Well, what
do you think, then,
other than "pretty,"
"cool," grunt.
I mean, look, you're...
...very technically skilled.
- Technically skilled.
- Yeah.
So you think have
no imagination.
You think I'm a bored rich girl
who has a generic hobby.
I don't think that.
You think that?
Probably every night
just before I fall asleep.
I think art should be,
like, messy,
messy as people are.
I don't know.
I don't...
Maybe you don't have a mess.
Are you kidding?
You know my mom
is sleeping around on my dad,
who is a thief,
apparently.
But I blame my mother
because she's the one
that's so obsessed
with everything being perfect
all the time,
and perfect is expensive.
My whole family
didn't notice
I didn't show up
to lunch today...
which makes sense
'cause I'm practically
just the spare to their heirs.
Cady is, "Gat this, Gat that,"
all the time,
and I don't remember
the last time
she asked me anything
about my personal life.
I lost my virginity
to some random.
And my technically good
portfolio
is never gonna
get me anywhere!
Fuck!
You should wait out the storm
in the boathouse.
I would like to have my
temper tantrum alone, please.
Mirren.
What?
Oh, it's, um...
I don't....
Oh.
The person I was angry
with was myself.
Luckily, my sponsor picked up
on the first ring.
Thank you for sharing, Vanya.
Does anyone else
have anything?
Uh, I do.
Hi.
Fuck.
I'm sorry.
I'm on mute, I think.
- Um...
- You are not.
- Oh, good.
- - Go ahead.
Uh...
I'm Carrie.
I'm a drug addict.
Hi, Carrie.
I have, uh, ten years sober.
I have not been
to a meeting in ages.
Um...
But I really needed this.
This summer...
so far, I have lost
my mother...
and did things
with my partner...
not because I wanted to.
And it's all been really hard
on my sons.
Why are you so worried
about Harris's approval
all of a sudden?
I mean, you're like
the Sinclair golden child.
That's Cadence, okay?
I just get "first male heir"
bonus points.
I'm just trying to get
my shit together, okay?
How?
How do you plan to do that?
By turning
into your grandfather?
What?
Like that's a bad thing?
It's really not a good thing.
I get it, okay?
You don't like me
or my family anymore.
You think I haven't heard your
shitty comments all summer?
You went to India,
you got enlightened,
and now you're
too good for us.
Way to level up.
Fucking congrats!
That's not true.
You and the Liars...
No, you and I got thrown
together on an island
when we were
eight years old, Gat.
And little kids,
they make friends
based on proximity, right?
But let's face it, dude, we
don't have shit else in common.
If we met in school now,
we wouldn't even be friends.
I think eventually
we were gonna grow apart,
and I guess eventually
is now.
It's no big deal, dude.
You get the canoes
put away?
Uh...
yeah, the green one's
out there.
The red one
wasn't on the beach.
Listen, I'm sorry.
I...
Wait, what?
You sure it wasn't
under the dock?
No, just the green one.
Why?
- Oh, fuck!
- Dude, what? What?
Will, he...he wanted to go
off island this morning,
- and I blew him off.
- Fuck. Okay, go, go.
Shit!
Fuck!
Wait!
Hey, Mom.
Have you seen Gat?
No one was at the...
Do you have
mercury poisoning?
Huh?
Has the chef
over-shell-fished you?
I'm sorry, what?
Maybe you're a changeling.
Maybe while I slept,
an evil witch
swapped out my chronically
well-behaved kid
for a demon pain in the ass,
because my kid would never
intentionally provoke
her grandfather when
I specifically asked her...
The word he used was...
If one absolutely
must correct Harris Sinclair,
one does it
in absolute privacy.
And pro tip, Cady, you never
absolutely must correct him.
You are 16, and he is one
of Forbes most powerful.
I am trying to be
a better person.
- Ah.
- I'm trying to call out
injustice when I see it
and use my...
...privilege for good.
Oh, sweet, merciful Jesus.
Look, I get it, you know?
I was also an idiot
around cute boys
when I was your age.
I know you've been spending
a lot of time with Gat.
Yeah, every summer
for the last eight years.
You know, when I was your age,
my dad made a rule...
no boys overnight
on Beechwood.
Gat didn't count.
But, clearly, things
have changed between you.
Hmm?
Maybe with Ed gone, it isn't
appropriate for him to be here.
You can't send him away.
Sinclair ladies
have discretion.
And Bess saw you two
on the beach.
- Bess?
- Mm-hmm.
Wow. Okay, well, she's one
to talk about discretion.
Stop.
Sit.
Spill.
Oh, my God, I'm shaking.
You can do it.
Okay.
Yeah, there you go.
Yeah.
Oh, my God.
I love it.
Have I lost it?
I have absolutely snapped.
Ah, this one,
it's taken me so long,
with the underpainting
and the glow of the lights.
I feel like
I'll never be finished.
It's my masterpiece.
♪ Ten in the morning,
we woke up ♪
♪ Sleep-deprived,
but we made love ♪
♪ Don't know
who started touching who... ♪
There it is.
♪ There was a song
that we both knew ♪
♪ And now my eyes are closed,
but my body's walking... ♪
Whoa, whoa,
not the uniform.
♪ And even though
I'm scared of heights ♪
♪ I'm running
on this wire... ♪
Oh, you're a mess.
Yeah, I am.
♪ Get to know me... ♪
♪ Won't say I'm falling,
but I could ♪
♪ 'Cause who knows?
It could be good ♪
♪ Keep it simple ♪
♪ We'll let go a little ♪
♪ Won't say I'm falling,
but I could ♪
♪ 'Cause who knows?
It could be good ♪
♪ Won't say I love you,
but I could ♪
♪ Yeah, it could be good ♪♪
I bet Windemere
doesn't leak.
Just you and Cadence
in that big house
while I'm stuck
tripping over the twins
in this haunted shack.
It was my turn to renovate,
and you know it.
Well, if Dad
sells Beechwood,
Cuddledown would be
a tear-down anyway.
In the meantime, you could get
your roof fixed with a barter.
You know, trade your body
for a good caulking.
Excuse me?
Your side piece
is an actual handyman.
Put him to work.
Your daughter saw you
with Salty Dan.
Boobs out in the boathouse.
I mean, no mind
for discretion at all.
But if you ever...
throw my kid under the bus
to get into Dad's
good graces again,
ever...
I won't have
any discretion either.
Fuck, I don't see anything!
Wait. Ed's staying
at the Harbor Inn, isn't he?
Will couldn't make it
that far.
Don't...don't say that shit.
But he knows the sound.
He'd...
- Find shelter.
- Yeah.
The cove!
Go, go, go!
Look, I know earlier
I might have been a bit rude.
I understand you didn't intend
on being bigoted,
so I'm very, very sorry.
Annabelle!
I'm out
of St. Adaline Reserve.
I just restocked it,
Mr. Sinclair.
Well, it's not here.
One of your maids must take it
for their St. Adaline Reserve.
Watch the rug.
Mom loves it more
than she loves us.
Have you seen Will,
Granddad?
Uh...no, no,
not for some time.
- He's nowhere.
- He's somewhere.
It's an island.
We've literally
looked everywhere.
Annabelle...
have the staff fan out
along the perimeter path.
But...but do you think he's...
- Where are you going?
- The water.
William!
William, Johnny!
- William!
- Dad!
Dad, what on Earth
are you doing?
The boat's gone.
I think the boys are, too.
Call the Coast Guard
and the marina.
And find Tipper.
They've gone...
No, no, God damn it!
Carrie!
Find Carrie.
Go.
William!
- Oh, my God.
- Okay.
I'll sneak you up to my room,
and you can shower there, okay?
You know, I'm still not
a...a sex object.
No, you're my muse.
No, I'm serious.
I'm trying to be serious.
I like you.
I liked you
for some time...
for real.
- Ebon, you barely know me.
- I know you.
I've driven you
for three summers.
You're funny,
and you're interesting,
and you're so frickin' weird.
And I like it.
I like you.
So you were spying
on me, then?
Mirren Sinclair Sheffield!
Oh, sorry.
Hey, we were looking
at her paintings up there.
- You need to leave.
- Mom, this is Ebon.
Ebon, leave, please.
Thank you.
Now.
Yeah, I'll...I'll...
I'll see you around.
Aunt Carrie?
Carrie?
Carrie.
- Carrie.
- Yeah? Yeah. Yeah.
Will's missing.
The beaches,
we have to get to the shore.
No, we already checked.
They're not there.
Cady, call Ed.
Okay.
Johnny! Faster!
I see it. I see...
Okay.
Please be okay. Please be okay.
Please be okay.
Whoa! Hey!
- What happened?
- I don't know! It won't move!
The propeller's
caught on something!
I...I can't get
the boat close enough.
Fuck!
- I'll jump in.
- No! Stay with the boat!
What are you doing? Wait!
Hey!
I'm on the fucking swim team.
Oh, come on!
Will! Will!
Will. Will.
Johnny!
- I'm sorry.
- It's okay. It's okay.
You're gonna be okay.
Here, put this on.
No, it's okay. It's okay.
You're gonna be okay.
You're okay, buddy?
You did good.
You did really good.
- Okay, okay.
- I'm really tired.
It's okay.
I've got you. It's okay.
Are you trying
to ruin my life?
I'm guessing that's
a rhetorical question.
My entire life is
about making things perfect
for other people.
I drive you to art class.
I pack your sister's lunch
and recitals
and field hockey games
and...and charity galas.
Oh, the galas, the galas.
They must be awful.
But the one time that
I do something that I want,
the one fucking time...
My private life
is not your gossip fodder.
Is this about Salty Dan?
Oh, my God.
If you need some me time,
get a hobby.
What?
Finish your degree maybe
or divorce dad
and then run away to Paris...
Oh.
...because at least
there's honor in that.
Cheating on him in open air
isn't self-care.
It's fucking disgusting!
God damn it!
If Penny doesn't spill
this to Harris
in some self-righteous fit,
she's gonna hold this
over my head
until we are in our grave!
Cady fucking told.
Your grandfather was
our only way out of this mess
that your father made.
What do you think
happens next, Mirren?
You think you're gonna go
to art school
when we are tens of millions
of dollars in debt?
That money was
your only ticket.
You are nothing
without it.
- None of us are! Oh!
- No!
God damn it!
You are not an artist!
You are a dilettante!
And you're a child!
I'm your child!
I didn't ask for you
to waste your life on me!
And neither did the twins!
You chose to be a mother.
You chose.
It's not our fault
that you decided
to hate it.
No!
Oh!
Jesus Christ!
Will, listen to me.
Keep the vest on.
Swim to...
Swim to Gat, okay?
- Gat!
- Go.
Don't leave me!
Johnny!
- Johnny!
- Can't reach!
Johnny.
Hang on to the ring,
all right?
Don't let go!
I'll pull us in.
It's okay.
I'm sorry, I can't.
It's not safe.
Then give me your keys and tell
your boss I stole the boat.
I can't. It's not safe.
- I'm sorry.
- Leave him alone.
Hey, Mirren,
Gat and Johnny are...
Oh, Gat. Shut up about Gat.
I don't care about his drama.
- No, you're not listening.
- I've heard it all summer!
- You're not listening.
- I've been there!
And I kept your secrets.
And the one time I tell you
something in confidence,
you go and tell
your mother?
- Mirren, they are...
- You're such a selfish bitch.
- They are gone, Mirren.
- Who? Who?
Gat and Johnny, the boys.
They took the boat,
and Will is missing.
Hey, they're fine.
They're good. The three
of them, they're all fine.
Coast Guard's got them.
They're fine.
This selfish bitch
better go tell everyone
our family didn't drown.
Fuck.
You're scared of me.
I don't remember
what I'm scared of.
Your mom has your pills.
She's worried about you.
We all are.
Look, I'm sorry
for yelling at you.
I'm sorry for everything.
But I don't know how you
ended up in the water,
and I don't know
how you got hurt,
but I know I didn't hurt you,
that is the truth.
Then why lie?
Come on.
Look, I did some things that
I don't want to talk about,
but it has nothing
to do with you, I swear.
Wait.
What did I miss
while I was out of it?
Well, um...
the sexy air-ambulance guy
who strapped you
to a gurney, for one,
the Vineyard Regatta,
Tisbury Street Fair.
We jumped Sunset Bluffs.
That was a rush.
Also, Mirren's art has been
considered for a gallery.
She's so nervous, she puked.
Maybe you can hype her up
a little.
What about Gat?
He's moping around,
reading sad poetry.
Okay.
Okay?
I don't think
you're a psychopath.
I don't think you're any
of the things I said you were.
Whoo!
Mirren, are you okay?
You look a little pale.
This is such a bad idea.
And it's making me
nauseous, so...
It'll be fun.
All right, who's
jumping first?
Nope. No, no.
Nobody's jumping, right?
Too dangerous.
- What?
- No, no, no, wait.
Johnny said you all jumped
while I was sick,
one of the many things
I missed out on.
Or was that a lie?
No, once is enough.
And there are rocks, Cady,
and you're not feeling well.
I feel better, actually.
I don't want to be
the only one missing out.
Cady, don't.
Please, don't...don't do it.
Don't do it, for me.
Don't be
such a buzzkill, okay?
Like, we're here.
Even the moms jumped
when they were teenagers.
They didn't have
brain trauma.
Doesn't matter, okay?
If you're precise and you go
exactly when that wave comes
and you jump where it's deep,
then it's fine.
Okay, Cady?
You're fine.
Johnny, can I talk to
you for a second, please?
You know what?
It wasn't even that fun.
Honest.
Whatever happened to Ebon?
He's not driving
the water taxi anymore.
I-I thought I told you.
I'm seeing someone new.
Ebon was...whatever.
It's making me so queasy.
Your stomach hurts
when you have a secret.
You've been sick.
That's what you just said.
You said you were done asking
about last year.
We've all been
saying things.
♪ Once you told me ♪
♪ Look for the North Star ♪
♪ And you'll see ♪
♪ Heavenly ♪
♪ I hear ♪
♪ Found my way ♪
♪ To the beach ♪
♪ There were waves... ♪
Damn it, Cadence!
I said be precise.
Come on, let's go.
Jesus Christ.
♪ ...at sea ♪
♪ Till you found me ♪
♪ Oh, oh, oh, oh ♪
♪ Heavenly... ♪
I'm gonna go wait
by the dock.
No. Come on, don't run.
No, look,
the Coast Guard said
they'll bring them back
when it's safe.
Keep your chin up.
It's gonna be okay.
Okay.
♪ I was found lost at sea... ♪
- Mom. Mom!
- Oh, thank God.
- Will!
- Thank God.
- Oh.
- Holy shit.
- Are you okay?
- Oh, God.
I'm so sorry.
I've got you.
- What happened?
- I'm sorry.
♪ Lost at sea... ♪
- How did you...
- Doesn't matter. They're safe.
Are you all right?
♪ Ah, ah ♪
Well, can we, uh...
can we get you something?
Oh, the boat's waiting
for me to get back.
You sure?
I'm sure.
Ed.
Thank you.
- Johnny.
- Hey, Granddad.
Don't ever, ever,
ever do that again, okay?
I won't.
Come on, let's get you warm.
It's all yours.
Gat, um...
...I would have been fucked
today without you.
Hey, what the hell
happened out there?
You just gave up
once Will was safe.
Just tell me what's going on.
Beaumont and his teammates
pissed in our lockers
during a tournament.
Okay, gross.
And?
And I decided to get revenge.
There was a cold snap,
and so I rented a water truck
with my emergency AmEx.
Fuck, how much
did that even cost?
We flooded
their indoor courts.
We left all the doors open
so the breeze would come
through and it would ice over.
And then this kid...
Seb Delgado,
busted us,
and I, uh...
and I kicked his ass.
And I left him there...
in the fucking cold.
And I wasn't thinking
about the cold.
When I found out
he was in the hospital,
I called my mom,
and...
she fixed it.
All our matches were canceled
for the ice,
but Seb didn't narc on me.
She paid him off?
- Yeah.
- Jesus.
His family, h-his teammates,
the paramedics.
But Beaumont has a video,
and it'll go viral...
if I don't pay.
Harris Sinclair's heir
destroying the family name.
Look, it was an accident.
An accident?
Are you even listening to me?
The team wanted to run.
I wanted to stay.
I wanted to fight.
I don't know why.
Delgado's a good kid.
He's a scholarship kid,
kind of kid that you'd want
to be friends with, Gat.
But I, um...
I don't know.
I saw red.
I remember
when I was little, my, uh...
when my dad would flip out
on my mom and I,
that's what she used to say.
She used to say, um...
just go
to your room, Johnny.
It's okay. He's just...
he's just seeing red.
Johnny,
you're not your dad.
Yeah, I'm not
Harris Sinclair either.
I'm the shitty thing
in between.
I'm not a good person.
I'm fucked up,
and I'm pissed off,
and I'm...I'm privileged
in all the worst ways.
And, yeah, you've been right
about me all summer.
Johnny...
So, Dad, I read Cadence
the Riot Act, obviously.
She does know better.
Oh, Cadence was
very helpful today.
Oh.
She's a responsible
young woman.
Here you go, Dad.
- You want anything else?
- No, thank you.
Okay.
Hi.
Um, Annabelle said
to tell you
that she found your gin
in Gran's closet.
It's not opened.
I swear.
Johnny, you
really scared us today.
You really should
have found an adult.
Oh, time was crucial.
Johnny did just
as I would have.
It was admirable.
Thank you, sir.
Carrie...
Hmm?
...why are you wearing
the pearls?
Have you had those
this whole time?
I was, um, putting
Nan's ring back in Mom's...
- with her things, and I...
- Carrie.
I forgot.
I didn't mean to keep it on.
Oh, Christ, while your kids
went missing.
It wasn't her fault, actually.
It was me.
I'm the reason Will ran off.
And I didn't save him.
I wasn't admirable.
I wasn't strong enough.
And I forgot the water safety
you taught us, Granddad,
but Gat remembered.
And Ed ran to the pier, and he
caught the Coast Guard leaving.
He showed them where
he thought Will would be
from all the times
he took us out canoeing.
Ed and Gat saved us both.
I just screwed up.
Um...
that's the truth.
I thought I saw
you come in here.
Emergency fruit delivery.
Fuck.
What happened in here?
And the spousal support?
Yes, I understand.
Um...
...Sam's investigator
is digging up old skeletons.
Yes, enough.
Thatcher, I am not paying you
to list my various sins.
I was present
when they were committed.
I am paying you
to make them go away.
Mm-hmm.
Hmm.
I'm gonna do better, Mom.
I promise.
I know.
Hi.
Gat.
Are you okay?
Yeah, it...
it's just a rope burn.
Ow.
I don't want to talk
to you right now.
I don't know what
you were trying to do all day,
but, fuck, I am so fucking done
with being scared for you.
When you have amnesia,
memories can get triggered
by your own body chemistry
if you're in the same
physical state as you were
when the trauma happened.
The same heart rate,
the same adrenaline rush
can bring you right back
to that moment.
So, to remember
the accident,
you wanted
to nearly drown again?
I wanted to see if it would
work, but it didn't.
The more you remember,
the worse you get.
I sat by your bed
while you had fever dreams
- and you took pills.
- I didn't ask you to be there.
Where the fuck else
am I going to be, then?
I don't know.
Where were you all year
- when I needed you most?
- It keeps coming back to this.
It'll always come
back to that, Gat.
I didn't just come
back here
because I wanted to know
how I got hurt.
I came back here
because I needed to know
why you didn't care
about me anymore.
How...how can you say that?
You know...
I don't know anything.
- You know how I feel.
- I don't.
I don't remember.
Fine. Maybe you don't remember,
but you must feel it.
I feel it
when we're together.
I...
Cady, I feel all of it.
I was...
I was so scared
I was gonna lose you.
You...you won't lose me.
I feel like I am...
...because you don't love
this place anymore.
You want more.
And you should.
You want
different summers.
- I don't blame you.
- Cadence.
I want you.
You said you hated
yourself for it.
I didn't mean it.
I hate myself
for a lot of things...
stealing from a bodega,
being a burden
to my mom...
being with Raquel, even though
I never stopped missing you.
I don't hate myself
for loving you.
You know how I feel.
♪ We got to keep it going ♪
I...
love you.
♪ Couldn't see it coming,
and time is always running ♪
I love you, too.
♪ It feels like a fire
is rising ♪
♪ I want to be alone,
try to keep it whole ♪
♪ Couldn't see it coming ♪
♪ And time is always running ♪
♪ It feels like a fire ♪
♪ Is rising ♪
Uh, just give me
a second here.
♪ And if it all goes away ♪
♪ Will you run and hide? ♪
♪ Go beyond the side ♪
♪ Everything can fade ♪
♪ Don't want to see
the signs ♪
♪ Are we gonna fight? ♪
♪ And if it all goes away ♪
♪ Will you run and hide? ♪
♪ Go beyond the side ♪
What?
Are you sure?
Yeah, I'm sure.
♪ Don't want to see
the signs ♪
♪ Are we gonna fight? ♪♪
♪ Stare into space ♪
♪ Out in the blue ♪
♪ My favorite place ♪
♪ Lying with you ♪
♪ And I'll always be ♪
♪ Your shadow ♪
♪ Take a photo ♪
♪ Make it real ♪
♪ You're the stardust ♪
♪ Stardust ♪
♪ Lighting the field ♪
♪ You're the only thing ♪
♪ That matters ♪♪