Cadence was
entirely out of line today.
She was just trying
to impress Gat.
Maybe you've been
too distracted
to notice them getting
all cozy this summer, Pen.
My mom made me go
to Clairmont this morning
dressed all respectably.
Mom says she needs to get
back on his good side.
Bess saw you two on the beach.
Wow, OK.
Well, she's one to talk
about discretion.
Your daughter saw you
with Salty Dan.
Cady fucking told.
You think you're gonna go
off to art school
when we are tens of millions
of dollars in debt?
No!
If you want to help,
you can prove to Harris
that you can be an asset
to the family.
He's the one keeping the roof
over our heads right now.
I came back here
because I needed to know
why you didn't care about me.
You know how I feel.
I don't! I don't remember.
I love you.
I love you too.
Tell me a story.
You're the writer.
I want to hear
what you come up with.
OK.
Once upon a time,
there was an island kingdom,
a mythical land...
...where it was always summer.
Mm, that's the one.
One day, a boy arrived
from a realm of noise and color
and buildings
that scraped the sky.
In his world, he was a knight.
But on the island,
he learned for the first time
that he was a mouse.
We brought Ed's nephew, Gat.
The poor kid stowed away
behind the captain's chair
the whole time.
And he felt
very small indeed,
until he met a princess.
Are you real?
I think so.
You're it!
And along with the princess
came more royalty.
And soon,
the mouse called them friends.
Liars forever!
The mouse thought
the princess was perfect.
He wanted to follow her
everywhere.
But she was royalty.
The mouse didn't belong
in her palace.
The annual Sinclair
family lemon hunt
will commence momentarily.
- OK.
- Come on!
Oh, you were gonna tell him
about the dress code.
I know. I'm sorry.
I completely forgot.
All right, all right.
There are 200 lemons
and one lime
hidden across the island.
The hunt begins at the bell.
And do you want to hear
about the prizes?
Yeah!
OK.
For the lemons,
a gift certificate
to the Edgartown Bookstore.
And for the lime,
it's a top-secret surprise.
It's fudge.
It's always fudge.
Now, there are none that
will endanger you to retrieve.
All right?
None on rooftops,
none in brambles.
And no child may
go swimming alone,
or your prize
will be forfeited.
But the losers are fed
to the sharks.
Yeah, no failures allowed
on Beechwood.
♪ The wild wind
upon my skin ♪
The mouse grew to love
the princess fiercely.
♪ Running through
the field together ♪
♪ The future
at our fingertips ♪
But the princess's
family wouldn't stand for it.
"He's only a mouse,"
the king said in disdain.
Watch yourself, young man.
Or you could get hurt.
The entire kingdom whispered,
"An animal masquerading
as a human...
it's unnatural."
But luckily, Orientals care
far more about money
than they do legalities.
That's the thing about
mythical island palaces.
Even the most important rulers
tend to be afraid
of tiny mice.
♪ Underneath... ♪
But the mouse could
stand anything
if he was with the princess...
♪ Anything is possible ♪
...and so he stayed...
♪ We can make it beautiful ♪
♪ This hope ♪
Ah!
...and stayed...
♪ Is frozen ♪
♪ Oh, but the world outside ♪
...and stayed.
♪ Is wide open ♪
♪ I feel my cold heart
caving in ♪
♪ I see the daylight
breaking through ♪
♪ We'll make it
out of the dark ♪
♪ We can follow the stars ♪
He tried to drown out
the whispers.
♪ Feel it all with you ♪
♪ Oh, oh ♪
♪ Feel it all with you ♪♪
So Harris found out about us,
and he scared you away,
and that's why
you didn't call all year.
No.
No, I was ready
to explain it to him,
to tell him I loved you.
But...
...he never mentioned it.
For a while,
I thought I got it wrong.
Cadence Sinclair Eastman!
Oh, shit.
Shit, shit, shit, shit.
Oh, God. OK, wait.
Uh, shit, my mom...
she can't see this place
like this.
She'd freak out.
- I gotta go.
- Cadence!
Cady, listen.
I'm coming!
Bye!
He stayed so long,
the mouse began to forget
he had been a knight once
somewhere else.
You can't keep hanging
around Cuddledown.
With Bess and the girls
staying with Harris,
it ought to be condemned.
It has, like,
one creaky floorboard.
Your granddad wants you
at breakfast.
You need to connect
with the family,
put on a smile.
I'm not hungry.
I don't care.
Hey! Hey! Hey!
My friend Alice just called.
She was on a charter
to Nantucket yesterday
and saw you literally
jump off a cliff.
You will have breakfast
with your family,
and then you are going
to go to your room and think,
because you are grounded.
Oh, so now this whole place
is like a prison or something?
Yeah, correct,
with five beaches,
unlimited crab cakes,
and an on-call tennis pro.
And I am the warden
who won't let her child
indulge a death wish.
What a tyrant.
I should call Dr. Moriarty,
have him put you
on some kind of hold.
You are not OK.
Cadence, leaping to your death?
What did Grandad do when
he found out about me and Gat?
I made that jump because I was
trying to trigger memories.
Oh, my God.
Who knows what
I'll have to try next
if you don't just tell me?
Cadence.
I mean,
could someone have hit me?
Was I the victim of a crime?
Crime? On Beechwood?
Come on, Cady.
Did Harris freak out?
Did he find me and Gat together
and then push me head-first
into the sea, half-dressed?
I mean, what happened
the night of my accident, Mom?
Just tell me!
I have told you!
I have told you
everything that I know
over and over again,
every day in the hospital,
every time you asked!
And every time,
you had an episode,
you got so sick,
and then you slept,
and then you woke up,
and you asked again!
I am your mother, Cady.
You can't...
you cannot ask me
to cause you pain.
You are doing this
to yourself, Cady.
It is your own broken brain
that is the enemy
you are raging against, not me.
You're lying.
I don't believe you.
Just go to your room.
Making an escape?
You wanna drive?
Still no.
Always no.
All right.
Whoa.
Where are you headed?
I need to get online.
At least Google
can't gaslight me.
New Clairmont has Wi-Fi.
New Clairmont has my mother.
You can't look at screens
without having a whole episode.
OK.
Then I'll have an episode, Gat,
a level 11 meltdown
in front of all of Edgartown.
I will puke
and foam at the mouth
and give them even more
to gossip about.
Are you coming?
♪ Let's all go
to a different ♪
Gat!
♪ World ♪
♪ You look so good ♪
♪ Come on, let's go ♪
♪ Let's go ♪
♪ Let's all go... ♪
This is my favorite day
of the summer.
Yeah, I know,
because of your straight-up
scary competitive streak.
You love it.
All right, all right, hold on.
I got you something.
"Cady, I thought nothing
was better than chocolate.
Silly me."
"Love, Gat."
Hey, Gat.
Harris wants to talk to you.
He's in his study.
What?
Why?
The silent treatment? Still?
Yeah, if I'm silent,
it's so that you don't go
blabbing my business
to the whole fucking
universe, Cady.
It's fine.
I'll go talk to Harris.
Yeah.
Hello, young man.
Close the door.
What do you think?
I'm not really a gun guy.
No, me neither.
I had Senator Carlisle
barred from poker night
when he took that NRA money.
Yeah, but this...
this isn't just a gun.
This is history.
Philip Schuyler gave this
to Hamilton.
Recently came up at auction.
Listen, Mr. Sinclair,
I'm sorry if...
Sit.
So, young man,
what are your intentions?
My what?
In life.
Your value on this planet.
Mm, I'd like to be
a journalist.
- A foreign correspondent...
- Oh.
...actually.
Is that right?
It's important work.
Grueling.
At times, dangerous.
Not for the faint of heart.
I know that, sir,
but I want to tell
the untold stories,
stories that don't make it
across oceans.
I want to give people a voice.
Ambitious.
Dad?
Oh, we have a visitor.
Oh, indeed.
Come in.
Hello. It's me.
I'm the visitor.
Uh...
Nice sweater, kiddo.
Mom.
Well, don't I get a hug?
- Hi.
- Honey.
Hello.
God, I really hoped this
tradition would die with Mom.
The silent treatment?
Still?
You threatened to expose me.
Oh, Bess.
I mean, technically, you...
...exposed yourself.
Come on, it was friendly fire.
Yeah, friendly now,
because with
my husband's implosion
and Carrie nearly letting
the two male heirs drown,
you're Dad's favorite again.
Eh. That was short-lived.
Last night, he informed me
that I have failed to protect
his precious first grandchild.
Protect her from what?
I'm not complaining.
They dropped me off
at the service dock,
so I haven't seen any...
Holy fucking shit.
♪ Turn around and enjoy ♪
♪ Enjoy the view ♪
♪ 'Cause you got the whole ♪
♪ Wide world
in front of you... ♪
It's not always like this, Mom.
It's the...
the...the lemon hunt.
Not a normal Tuesday.
And how often are
Tuesdays normal?
Hi. I'm...
Cadence!
Oh.
Gosh.
You're a beauty in pictures,
but man,
you're a stunner in person.
I'm Maya, his beloved mother,
since he's forgotten
his manners.
Sorry about crashing the party.
Oh, the more, the merrier.
Come on.
Show me all the different
yellow food items
while we gossip about my son.
♪ The whole wide world ♪
♪ In front of you ♪♪
So what's the plan?
Google "Sinclair secrets"
and hope for the best?
You said you don't know
what happened to me
alone in the water that night.
And I don't.
Then nothing that I find out
will change the way
I feel about you, Gat.
Do what you need to do.
I'm here.
Here goes nothing.
Hey, hey. Cady, you OK?
Hey.
I got you. I got you.
I got you.
Uh...
people are staring.
Maybe we should save this
for later?
We can come back
before closing.
And until then?
♪ You say I've got ♪
Thank you.
♪ A reckless streak... ♪
Ice cream is always the cure.
Thank you.
This is kind of like
our first real date, no?
Yeah.
And kind of like our millionth.
What if my mom wasn't totally
wrong about me losing my mind?
I mean, maybe
there's always been
something a little off
about my brain.
You just need
more time to heal.
That's it.
But I'll be here with you,
as long as it takes.
Mm, the knight mouse will be
missed by his family
if he never leaves
the princess's side.
My mom is highly adaptable,
so we're good.
She visited last summer.
Do you remember any of that?
Kind of.
Mm, the lemon hunt.
Mm, yeah.
I suddenly saw Beechwood
and the whole Sinclair thing
through her eyes.
It was a lot.
All right.
Gather round, everyone.
All right. Excited?
The time has come.
All right now.
As usual, there are
200 lemons hidden and one lime.
None on rooftops
or in brambles.
Mm, those are the old rules.
This time, all's fair.
No rules.
It's like an Easter egg hunt.
Thank you.
- Sounds incredibly...
- Now...
...wholesome.
...for the prizes.
The one who finds
the most lemons
will win the Boston house.
Are you OK?
Sorry, just choked
on my edible orchid.
And should you find the lime,
I will name you
the sole recipient
of Beechwood upon my death.
- Dad.
- No.
What? Is he joking?
We'll begin on my signal...
...and you'll know it
when you hear it.
And for now...
Is he serious?
...enjoy the food.
You'll need your strength.
Dad.
Come on.
So like an Easter egg hunt.
That's not usually
what happens.
Cadence. Cadence.
Come here. Excuse me.
- Cadence.
- Mom.
It's OK. Come here, come here.
Listen to me. Listen to me.
We are at a disadvantage
because there are
only two of us.
Let go of my arm.
Look, we don't need
an entire island.
We have Windermere.
Oh, babe, did you know
your grandfather has
two brothers?
No.
Because Harris inherited
the island,
and he exiled his brothers.
I mean, do you think that
when Johnny is 60
and he has his own grandkids
filling up the place,
he's going to want
to invite you and yours?
Will Mirren?
Mom, that's, like,
a million years away.
Yeah, well, time flies.
Come on, you think
I haven't noticed
you've been avoiding
your cousins?
What, is there tension
in Liar Land?
Childhood friendship
only lasts so long.
Then you remember
that you're a family.
Some part of you must
want to see their faces
when you beat them.
Mom, what is Maya doing here?
I don't know.
She always turned down
our invitations.
Then today,
she texts from the marina
she's here, so I sent a boat.
It's very awkward.
Well, yeah.
You did dump
her dead husband's brother.
Listen.
The lemons...
A win for you or me or Will,
it could actually set us free.
It could.
Just try.
OK.
And island for a lime?
That's the craziest thing
I've ever heard.
And I hear a lot of shit.
I know.
Psychological warfare.
And I don't wanna play.
Yeah, yeah.
On one hand, I get that.
On the other hand,
you could go to sleep tonight
owning all this.
No, not me.
I don't think
I've ever won ever.
I'm always out-strategized.
And plus, when I fail today,
it'll just give my mom
another reason to hate me.
You know, what your mother did
was fucked up.
But in my experience,
everyone's fucked up
in one way or another.
And hurt people hurt people.
And if someone doesn't break
that cycle of hurt,
then it just goes on forever.
At least, it did in my family.
So, you know, you could...
you could reason
with your mother.
Just saying you could.
Or you can say fuck it.
I'll call out of work later.
You come over
to the seasonal worker bunks,
use me as a sex object.
Mm.
Yeah, abandoning the lemon hunt
would definitely be
the ultimate act of rebellion.
Before this summer, I never
actually wanted to rebel.
I wanted to be
the perfect Sinclair,
like my mom,
like Cady.
I try so hard, but...
they seem to only notice
when I mess up.
I could kill anyone who made
you feel like that, Mirren.
Yeah, you probably could.
You're really muscly.
OK.
All right, all right.
Look, so here it is.
You talk to your mother,
you run away
with the water taxi driver,
or there is a third option.
I fling myself into the sea.
Show your mom
she's wrong about you.
You find all the motherfucking
citrus on this island.
Can we still do that
other thing tomorrow?
Yes.
Yep, that's his new bell.
God.
Right. Right.
Well, yeah.
Tomorrow's great.
Good. Yeah, great.
Go on.
I'll find these fucking lemons.
- Do it.
- I swear to God.
♪ Oh, oh, oh ♪
♪ I am always screaming
in your room ♪
♪ We know it echoes
in the house ♪
♪ But we do not give
a shit because ♪
I see one!
♪ Your parents are
pretty chill about it ♪
♪ But when I'm eating dinner ♪
♪ With your parents ♪
♪ And they are
going on and on ♪
♪ About the Dom Pérignon ♪
♪ Well, I don't know
if I can do this because ♪
♪ Fuck the bourgeoisie ♪
Ah! Ah!
Ah.
♪ Marx is my new daddy ♪
♪ Fuck the bourgeoisie ♪
♪ I mean, I did, I did ♪
♪ I did, I did ♪
♪ I did, I did... ♪
All right, Littles. Listen up.
What will you even do
with a dusty old house, hmm?
But if you give me your lemons,
I'll give you
whatever you want.
William.
William, William, William.
That mega sprayer Nerf gun?
Mom says it perpetuates
American violence worship.
But I'm not Mom.
I'm your desperate
delinquent brother.
Pleasure doing
business with you.
Good boy.
Lemons, basket.
Liberty,
I know that Bess took away
your limited edition
Hailey Bieber peptide lip tint.
I'll get you five.
Throw in a pound of fudge.
Money in the bank.
Put it right there.
Thank you.
Lemons, basket.
Bonnie.
Bonnie, Bonnie, Bonnie.
Let's do this.
What do you need?
I want a sacrificial
altar knife for my spells.
♪ I did, I did ♪
OK, deal. Great.
Let's do this.
♪ I did ♪♪
Should we?
Sinclairs are
really competitive,
so I usually sit it out.
Have you ever won?
The first year,
I found the lime.
Johnny cried, though.
So Harris decided
to split the fudge
on account
of suspected cheating.
- Oh, Gat.
- Oh, whatever.
It's fine.
It's just candy.
Gat, can we acknowledge
how absolutely batshit
these people are?
Trading mansions as if
they're Monopoly properties?
Mom, they're not
always like this.
And they're not all like this.
I swear.
This isn't normal.
When Ed first brought you here,
I was in a bad place.
Still figuring out how to exist
without your father.
I thought it would be good
if you got away from me.
Look, I'll admit,
having you here, away
from our sticky, tiny apartment
in the summer months,
it helped.
And you looked so happy
in those pictures.
But this?
This is like some Knives Out
meets Get Out shit.
Look at you.
You're wearing pastels.
You're talking different.
You're not wearing
the earring I hate.
You're code switching
because you don't belong
with these people.
Mom, I know that.
What, you think
I don't know that?
I just don't care.
I'm sorry.
I want to be where Cady is.
No, no. Don't you dare!
Don't you...
Oh, my God!
There's no hitting
in the lemon hunt.
Well, technically,
that was Mom's rule.
Dad apparently has
chosen violence.
Still, have some decorum,
Penny.
Oh, unclench, Bess.
Clearly, your fishmonger
is doing a terrible job
of clearing out your cobwebs.
Salty Dan?
You didn't.
Mirren saw.
- She didn't.
- Mm.
I'm not the one who spent
the early aughts
sucking dealer dick for coke.
Stop.
Yes, Bess, stop.
Carrie scored the classy way,
doctor hopping
and raiding medicine cabinets
at dinner parties.
Would you just shut up,
both of you?
I'm so sick of you
belittling my sobriety.
The addiction was not my fault.
They teach you that
at Silver Hill
or at the Newport Institute
for Change?
Actually,
I learned that from Ed
when I learned that I was
capable of being happy.
But that's a foreign concept
for the two of you.
I'm perfectly happy,
thank you very much.
You can't stand yourself.
Neither can you.
I'm perfectly confident
in who I am.
Yeah?
Because from here,
it seems like you spend
half of your time
trying to be our mom
and the other half trying to be
a dead 11-year-old girl.
So who are you?
Oh, I'm sorry.
Do you want me to have
a panic attack?
Is that gonna make you feel
less alone in your unraveling?
Oh, this used to be fun.
Oh, my God.
Help...help me!
Hey!
Ha-ha.
Bess, stop it!
Mine.
Decorum, Bess.
Oh, my God.
Stop.
Put them in my...Bess.
Yeah?
Carrie?
What's happening?
What is she doing?
Carrie. Carrie.
Carrie, stop.
- Move along!
- Nothing to see here.
- Just move along.
- Go on.
Come on.
♪ Making a living
the old hard way ♪
♪ Taking and giving
by day by day ♪
♪ I dig snow and rain ♪
♪ And the bright sunshine ♪
♪ Draggin' the line ♪
♪ My dog Sam eats
purple flowers ♪
♪ Ain't got much
but what we got's ours ♪
♪ We dig snow and rain ♪
♪ And bright sunshine ♪
♪ Draggin' the line ♪
♪ I feel fine ♪
♪ I'm talking about
peace of mind... ♪
Good eye!
Poor strategy.
- My fruit, fuck face!
- Ah!
Ah! Get off me.
- Give it!
- Get off me!
Don't even fuck...
Get off me, you rabid...
Give me that fucking fruit!
Thanks for the assist.
- No!
- That's mine!
I saw it first!
Follow-through is everything.
I worked for that!
I'm so sick of everything
coming to you so easy
all the time!
All of us can't all be
such try-hards.
Oh!
- Stop!
- Ha-ha-ha!
Johnny!
Give that to me.
Get off me!
Come on, give it!
Give me the lemon!
No, don't!
This actually
matters to me, OK?
Why?
So you can turn
the Boston house into
- your fucking stoner cave?
- Yeah? Oh, yeah?
You're worried that he's not
going to pay for your rent
whenever you don't make it
as a starving artist?
- Oh, no, fuck you!
- So immature.
What are you doing?
You sound like your moms.
Fuck.
Gat.
You just won Beechwood.
No, I didn't.
You did.
I can't win.
You all know I can't win.
Look...look at yourselves.
Look at us.
We used to be best friends.
And now you're...
now you're hurling
the worst insults you can,
and why?
Why, because of an old man's
power trip?
Where was it?
Harris had it the whole time.
He was never gonna
surrender Beechwood.
He thinks he's a king.
He needs his kingdom.
And he doesn't...
he doesn't care
if people are miserable in it.
He doesn't care
as long as people
are miserable under his power.
And everybody seems
pretty miserable.
You guys are playing
right into it.
Right.
I'm really sorry about
everything that I said.
I really didn't mean any of it.
No, no, no. You were right.
Because I was
so wrapped up in myself, I...
I'm so sorry.
Come here.
I love you.
I accept both your apologies.
No, seriously, though, um,
I've been shit to all of you.
I'm sorry.
Deeply, deeply sorry.
Forgive me, Gatwick.
We all...
Well, Liars,
life's given us lemons.
Your dad is counting lemons
in the living room...
one of the living rooms.
Your living room has
living rooms.
It's called the Great Room.
I know.
I heard it as I said it.
Do you want some of this?
Ice cream is always the cure.
Is he eating?
If you count Takis Fuego
from the hotel
vending machine, sure.
I didn't mean to hurt him.
Mm, and yet...
Sorry.
No.
My husband is no longer here
to defend his kid brother,
so it falls to me.
I had to choose between
being the kind of parent
that my kids needed me to be
and being the partner
that Ed deserved.
And it wasn't a choice.
He's better off without me,
without all of this.
Sometimes I wonder
if I would have had kids
if I knew
what it would be like.
Who would volunteer
to love something so fiercely
that you just let it
consume you whole?
And then I hate myself
for thinking that way,
because who thinks like that
about their own kids?
When Jay died,
oh, I fell apart.
Some days, I would just
stare at this little boy
who looked so much like him
and love him so hard, it hurt.
So hard I thought
it was gonna kill me.
That's the thing.
Motherhood is filled with hurt.
It's like your heart outside
your body while you bleed.
Mom, it's your turn
for the count.
I'm so tired.
Seven.
Where are the Liars?
Right here.
Couldn't find any lemons.
Yeah, me neither.
No lemons.
Oh.
I found a few.
Oh, my God.
You Liars.
I suppose it's my own fault
that you are so clever.
Sinclair genes.
Mm.
Well, then, clearly,
rules have been violated,
so the prizes are void.
But I do have something
valuable to offer Gat.
You, um...
you have such ambition.
But you can't change the world
without opportunity.
Now, Tipper's
scholarship program
was her pet project,
a chance for high-achievers
to travel the world,
pursue an immersive education
while making a positive impact
on refugee communities.
She'd already chosen
this year's recipients,
of course,
but there's an opening.
Now, there are several
candidates vying for it,
so this isn't a handout.
I don't do handouts.
But I do make recommendations.
Now, you have an interview
the morning after next
back in New York,
if you're interested.
♪ Look at the stars ♪
♪ Look how they shine
for you... ♪
Oh.
Hi.
Were you crying?
No, no, no.
I was just washing my face.
You know, you should wear
the, uh...
the jacket you wore
to the funeral
for your interview.
You looked so...
I'm not doing the interview.
Don't want to owe Harris
anything.
It's not his program.
It's Tipper's.
And she would want you
to be a part of it.
You wouldn't owe him anything.
I would.
Look, he said there were
other candidates, right?
So you'll earn it
for yourself at that interview.
Hey.
You have to try again.
Come on.
Hasn't being around the
Sinclairs taught you anything?
Where's your
competitive spirit?
You're being incredibly
selfless right now.
I don't like it.
Yeah, well, I used to be
pretty selfish.
And then this guy
that I'm kind of into
showed me how important
it was to consider
other people's needs
before my wants.
Sounds like a dick.
Yeah, well,
he's pretty cute, so.
♪ You know I love you so... ♪
If I get the internship, I
won't be back here next summer.
Oh.
Yeah.
OK.
I, uh...
♪ Look how they shine for... ♪
What's this?
Don't open it until
your birthday next week, OK?
OK.
♪ Look at the stars ♪
♪ Look how they shine
for you ♪
♪ And all the things
that you do ♪♪
I don't want to hear
the lecture about
how it's my fault that
we lost the Boston house.
Cancer?
Mind your business?
You know, I used to think that
I knew everything about my mom
and that everything she did
was just so flawless
in this way that
I could never duplicate.
Yeah, I tried, God knows,
but why it came so easy to her
and not me...
I used to wonder if
she ever just fucking cried.
I wish I could ask her.
Did you ever just lock yourself
in the bathroom and cry, Mom?
God, did it ever feel
like this for you?
I never asked.
Now I can't.
And I'm just...
so fucking empty.
You made a choice today,
Mirren.
That's fine.
It's a big old "fuck you"
to the family.
I really hope your convictions
keep you and your sisters warm
this winter,
'cause I don't have
any moves left.
The lemons were fucking it.
You know, I thought
you might just reinstate
the "no boyfriends
on Beechwood" rule.
But this was impressive.
Why make yourself a bad guy
when you can just
show his mother that
he doesn't belong here,
make her drag him away?
I didn't make anyone
do anything.
No, you just dangled
two semesters abroad,
followed by a summer
teaching refugees English,
which takes care
of next summer too.
It's very elegant, Dad.
Kids are gonna miss him.
Cadence will be just fine.
I won't let her make
the same mistakes that you did.
Well, that's...
That's for the best.
Love you, Dad.
Mm.
You know,
it might not seem like it,
but I'm glad that you came.
Yeah.
Well, when Harris Sinclair
invites you
on a private jet
to the vineyard...
Harris sent for you?
He called.
He thought with Ed gone,
I might wanna check in.
I figured you were
homesick or lonely,
but apparently, the alien
that's taken over my son's body
is quite happy here.
So I don't know
why he invited me.
I do.
I was too happy here.
Do you remember the book
Harris told me to read?
Wuthering Heights?
Yeah.
It's about
a poor brown-skinned boy,
gets taken in by a rich family.
He falls in love
with the daughter
and becomes a gentleman.
But everyone somehow still
sees him as an animal.
So eventually, he becomes one.
Heathcliff had evil in him,
and you don't.
You're my Gat.
What?
I've done fucked up things.
I'm doing something
fucked up now.
Will you please not
speak at me like
I'm some error
in your judgment?
Hey.
I love you.
I do. I love you.
And I know...
I know we don't make any sense.
To who?
You might be right
about Harris,
but I am the eldest grandchild.
So let's go back to Beechwood,
and I'll fix this.
I'll make it better.
At Beechwood?
Where are the boat keys?
Boat keys?
Cady, do you know
where you are right now?
Oh...
Cady?
Hey, Cadence!
Cadence. Cadence.
What happened?
You aren't really making sense.
Did I get sick
down by the water?
By the water? No, you...
you...you had an episode,
but at the bookstore.
The bookstore?
I didn't know how to help you.
So they had to call your mom
to bring you home.
What about the ice cream
and the sunset?
Our first date?
There wasn't a date.
We never went for ice cream.
You're...you're scaring me.
We've...we've been here talking
since we got back.
Is my mom right?
Maybe you should go.
I'm not leaving you.
I barely know
where I am right now.
Look, I don't care
where you are, right?
I'll follow you there,
and that's it.
Why are you here?
What do you mean,
why am I here?
I'm here for you.
No, the scholarship.
You should be gone by now.
You didn't get it?
I never made it
to the interview.
We were supposed to leave
the next night,
but something happened.
I called the cab
to the airport.
Your mom on her way?
Yeah, as soon as
she gets her eyeliner
even on both sides.
Oh, you might miss
your interview.
Can I ask you something?
Yeah.
Now that it's over,
do you regret Carrie?
Fuck. Um...
...I regret things.
I regret not marrying her
years ago.
I regret that when
she was ready to have a baby,
I said we should wait
until we could afford
to send our kid
to the same schools
as Will and Johnny went to...
...you know,
without help from Harris.
I thought that I needed
to raise another Sinclair.
I was too proud.
You think it's, uh...
you think it's too late
for the Liars
to grow up different
from the rest?
Mate, I know it feels like
you've lived your entire life,
but you're only 16.
The four of you are
gonna do great things,
and stupid things,
and then greater things.
You aren't even
an ounce of the person
you're gonna grow into,
any of you.
Gat, you have all the time
in the world.
I've got to go.
Yeah.
Oh.
Your mom's gonna kill me.
♪ Won't you leave me? ♪
Sorry, excuse me.
Hey, can I get a lift
to Beechwood, please?
- Oh, sorry...
- What? What?
Emergency boats only
to Beechwood
till further notice.
What emergency?
Is someone hurt?
On the island, is someone hurt?
They don't call in the chopper
if someone isn't.
♪ I fell into the water ♪
♪ Water won't let me breathe ♪
♪ I got lost in the deep end ♪
♪ It's a bad ♪
♪ It's a bad dream ♪♪
♪ I'm screaming underwater ♪
♪ Only till you
start breathing ♪
♪ What you know ♪
♪ I can't ♪
♪ Give you ♪