What happened
the night of my accident, Mom?
Just tell me!
I have told you!
Over and over again!
And every time,
you had an episode.
You cannot ask me
to cause you pain.
Is that ivory?
You will want to include them
in an asset inventory, though.
You're changing your will?
To account for
new circumstances.
What did you do, Johnny?
This kid, Delgado,
I kicked his ass.
I found out he was
in the hospital.
I called my mom,
and she fixed it.
- She paid him off?
- Yeah.
But Beaumont has a video, and
it'll go viral if I don't pay.
I do have something valuable
to offer Gat...
Tipper's scholarship program.
You have an interview
back in New York.
Hey, you have to try again.
Cadence will be just fine.
I won't let her make
the same mistakes that you did.
Is someone hurt?
On the island, is someone hurt?
I'm scared, Mirren.
I don't think my memory
can be trusted.
I think I might be crazy.
You know, not just
head-injury crazy,
but hallucination,
psycho, actual crazy.
I think my mom might be right,
that I'm lying to myself.
I just...I don't
know what's real.
God, reality is overrated.
I was hoping that you could
confirm or deny some memories.
Sure.
I have these flashes
from Summer 16
that I still can't place.
You filling up
the boat with gas.
Granddad at the end of summer
beach bonfire.
And the four of us
Liars together.
The four of us.
I thought that when Gat left,
I might never see him again,
but he came back, didn't he?
Gat will always come
back for you, Cady.
I heard the two of you at
Cuddledown the other night.
Stop.
Cady, I think you
should leave him alone.
That's just...
making things harder.
How?
I love him.
I don't want...
You know I've always loved him.
No, I just don't
want either of you guys
to get hurt, that's all.
Look, Gat is
worth the risk, okay?
My whole life is pills
and headaches and my mom and...
I'm sorry.
...he is the only thing that...
I can't...I can't
feel sorry for you.
You're the first
Sinclair grandchild.
You have money.
You have a doctor.
You have education.
It's not like you're dying
of cancer or anything, so.
Everything's possible for you.
Bonnie.
The sun. You're blocking it.
You're turning red.
Hi, Bonnie.
Cady, tell me a ghost story.
I'm fresh out. Ask Mirren.
Hilarious.
I tried to tell
her one last night.
I messed up the narratives.
I was too tired.
Cadence, you also
know that you're
the only source of
entertainment on this island.
Come on.
Fine.
There was once a king with
three beautiful princesses.
Not a fairy tale...
a horror story.
I promise, this one gets scary.
Cadence, I'm heading to town.
Join me.
Um...just me?
Come on, let's go.
See you guys later.
Hi.
"Proceeds to Martha's
Vineyard Migrants."
I know you can't resist
a charitable cause.
Licorice, that's your
favorite, isn't it?
It's lemon cream.
Then lemon cream it is.
Yep, lemon cream it is.
- Here we go.
- All right.
Thank you.
- Oh.
- What?
So that's what this is about.
You brought me
to go see a doctor?
You've seen every doctor
in New England.
No, I'm gonna go in
and say hello to Moriarty.
He's an old friend.
I'll just...
I'll meet you, uh...
here.
Here.
I'll meet you at the bookstore.
My mom says
I shouldn't be left alone
since I had that episode.
Look.
I made a mistake with your
mother and her sisters.
I let them squander
their opportunity,
choose unworthy partners,
dig themselves into deep holes
with their silver spoons.
But not you.
You're the first grandchild.
You are a fresh chance.
And you are of sound mind.
And I expect you
to act accordingly.
Understood?
Can't just outclass PTSD.
Combat veterans have PTSD.
You have a lack
of guff and gall.
Lemon cream.
Your favorite.
Have one.
There was once a king
whose island was under siege.
A fire-breathing dragon
was burning his villages.
And every brave warrior
he sent to slay the beast
was slaughtered.
The king reasoned
that while all
the armored knights failed,
a beautiful maiden might
melt the dragon's heart.
Luckily, he had
three daughters.
First, he sent his strongest
daughter to face the dragon.
She went gladly
to save the kingdom.
Its claws shredded her
to pieces.
So he sent his
sweetest daughter,
who was glad to earn his love,
to beg the dragon for mercy.
It swallowed her in one bite.
The king turned
to his eldest daughter.
She saw his grief
and was eager to please him,
to save his crops
and strongholds.
The dragon turned her
to ashes.
♪ He will not
weather it ♪
♪ Like that man ♪
Oh, good, you found
the new dress I got you.
Do you like it?
I don't need more dresses.
I was trying to make you smile.
You don't despair
over boys, Cadence.
It's pitiful.
Sinclairs are not pitied.
Gat is gone.
Can I have two minutes
of despair
before I have to
put my chin up?
Or you could be happy for him.
Grateful to your granddad
for giving him
such an amazing opportunity,
even after you all
disrespected Tipper's
favorite summer tradition.
Granddad is the one
who ruined the lemon hunt
with all those crazy prizes.
He is a capitalist.
He just believes that
competition makes
the best people rise
to the top.
That's why I need you
to be at your best tonight.
Look, he's been
revising his will.
Given the way he
tested us at the hunt,
I think he plans
to leave all of it
to one favored daughter
or grandchild.
Don't you ever get sick
of being a Sinclair?
You say that like
we have a choice.
We will always be Sinclairs.
The only choice that you have
is if you will be a Sinclair
fallen from grace,
a pitied, poor little rich girl
whose newfound misfortune
thrills the teeming masses,
or if you will be
a Sinclair with potential.
You wanna make a difference
in the world, Cadence?
Great.
Build orphanages.
Fund social justice movements.
Topple evil empires.
But honey, you are gonna need
a lot of money
to get that done.
I am only asking you to be your
polite, lovely,
intelligent self to ease your
grandfather's heartache...
and to remind him how much
you miss Tipper.
I do miss her.
Lemons always make me
think of her.
Hmm.
You know, you're making
feelings I actually have
feel very cheap.
Nothing on Beechwood is cheap.
The question,
of course, is this.
Who really killed
the princesses?
The dragon or the king?
♪ Every time ♪
♪ I burn through the world
I'd see ♪
♪ That the world ♪
♪ It burns through me ♪♪
Don't. Don't do that.
What?
Don't be gentle with me.
I'm going into battle today.
I don't need to be coddled.
I need to be provoked.
Mom, you're bleeding.
Wear a jacket
to dinner tonight, okay?
You rattled Harris
with that lemon hunt stunt.
Now the summer is ending,
and with it, any opportunity
to win back favors.
And if we can't win him over?
If it's...if it's gone
too far already, what?
Then what?
When you were born, he called
you his bright young heir.
Said that you were made
in his image or...
some bullshit like that.
I'm not, though.
I'm not like him.
I'm different from Harris, Mom.
I don't think I'm the type of
Sinclair boy that he wants.
I'm saying...
I wanna
tell you something, Mom.
And it's...
Stop, stop.
Johnny, we can have
this conversation tomorrow.
I promise.
Right now, I have
to get Will packed.
I...it's just...
You can talk to me about it.
I think you're
a good Sinclair boy.
Just so you know.
Thanks, buddy. Thanks a lot.
It's okay. Everything's cool.
I love you.
Love you too.
I know.
I'm gonna get ready for dinner.
No, the twins are
looking for you.
Your dad's taking them
to camp for the weekend.
What happened? Did you fall?
Oh, um, no. I'm okay.
The staff hasn't been tending
to the tennis courts properly.
I swear they're getting lazier.
Here.
Take these to the family dock.
You can probably
still catch them.
I'm good.
Your sisters wanna say
goodbye to you, Mirren.
Yeah, well,
I don't wanna see Dad.
Your hair looks nice today.
Hey, light.
- There you go.
- Yeah.
I know he had to go, but...
I keep looking
out at the water,
thinking maybe he'll change
his mind and come back.
Blame fairy tales.
Well, it's time for dinner.
With a side of
extreme scrutiny.
I feel like we're
walking into a tribunal.
I feel like summer ending
is the end of days
for our mothers.
Well, at least Gat
is spared this one.
There were summers before Gat.
And there will
be summers after.
- Ooh.
- Yeah.
Thank you.
Oh, thank you. Sherry.
Well, you all look lovely.
All right, sit.
What a relief to finally
have the island to ourselves.
It's better this way.
I'm sure you agree.
Just us.
We're missing
the smallest Sinclairs.
I assume they didn't cast out,
unsupervised, to the sea.
The twins have their horse camp
in Boston, remember?
Uh, Will wanted to go,
too, so we signed him up,
and Brody took them
earlier today.
And why didn't one of you
escort the kids to camp?
We thought that
you wouldn't want us
to miss this family dinner.
Well, is this particular dinner
important for some reason
that I am unaware of?
So important that you would
entrust your children to him?
Well, they're his children.
Will's not.
Dad made a mistake.
It's not like he's gonna
traffic the twins
to make good with the IRS.
Come on.
Okay, look.
I hold members of this family
to a high standard.
Mirren, your father,
he didn't accidentally
steal from his clients
and from the trust fund
that I worked hard to provide
to you and your mother.
Brody schemed and lied.
A mistake is made one time...
when made repeatedly,
it becomes a pattern.
And patterns of behavior
define character.
Thus, he is a criminal.
Isn't that right, Bess?
You don't have to worry
about Mirren, Dad.
She knows right from wrong.
I'm a very hands-on parent.
I really learned from
watching Carrie's struggles.
Excuse me?
Oh, that's not
a criticism, Care.
I'm saying that
I admire your progress.
You could barely
hold it together
when Johnny was little,
and now he's a fine young man.
Honestly, when you consider
all of the obstacles
that he's had to overcome
at home,
what's a little vandalism
and assault, hmm?
Bitsy Beaumont called me.
She said she found something
on her son's phone?
It will be handled.
We will not talk about
that incident again.
Understood?
Yeah, I figured you'd call
Thatcher in to fix it, Dad.
He is such a pro at making
ugly secrets just disappear,
which is why I really do think
he's an excellent addition
to your divorce team, Pen.
I...
Sorry, I picked up
the landline.
It was an innocent mistake.
Are the goldens fed?
I'll get them.
How'd you get
those scratches, Bess?
Excuse me?
Well, I wasn't
gonna say anything,
but it seems like
we are saying things.
So, um, you have a chain-link
fence on your back.
You might not wanna show
so much skin
the next time you
and the lobster hunter
wanna defile the tennis court.
But if you wanna go ahead
and keep talking to me
about parenting...
I'd love to talk
to you about parenting.
The second course, sir.
Indeed.
And the Glengoyne single malt
from the study, please, Lydia.
Yes, sir.
Penny...
I'm on it!
It's coming, it's coming.
Why is everyone so tense today?
What are you doing?
I'm giving the dogs
their thunder pills.
They get agitated
when we're agitated.
You're just sitting there
while they destroy each other.
That is the plan.
Let Bess bring both guns
blazing to the battle of wits
and let Carrie's
ticking time bomb go off
while you and I,
we just sit there, impeccable.
But you didn't expect them
to bring up your ugly secrets.
Cadence...
I know it doesn't
seem like it right now,
but you and I, we are winning.
All we have to do is
stay the course and deflect.
Beechwood is not
supposed to be like this!
Summers here
are supposed to be perfect!
Aw, kid, life is never perfect.
I know when you are little,
you are protected from that.
You are sent off
to horse camp at the first sign
that things are messy
so that later,
yes, you can have these
watercolor, idyllic memories
to wax nostalgic about.
You are not little anymore.
Welcome to the real
family tradition.
Mom.
Pro tip...dog benzos
and human benzos?
Same fucking benzos.
Come on, guys.
Close the door when you leave.
They feel safe in here.
Well, try a tartlet.
Lydia's outdone herself.
Oh, that's all right,
I'm gonna save room for salad.
Just have...one.
Absolutely.
Mmm.
Oh, that reminds me, Cady,
tell your grandad
what you were saying to me
earlier about the lemons,
what they always remind you of.
Did you know lemons are kind
of a symbol of colonization?
It's true, Granddad.
Yeah, Columbus brought
citrus seeds from the Americas.
So technically,
our yearly lemon fest tradition
only exists because
of a genocidal slave trader.
Whoa, fascinating.
Well, that is
her AP history talking,
because she is determined
to get into Harvard
on her own merit, Dad.
Well, I've been thinking a lot
about Harvard lately.
I think it might be nice
to leave a good portion
of my estate to my alma mater.
Actually, you know,
I didn't learn the thing
about Columbus and the lemons
from history class, Mom.
Gat read about it.
He's the smartest Liar, right?
You know what?
Maybe next year we should
have an apple hunt.
Or drop the hunt entirely.
Um...
He's being sarcastic.
Well, the lemon hunt is, uh...
it's Tipper's
favorite tradition.
My mom says that
traditions lack
originality and imagination.
- No, I didn't.
- Yes, you did.
No, I didn't.
When you and Ed froze embryos,
I remember you
had an argument about
whether you were gonna get
married first.
Actually,
it wasn't an argument.
I know it was...
more love between you guys.
But I remember you said,
"Fuck tradition, baby."
I remember.
That's what you said.
Well, I don't know why you had
to bring embryos into it.
And God, you knew you would
never go through with that,
Carrie.
I wanted a baby with Ed.
- Until you didn't.
- Yes, I d...
I still do.
Well, then you must have
wanted something else more.
- Did you trade your partner?
- That is enough, Penny.
W...what does...
what does that mean?
Eat your tartlet.
Cadence, tell me...
...how is Windemere?
Bess was, uh, worried
that you two
might be lonely
with five bedrooms.
We are not lonely.
Cadence loves Windemere because
you built it for me, Dad.
She wants to raise
her children there.
Tell him, Cady.
It's too big.
Well, next summer, perhaps
you two will take Cuddledown.
And Bess and the girls
can take Windemere.
No, no, no, no.
I won't be here next summer.
Not if it's like this.
I'm gonna go travel.
With Gat.
Oh, Jesus Christ,
I don't understand your need
to constantly bring up
that boy at my table.
Why do you always
call him that?
You never say his name.
It's always
"that boy" or "kid."
Or "young man."
You always called Ed
"young man."
Stop talking about Ed.
- He has gray hair.
- Stop!
Then tell me what she meant
just then,
when she said that
you traded him?
For what?
An inheritance, Mom?
You made her choose?
- More wine, Miss?
- Just...just leave the bottle.
Penny, relax.
God, it's
kind of hard to relax when
you make us all fucking crazy.
We don't mumble.
She said that you're
making them crazy, Granddad.
Mirren!
All right, listen!
All of you,
pull yourselves together.
If you are going crazy,
it's your own damn choice.
All right.
The inheritance...
...is no longer a factor.
Hmm? The plans have been made.
Thatcher will
collect the papers
and file them in the morning.
And you will each get
exactly what you've earned,
exactly...what you deserve.
After all, I can't
leave my estate
to a bunch of crazy people.
Hey.
What did they mean about Gat
and Ed and the inheritance?
Franklin? Eleanor?
- Granddad.
- Where are the dogs?
Asleep in the laundry.
Did you tell Carrie
you would cut her off
because she was with Ed?
Carrie's a grown woman.
She had a choice to make.
You never liked them, did you?
Gat and Ed.
You could barely stomach them.
That's why you never
use their names.
On the contrary,
they never liked us.
No.
I have high standards, Cadence.
I will not apologize for them.
White standards?
Are you saying I'm racist?
I think you don't
like Gat with me,
and you don't like Carrie
with Ed.
I think you tolerated them
for a long time
because you wanted to believe
certain things about
who you are.
No, I believe in who we are,
who we have been for centuries.
It's my duty
to protect this family.
You tolerated Gat and Ed.
But when Carrie talked about
babies, it made you sick.
You couldn't let them
mess up the family.
Sinclairs are blonde
and square-chinned.
We freckle in the sun.
That's what this is, isn't it?
You don't want
Indian grandchildren.
You don't wanna
ruin the pictures.
Oh, for Christ's sake,
Cadence, I'm a Democrat!
No!
Grandad!
Granddad! Granddad!
Help!
Cadence?
Oh.
I'm right...here.
Oh, no...oh, no...
The hair.
I almost didn't recognize you.
Are you all right?
Uh, grandfathers,
they never like hair dye.
What did
Dr. Moriarty have to say?
Oh, um, he, um...
he said that, oh, um,
that the oysters are, uh,
at the First Street market...
they're...
they are particularly
good...today.
Uh, we'll pick some up
on the way home.
A 68-year-old male
with head trauma.
ETA 12 minutes.
- I'm so sorry, I didn't...
- It's okay. It's okay.
Search his office
for the draft of his will.
Search everywhere.
If it doesn't favor us,
burn it.
Bess, pack his bag!
Carrie, call Harbor Services.
You need a water taxi
to the mainland.
No, I'll just come
with you right now.
There is only room for one.
Oh, God.
She is good in a crisis.
That for Penny or Dad?
The whole fucking universe.
You were so mean to Carrie.
We're sisters.
We don't have to be
kind all the time.
Yeah, well, you could be.
And you weren't
sisterly bitchy.
You were just mean.
You know, just once
I'd like to be the one
you take a stand to defend.
Harris was poking at me,
and I needed to pivot.
Can you grab his slippers?
Yeah, which ones?
Uh, either. Both.
I don't care.
None of this should be
happening right now.
- Except your father...
- Oh, my God!
We know Dad screwed up, Mom.
But when did you know it?
Was it before or after
you decided
to fuck Salty Dan
all over this island?
Don't you dare
throw that in my face!
Which part? The boathouse?
- Stop.
- The tennis court?
- Is that a mistake?
Or is that a pattern?
And which one defines
character again, Mom?
Stop it!
I was the good daughter.
Carrie's a crisis.
Penny's a brick wall.
And now he thinks
that I'm the weak one.
But I was the good one.
When Rosemary died,
I was the baby,
and everyone was supposed
to love me the most.
Oh, God.
I did everything
I was supposed to do.
I stayed close to home.
And I hate Boston!
I hate it!
I wanted sunshine
and sand and desert roses.
I wanted desert roses.
I didn't get to go
because my sisters left,
and I had to stay in case
my mom or dad needed me.
I didn't starve myself.
Or take pills.
I didn't make messes.
I sure as hell had to get my
hands dirty cleaning them up,
but I didn't complain because
I am the good daughter.
And I am the good wife.
And I'm the good mother!
And I'm the good one!
What the hell happened to me?
What are you looking for?
Oh.
Nothing.
Well, don't stop looking
on my account.
Do you think he'll be okay?
Yeah.
He'll be fine.
Do you want him to be?
What kind of question is that?
One that deserves
an actual answer.
Yes.
Johnny, I don't, um,
hate my father.
I think I might a little.
Ran off Gat.
Made you break up with Ed.
That's what that
all was, right?
He paid off the debt that I
caused on one condition, right?
You couldn't marry Ed.
Yes.
That doesn't make you furious?
'Cause I'd be angry
if I were you, Mom.
But you're so calm.
I am focused.
I have to go to the hospital.
And I might need to spend
the night on the Vineyard,
so I need to make sure
that I have everything.
And...that's it.
Yeah, okay, well,
then let me help you find
what you're looking for, Mom.
Bottom shelf, behind the
cast iron that no one uses.
Right?
I always knew
your hiding spots.
Just haven't had to look
for a long time.
But I know this you, Mom.
Nothing gets under your skin.
You're zen.
I remember this you
from when I was little,
when Dad was around.
And he'd see red.
And you were always just...
very still.
And then you got sober.
And Will's only ever known
you as this...
beautiful blur of motion.
But then Ed left,
and now I see this you,
this old you, every f...
every night.
Those are Gran's pain pills
for her knees, Mom,
and she never left them
where you could see them,
because she was trying
to protect you from yourself.
But now she's gone.
And you never talk about it.
You never talk to me.
You're so...calm.
So still.
We will talk about this...
tomorrow.
Well, that was...
God, I hope we're
not like them.
I think it's
genetically unavoidable.
Cady!
Gat.
Wait, are you all okay?
I saw a helicopter.
What...what happened?
Total Last Supper vibes.
I don't think I've ever
seen this place dirty.
Lydia was literally scrubbing
blood off the patio steps.
So you know, I couldn't watch,
and I sent
the whole staff home.
They went through enough today.
So we have the whole island
to ourselves?
For the first time ever, yeah.
We could do anything we want.
Huh.
- I'll stack.
- I'll scrub.
- I'll load.
- I'll dry.
Let's do it.
♪ I'm starving, darling ♪
♪ I wanna smell
the dinner cooking ♪
♪ I wanna feel the edges
start to burn...
Stop!
♪ Honey, I wanna
race you to the table ♪
♪ If you hesitate,
the gettin' is gone ♪
♪ I won't lie ♪
♪ If there's something
to be gained ♪
♪ There's money to be made ♪
♪ Whatever is still to come ♪
♪ Get some ♪
♪ Pull up the ladder
when the flood comes ♪
♪ Throw enough rope
until the legs have swung ♪
♪ Seven new ways that
you can eat your young ♪
♪ Come and get some ♪
♪ Skinning the children
for a war drum ♪
♪ Putting food on the table,
selling ♪
♪ Eat your young...
♪ Come and get some ♪
♪ Skinning the children
for a war drum ♪
♪ Putting food on the table,
selling bombs and guns ♪
♪ It's quicker and easier
to eat your young ♪♪
Cheers!
Ah.
I found them.
Not the good scissors.
Gran never let us use them.
We're completely unsupervised,
and you wanna collage?
It's on brand.
No, my brand is
people-pleasing bullshit.
And you know what?
If I want desert roses,
I'm gonna chase desert roses.
I don't wanna be some old lady
crying about desert roses!
Well, you're pretty much
my favorite person
on this whole stupid planet.
So I am all for
whatever happens next.
What are you doing up here?
It's not obvious?
Pretending I'm king
of Beechwood Island.
What, did you
overthrow the last guy?
No, no, I...
married into
the line of succession.
Okay.
- Yeah.
- No, I like this fairy tale.
Tell me more.
Okay, okay.
Together, we slay the dragons
and return the land
where it's always summer
to its former glory.
Gates are always open.
All are welcome.
No one's ever banished.
Why'd you come back?
You were finally
free of this place.
I love this place.
It's where I found you.
Actually, I found you,
hiding in a boathouse.
Yeah, yeah.
I did that after my dad died.
I'd get overwhelmed
and try to find some tiny nook
to hide from real life.
And then you came in.
You bent down,
you looked at me,
and you went, are you real?
- Remember that?
- Yeah.
You asked me if I
was real, like as if...
I don't know, as if
I didn't have to be.
Like life could
just be cannonballs
and Scrabble tiles and...
and you and Johnny and Mirren.
Reality could wait.
Hands.
- Give me your hands.
- Okay.
Come on.
You know, I think Beechwood is
a tiny nook that
we're all hiding in.
But reality is
starting to seep in.
"Always do what
you're afraid to do."
It's a motto.
Or, you know, a reminder,
in case you ever find yourself
looking for a safe space
to hide.
Give me the pen.
- And your hands.
- Okay.
♪ 'Cause nothing
ever really dies...
You know, at the beginning
of the summer,
you thought that
I didn't see you.
But I do now.
My family never will, though.
God, I do not know what to do.
I just don't know how
to slay the dragons.
"Never surrender
to the devil you know best."
♪ Just take those
old records on the shelf ♪
♪ I'll sit and listen
to 'em by myself ♪
♪ Today's music
ain't got the same soul ♪
♪ I like that old time
rock and roll ♪
♪ Don't try to take me
to a disco ♪
♪You'll never even get me
out on the floor ♪
♪ In ten minutes
I'll be late for the door ♪
♪ I like that old time
rock and roll ♪
♪ Still like that old time
♪ That kind of music
just soothes the soul ♪
♪ I reminisce about
the days of old...
Oh, fuck!
Shit, shit.
The moms are going to kill you.
It was an accident.
Those things cost, like,
a hundred grand each.
Fuck it.
- Mirren!
- What?
That shit doesn't matter.
Why are you guys all
looking at me like that?
Come on.
It's not like we're gonna
sell that on the black market
and save a starving family.
We barely know how
to get on the dark web.
Your hair, Mirren.
- It looks awesome.
- I know!
I know, I said that.
Thank you.
It's symbolic.
Just like those
dumb elephants are.
We're gonna be grounded
until graduation.
Oh, my God, Granddad!
- Okay.
- Pants, Jonathan.
Yeah, I know.
Wait.
What if they're calling to say
that Granddad's dead?
Hello?
We say "Sinclair residence"
when we pick up the phone.
Great, I'll add it
to the list of things we do.
Is Granddad okay?
Is it loud on my end?
I'm sure it is.
They refused to give us
a private waiting area.
We've been in this
petri dish for hours.
- Is he okay?
- - Yeah, he's fine.
He's had a...a concussion
and a few stitches.
There was a lot of blood.
Well, he's elderly
and had a drink.
It was a head wound.
It was the trifecta.
His CTs came back
with some abnormalities,
uh, not from the fall.
Seems he's been
skipping checkups.
Wait, so there's something
wrong with his brain?
It would explain a lot.
We're transferring him
to Boston.
- He's a beloved benefactor...
- Hey, have you seen him?
He's not in his room.
You lost him?
You know he refuses
to see a doctor
outside of a putting green.
Oh, my God, Christ.
He thinks he's invincible.
I have to go.
Okay, let's go find Dad.
Well, he's alive.
Yay.
- What is that?
- Oh! What?
Oh.
Foam party!
Like Ibiza.
Mirren, have you ever
loaded a dishwasher before?
I don't think
I'm gonna be very good
at being a poor person.
Question.
What?
Is it messed up to feel
this happy with you
when your grandfather just got
helicoptered to the hospital?
He thinks it's messed up
that you and I feel this way
about each other at all.
I didn't think you'd notice.
I'm sorry I didn't
notice sooner.
I'm sorry about so many things.
Hey.
You have nothing
to apologize for.
Oh! Sorry.
Wait, if you wanna be alone,
we...
Come on, losers, get in here.
That's good, yeah.
You guys remember Summer 9,
when we had our sleepover
in here?
Yeah, and we wanted
to sleep outside,
but the moms were riled up
about hypothermia
and sand crabs.
Yeah, so Granddad
brought us in here,
made us some s'mores,
told us stories,
like how his dad
started the newspaper,
or how he wooed Gran away
from that other guy.
How can Harris be that person,
our Granddad, and then...
who he was tonight?
Maybe our granddad
who taught us
water safety and checkers
is just locked up in his mind
and needs to be rescued.
Maybe if we just
talk to him or you...
Talk to him?
I'm sorry, guys.
I mean, I...
I wanna believe that people
are capable of change
because, I mean,
if they're not,
what is the point in trying?
But...
look, it's...it's one thing
to see a racist politician
on the TV or hear shitty
comments on the subway,
I mean, from someone
I don't even know.
I mean, I've dealt with that
my entire life.
But this?
This is different.
I mean, Harris...
Harris has known me
since I was a little boy.
He's seen me chase fireflies
and dig up seashells.
And...and he still hates me.
And I didn't even
do anything, you know?
I mean, what have I done?
I haven't done anything
apart from just being me.
The point is...
talking, Mirren...
no offense, but talking
is not gonna do shit.
As a matter of fact,
nothing will ever
fucking make a difference.
I'm sorry.
He's your grandfather.
I didn't...I didn't mean...
No, he's our granddad.
And he's a racist piece of shit
who doesn't like Gat or Ed
because of the color
of their skin.
There is no use in
trying to talk to him.
I think we all know that.
He's too far gone.
It's way too late.
If he was always like this,
no wonder all the moms'
priorities became so skewed.
Maybe he's been torturing them
with these inheritance games
for a long time now,
and we just...
we were just too young
to notice it.
Well, game over,
because he's pouring it all
into a new student hall
for Harvard.
Not all of it.
What is that?
The last will and testament
of Harris Sinclair.
Your mom gets
the Boston house when he dies.
My mom hates Boston.
- And he probably knew that.
- Hmm.
And Carrie gets
a quarterly stipend.
It's a lot of money.
What's the catch?
She only gets it
if she stays unmarried.
- Same with my mom.
- Mm.
What?
Your mom has a secret
Black boyfriend or something?
No, but she definitely
has some secrets.
I mean, you saw Bess, right?
You heard her
at dinner tonight.
You know, tomorrow...
...we're gonna leave
this island,
and the moms
will yell about the...
the elephants
and the Persian rugs
and Mirren's hair because
that's what Sinclairs do.
Yeah, we spiral over things
that mean nothing.
Cady.
He'll be so mad.
We refuse to talk
about anything real.
And then we cover things up
and go back to normal.
We should trash the house
and crash his boat,
run naked through Edgartown.
Give him something
real to yell about.
Oh, the Sinclair angels
would never do something
so uncouth.
No, no, but you guys
were under the influence
of the brown boy.
He could be
a cult leader, right?
I mean, he's so
charismatic and cunning.
Oh, my God.
Can you imagine the headlines?
No, there wouldn't be any.
I'm serious.
He would cover it up,
make it disappear.
God.
What if we made...
a mess so big...
...only a Sinclair
could clean it up?
What if all the petty
material things
that tore our family apart
were just gone?
Just like that.
Okay, I think Cady's
the cult leader.
I'm serious.
I mean, Clairmont is built
on a foundation of hate.
Ooh.
We could tear it down.
Teach Harris and the moms
the ultimate lesson.
What did you have in mind?
Hey, you're back.
You okay?
There was a fire.
I remember it now.
We burnt this place
to the ground.
♪ Howl, caught in the open ♪
♪ Down, it's bleak
and it's sobering ♪
♪ Flower bloom in the broken ♪
♪ Cower, doped to recovering ♪
♪ Grow crown and suffer ♪
♪ You stole ♪
♪ You stole in featherweight ♪
♪ Bring an ocean down ♪♪