Something terrible
happened last summer,
and I have no memory
of what or who hurt me.
We're not allowed to talk
about Summer 16.
The doctors,
they said it was best
if you remember on your own.
I've known that Gran passed,
but knowing is different
than remembering.
The fuck?
We agreed she would
be buried in those.
We didn't agree on anything.
It breaks my heart to be
as ashamed as I am now.
My checkbook is closed.
There'll be no more handouts.
Not until I see people
worth my investment.
When I saw you
writing that letter to Raquel,
I thought you were
writing it for me.
And now I feel so stupid.
Cady, do we forgive Gat?
Yeah, we forgive him.
Sexter's here.
There's this guy
from a rival tennis team here
that I really don't wanna see.
And that kid
was not subtle
about bagging a Sinclair.
And you really shouldn't be
spying on people, Ebon.
And we won't be needing
your services any longer.
What, you're gonna ruin my life
like you did that poor kid?
You almost murdered him,
you psychopath.
There's video.
Why did he lie to me?
And why did Mirren
cover for him?
I need answers.
♪ How did...
When a kingdom
loses its matriarch,
there's normally
a mourning period,
the castle draped
with black flags,
loyal subjects bowing
their veiled heads,
lamenting what was lost.
But on the mythical island
where it was always summer,
the king and the princesses
did not grieve openly.
♪ Trying to fight ♪
♪ When you became
a stranger to me ♪
In the weeks
that followed
the Fairy Queen's death,
her family realized
they, too, must be mortal.
And that was a secret
that must be kept.
So they went on as if
she had never existed at all.
People who live in castles
do not know the difference
between pretending and lying.
Take some more from that side.
Perfect.
Just like that.
Ow.
I can literally feel you
messing it up.
She's doing just fine.
Don't complain while
I'm trying to make you pretty.
She's already pretty.
Says the family goth.
Are you a drug addict?
Will says you are.
Oh, God. I'm sorry, Cady.
That's so rude.
Her hair is black.
She looks like a dead vampire.
Hey, Mom said
we have to be nice to her.
Why are you so obsessed
with dead things?
I was nice.
Vampires are sexy.
It's a documented fact.
Ignore Bonnie.
She's...
going through something.
Going through what?
Good morning, Sinclairs.
William and I just collected
a delivery from New Hampshire.
They're illegal
in Massachusetts.
Yeah, well, this is Beechwood.
We make our own laws here.
So we're gonna
celebrate the Fourth
the way I did when I was a boy.
Happy Fourth of July,
Cady.
Happy Fourth, Will.
Whoa. Whoa, whoa, whoa.
- Okay.
I think we're gonna need
a second hammock out here.
We fit.
Hey, am I allowed
to think it's weird
that Harris didn't cancel the
Fourth of July party this year?
I mean, it was kind of
Tipper's thing,
the one-woman pie contest
and all.
Yeah, it's one of his rules,
never show that you feel loss.
Living a joyful life is the
polite thing to do, obviously.
Right. Yeah.
What you reading?
- Oh, nothing.
- Seriously, what is it?
It's nothing.
Exploitative true crime,
werewolf erotica?
No. Stop.
- What?
- No, no.
It's worse. Okay?
Performative social justice
how-to manual.
Wow.
Stop. I'm...I'm trying.
I know. I know.
I see it.
I'm impressed.
I'm not trying
to impress you, Gat.
I'm trying to be
a better person, to see.
I know.
I...I'm trying to be
a better person too.
It's just...it's hard
to change your heart...
especially here.
Yeah, this hammock is
kinda just too small, Gat.
Right. Right.
Well, let's go
live a joyful life.
♪ I'm broke, but I'm happy...
This is smudged.
What does that say?
A half pound of butter.
Butter is a dairy product, Pen,
made from the chilling of fat.
Oh, don't torture her, Bess.
She's already gotta be
regretting
this ridiculous promise
that she made to Dad.
Dad loved showing Mom's
pies off at this party.
If there are no pies,
how will he show high society
how strong we're all being?
He needs this. He...needs us.
So it's a power move?
You really think pies
are gonna make Dad just forget
about your embarrassing
financial situation?
You know, I've never even
touched my trust fund.
Yes, Bess...
We know.
Well, it's true.
This is a you problem, Pen.
And Carrie's doing just fine.
Ed told Brody that you two have
a little nest egg saved up.
I mean, a quail-sized egg,
but still an egg.
Neither of you would be here
if you didn't have
some dog in this fight.
We acted like a sack of idiots
at that memorial.
So if we can make it up
to Dad with pie, why not?
Well, convenient,
given that I'm the only one
who knows how to cook.
Where's Lydia?
She is in the staff building,
wrangling crustaceans.
- I'll go ask her.
- No, no.
Hey, we are not
disarming a nuclear bomb.
It's pie.
Mom did this by herself.
There are three of us.
We can handle it.
Hi. Sorry.
Got a delivery for Sinclair?
You have the wrong house.
Just, um, follow the signs
for Windemere down the path.
Right.
I was never here.
Shame.
I hoped it'd be Salty Dan
that would deliver our kids'
contraband, for Penny's sake.
Are our spawn hosting a rager?
Yeah.
Well, I said they could have
a few friends at my house.
You know, keep the teens
out of Dad's hair.
Oh, yeah, Cady asked Lydia
to order red and blue Jell-O.
I had a flashback to 1998's
technicolor vomit catastrophe.
Oh, God.
It's amazing how our kids
think they've invented
pulling one over
on their parents.
Yeah, she said,
preparing to bamboozle Dad
into thinking we've all
miraculously become our mother.
Mm! Booze!
Check.
Squirty sucker thing guns.
- Check.
- Slip-n-slide.
- I've got these.
Perfect. Okay.
I told the field club jerks
to come here
after they do the polite hello
thing at Clairmont.
And I invited
a few local baddies.
Beautiful. I'll do the slide.
Perfect. Cady, we need limes.
Gat, you make a playlist.
Party on three.
One, two...
One, two, party!
You legends, I love you.
Mwah.
What a day.
He's cheerful.
He's compensating.
It's been a little sad
around here.
Yeah.
Well, I have to go to Clairmont
for limes, so I'll see you.
No, I'll come with you.
Hey, you and I are fine.
I swear. Friends again.
You don't have to, like,
stick to me.
Noted.
But I need Wi-Fi
for the music, so...
♪ Oops, was that my fault? ♪
♪ Well, I'm not sorry
'bout it ♪
♪ I'm not sorry 'bout it ♪
Whoa. Hey.
Aren't there
adult things happening
on the adult side
of the island?
You are not invited
to our secret party.
Oh, no.
But I love skunked beer
and twerking to Ice Spice.
If you're locking up
the valuables,
you're gonna need
a bigger safe.
That's not exactly...
Oh, is that...
- wait, are you gonna...
- Depends.
Does the sight of it make
you wanna punch someone
or plan a bachelor party?
I won't do it without
your approval.
Oh. Okay.
Well, I guess that's a yes.
Hey, are you okay?
Yeah.
Yeah, sorry, things have just
been a little rough lately.
Don't tell anyone.
Yeah.
Grief is...grief is hard
in this family.
Yeah. Yeah, I guess.
Something else
on your mind, or...
No, no. I mean, you know me.
I'm...I'm always dancing on
the edge of a fall from grace.
Are you gonna ask her today?
Every Fourth, your mom and I
sneak away
from the party
and watch the fireworks
together from the beach,
so I'm gonna do it then.
You romantic fuck.
Okay, but I still
have to ask Will.
Although he's easily bribed.
Mom's been wanting this
for a long time.
We all have.
Congrats in advance, Ed.
Thanks.
Whoo.
Hey.
I got all turned around
on the path.
Never saw the signs.
Who names houses?
People with several
to keep track of.
What are you doing here,
spying again?
You're literally
paying me to be here.
We don't...we don't usually
do deliveries,
but the captain said
you called, requested us.
Didn't specifically
request the eavesdropper.
I just said to not
send Slutty Dan.
Oh, right.
I guess I can't blame you.
That whole thing sucks.
Oh, my God, you know?
What, were you watching him
while he banged my mother?
Again, I don't spy. All right?
He probably told a friend,
and it got back to me.
It's like I said.
People talk on the water taxi
like I'm invisible.
Then you go around
repeating their business.
How righteous of you.
Yeah, that's me, town gossip.
All right, you want me
to tap this for you?
I got it, thanks.
I'll get your tip.
No, no, no. You're good.
I don't take money
from people I feel sorry for.
Excuse me.
♪ I swore I would be true ♪
♪ And, honey, so did you ♪
♪ So why were you
holding her hand? ♪
♪ Is that the way you stand? ♪
♪ Were you lying
all the time ♪
♪ Or was it just a game
to you? ♪
♪ You know I'm such
a fool for you ♪
♪ You've got me wrapped
around your finger ♪
♪ Did you have to
let it linger? ♪
♪ Do you have to?
Do you have to? ♪
♪ Do you have to
let it linger? ♪
Oh!
Oh, Carrie!
God, no, there's a lid
to the food processor.
Do I have to do everything?
Is it too late to order backup?
Yeah, if you want your kid
to go to public school.
Oh, damn it.
My crust keeps cracking.
Oh, you just didn't
add enough water.
And Mom used to mix it by hand.
Oh, did either of you
get any of her DNA?
She always wanted to teach us.
We just never made the time.
Okay, stop. Stop.
People are arriving.
There is no time for sulking.
- Just chin up.
- Oh, God, Penny.
Could I just have
just a moment?
Oh, God.
Now I am flashing back
to the '90s.
Fuck.
What's that supposed to mean?
Nothing.
Never mind.
Because I didn't cry
oceans enough for you
when Rosie died either?
Is that it?
It was never enough for you.
Mom was pragmatic.
She knew how
to maintain composure
and get what she needed
from Dad
while making him think
it was his idea.
And that is the DNA that I got.
Where's my fucking recipe card?
I'm starting over.
- Here, I can do it.
- Yeah.
So you can take credit? Thanks.
Right, right, right.
So you wanna be on my team?
Hey, we're just
grabbing some...
Healthy snacks.
Yeah.
Carrot sticks.
Gat, when I was
in town earlier,
I ran into your friend.
Can't remember her name.
The woman that we...
we took to the Knicks game.
Raquel?
Raquel's in town? This town?
Said she's staying for the week
with her aunt in Chilmark.
Is she gonna come to
your unsanctioned party?
Oh, you know, she knows
I don't have much
cell service
when I'm here, so...
Right, but you have
Wi-Fi now, so...
invite her.
You should definitely
That would be...be so much fun.
The more the merrier.
Yep.
Sorry.
You invited Gat's girlfriend?
Aunt Carrie dropped the
Raquel bomb out of nowhere,
and Gat was just looking at me
like he pitied me.
And I didn't wanna seem like
some pining, pathetic girl,
so I tried to be cool.
Wow. God.
Wow, good job.
Okay, I choked.
And now he's off island,
probably picking her up
and giving her a beach rose
and sweeping her off her feet.
Well, it's a party.
Get over Gat
by getting under someone else.
Oh, God.
Sex is not the solution
to all of your problems.
You know, sex actually
turns perfectly sane people
into lunatics.
Fair, but flirting
never hurt anyone.
What's your type, Cady?
We'll round 'em up.
I'm in the mood for frat boys,
guys who play guitar,
guys with dumb tattoos,
guys with podcasts.
- Yeah!
- Oh, my God.
Douchebags Gat will hate.
You guys are both disgusting.
But I will make
a douchebag group chat, okay?
Mm-hmm!
Just PS, I personally endorse
a life of celibacy.
For...for real, though.
Yeah.
♪ I like the boom, boom ♪
♪ I like to go fast ♪
God, get a load of this guy.
PS, I personally
endorse a life of celibacy.
Okay. That's enough? Okay.
Nope. Nope. Nope.
- Ugh. Whoo!
- Ugh!
You need to follow
my three rules.
I know...the sugar in the mixer
makes you sicker
than the booze.
Never leave a drink unattended
when drunk country club bros
are near.
And it's only fun until
someone gets sued.
Hey. Be careful.
I always am, pathologically so.
Okay.
Well, I need to get
back to Clairmont,
deal with some work drama.
On the Fourth?
Literally always.
Your mom likes very
fancy shoes, Little Bug.
- Dad?
- Yeah?
I need to tell you something.
- It's about Mom.
- Oh.
Sounds like
mother-daughter business,
and I don't really wanna...
hey, have fun today.
Yeah?
I'll see you for the fireworks?
Mm-hmm.
♪ Well, she was
an American girl ♪
♪ Raised on promises ♪
♪ She couldn't help
thinking that there ♪
♪ Was a little more to life ♪
♪ Somewhere else ♪
♪ After all
it was a great big world ♪
♪ With lots of places
to run to ♪
♪ And if she had
to die trying ♪
♪ She had one little promise
she was gonna keep ♪
♪ Oh, yeah ♪
♪ All right ♪
♪ Take it easy, baby ♪
♪ Make it last all night ♪
♪ She was an American girl ♪
♪ Well, it was
kind of cold that night ♪
♪ She stood alone
on a balcony ♪
♪ Yeah, she could hear
the cars roll by ♪
♪ Out on 441 ♪
♪ Like waves crashing
on the beach ♪
♪ And for one
desperate moment there...
Oh, wow.
That's beautiful.
Ours have two minutes, Carrie.
Told you we'd pull it off.
Oh, where is the good china?
Packed.
I'm shipping it
back to Cambridge.
We never use it here.
That is antique rose medallion.
We do need to talk
about these things.
Fine china is used when
you cook a nice meal.
Pen's culinary expertise is
limited to literal dog food.
Yeah, except this isn't
about your tablescape,
because I know how much
the punch bowl auction's for.
Do you think
we're fucking idiots?
You barely even eat.
Well, Bess, we can't
all have the metabolism
and the grating personality
of a hummingbird on crack.
Okay, that's enough.
Let's not go for the Achilles
just five minutes before
we're supposed to play hostess,
okay?
Oh!
Whoop, whoop, whoop.
- Oh, God!
- No, no, no, no.
- Oh, God.
- Jesus.
- Oh!
They were fine
five minutes ago.
They were totally fine.
What did you do?
Did you turn the heat up?
Did you turn the broiler on?
I don't know what
the broiler is, Bess.
I don't cook.
Well, your fucking pie
is perfect and you...
Okay, relax, relax.
You have nothing
to worry about today.
Thanks to the
well-bred income source
that Dad instructed you
to marry,
your trust fund is intact.
Oh, yeah, 'cause you married
middle class for true love.
What? No.
She never even loved Sam.
And you are pushing 40
in a crop top,
hoping your husband
will throw a glance your way
on his way to the golf course.
Please, Bess, tell me
what you know about love.
I know that I don't
remember the last time
I saw you feel it.
I know you use us
like sparring bags.
You polish up your daughter
like some trophy.
Oh, perfect Penny,
so good in a crisis
she can plan a whole funeral
but won't shed
one single tear at it.
God, you don't love anyone.
You just tolerate them
until they leave you.
Ah, Bess!
You need to breathe.
It's a panic attack, okay?
It's a panic attack.
Just breathe.
It's just a pie.
You have no idea
what it feels like...
to be a failure in Dad's eyes.
He still thinks that
you walk on water.
Penny's broke.
She's not hurting.
She's just pretending
to break down
so that you'll
feel bad for her,
and you'll swoop in
and defend her.
And it's working,
like it always does.
Bess.
You've been the baby
for a long time now.
But have you honestly forgotten
what it feels like
to see your little sister cry?
♪ I wanna get numb
numb, numb, numb... ♪
♪ 'Cause lookin'
in your eyes ♪
♪ Like lookin' at the sun ♪
♪ I feel like
you're the moon ♪
♪ I feel like I'm the one ♪
♪ I wanna get numb
numb, numb, numb...
- I got you. Don't worry.
- Here, let me take that.
Thank you.
No way.
Hey, hey.
Your fresh delivery
of patriotic
and horny prep school scum.
Just what I ordered.
All right.
I'm definitely
gonna need help.
Wow.
Let's go.
- Hey, Cady, listen.
- Hey.
Um, I think Johnny's
looking for you.
You have the music, right?
Oh, sorry.
- Hey.
- Hi. So glad you came.
On it.
- We'll see you in there.
- Okay, cool.
Yeah, all right.
Which one of those two girls
looks like a Raquel to you?
- Okay, let's go.
- What?
Never mind.
Wanna come to a party?
♪ I'm young, I'm dumb
I'm full of it ♪
♪ I'm free, I'll run
I'm livin' it ♪
♪ I'm someone's son
no hypocrite ♪
♪ Never gonna grow up
never gonna face it ♪
♪ I'm young, I'm dumb
I'm full of it ♪
♪ I'm free, I'll run
I'm livin' it ♪
♪ I'm someone's son
no hypocrite ♪
♪ Never gonna grow up
but I'm gonna make it...
Whoo!
Cady!
Cady, where's Gat?
We're gonna do a Liars shot
to kick this thing off.
Oh, he's somewhere
around here with, uh, Raquel.
You saw them?
Uh-huh.
Uh, Liars plus-one shot?
Ow. Okay, or not.
Who the fuck invited them?
The tennis boys?
Probably me.
Cady needed options.
Next time you decide to
invite people from my school
to my party, how about
you run them by me first?
Fuck's sake, Mirren.
God, that was dramatic.
I'm so sick of all
his ups and downs, man.
Hey, look,
don't let it ruin your vibe.
Look at me.
I am not letting Raquel
ruin mine.
Sure you're not.
Hold my beer.
Yeah. Whoo!
Stop, stop.
- I swear to God.
- No. Stop it.
I told you I don't feel good.
Ow! Stop it!
Stop!
Do you remember Johnny's
tennis friends from last year?
Vaguely.
Yeah, well, I thought that
they were all pals and stuff,
but now I remember that
when they got to the party,
Johnny was so pissed
that they were there.
He had that scary look
in his eye,
like he did with Blake Beaumont
at the funeral.
See, the key to my
friendship with Johnny
is that I pretty much
never pretend
to care about the intricacies
of rich kid drama.
But last year, I was
so caught up with you,
and you were
so caught up with Raquel,
that we didn't realize that
there was something off
with Johnny.
Have you ever thought that
you're not remembering
for a reason,
that your mind is trying
to protect you?
- My mind wants answers.
- Fine. All right.
Maybe you could believe that
I'm trying to protect you?
You were MIA all year, Gat.
It's too late to do the whole
Prince Charming thing now.
I'll just figure
this out myself.
Come on, Johnny.
Nice.
Happy Fourth.
- Happy Fourth.
- I'm sorry.
Cady.
Hi.
Happy Fourth, Gat.
♪ I'm over it ♪
- Hi.
- Oh.
Okay.
Oh. Yeah. Love to.
Another. Let's do it.
- Okay, you sure?
- No, she's literally...
- I need a refill.
- Okay.
Wait, you're here again?
Your cousin invited me.
It's like she doesn't
know that you're a lurker.
I'm not lurking.
I'm eating a carrot stick,
and I'm talking to you.
That's impossible,
'cause I'm not talking to you.
Ebon, dance with me.
Oh, I'm not much of a dancer.
Oh, come on.
- Dance with me.
- I'll dance.
Hey, you're cute.
Okay, you're off
the hook for now.
- All right.
Hi.
I'm Jackson.
Oh, you're...oh.
You're Johnny's
doubles partner.
No, I used to be.
You're looking good.
Hey.
Where is he?
I haven't seen him
this whole party.
If you came to declare
your intentions, I wouldn't.
This island is cursed.
Love crashes and burns here.
No, we're way over.
Then why did you come?
The guy said Beechwood parties
are legendary.
True.
And 'cause he's not
answering any of my texts.
Oh, well, we don't really
have Wi-Fi here.
When you see him,
tell him I just wanna talk.
About what?
He'll know.
♪ 'Cause I'm
'cause I'm, I'm over it ♪♪
There you are.
Having a nice time?
Oh, come on, Dad.
They're just pies.
They were important.
It's literally impossible
to make you proud.
Well, nothing about
any of your behavior lately
has been worthy of my pride.
Okay. Okay.
We got a little worked up
about Mom's stuff.
But you know what?
We are grieving.
We're just clearly
not very good at it.
Grieving over her loss
or the fact that she's not
around anymore to bail you out?
Look, I don't know
what's happening
with Penny's finances,
but you should have
seen her earlier.
She's not made of stone.
Well, Penny is spending
twice her budget,
and Bess is skating
along the edge of zero.
What?
Running on empty.
And then there's you.
What about me?
I thought that you
and your young man,
you were staying afloat, even
after you spent your trust
on drugs and fancy rehabs.
But you've been working
overtime to impress me,
now trying to make pie.
You need something from me.
Ed and I were fine.
We had savings,
enough for a wedding, IVF.
And then there was an incident
at Johnny's school.
He got into some trouble,
some very bad, very expensive,
very fucked up trouble,
the kind that
you would not like associated
with the Sinclair name.
So I did what I thought
you would do,
and I took care of it.
And now there is nothing.
Nothing.
And Ed does not know,
because if Ed knew,
he would make me do what
he thinks is the right thing.
And I can't do that.
So, yes, I do need you.
- Hands off.
- Hey, hey, hey!
Dance amongst yourselves.
You need some water or
you're gonna be passed out
before the fireworks start.
Gat disappeared.
He's definitely trying to make
out with Raquel somewhere.
Not in your kitchen,
where the water is.
Go.
You jealous she's
getting all the attention?
Cadence is the eldest heir
in the Sinclair legacy.
If I had an issue with getting
attention, I'd be screwed.
No, I was just helping
a vulnerable girl out, so.
Oh, so like I was trying to do
when you were crying
over Blake Beaumont
at a dock at a funeral, right?
I don't need rescuing.
She does.
Look, you see that guy, Jake?
He sells pills
to sixth-graders.
And Deacon is so alt-right,
he's a fascist.
And Kurt sexually assaulted
his best friend's sister
when she was too drunk
to fight him off.
So yeah, I'm sorry, but they
don't get to give my cousin
any kind of attention.
How do you know that?
It's just like you said.
People talk around people that
they perceive to be invisible.
And invisibility isn't just
for water taxi drivers.
It also applies to girls that
they don't think are hot.
They think you're hot.
No, they think I'm weird.
And weird cancels out hot, so.
You know, I...I sort of, uh...
pride myself on being the
keeper of Vineyard secrets,
you know, dark shit,
secret families, embezzlers,
transphobe Republican senators
that keep gay escorts
on speed dial.
Seriously, it sucks
sometimes knowing all that.
Secrets poison you.
Yeah, they do.
But I keep them...
because...I don't know.
I don't know.
It makes me feel powerful
or something.
But I told you about
Blake Beaumont,
and I told you about the thing
with your mother.
Yeah, because you pitied me.
You made that very clear.
No, it's because
I think you're weird.
And I think you're hot.
You hate me.
Yeah, well,
they're not mutually exclusive.
♪ It's right here
right now ♪
♪ We run ♪
♪ Go on the run ♪
♪ Cannonball ♪♪
I assume that beer is for me.
She's gonna love it.
Oh, man, I hope so.
All right.
You're a really
good person, Ed.
I mean it.
Have you ever done
anything bad in your life?
Oh, yeah. Yeah, Coachella 2011.
No, I mean, like, really bad.
Are you all right?
You know you can tell me stuff.
Look, I want you
to know that, Johnny.
I love you.
Ed?
What is this?
You're early.
Um.
Johnny, will you just
leave us alone?
I need to talk to Ed.
What's going on?
Nothing, just family stuff.
Family stuff?
- I was about to ask you...
- Don't.
Thanks.
Hey, can you keep it down?
Oh.
That was rude.
You're rude for bringing
your girlfriend to our island
and not introducing me.
- It's your island.
- Right.
That's why you think
I'm shallow and selfish,
because I have an island.
But you're still here,
torturing me.
I'm...I'm torturing you?
Clearly,
you're torturing me, Gat.
Clearly, I'm tortured.
Like...
Yeah, Cadence, you look it.
Thanks...uh.
It's just not fair
'cause...ah.
Ow.
I always loved my Nan's ring.
Funny, my mom wouldn't part
with it for my first wedding.
I think she always
knew he'd bail.
She knew I wouldn't.
So I...I need you to hear me.
Whatever it is,
you can tell me.
Johnny's problems
are my problems.
I am here for you, the boys,
our future kids,
all of it, Carrie.
I can't marry you, Ed.
I'm sorry.
Because of Johnny?
I don't get it.
I know.
I can't...I can't explain it.
Even if I tried,
you would not understand.
I got Harris's approval.
His approval is fleeting.
Fine, then we don't need him.
I...
I do.
I lost my mom,
and I need my dad.
I'm sorry.
I'm so, so sorry.
♪ All right ♪
♪ Gotta know how to pony ♪
♪ Like Bony Maronie...
He had them flown in.
From Four and Twenty
Blackbirds.
A pre-order.
He didn't believe
in us for a second.
Ed just asked me to marry him
with Nan's ring.
I said no.
What? Why?
What...he's so likable.
Hope you got the ring back.
What is wrong with you?
God, she's deranged.
She has no regard for
what you're going through.
It is a sentimental
heirloom, Bess.
Well, you don't
do sentiment, Penny.
You thought that I didn't need
to succeed today
because I don't need
Dad's money.
Did you consider that
maybe I just wanted
to give him a tiny bright spot
given that he just
lost the love of his life?
Mm...
go fuck yourself, Bess.
Acting like you're all
so above us.
I know about your trust fund.
What?
Drained.
Mm!
One oat latte away
from an overdraft fee.
He knows too.
Oh.
Why do you lie all the time?
Well?
♪ Summer holiday ♪
♪ Having fun ♪
♪ Happiness is
between two buns ♪
♪ Yes, indeed...
- Cute house.
- Stop talking.
We only have 20 minutes.
To do what exactly?
Pretty much
anything you'd like.
You can't surprise me.
I've got a vivid imagination,
and I wanna do it all,
instead of talking about it
and worrying about it.
I worry about everything
all the time
while everyone else
is just doing stuff.
And I got weird again.
Arms up, boat boy.
♪ Dragged by my
sockets to a better place...
But you hate me.
I think you're hot.
They're not mutually exclusive.
♪ Summer holiday ♪
♪ Having fun ♪
Hey, gorgeous.
I'll be done in time
for the fireworks.
Are you sure?
You've been hiding
in here for hours.
Half your old lacrosse
team's out there.
That's usually your scene.
Babe, I'll be there.
You know, you disappeared
for most of the funeral too.
And I was kind of
counting on you that day.
I'm so sorry.
It's a holiday, Brody.
You're in here because
you're avoiding someone.
And for weeks,
I thought it was me.
But it isn't...
is it?
It's one of those men out there
who pays you to manage
his brand new money,
maybe even more than one.
Are you afraid that
they're onto you, Brody?
Hmm?
I mean, not me, of course.
No, no need to worry
about pretty little Bess.
You worry about the men
so that when you screwed up
and you owe them money,
you just steal it from me
because you think
I'm a fucking idiot.
What? Bess, I have no idea...
No, no, no, don't you dare
try to gaslight me.
That money was
for our daughters.
How long have you
been robbing them?
Get the fuck off this island.
Hey, Gat.
We're all gathering
to watch fireworks.
Yeah, I'm just gonna watch
from here.
Not alone.
Here.
Sit on this.
There's not enough room.
Squeeze. It's an apology towel.
I'm...I'm kind of mad at you.
You're dancing
with all those randoms.
I was just trying
to make you jealous.
Okay?
Because I've been jealous for
weeks, and it feels like shit.
If you wanted me
to feel like shit, it worked.
You must have known
that it killed me
when you brought Raquel today.
Raquel wasn't here today.
You told me to invite her,
but I didn't.
But you...you went to go
pick her up at the Vineyard.
I went to break up with her.
In person,
'cause she deserves that...
...just like, uh...
she deserves better
than some guy who...
...completely forgets
she exists
when he's in a hammock
with his best friend.
- Oh.
- Yeah, I...
I fucked things up, I know.
I just...I was
trying to fix it.
What happened?
Oh.
Drunk happened.
Okay.
Let me see.
It's gonna sting, all right?
Mm.
There you go.
Give me your hand.
My hand?
Yeah, give me your hand.
What are you doing?
You'll see.
Fuck! Oh, damn it!
Shit.
- Fuck!
- Johnny?
What's wrong?
Dude, what are you doing?
Stay away from me.
You're going to fall.
Just tell us what's going on.
No. Just leave me alone.
Let us help you.
I don't want your help,
Cady, okay?
I wanna be left the fuck alone.
♪ If you ♪
♪ If you could return ♪
♪ Don't let it burn ♪
♪ Don't let it fade ♪
♪ You're not being rude ♪
♪ It's just your attitude... ♪
Yo, Johnny.
Are you proud of yourself?
Hey, they fucking deserved it,
okay?
Whoo!
Hey, how much
did this shit cost?
- Fuck.
- Fuck, run.
No, no, no, no.
Wait, wait. Hey.
Hey, Delgado, was it worth it?
- Fuck!
- Johnny, stop!
Johnny, stop.
Johnny, you kicked his ass.
Let's go.
Fine, fine.
Fine, fine. I'll go.
Cady?
What are you...
what...is this Johnny's phone?
I didn't...I'm sorry.
Why do you have it?
Uh...
♪ Do you have to
let it linger...
Oh. Oh, Johnny...
Mom, why do you have my phone?
Just leave it alone, Mom.
Please, just give it back.
Mom, please.
♪ I thought nothing
could go wrong ♪
♪ I was wrong ♪
♪ If you ♪
♪ If you could get by...
Hey. You disappeared.
Got so worried.
I saw something,
a video on Johnny's phone.
He hurt someone, Gat.
- You hacked his phone?
- Yes, she did.
She unlocked my phone,
and she gave it to my mother,
who is now seeing my entire
private life, Cadence.
My texts with my dealer,
my Grindr profile.
She's crying so hard,
she won't even yell at me.
- Who does that?
- You lied to me.
Yes, yes, I kept some secrets.
Why would that give you the
right to go through my phone?
- Don't yell at her, man.
- What, because she's sick?
She's also fucking crazy.
I wouldn't have
to do all of this
if someone would just
tell me the fucking truth.
You wanna know
the truth, Cadence?
Yeah.
I'm a terrible person.
Maybe I'm a psycho.
Maybe everything that
happened to you was my fault.
You wanna believe that?
Do you wanna
believe that, Cadence?
No, no, I'm fucking sick of it!
I'm sick of the
fucking victim card!
Hey, stop, dude!
What did you do, Johnny?
What did you do?
Hey. Hey, hey, hey.
How can you sleep?
Are you okay?
Cadence!
Somebody please get
fucking help!
Cadence! Get help, please.
Cady.
What happened? What happened?
♪ Do you have to?
Do you have to...
You're all right.
♪ Do, do, do, do ♪
♪ Do you have to
let it linger? ♪
What's wrong with her?
Cady, Cady, Cady, Cady.
♪ The sky, the sky, the sky ♪
♪ Is running out of blue ♪
♪ No matter how I try ♪
♪ There's no
breaking through ♪
♪ Oh, save me now ♪
♪ I try but I
can't help myself ♪
♪ I need the hands
of someone else right now ♪
of someone else right now ♪♪