.
- Previously
on "Good Girls"...
- I told you everything I know.
- Pack your kids up.
I'm booking you tonight.
- One of them's married
to a cop.
- I want you out.
- Not an option.
- No more pen cap.
There's no saving my soul.
I'm already going to hell.
- He said
there's someone else.
- Hey, they were
out of cinnamon, so...
- I'm the dick
who slept with your dad.
- What?
- Did you forgive him?
- I think I did.
- You're a better person
than me.
- How many women did my husband
cheat on me with?
- Including Amber?
Four.
- [moaning]
I think the dealership
could be great again.
Buy with fake
and sell for real,
and we'll take a cut.
- Cars for cash.
- Then come on down to the new
and improved Boland Motors.
I've been working
on your calendar.
- Where are you going to be?
- Here, at work.
We can't both steer the ship.
- You guys--No!
No mustaches in the morning.
There's no--
Come on, you guys.
Did you brush your teeth?
No, you didn't
brush your teeth.
I can smell it from here.
Here.
And pants, young lady.
You need pants.
What is your deal
with the pants?
Kenny!
Hey, K-Man!
Do not forget your
homework upstairs.
All right, guys,
let's get breakfast.
Oh, Dad forgot milk, so we're
gonna do it dry, okay?
Just--it's just as delicious,
just not as wet.
- [on TV] On-site day care
while you shop.
- There you go.
And here's some.
I'll clean that up.
- Hey, you guys, look.
Mommy's on TV
- Oh.
- Yay!
- Our flexible hours will suit
any woman's schedule,
whether you're stuck
at ho--
Where are the lunches?
- Um...
Oh...
- Okay, it's a hot-lunch day.
- Who's gonna do my hair?
- Daddy's going to.
- Here.
- But he can't do
the bun for ballet.
- He'll learn.
- I will--I will learn.
- All right, love you.
- Give me your face. Come here.
- Mwah.
Love you. I love you.
- Hey, are you gonna be late?
- Don't wait up.
[door opens, closes]
- [sighs]
Good morning, Mrs. Boland.
- How's the baby?
- Not sleeping, Mrs. Boland.
- Told you--white noise,
blackout curtains,
and let him cry.
- [chuckles]
- Morning, Ms. Boland.
[indistinct chatter]
[music playing faintly]
♪
- How can I help you?
- Yeah, I got some cars
coming in today from up north.
- What kind of cars?
- Ah, blue ones, green ones.
You know.
- Well, my lot's full.
- Yeah, these
are for me, though.
- What do you mean?
- You know, you don't got
to worry about all that stuff.
Just stay
in your little lane.
I am going to need you to
deliver me one, though, yeah?
- What did you put
in the cars?
- [scoffs] Why I got to push
ten different buttons
to get a cappuccino?
[chuckles]
Mocha--no.
Vanilla--no.
- What's in the cars?
- "What's in the box?
What's in the box?"
[chuckles]
Just bring them, all right?
It won't be good for nobody
if you don't.
Love what you've done
with the place.
[Fassine's
"Bring the Weight Down"]
[car carrier rattling]
♪
- ♪ Wave the Flag,
wear the mask ♪
♪
♪ Move slowly
through the past ♪
♪
♪ Oh, yeah,
bring the weight down ♪
♪
♪ I'm on fire
♪ Bring the weight down
♪
♪ I'm on f--
[music stops]
[brakes squeal]
- What are you doing here?
- Well, I-I have
a surprise for you.
- Nancy's picking me up.
- Well, I think
you're going to like it.
Okay. You know how you've
always wanted a puppy?
- You did not.
- I did not.
But I am seriously open
to the possibility.
- You're allergic.
- I may or may not
have made that up.
[scoffs] I'm sorry, it's--
The new me is trying
to be 100% honest.
- How is Nancy?
- Pregnant.
- I mean, like, mentally.
Is she all right?
- What do you think?
- [scoffs]
How much longer
are you gonna stay there?
- I don't know.
- You know, I'm talking
to the turtle again.
We're having deep conversations
about life and love.
- Please. Just--just go.
- [sighs] I'm sorry.
I made a bad decision.
But you know
what Julia Ormond says.
- Who's Julia Ormond?
- Not her.
You know, the--the financial
lady with the rooster head?
Anyway,
she says that bad decisions
make teachable moments.
- So what did you learn?
- I learned
that I'm a complete idiot.
And I miss you.
And I'm lonely.
- Nancy's lonely, too.
- [sighs]
- So now we're
in the delivery business.
- [sighs]
She's in a fog, man.
- What the hell is
in those cars anyway?
- Dong fog.
It's eating her brain.
- I mean, fake cash, sure.
- Ugh. I can't even stand
to watch them together.
- But what else--
like, guns, people?
- She presents like a baboon.
You know,
with the flared anus.
- Never, ever say that word.
- Which--
"flared" or "anus"?
- Either.
[footsteps approaching]
- [sighs]
- So what's in the car?
- Nothing.
- What do you mean "nothing"?
- I mean, obviously something,
but I tore
every single one apart.
- Shady S.O.B.
- "Stay in your lane."
I am in my lane.
- Yeah, you are.
- He's in my lane.
- Yeah, he is.
- 'Cause you know
who's gonna go down for this
when he gets caught smuggling
whatever it is he's smuggling.
- Yeah, you.
Well, us.
- Hey, there he is.
- What's he doing?
- Hey, now.
- Ooh. Nuh-uh.
- Yuh-huh.
- Hmm.
-Mm-hmm.
Sweetie,
it's probably just business.
- Yeah, I mean,
what do they say?
You know, why make a sale when
you can make a loyal customer?
- Right, I mean, relationships
are everything in, you know...
- The biz.
- Yeah.
[engine turning over]
- Hey, maybe we should grab
a snack or, like,
a smoothie or something.
- I'm so hungry.
- Drive.
[engine turning over]
.
[fast hip-hop music]
♪
- What, next point wins?
- You better D up.
- Oh!
- Yay!
Good game, baby.
[grunts]
- Anybody got next?
[man speaking indistinctly
over PA]
- [exhales sharply]
You know what?
Maybe next time. I got to...
- Promise to take it easy.
- Well, no,
I got my shift so...
- Ah, you worried you might
get schooled, huh?
- [chuckles]
- Come on, quick game to three.
- Uh...
Three, huh?
- Quick game to three.
- Okay.
Did play in college?
- Let's just say
I'm still bitter
that Carolina took
Jordan over me.
Oh!
[chuckles]
- Looks like they made
the right choice.
[both chuckle]
- Where you from?
- 313,
born and raised.
- Ooh.
You married?
- Yep.
- How long?
- 22 years.
[rim rattles, net swishes]
- Whoo! 22.
How many good years?
- All of them good.
- All of them good?
Lucky man.
Must be hard
being married to a cop.
- You know what? I should
probably get out of here--
- No, no, no, come on, man.
Come on, man.
I haven't rolled with somebody
who can actually play ball
since Baltimore.
You know what I miss the most?
- What's that?
- Ah. The food.
[grunts]
[net swishes]
- The food?
We got the best Coney dog
game in the world here.
- Yeah,
I been living off of them.
- Yeah? Lafayette or American?
- Lafayette.
- You complaining?
- Well, I'm just more of a...
home-cooked-meal
kind of guy--Oh!
[sighs]
Your wife got
cooking skills, huh?
- My wife?
Uh...
Yeah, yeah,
I mean, yeah, for--yeah.
- What's her go-to?
- You know, um...
[stammers] Lasagna, whatever.
- Oh, boom.
[net swishes]
Game.
- Good game.
- You didn't say lasagna,
did you?
- Uh...yeah, I guess I--did I?
I said that?
- That's like my death row meal
right there.
- That's your jam
right there, huh?
- Oh, yeah.
- [laughs]
Home-cooked.
Yeah.
- Look girl, if you
don't stop moving your head...
So which one is Alex again?
- You always forget.
- Curly afro or zitty braces?
- Afro!
- Okay, chill.
- Janelle says he likes me.
- "What is your favorite food?
Mine is pizza."
- You think?
- Oh, it's on.
- But he put the same thing
in Rochelle's locker.
- The same note...with all
those stupid questions?
- Plus fav movie and fav song.
- Let me tell you something
about the boys, baby girl.
They love to put their stuff
in a whole bunch of lockers.
- All at the same time?
- Oh, yeah.
So, just when you think
your locker is special,
they are working lockers
all over town.
You know what I'm saying?
Trying to keep
their options open,
'cause there's a bunch out
there to choose from, right?
Different sizes,
shapes, colors.
- Ours all look the same.
- And they don't even bother
to hide it now.
Just all out in public,
all janky-like.
So, if I were you, I would keep
that locker closed up tight
for as long as possible.
You hear me?
Babe...
it is so real out there
right now.
- You like my hair, Daddy?
- I love it, baby.
- Hey, y-you just about done?
- You invited him to dinner?
- What was I supposed to do?
- How about not do that?
- He invited himself.
- My name is
on that hostage list.
- Your maiden name, right?
- Yeah.
- Okay, so he might not know.
- He's FBI, Stanley.
- Babe, he--he--he wants
to bring his boyfriend.
- So?
- So what's he gonna do--
shake us down
at the dinner table?
Maybe he just--
maybe it's just dinner.
- Have you seen any episode
of "Columbo", like, ever?
- [sighs]
- What's this?
- This? This is me not getting
hauled off in cuffs,
me not doing life
without parole.
And these?
These are my children
not dressing up for Christmas
to come visit me in prison.
Your new bestie can enjoy
his home-cooked meal
in his own home.
- You want me to just
drop these off?
- Yep.
- 'Cause that's not
going to be weird.
- I don't care.
- He's gonna think
we're hiding something.
- We are hiding something.
- [sighs]
It's not a good look.
- You want to know
what's not a good look?
You at the dinner table
doing the shaky leg.
- What are you talking about?
- You got no poker face, babe.
And I love you for it,
but it's gonna bring
the both of us down...hard.
- I'll drop the dinner off.
- Yeah, you will.
- ♪ What is the word?
♪ An unhuman search
♪
♪ Memories touching
♪ Heavy fog masking
♪ I am a vessel
♪
♪ Are you a vessel?
[toys squeaking]
♪
- I'm sorry,
I was gonna do that.
- When?
- Uh...
Well, I had to--
I had to make dinner.
- It's not that complicated.
- Well, and then I had
to get them in the bath
and get them to bed.
- No one wants
to come home to this.
- Emma is upset about her hair,
and Kenny is getting
his butt kicked in Krav Maga.
And then Janey
won't wear pajamas.
I don't know
if you noticed,
but all that kid
likes to do right now is--
- Yeah, I know. She does that.
- Yeah, well...
while I'm reading
her bedtime stories?
- It's her time.
She just sits there,
like, with her hands--
- It's normal, Dean.
- Okay, well, I'm exhausted.
- Well, don't shame her.
- It's exhausting.
- Yeah.
- I tried to put the booster
seats in the Malibu,
but I couldn't
get Janey's to budge.
- The latch gets stuck.
You've got to wiggle it.
- When Danny is in the front
seat, I turn the air bags off
and then keep them on
with Kenny--is that right?
I just feel like the rules
keep changing.
You okay?
[upbeat music]
♪
[horn honks]
[horn honking]
♪
[tires squeal]
.
- But I had the illest
second rebuttal, man.
I was all like, "Guess what.
"The imperative's on your ass.
There's no solvency here.
"Your case is inherently
non-unique,
and your argument
is moot, bitch!"
- Whoo!
So did you win or what?
- Headed to Nationals, dog.
- Nice.
[both laugh]
So my man here is, like,
a college-level debater.
- Well, then this
is all kinds of wrong.
- Can you tell us what it is?
- Um...
I'm not getting
much of a reading here.
- Think it's synthetic?
- Let's see.
Fo sho.
- [sighs]
- What does that even mean?
Well, could be anything
from Special K, vitamin E,
Kibbles and Bits, gamma-H,
barbies, phennies,
roachies, egg rolls.
- Okay, check it.
This one right here--
- Yeah.
- PD 155. It's like a statin
I think they call it.
- Jesus.
- What does that do to you?
- It lowers cholesterol?
- What, like, robo-tripping?
Like, you got to pop
a ton of them or...?
- I don't know.
My--my dad just pops one
in the morning with milk.
But, yeah, you--you got a
pretty diverse portfolio here.
- Um, Prevacid, that's gonna be
for heartburn.
Beta blockers for
blood pressure.
Ooh, I think this might
actually be
some sort
of antidepressant.
Would have to cross-reference.
- I'm sorry.
So these are all just,
like, normal-people drugs?
- That's what it looks like.
- So there's nothing here
that a junkie would want?
- A junkie
with arterial plaque buildup?
- Is this the statin
or the, um, blood pressure?
I can't tell.
- Let me see here.
Hmm.
L 159...
is a boner pill.
- Great. Here's more.
- Thank you. [pops lips]
- So we sell drugs now.
- Hmm.
This one
doesn't have a number.
- It might be an Altoid.
- Or Oxy.
What if it was Oxy?
- [chuckling]
- I am on the board
of D.A.R.E., okay?
And the FBI guy has been
sniffing around Stan.
- Well, does he have anything,
or is he just sniffing?
- He loves to sniff.
- I don't know.
But I can't afford to be
a drug dealer right now.
- But these drugs
are good for people.
- Who knew there was
a black market
for, um, acid-reflux pills?
Not me.
- It's pretty cool.
- Are y'all for real?
- What? It's not fair.
We deserve a cut.
- 'Cause that's
what it's about.
- What else would it be about?
Drug Beth?
- [scoffs]
Whatever.
- Wait, what's Drug Beth?
- Counterfeit Beth, Drug Beth,
and you know
he's got a Gun Beth
and a Blood Diamond Beth...
- Okay.
- And a Human Trafficking Beth.
- Let's just take it easy.
- Oh, so now you're cool
with the fog?
- Our values have realigned.
- Our girl is a side piece.
- You think I care
who he sleeps with?
I so don't.
I'm like--
I'm like, "Who cares?"
I don't--
And he's making money
off our backs.
- Yeah. Yeah, and with
our asses on the line.
- So what? We just say,
"Cut us in, pretty please"?
- No, we take every pill
from every car,
and we bleed him dry.
- Hell, yeah.
- And then he shoots us
in the face.
- He can't shoot us in the face
if we have his product.
- Can't he?
- He won't.
- Won't he?
[jazzy music]
- Good morning, Mrs. Boland.
- Good morning, Linda.
- Hey, guess what.
- What did I say?
- I let him cry, and it worked.
- Told you.
♪
George?
I would like you to show
my friend Darren here
how to open
an air-bag compartment.
- What?
- Yeah, I got a--
I got a school project.
♪
- Yes!
- Keep it coming.
♪
[musical flourish]
[brakes squeal]
How was school?
- You're being a stalker.
- Well, you're making me
be one.
- It's weird.
- Well, I'd be a lot less weird
if you'd just come home.
- Nancy's making vegan pizza.
- You know she's
gonna try to slip you
some of that nut cheese.
- What do you want?
- Can I just show you
something?
Pick a prize!
Any prize.
[children chattering
indistinctly]
Look, I feel bad
that you feel bad,
so I got you a present.
- You got me a mall.
- Well, look. Uh, here.
Huh? It basically, like,
lives your entire life for you.
It's obviously really dumb,
but I feel like it's gonna make
all your friends super jelly.
- How do you have
the money for this?
- I picked up some
extra shifts.
- At your grocery store?
- Excuse me,
why do you say it like that?
It is literally a grocery
store, and, you know,
me and your auntie Beth
are working on something.
- What?
- Like a
"new business venture" thingy.
- What?
- We are diversifying
our portfolio,
and I am projecting some
extremely sick profits, okay?
- Now you're just saying
random words.
- No, Sadie, I'm not.
I'm trying to
explain to you, but I--
- You're lying again.
- What do you mean again?
- You lie about everything.
- No, I don't.
- About Dad.
Where you're going, why you're
late, why you're early.
- I'm never early.
- You want me to come home?
- Yes, please.
- Tell me where
you got the money.
- Does this mean
you don't want the watch?
Sadie.
[sighs]
[laughter, indistinct chatter]
- Ah, Mommy's home.
Hi, Mommy. Hey, babe.
- Hi, Mommy.
- We've, uh--we got company.
Say hi to Mommy.
It's Agent Turner
and his boyfriend.
[dramatic music]
- [scoffs]
- Well, I am happy to meet you.
Call me Jimmy.
- Hi, there. Hi.
- Mm, uh, this is Douglas.
- How you doing?
- [chuckles]
- Your kids are hilarious.
- Yeah, Little Money
was playing
his piano recital
for them...twice.
- [chuckles]
Lucky you.
- And you really put your foot
in the meal you sent us.
Can always tell when something
is made with love.
- Oh, that came through, huh?
- Mm.
So I just had to say
thank you face-to-face.
- Oh, it's not necessary.
- Well, Rosemary Turner
would disagree.
She would say,
"Son, you never
return a dish empty."
- Oh, uh,
you brought dinner?
- Oh, yeah.
It's payback time.
- [chuckles]
It's so nice, right?
- [chuckles] So nice.
[man laughs]
- Um...
- You really made this
mac and cheese from scratch?
- For real for real.
- You think it's better
than the box?
- I mean, the box stuff...
[continues indistinctly]
.
[water running]
[water stops]
[door opens, closes]
- Where is it?
- I trusted you.
- That's your fault.
- They're my cars.
- My money.
- My dealership.
- Where is it?
- Not here.
- You know, I think this thing
with me and you
has run its course, yeah?
- Well, then you won't
get your pills.
- I got more coming.
- Not in my cars, you don't.
- Where is it?
- I'll tell you
when you cut us in.
- Oh, you think
you special, huh?
- You need me.
- You ain't nothing.
I don't need you.
- So go buy a sketchy lot
down on Carson.
Use fake cash,
staff it up with gang bangers.
That won't look shady at all.
How long do you think
till the Feds show up, huh?
A month? A week?
They're already watching you.
They just need a reason.
[dramatic music]
You need me
so they don't find one.
♪
[door opens]
- Mama? Can you lay with me?
- Yes, sweetie.
I promise.
- Yeah.
- Hey, okay.
Let's go get some popcorn.
What the hell was that about?
- Business.
- Did he--did he have a gun?
- No.
- I think he did.
- He was upset.
- Why?
- Why what?
- Why him?
- What are you
even talking about?
- It's like you're
losing your mind.
You're putting yourself
in these insane situations.
Is it the tattoos?
Is that it?
- Come on.
- The danger? The strange?
I don't get it at all,
and I want to get it.
- You know what I want to get?
- What?
- What was it about Amber?
- What does that have
to do with--
Or anyone else at Team Boland
that sat on your penis.
- [scoffs] I was lonely.
And I didn't know
how to say it.
- Well, you said something.
- Loud and clear, huh?
- It's business.
- Okay.
- And it's for us.
My God.
- So, uh,
Harry has this one buddy--
- Frankie.
- Mm-hmm.
Smallest one in the crew.
- Causes big-time
trouble, though.
- Right? But I had to get real
with Little Money
and let him know
that at the end of the day,
his buddy Frankie's skin
doesn't look like his.
- Mm-hmm.
- You feel me?
And so, when you are all
at the mall...
[stammering]
And it goes sideways...
- And you know it will.
- Mm-hmm.
- You know, when they start
rounding folks up...
- Where's Frankie going to be?
- Home.
- And where are you?
- Handcuffed on the curb
with a flashlight in your face.
- Mm.
- I mean, he is only six.
- All right, well, you know,
it's never too young
to give the boy perspective.
- So first day
of pre-K, right?
- Oh, for you, that early?
- Oh, Pops laid out
all the rules.
Don't run with scissors,
don't play in the street,
and don't get pissed when they
assume you're on financial aid.
- I mean, but you were,
so there's that.
[both laugh]
- I don't know.
- What? What don't
you know, baby?
- That light in their eyes
right now.
I don't want to put it out
so soon.
- Either way it's going out.
- That why you're a cop?
- How you mean?
- Show 'em you're
one of the good guys.
- Hmm.
Uh, maybe.
[footsteps running]
- Ladies and gentlemen,
take your seats,
the show is about to begin.
- Here we go.
- Tickets, please!
- [laughs]
I got a ticket.
- There you are.
- [chuckles]
- All right, good luck.
- Now, how long you guys
been playing?
- I've been playing four years.
- [sighs]
How you doing?
- You?
- I'm good. [stammering]
I think we're good.
- Daddy, come fix the bench.
He can't reach the peddles.
- Huh? Oh, okay.
Copy.
- Need a hand?
- Concert's over already?
- I think the maestro
is getting put to bed.
- You got a good one in there.
- Yeah? I should keep him?
- Mm-hmm.
You guys are sweet together.
- Eh...
20 years of marriage, you get
to know a person real good.
- I bet.
- I should have offered you
whipped cream.
- It'll be worse for him.
You get that, right?
- Sorry?
- When they find out
he took the pen cap.
He don't look like
Lil Frankie either.
The part that kills me
is that he just wants
your son to look at him
and see a good cop.
So you let me know
how you want to play it.
[plates rattle]
It's pie time, y'all.
- Hey, now!
- I want whipped cream on mine!
[indistinct chatter]
.
- And did you find everything
that you needed today?
- Almost.
Hi, Darren.
- Hi, Mrs. Cooper.
Good morning.
- Say hi to your mother.
- Will do.
And you have
a Fine and Frugal day,
Mrs. Cooper.
- Here you go, Mrs. Cooper.
- Thanks.
- [on PA] Fine and Frugal
fresh flowers, $5.99 and up.
- What are
your parents like, Darren?
- Oh, so dope.
- Oh.
Really?
You're--you're cool with them?
- Dude, we're, like,
best friends.
- Hmm. But they--they obviously
don't know what you do.
- Oh, no, they do.
They do.
They just don't mess
with my steez.
- Oh.
- They're just, like,
I don't know, super chill--
kind of like you are
with, uh...
S--I'm sorry, what's her name?
- S-Sadie.
- Yeah, yeah, yeah. But, like,
when my dad first found out,
he got super freaked out.
He was all like,
"Colleen, he could go to jail."
But my mom just goes, you know,
"Sometimes bad decisions
make teachable moments."
You know, and I'm like, "you
know, I'm making money, man."
[conversation fades]
[engine revving]
[tires screeching]
- Jesus.
- Get in the car.
- No!
[shifter clacks]
- Get in the car right now,
young lady.
- "Young lady"?
- Now!
- I have plans with Nancy.
- It is my night,
and you will sleep at my house.
- Tell me where
you got the money.
- I'm going to explain
a few things to you.
What I did was wrong,
and I am sorry.
It was confusing
and hurtful for you,
and I feel sick
about that.
Believe me, I do.
I wish that I had handled it
differently.
That being said,
I am your parent,
and if I tell you to do
something, I need it done.
Three nights a week and every
other weekend, you are mine.
So get your ass
in the damn car, now.
[car door opens]
[indistinct chatter]
- [breathes deeply]
Here, baby.
- Thanks.
- Okay! My peoples, all right,
I'm thinking
if we leave right now,
we can be there before 5:00.
- Where?
- Happiest place on earth.
- Disneyland?
- My bad--poor choice of words.
The zoo! Ha!
Just as fun, right?
- No.
- Come on.
- They have a new baby penguin.
- They do?
- I was thinking we could get
some funnel cakes,
you know,
ride the elephants.
- Feed the monkeys?
- That's what
I'm talking about. 100%.
Oh, uh, oh, what about those
nitrogen ice cream things.
We could take videos of the
smoke coming out of our mouths.
- Yeah.
- Pet some giraffes,
and then--then we could find
that baby penguin
and then buy some
overpriced pictures of us...
[clicks tongue]
With the baby penguin
and then come back home
with a big, happy stomachache.
- Yeah! Hey, hey, hey!
- Yeah, I'm liking the energy.
Mommy not so much.
- [sighs]
Don't you have a shift?
- I took the night off
because I love my family,
and I need to get
my Instagram story game up.
[chuckles]
Hey, so kids three and under
still get in for free.
You think you can pull it off?
- No way.
- Okay, so get some sunscreen,
some towels, and a sweatshirt.
Fun bus leaves in 30.
[slaps counter]
30! Chop-chop.
Sara, what's up?
Come on, let's go.
Come on, now. We got to
celebrate a little, right?
- You guys go.
I got to run errands.
- No, you're gonna
miss the fun train?
- I thought it was a bus.
- I see you.
You're paying attention.
Good job.
Okay, who's not ready?
Who's not ready?
Harry, you ready?
- Ready.
- Sara, what is wrong with you?
Come on!
- Let's--let's go!
[somber music]
[door opens]
- Bye, Mommy!
♪
- Bye.
Whatever you need to know.
♪
But he has to stay out of it.
- He's gonna be fine.
- Thank you.
- You will, too.
♪
- Isn't this the part
where y'all arrest me?
- I don't want to do that.
You guys are good people.
- What do you want, then?
- Her.
♪
- Cars will keep
coming in from up north.
All you got to do is get them
to the appropriate parties
for distro.
- And what are we
talking about?
- 30.
- Please.
- Excuse me?
- My name's on the door.
- So what?
- So I have more to lose.
- 40.
- Do you want
your pharmacy back?
- Why--
Why don't you just tell me
what you're looking for?
- 50/50.
- [chuckles]
- Assuming you're buying
generic Canadian,
with your typical
drug-dealer markup,
your profit margins should be
at least five times
what I'm making
washing your fake cash.
And if it's not,
you're doing something wrong,
and I'll happily look
into that.
- You look good
behind that desk.
- Thank you.
- Hell, you'd look
so much better on top of it.
- Do we have a deal or not?
- Mm-hmm.
- Great.
- Where is it?
- Gratiot and Mack.
- Storage unit?
- Keys to the kingdom.
- Right...
- By the way...
I would have taken 40.
[Mattiel's
"Count Your Blessings"]
♪
- ♪ Your shoes keep turning
different shades of blue ♪
♪ The colors of the other
fools before you ♪
♪ And skin keeps turning
different shades of red ♪
♪
♪ The colors
of the other voice ♪
♪ That's swimming
in your head ♪
♪ Make yourself
at home again ♪
♪ Count your blessings,
one to ten ♪
♪ Your body
will be whole again ♪
♪ Make yourself
at home again ♪
♪ Count your blessings,
one to ten ♪
♪
- No big deal or whatever.
You can just call me
the bun ninja.
YouTubed it, right?
Take a vacuum cleaner,
you suck up the hair.
Sounds crazy
and a bit dangerous,
but it totally works.
What?
- Take off your pants.
- [chuckles]
What?
♪
- Take off your pants...
now.
♪
- Right here?
- Oh, my God.
♪
Beth.
- No, no, no.
- What do you want?
Just tell me what you want.
- Just--just--
just do it.
- Oh, okay.
- Hurry up.
♪
Come on.
Do it.
♪
- Arms up.
[blow lands]
Arms up!
Chin down. Oh!
- Excuse me. Hi, Dean.
I'm Kenny's dad.
- Mm-hmm.
- This has been
so, so great for him.
Um, you know,
he's got some anxiety stuff,
but he's doing
so much better now.
- He's, uh--he's, uh,
such a great kid, you know?
- Yeah, he--he thinks you're
the--you know, the coolest.
- [laughing]
I don't know about that.
- He said you're former
Mossad or whatever?
- That's the rumor, right?
[both laughing]
- So is it true?
- That was
a long time ago, man.
[laughs]
- Yeah, yeah.
Did you ever,
like, kill a dude?
- Jesus, man.
- I know, right?
- [chuckles]
You're hilarious.
- That would be nuts.
[both laughing]
But have you?
- [laughing wildly]
- [laughing]
[laughter fades]