.
- Previously on "Good Girls":
- I'm giving you the keys
to the kingdom here.
Kingdom's in your name.
[shutter door rattling]
- He took it back.
I'm about to be arrested
for murder!
- Hey, I don't work while
I'm on vacation.
- That's what I am? Work?
Your money's cooked.
The Feds know everything.
- I'm going to make it as easy
as possible for the kids.
I need to protect my family.
- Do you still love
each other?
- I found this thing online.
We would rent a place
and the kids would stay here,
and you and I would switch
off every couple of days.
- Okay.
- How's it going with
the sister?
- Not in the Friend Zone.
- Already?
- You're FBI!
- I love you.
- So what happens next?
- I'm sure you have
much bigger fish to fry
than a mother of four.
- Come on.
You are way more than that.
- What's your angle here, man?
- Go on record saying you saw
Leslie Peterson's murder.
How Beth Boland chopped him up.
- Is he going
to take Daddy again?
- I'm still hoping
we can work it out.
- They're counterfeiters!
- If we dig deeper--
- You get motive
for the murder too.
- You are ratting out a gang!
You think they're going
to let you talk?
You gotta disappear for good.
I meant what I said.
If it's not us, it'll be them.
You'll get the other half when
we know you left the country.
- He was stealing from me,
wasn't he?
- [yells] I'm gonna kill him!
It was an accident.
- She murdered him, Beth.
What are we supposed to do
with this?
- What color
was Boomer's hair?
- We call the cops.
- You want to explain
that we dumped the wrong body?
- You rather get put away for
murdering a guy who's not dead?
- Thought you might want
your key back.
Annie Banannie.
[Mattiel's
"Baron's Sunday Best" plays]
- ♪ La, la, la
♪
♪ You got 20 foot ceilings
on the Lower East side ♪
♪ Charging people money
for carbon dioxide ♪
♪ You got a silver spoon when
you took your first step ♪
♪ Yeah, it's so much fun
when you get upset ♪
♪ A-Baron is a-wearin'
his Sunday best ♪
♪ Yes, Baron is a-wearin'
♪ Everybody knows
he couldn't care less ♪
♪ A-Baron is a-wearin'
his Sunday best ♪
♪ La, la, la
[scatting]
♪
♪ La, la, la
[scatting]
The croissants are filled
with chocolate-hazelnut,
and that's streusel
with Saigon cinnamon
and burnt orange
morning roll.
- No buckle?
- Not today.
Don't be shy!
[beep]
- Whenever you're ready,
Mrs. Boland.
- My name is
Elizabeth Irene Boland.
And this is how I murdered
Leslie Peterson.
[country music]
♪
- ♪ Light the candle
by the bed ♪
♪ I whisper softly...
- So who's the new manager?
Whoever it is,
he's phoning it in.
Nana got sold a yogurt
from September.
No way he's rotating
the milk.
- We are being charged with
your murder, you piece of--
- Would anyone like
a soft drink?
[dish clinks]
Girls?
- No, thank you.
- All good.
- I'll have a Tab.
- Oh.
♪
- What are you doing?
- Calling the cops and telling
them that you're alive.
- You can't do that.
- Watch.
- They'll kill me.
- The cops?
- The gang!
- Screw this fool!
You're gonna go in there,
you're gonna show them
your new Flavor Savor,
and you're gonna tell them
you've never been better.
- Oh. Oh yeah, okay.
- Yeah, 'cause we're not about
to go down for your sorry ass.
- Then I'll tell them about
the other sorry ass.
- [scoffs]
What other sorry ass?
- The one in the trash bag.
[footsteps approaching]
[ice rattling]
I'm gonna need a straw,
Nana.
I saw how you threw him
in the back of a minivan
like a wet dog.
- How?
- I hid out behind Mary Pat's.
Lived off the land.
You can drink your own urine
till it's brown.
[slurp]
- You were like 100 yards
from a 7-Eleven.
- They have cameras.
- I'm sorry.
So that's your plan?
You're gonna hole up
like Anne Frank up there
for the rest of your life?
- No.
There's a surgeon in Tampa.
Does full facial
reconstruction.
He's the only guy Escobar
would ever use.
It's like witness protection,
but only better.
You know, I get a new face,
I get to start over.
- That's...
the dumbest thing
I've ever heard.
- I want my life back, okay?
You know, whatever.
What do you care?
[sniffs]
Thank you.
- How much?
- All of it.
Nose, cheekbones, jaw.
Nana, get my vision board.
- Which one?
The girls or the cards?
- The face one.
- How much does it cost?
- No!
- You couldn't afford it.
- Neither can you.
- We are not going down
this road again.
We're gonna buy him a new face
and he's going to ghost us.
Again.
- First you show cops old face.
- First you show me money.
- Well,
who are you even going for?
- Rupert Grint.
- The ginger from Harry Potter?
- Yes, the doctor said he's
closest to my bone structure.
You know what?
It's not that far off.
Where is she with
the vision board? Nana!
- Jesus.
[pounding on door]
[suspenseful music]
♪
[cell phone vibrating]
- Hi.
- Hey.
- How are you?
- What's going on?
- Your neighbors said
you moved out.
- Yeah, something like that.
- Where'd you go this time?
Epcot? Six Flags?
- What do you want,
Elizabeth?
♪
- I need some money again.
- I gave you
the keys to the kingdom.
- I know.
- But you didn't want them.
- If I could ask anyone
but you, I would.
♪
I'm in real trouble,
all right?
- That Fed's got
a real hard-on for you, huh?
- Not the good kind.
- Thing is, I'm a little dry
right now. You know how it is.
What are you doing?
- What do you mean?
- I mean, right now.
What are you doing?
♪
- Nothing.
Just getting my hair cut.
- Don't.
- What?
- Don't cut it.
- [chuckles]
It's just a little trim.
- I like pushing it
out of your face.
Yeah, just like that.
♪
Ha, you got me.
So listen,
I wish I could help.
- You could.
You choose not to.
- Ah, don't be like that,
Elizabeth.
[click]
[beeping]
- Like a toddler
playing with his food,
the orca tosses the seal pup
high into the air
before devouring him,
and what began as...
- Turner's got a warrant.
[narrator continues
indistinctly]
- How long?
- 48 hours.
- Let's get out of here.
Let's just go right now.
- I have a son.
- So just bring him!
- He has a dad.
- [sighs]
[narrator continues
indistinctly]
- [sighs]
When it goes down, I got...
I got to do my job.
[sighs]
- [sighs]
Do you want to make cookies?
[chuckles]
- What?
- Never done it.
- Yeah, why not?
[sighs]
- It's a suicide mission.
- It worked.
So this guy would go
to a bar, order a beer,
order lunch like a burger,
awesome blossom, whatever
and then he would
take a coaster,
put it on the top
of his glass
like he was going to
the bathroom or something.
Excuse me! I'm sorry.
Could we get some ketchup?
Then he would rob the place,
come back with a bag of cash,
enjoy the game and, like,
finish his lunch.
- Stupid is what it is.
- It's kind of
a perfect alibi.
- Not if he was on "20/20"
talking about
how he got caught.
- What do you want to do?
- Call the cops on
that weasely little bitch.
- Okay.
- Okay and then he, um,
tells 'em about Jeff
and they dig him
out of my front yard.
- We do this,
we're straight up hoodlums.
- I hear you, but Jeff...
- It's insane!
- Thank you.
Jeff.
- We didn't kill him.
- Excuse me. I'm sorry.
Can we also get
a side of ranch?
- Ooh, yes. Ranch.
Thanks.
- But Turner will make it
look like we did.
- [sighs]
- Couple of cameras,
one security guard.
Everybody is old.
I'm not talking
Liam Neeson old,
I'm talking, like,
Benjamin Button old.
I mean, like, little.
Like I mean I could take them,
you know?
Honestly, I'm not sure
why we waited so long.
Who's winning?
[customers shouting,
laughing]
.
- This one's for friendship,
that one's for cooking.
- What's happening?
- That one's for navigation.
- I FaceTime'd your mother.
- This one's for service.
- Why would you do that?
- I want them to
know her more.
- You feeling okay, babe?
- You're facing
three to five.
- Okay,
but they still got you.
[clattering]
- Tomorrow,
I'm robbing a bank.
[suspenseful music]
♪
- All children! Please
report to the dance floor!
All children
to the dance floor, please!
- What's going on?
- Making moments, kid.
- Can't we do it
in the morning?
- If you plan it,
it's not a moment! Duh!
Now I'm gonna need you to get
up and shake some booty!
Let's go!
- I got to pay that
little dick off.
- Ruby.
- Or get life for killing him.
- Ruby--
- Or life for dumping a body,
dragging it all over town
and using it to mulch
my girl's flower bed.
- Yeah, but if you kick
in the bank part
then you're gonna
get life plus 20.
- They got warrants, Stan.
♪
- [sighs]
- So it's got two closets so we
can both keep some stuff there.
It's kind of all we can afford,
but I--I think it's going help
it feel normal for the kids.
- It reminds me of our old
place in Hamtramck.
- [chuckles]
With the linoleum?
- Do you remember that
the hallway
always smelled like pierogis?
- Oh God,
what was that about?
It was terrible.
Like pierogis 24/7.
- I think it was a candle
or something.
- Candle? Who does that?
Nobody has ever wanted
that smell ever. Ugh!
- I know, but every night.
Every night, pierogis.
- Terrible. I like pierogis.
- I love pierogis.
- Oh, my God.
What happened to us?
♪
[chuckles]
- ♪ This too shall pass
♪ Over you
♪ Oh oh oh
♪ Oh oh
- Which one?
- First Detroit.
Warren and Brush.
♪
- All right, do it at 2:00.
- Why?
- Uh, shift change.
Less cops there.
♪
[sighs]
[TV chatter]
[background chatter]
- Excuse me. Hi, um,
they're in the bathroom
but, um, I can order.
Um, she's going to have
the black bean burger,
and she'll have
the chicken quesadilla.
- Our kingdom is fully stocked
and ready to serve your needs.
We offer wholesale pricing.
So why sleep like a pauper
when you can sleep
like a king?
Come visit Detroit's
premiere mattress store
and we'll give you the keys
to the kingdom.
[hip-hop music]
♪
[click, clattering]
-So if I'm depositing
checks and cash,
do I list it separate?
- I'm not sure.
- Or is it just, like,
one total?
- I wouldn't know.
- Don't you work here?
♪
[line ringing]
- Oh, come on!
Come on, come on, come on,
come on, come on.
- So you put the subtotal
right here.
- Mmm. Mm-hmm.
- See?
[cell phone vibrating]
♪
- Don't!
- And how would you like this?
- Two 5s and a 10, please.
[chuckles]
- Don't forget my sucker.
Purple flavor, please.
- Thank you.
[chuckles]
Take care.
- Okay.
.
[folk music]
♪
- ♪ La la la la la la la
♪ La la-la
-It's like $400 cashmere.
- All in my name.
- Why?
- Think I can take some
for Stan?
- So where is he?
- Who is he?
[camera shutter clicks]
It's not Photoshopped.
- Where is it?
- Dequinder and McNichols.
- Where?
- In a storage unit.
- Nobody's gonna
low five you, dick.
- Give me the key.
- After you go in to the cops.
- Oh, I'll go in.
- Yeah, you will.
- After I get the key.
- We're not doing that again.
- Okay, well,
then deal's off.
- Then you don't get
your money.
- Oh yeah, I do.
- Nuh-uh.
- Uh-huh.
- How's that?
- Ever watch "Storage Wars"?
You'll be in jail,
you won't make rent,
all this will go to auction,
and I'll get it for less
than you bitches will pay
hustling smokes in the yard.
- Okay, wait, wait.
Just wait.
- Uh, Nana? 86 the milk,
company's leaving.
- What--what if
you FaceTime the cops?
- Yeah, yeah!
Boomer, FaceTime 'em!
- I'll give you the key.
You can hold it.
- Or--or Snapchat.
That'd be cool too.
- That's like a video,
so it's not live.
- Why is that not live?
- It's just not.
It's a video
and then you send it.
- What's live? Periscope!
- Boomer, please!
Just--just think about it
for one second, okay?
- Nah, my way's better.
I get to stay dead.
[Connie Converse's "Trouble"
plays]
♪
- ♪ Ever since we met
the world's been upside down ♪
♪ And if you don't stop
troubling me ♪
♪ You'll drive me
out of town ♪
♪ But if you go away
as trouble ought to do ♪
♪ Where will I find another
soul to tell my trouble to ♪
♪
- I got us tickets to Bey.
Happy birthday.
- It's not for two months.
- Surprise!
- Are you trying to age me?
- Take Stan, okay?
- What if he's in jail?
- He won't be.
- How do you know?
- 'Cause he's going
to take that deal.
It's my fault.
- Okay, I'm cutting you off.
- I'm turning myself in.
- Okay.
- Why should it be you
or Annie?
I made you do it.
Can I have my drink back?
- Made us? Which part?
- The store, the money, Jeff,
all of it.
Take your pick.
- We could've said no.
- But you never say no.
- I am not your yes man.
- No,
you're a really good friend.
[sighs]
Do you think she'll open with
"Single Ladies"?
- This is crazy.
- No, that'd be an encore.
- I'm not gonna let you.
- Then we all go down.
And what is that?
That's stupid?
- So now I'm stupid?
- Shut up.
Can I have my drink?
[song resumes]
- ♪ But if you go away,
as trouble ought to do ♪
♪ Where will I find
another soul ♪
♪ To tell my trouble to
- Ow! Too hard!
- Well,
you're just too delicious.
- What's, uh,
what's on tap for you today?
- [sniffles] The usual.
- Hmm, you made enough
for an army.
- Book club.
- All right, let's go, people.
Let's go.
- Come here.
[chuckles]
Oh!
- Go on, put it on.
Let's go.
[claps]
Come on. All right, let's go.
Move out!
Chop chop, chop chop.
- Dean.
You look nice.
- See you later.
- Yup.
- All right, let's go.
[claps]
[upbeat music]
- ♪ Oh, I love ya
♪ I can't be without ya
♪ Left all alone
♪ I still feel this way
about ya ♪
♪ Everything's clear
♪ Clear is here
♪ And everything
is as it appears ♪
♪ To be so
♪ Here,
am I dreaming? ♪
♪ I stand by...
- Gift from the D.A.
It's what we talked about.
Country club living,
time for good behavior.
All of it.
- And everyone else walks away?
- D.A. signed off.
Now you.
Where do you want to do this?
- I put out some sweets
in the other room.
My name is
Elizabeth Irene Boland,
and this is how I murdered
Leslie Peterson.
[engine running]
[click]
- Where's Hardee's?
♪
- And then I backed my car
over him.
And I wrapped him in a tarp.
- Officer Hill said in
his affidavit this morning
that you put the body
in the freezer.
- Does it matter?
- I'm afraid it does.
- How did you fit the body
in the freezer?
- You know those
electric knives,
the ones you use
at Thanksgiving?
- Do you remember starting
a fire in the lunchroom?
- No.
- And when the Principal
gave you detention,
you smashed in
his car windows?
- If I say yes,
can I get curly fries?
- Then you blamed it
on the special needs girl.
- I apologized for that.
- No, I did.
Then I gave them some story
about you having special needs
too so they'd keep you.
- I can't go in there.
- I can't keep making up
stories, Leslie.
- I am not a kid anymore,
Nana.
- Then go be a big boy.
- ♪ You know, we love ya
♪ We can't be without ya
♪ But we're at home
- You need a water
or something?
- That would be nice.
- Do you want to call
your husband?
- In a bit.
He's at a job interview.
- Oh.
This way.
- Hey, Jimmy.
How you been?
.
- Hey, how was, uh,
how was book club?
I lied.
I didn't read the book.
- I didn't get that job.
- Then it wasn't meant to be.
- Where we're getting money
from, I have no idea.
- We could put the
apartment thing on hold.
Until we can afford it,
you know?
- Yeah.
[chuckles] Smart.
[indistinct TV chatter]
- Oh, no!
- Like a fine wine.
Ooh, so good!
"I shall serve no fries
before their time."
- How many times
have you seen this?
- It's...impossible to count.
- [laughs]
Yeah, no, it's impossible.
- I shall serve no fries
before their time.
- [giggles]
[both laugh]
- Hey, move over.
- [groaning] I crashed.
[groans]
- So have you heard anything?
- Word is, Turner's got
so much egg on his face,
the D.A.'s talking about
tossing the whole thing.
- I mean...
you think it's, like,
overover?
- Well, if it is,
we are the stupidest, luckiest
sons of bitches in the world.
[sighs]
Never again though, right?
You're through with it.
Choose us from now on.
- Okay.
- Introducing the new Waterpik
whitening water flosser,
the first device that delivers
precision whitening
while you floss.
It restores your natural
whiteness in just four weeks.
- What I've noticed
the most
after using
the whitening water flosser
is how bright my smile is.
Um, I feel so much
more confident
in talking to people
with my smile
and also my breath is just
so much fresher
for hours after using it.
- The secret is Waterpik's
patented whitening
and fuser technology
that expertly mixes water with
a gentle whitening agent
to remove stubborn
and hard-to-reach stains.
The whitening water flosser
is clinically proven
to remove 25% more stains
than brushing alone.
It's up to 50% more effective
than string floss
for improving gum health--
- [yelling]
[brushing]
- Did you really go
to Michigan State?
- Hmm.
[spits]
Naval Academy.
[brushing]
- So you're, like,
super smart.
- [chuckles]
[clattering]
But you grew up
in Minneapolis, yes?
- Philly.
[clattering]
- Hmm.
Do you really like kids?
- [chuckles]
Yeah, I have one.
His name's Justin.
He's six.
Lives in Arizona.
[inhales]
[paper rips]
[toilet flushes]
- [sighs]
[water running]
- You know, they might
transfer me to Phoenix.
Since, um,
since all this went south.
- You mean the job?
- Yes.
- [sighs]
Well, that'd be good.
You could see your son.
- It's a direct flight.
- [chuckles]
Yeah.
Well...
I burn super easy.
- I'll buy you sunscreen.
- Let's, um...
[cap pops]
Let's just go to bed.
- [sobbing]
[gasps]
- I got you a gift.
- What is wrong with you?
- You know you're always saying
I don't help?
That's me helping.
[chuckles]
[mellow hip hop]
♪
- This right here?
That's your problem.
Take care of it.
- I already did.
- Nah, he's not just gonna
let you walk away now.
♪
- I fixed it.
- He knows your entire
bag of tricks, darling...
what you do,
who you are.
He even knows what makes
your garden grow.
Oh. my bad. [laughs]
Yeah, I might've let
that last one slip.
Now, a guy like that
can't let that slide.
- [sobbing]
- How does that saying go?
Cockle shells, silver bells,
bodies all in a row?
Ain't that right, boss?
♪
[gun cocks]
Come on.
Just like we practiced.
♪
.
[Lee Hazlewood's
"Won't You Tell Your Dreams"]
♪
♪ I've learned to do
♪ Some simple things
♪ Like lock the door
♪ And shut the lights
♪ And pay the paperboy
on time ♪
♪ And try to miss
you less each night ♪
♪ So please won't you tell
your dreams ♪
♪ Leave my room alone
♪ Please won't you tell
your dreams ♪
♪ To leave my room alone
- Wait, tighten this up...
Oh...
[indistinct chatter,
laughter]
Where'd you go so early today?
- ♪ I gave the laundry man
a beer ♪
- Hey, uh, you want some
French toast?
It's hot.
[hisses]
Ow, ow.
Want syrup?
- ♪ And took your picture off
the mirror ♪
♪ So please won't you tell
your dreams ♪
♪ To leave my room alone
♪ Alone
- That place with
the ball pit?
- No, that place is a zoo.
- The kids love it.
- Not enough Purell
in the world.
- What about that place with
the really good kid's menu?
- No, no, no.
Germy kid goes there.
The one with the mom
who talks a lot.
[indistinct echoing chatter]
[ominous bass sound]
♪
- Beth?
- You coming to lunch?
- No.
[funky music]
♪
[singing in French]
[crank]
♪
[knocking on door]
- Got a minute?
You know what I'm going to miss
most about this city?
Nothing.
- What about the lakes?
- Uh, I lived in corporate
housing
two blocks
from a muffler factory.
- I guess you were busy too.
- Hmm.
- Do you want milk?
- How are you going to fill
your time now, Mrs. Boland?
[timer ticking]
- [sighs] You know,
I just wanna be a mom.
- What about that garden?
- Are you gonna arrest me?
- [sighs]
I want to take a long vacation
with my fella.
Maybe hit up
one of those lakes.
- And then what?
- Thanks for the coffee.
[footsteps receding]
- Oh, my God
and then what?
- Let's see how you do.
[ticking]
[ding]
- Go and be a mom.
[door opening and closing]
[music resumes]
♪
[singing in French]
- Hey guys,
I made you something.
- What do you mean
you made it?
- It's literally, like,
nail polish remover,
hydrogen peroxide,
and bleach.
It's, like, so easy.
- It's kinda janky.
- Well, yeah,
because I used Dean's ink jet
just to see if it would work,
but we'd obviously get
a better printer and maybe
even a graphic designer.
There's this mom who has
a booth at the farmer's market.
She does business cards,
but she's super talented,
and she's divorced.
What?
- Don't "what" us.
- [chuckles]
She knows what's what.
- We can totally do
this without him.
[slow music]
♪
- You got this.
Come on.
♪
- I don't want it.
- Yeah, well,
I didn't get a gift receipt.
- Then why don't you do it?
- 'Cause it's on you.
- No, it's not!
- Yeah.
Yeah it is, mama.
- You put it on me.
- You asked for it.
- You put everything on me!
The money, the dealership.
- Not easy being king, right?
- You put it all on me
so it's never on you.
Nothing's ever on you!
- Yeah, well,
now you got
a bigger problem, don't you?
♪
- You think he's my problem?
- So put on your big girl
panties and take care of it.
- He's not my problem.
- Shut your mouth,
bitch, okay, and just--
[gunshot]
- Ah!
♪
[gunshot]
- Uhh--
O--
[coughing, groaning]
- [sobbing]
♪
- [groaning]
- Give me the gun.
Go.
Go!
- [mumbled speech, gurgling]
[groaning]
[gags, choked cough]
[gagging]
[groaning]
- You don't look so good,
buddy.
- [grunting]
[wheezing]
- What do they say?
One's the loneliness number?
- [breathing hard]
- It ain't gotta be.
Ah!
- [moans]
- You know this means
you're gonna owe me, right?
What do you say?
I call them now,
you still got odds.
- [strained laugh]
- We got a deal?
- [chuckles]
[laughter echoes]
- He's gone.
We're free.
♪
- ♪ In love
♪ Aware
♪ In love and aware
♪