Heaven and Earth will disappear,
but my words remain forever.
But no one knows the date now
when the end will be,
not even the angels.
No, nor even God's son.
Only the Father knows.
The world will be at ease,
banquets and parties and weddings,
just as it was in Noah's time
before the sudden coming of the flood.
People wouldn't believe
what was going to happen
until the flood actually arrived
and took them all away.
So shall my coming be.
Two men will be working together
in the fields,
and one will be taken, the other left.
Two women will be going about
their household tasks.
One will be taken, the other left.
So be prepared, for you don't know
what day your Lord is coming.
Morning.
You can talk. It's okay.
You're much better at this than me.
Maybe you should be in charge.
You like Siegfried and Roy,
the magic guys in Vegas?
They did tricks
with those beautiful tigers.
Every night, a tiger disappears,
and the tiger comes back.
They made calendars with those tigers.
They just laid right on top of them
like they were carpets.
It's just a matter of time before
one of those fuckers bites your face off.
- Go, go, go! Let's go, get in.
- Clear out!
Hurry up, come on, go!
Go, go!
- Hey, over here. Come ahead.
That's it. Keep moving.
Chief.
Yeah, go ahead.
Count's getting up there.
We're over 700,
and it's not even lunchtime.
You want us to try and slow the flow?
All are welcome, Dickie.
Copy that.
How you doing, Andy?
Let's go.
- Come on ! Go!
- Come on, keep moving. Let's go.
Keep it rolling.
Excuse me.
Officer, do we need to get wristbands?
No, ma'am, not anymore.
Is there somewhere we can park?
Uh, yeah. There's a campground
about a half-mile up the road.
Follow me.
Come on.
Come on. Let's go.
- It's Busey!
- ...in our town, okay?
-He's Departed. He's not--
-It's Busey.
I don't care who it is, all right?
There's a height ordinance.
Nothing above 15 feet.
You gotta take it down.
That dude on the pillar
is over 15 feet, man !
Whoa, whoa, whoa. Hang on.
The guy on the pillar
was grandfathered in.
-Hey, Chief.
-What's going on?
Uh, these gentlemen don't seem to wanna
deflate their little joke here.
All right, no, no. It is not a joke, okay?
Mr. Gary Busey's coming back from heaven
on the 14th.
How is he gonna know where to land?
All right.
Here's what I'm gonna do.
I'm gonna let you keep Gary up there,
but you guys have to be my deputies.
You see anyone or anything
that seems remotely dangerous,
call me, personally.
Nuts, man. Fucking nuts!
You never underestimate the spirit.
Yeah, man.
-That was smart.
-Yeah.
See what happens
when you make people feel important?
Should I be writing this down?
Listen, we're already over our number.
We're a few bodies short
down at the bridge.
You mind running down there
till roll call?
-No, not at all.
-All right.
And we got dinner tonight.
6:00 sharp. Don't forget.
5:30 works a little better for me.
Well, 6:00 works better for me.
Okay. 6:00 it is.
You guys do remember
it's my birthday today, right?
- Get to the bridge.
- All right, Chief.
The King of Babylon
had a dream,
and that dream was terrifying.
So, Daniel comes, he cracks his knuckles.
"Okay, tell me what you've got."
"I dreamed," says the King,
"of a great tree
stretching all the way to the heavens.
"A tree that provides
all things to all people,
"but then it was cut down, destroyed."
Daniel nods. "Ah."
"You know what it means?" asked the King.
"You are the tree," says Daniel.
"I am?" says the King.
"You are," answers Daniel.
"And you getting cut down
isn't the worst part either,
"because once you are down,
you will lose your mind.
"You will go mad, my King.
"You will live amongst the wild animals,
and eat grass like an ox."
"Forever?" asked the King.
"No," says Daniel.
"Just for seven years."
Deuteronomy. "Every seven years,
you must cancel all debts."
Genesis. "Seven years of famine began."
Ezekiel. "They shall burn them with fire
for seven years."
So, what will happen on October 14th,
just a couple of weeks from now?
Probably nothing.
But if something were to happen,
it would happen here in Jarden, Texas,
in Miracle.
Because I get a feeling
in this place, sometimes,
the same feeling I got when my wife awoke
from a three-year coma
the day I brought her here. Mary.
The same feeling I had
after being told by countless doctors
that Mary could not bear a child.
But she bore one here.
- Noah's a little shy like his dad.
My friends, I've got that feeling again.
So if something does happen
on October 14th,
you've all come to the right place.
- Amen to that. Amen to that.
Hallelujah.
Hallelujah!
I see a lot of new faces. Welcome.
If you want to be baptized
here in Miracle,
just come on down tomorrow morning.
We'll be at the spring
on the east edge of town,
which the good Lord has seen fit
to replenish with water.
You watching porn?
What?
Oh, when people are watching porn,
they shut...
Ah, never mind. Forget it.
Okay.
You coming tonight?
I told Tommy 6:00 sharp.
Mmm-hmm.
- Hey there, Chief.
- Hey.
Mmm, what are you two talking about?
Just Tom's party.
Oh. Yeah, can't wait.
I'm sorry about the church.
I know we're over capacity.
It's just so many people want to come.
Yeah, well, then look.
Maybe you should, um, stop advertising.
What's that?
The address
for the church is right on it.
No one loves handing out flyers
more than you do.
I swear I didn't do this.
You heard what I said in there.
No, I heard what you said in there,
and you said nothing's gonna happen
on the 14th
unless everything happens on the 14th.
I can't afford to have this place
explode again, all right?
Just tone it down.
Of course. You're right. Will do.
"Will do"?
If you're asking me
to tone it down, Kevin,
I'll tone it down.
Good.
Did he see it?
Okay, everybody. Settle down.
Listen, we are two weeks out
from the 14th,
and, uh, currently, our estimates are low.
We are looking now at an influx
of anywhere from 5,000 to 10,000 pilgrims
between then and now.
Uh, as of now, you're all approved
for permanent OT, effective immediately.
Am I late?
No, you're right on time.
Um, Agent Nora Durst from the DSD is gonna
tell us about procedures moving forward.
So, everybody, uh, listen up.
Thanks, Chief.
- Can you guys hear me okay?
- Yeah.
Okay, great. So, I know we went over this
a couple of months ago,
but there's been some confusion.
So, let's talk about the "D" word.
Yes, I get it.
If a guy says his girlfriend
vanished into thin air,
there's a good chance
she's decomposing in his trunk.
But as frustrating as it is
to indulge the bullshit,
there is a process in place
that we all must go through.
If a suspect asks for a lawyer,
you get a lawyer.
If a suspects says "Departure,"
you get me. Cool?
- Yeah.
- Got ya.
Dismissed, assholes.
-Walk you out, Agent Durst?
-Absolutely, Chief Garvey. Thank you.
Tommy knows.
Kevin, there's no such thing
as a surprise party.
-Well, then why the hell are we doing it?
-Because it's fun to pretend.
Hey, help me out. Between the blades.
- Get right up in there.
- Oh, yeah. Ooh, higher.
I'm gonna miss this cast.
Yet you never asked to sign it.
-Bye.
Hey, Chief.
A guy just came in,
and says he needs to talk to you.
Is he a tinfoil hat or a Kenneth?
Neither.
Knows you from New York.
Says you guys were hunting buddies?
Christ, it's good to see you.
- Good to see you, too.
-Well, you remember me, right?
-Yeah.
-Dean.
-Of course. Dean, yeah.
What can I do for you?
You know, uh, probably I...
I should hold back on some of the details
until I can provide you
with unassailable proof,
but if I'm being completely honest,
it's... It's a little out-there,
you know...
Sure.
I... I tried to keep you out of this...
But I gotta regretfully inform you
that our prey,
previously unsophisticated
and easily killable...
...has adapted.
So, Wyoming Senator Y. Woodrow Huffman,
the incumbent, mind you,
has a swanky fundraiser a week back.
Food's high-class, all right?
Crab cakes, Cornish game hens.
But this motherfucker, Huffman,
he asks me for a peanut butter sandwich.
Wait, he asked you for--
Yeah, I was undercover
on the catering staff.
Well, the Senator was a guest of honor,
the man of the hour,
so fucking A right,
we got him his sandwich.
You know, peanut butter.
Man, they love that shit.
And he's the only one who touched it,
only one who bit it.
His saliva.
So when you test it, you...
You know that it's uncorrupted.
Test it for what?
Canine DNA.
Now, I... I know what you're thinking.
All right. Why take on human form?
What do they want?
Right? Today, it's the Senator.
Tomorrow, it's the Secretary
of, you know, goddamn Agriculture.
And then, it's the President.
The leader of the free fucking world.
And that, my friend, is how the world ends
two weeks from now.
That's how they get their finger
on the button.
Paw.
Sorry?
That's how they get their paw on the...
On the button.
So, you... You don't believe me.
What you're thinking is happening...
Isn't.
It's all in your head, man.
It's not real.
Look, Valdivia tells me
you're staying down by the trailer park.
--So, tomorrow, I'm gonna come by,
and we're gonna talk.
Just...
-All right, Chief, see you tomorrow.
-I'll see you, Dean.
Perfect. The Wet-Naps are over there.
So, what do you want to know?
Look, no offense, all right,
but, uh, my wife made me come here.
And I don't really believe
in any of this shit.
"Shit"?
Yeah.
Well, you already paid,
so you might as well hear what I got, man.
So, what, you just, uh...
You look at my palm print,
you talk to my dead father?
Don't you think you should light
some candles, you know?
Maybe get out
a Ouija board or something?
Pat Benatar.
Now how'd you know about that?
Look, I can't talk to your dad, man.
It's more like turning a radio dial
and seeing what you pick up.
But you ask the right questions,
you usually get something back.
So, what do you want to know?
Why did he do it on my birthday?
I'm sorry to interrupt.
I'm gonna grab something upstairs.
No problem. I'll see you later, Kev.
- Yeah. Sorry.
Mmm-hmm.
All right.
Okay, now listen.
I know there's a part of you
that is hoping that he didn't even know
it was your birthday.
But there are some things
you need to know about him first.
He believed himself
to be a failure.
He believed himself to be a failure.
He--
- He failed his family.
He failed at his job.
He failed at being the man
that he wanted to be.
He was... He was sad. He was always sad.
And he didn't want anyone to know,
especially his kids.
He hid it from...
He hid it from Annemarie, and Billy,
and you.
I'm so sorry,
but the truth is he was so broken
that he didn't even know
it was your birthday
when he took his life.
He was only thinking about one thing.
Escaping.
So, that's what he did.
He escaped.
And that's what he did.
Okay. You can hug him now.
They won't believe it unless it's harsh.
- Jeez, now I know why I quit therapy.
What brings you by, Kev-o?
We got a problem.
We gotta keep it between you and me.
Okay.
Apparently, dogs are taking on human form,
and they are infiltrating
the highest levels of our government.
And... And where did you
come by this information, Chief Garvey?
A guy I used to know in Mapleton
a few years back.
Maybe we shot some dogs together.
You were in the GR. I was, uh, coping.
So this is my fault?
No, it's his fault
'cause he's fucking crazy.
Did you tell him he was crazy?
Maybe.
You never tell someone who is
experiencing a delusion of that magnitude
that they are delusional.
You told me I was delusional
when I told you I was talking to Patti.
And then you went
and drank poison.
I'm better now.
Of course you are.
Just please talk to this guy?
I'm worried about him. He's...
- You got it.
-Hey, man.
-How you doing, man?
Uh...
You and Nora need any help
setting up Tommy's thing?
- Yeah, that'd be great.
- Yeah?
How much is that?
It's, uh, 80 bucks.
- You just...
She's good, isn't she?
She's the best.
-Pat Benatar.
Whoo!
Let's party.
Okay, shh !
He's coming, he's coming,
he's coming ! Okay. Okay.
Surprise!
Oh, my God. A party?
Happy birthday, dear Tommy
Happy birthday, buddy.
Happy birthday to you
Go on, make a wish.
A wish, huh? What should I wish for?
Let's see.
That's a lot of responsibility, Dad.
I could wish for world peace.
That's always a classic.
-Boo.
-No need to ask for a bigger family
since everybody seems to be
marrying each other.
I always wanted a little brother,
by the way, dude.
Or I could-- I could give it away.
Anyone need anything?
It's your wish, honey.
All right. I... I got it, I got it.
- Someone's at the door.
- Those are so annoying.
This the house
where all the fucked up people live?
What? What?
- Wishes do come true!
- Oh!
Mary and me were in Guatemala.
"Huatemala"?
- You don't pronounce the "G," Thomas.
That's the first thing
they told the missionaries.
What they didn't tell us
was not to eat the cow brains.
I threw up for five days straight,
and apparently, hallucinated multiple
conversations with a burning bush.
-What did it say?
-Well, my Spanish wasn't so great.
Something along the lines of,
"Please put me out."
Where were you, John?
Uh, well, let me see. Uh...
I was about a mile and a half that way.
Uh, Erika was in med school,
- and I was working at a liquor store.
Uh-oh.
Yeah.  Which, uh,
didn't turn out to be so good. Uh...
Your turn, Kev-o.
Oh.
Me at 25? Jesus.
I was, uh... I was a cop.
I worked for my dad, the chief.
And, uh, this was long before he decided
to go off the grid and move to Australia.
But, on my 25th birthday,
I was, uh...
I was driving through an intersection,
and bam, back of my cruiser gets clipped.
I jump out of the car,
and, uh, the airbags have gone off.
The woman who hit me, she's shaken,
but she's okay. And I go over to her car.
There's a little 2-year-old boy
in a car seat.
And he's just calm as can be.
He's just smiling at me.
Must have liked the uniform.
- Wait, that was Laurie?
- Yeah.
A year later, I married her,
- adopted smiley over here.
- Oh!
All because we both thought
we had the green light.
And it turned out
that the switcher was busted.
So, you know.
Well, divine intervention.
What do you mean?
You know, like, uh, karma,
or kismet, whatever.
You know?
What?
Oh, nothing. I... I'd never heard
the story before. It's lovely.
To being in the right place
at the right time.
- Yeah, right place, right time.
- Right place, right time.
Sure you wanna drive back to campus?
You could stay here with us tonight.
If I stay with you guys,
it'll just hurt Mom's feelings.
Then stay with her and John.
It's not like it's a far walk.
Yeah, but...
If I stay with her,
she'll just keep me up
all night apologizing.
So, this is the last time
we're ever gonna see each other, huh?
What do you... What do you mean?
Just the world is ending.
Oh, yeah. Well, right.
How's Nora?
She's great.
She ever talk about Lily?
No.
Should I try and get her to?
What do I know?
You still got your crown on.
I know I do.
What were you guys talking about
out on the porch? Your penises?
No, we were talking about
what we were doing when we were 25.
And, uh, I told the story about how
when Laurie crashed into the back of me.
Oh, how romantic.
It's more romantic than
when we met in divorce court,
and you told me fuck my daughter.
That's not where we met.
We met at the Christmas dance
and you told me you cheated on your wife.
-We gotta work on our story.
-Mmm. Yeah.
-Here, let me get that.
-I got it.
-Come here.
-Thank you.
- When do you get your cast off?
- Um...
Day after tomorrow.
I was watching you
from the porch, with Noah.
Mmm, yeah. He's yummy, isn't he?
Mmm-hmm.
Good morning.
-What time is it?
-It's Sunday morning. Sleep in.
I'm just gonna go for a ride.
I should get on the bridge.
Suit yourself, Sheriff.
Everybody knows
you just like to ride that horse.
--Giddy-up.
-I love you.
-I love you, too.
- Hey, Chief, you there?
- Go ahead, Tommy.
The church was doing baptisms,
and these kids poisoned the water.
- You should probably get down here.
On my way.
Keep moving ! Move!
- They poisoned the water!
- What?
They poisoned the water, Kevin.
Come on ! Come on ! Stand back!
-What the fuck happened?
-These guys interrupted a baptism,
and spilled barrels in the springs!
What the fuck is in those barrels?
This water isn't holy!
This water is a symbol of hypocrisy.
I need you to calm the fuck down.
-Three years ago, October 15th...
-I need you to calm the fuck down !
The Bureau of Alcohol, Tobacco,
Firearms and Cults
assassinated 93 unarmed members
of the Guilty Remnant.
They were targeted by a military drone
and vaporized.
Megan Abbott!
Evangeline Murphy!
-Remember them. Remember them--
-Taylor Truitt! Nicholas Brody!
Go to hell!
I need you to calm down !
Stay back!
Calm down !
Just listen, please!
Dad !
The water's fine.
It's a prank.
The water's safe. It's a stupid prank.
Trust me.
Do you accept Jesus Christ
as your Lord and savior?
What?
Do you accept Jesus Christ
as your Lord and savior?
Yes.
Then I baptize you, Kevin Garvey,
in the name of the Father, the Son,
and the Holy Spirit,
buried in the likeness of his death
and raised
in the likeness of his resurrection.
He is saved.
That didn't count.
Want me to put the air on, dry you out?
That's very funny.
Those kids
with "Evie" on their shirts,
they were telling the truth
about what happened.
On the morning of October 15th,
three years ago,
there was an unexpected gas leak
at the visitor center.
As the result of a cigarette being lit
by a member of the Guilty Remnant,
who were occupying the center at the time,
the gas ignited, and the building
and the people inside were incinerated.
We pray for the families
of those that were lost.
And that's the story, Tommy.
But it's bullshit.
How'd you know the water wasn't poisoned?
I just knew.
That's bullshit, too.
Oh, shit!
Fuck!
Tommy!
You changed, you son of a bitch.
I got him.
Folks, this is a crime scene.
Stay behind the yellow tape.
Let me bum one of those.
You have to talk to someone.
I gave Billy my statement.
No. You gotta talk to a shrink.
I was just doing my job. I'm fine.
I was just doing my job
when I killed someone.
It still fucked me up.
You gotta talk. Talking helps.
You killed someone?
Yeah.
A, um...
A woman.
I had to. She, um...
You know, she had armed security
with her, and I...
Well, I killed them, too.
Hey, get away from there!
Stinkin' mutt!
It's a sandwich.
Hey.
Hi.
What's going on?
Can I tell him?
Mary's leaving.
She and Noah are going back to Mapleton.
What?
Well, when?
Now. Tonight.
We've got a flight out of Austin.
For how long?
Ever, Kevin.
We're going forever.
Uh, I don't--
I don't understand.
Without Matt?
All of those years
that he took care of you?
He loves you.
Did you know that Matt won't let me
cross the city limits?
He thinks if I go over that bridge,
the magical spell that woke me
from my slumber will break,
and I'll go back into a coma.
Listen, I know Matt can get carried away,
but his heart's in the right place.
He's writing a book about you.
He what?
A book.
He thinks the New Testament's getting old.
I've only read some of it,
but you figure fairly prominently, Kevin.
-Did you know about this?
-No, I did not.
He got pretty excited
when you rose from the dead.
Where the fuck is he?
Chief.
Can you give us a second, Michael?
I gotta talk to Matt.
He knows.
What do I know?
-Michael.
-He knows, Matt.
Was it Mary?
Well, whatever she said, she's
very upset right now. She just, uh...
Where's the book?
Can we just take a moment here?
You don't even know
what it is you're asking for.
Am I in it?
Yes.
Is it about my life?
Just give it to me.
I can't. There's only one copy.
Written by hand.
I don't care how many copies there are.
'Cause whatever little story
you're making up is bullshit.
I'm not making anything up.
It's all true. It all happened.
It's still happening.
Brought y'all some supper.
What's going on?
Well, John, I'm glad you asked,
'cause what's going on is Matt and
your son are writing a gospel about me.
Oh.
"Oh"?
I shot you in the chest...
Point-blank.
And you got up, walked back into town,
didn't even go to the hospital
until the next day.
You tried to drown yourself,
and an earthquake saved your life.
You drank poison.
I buried you,
and you went to the other place...
And came back.
You told them about the, uh,
hotel?
It seemed important.
I'm not, um...
I can die.
Of course you can.
Just not here.
What?
Here.
You can't die here, in Miracle.
And that twisted bullshit, Matt,
is why your wife is taking your son
and leaving you.
"If you come to me,
"but will not leave your family,
you cannot be my follower."
Is that from your book?
No, Kevin. That's Jesus.
Well, I'm not fucking Jesus.
I'm not saying you are,
but, uh, the beard looks good on you.
Go get the book!
Where the fuck is the book, Michael?
No, no, no! He's not ready.
- He'll destroy it!
- No, he won't.
The fuck I won't, John !
All right, then so be it.
Him I understand, but you?
Come on, John.
Well, we can't just be going through
all of this for nothing, man.
You're going through this
because your daughter died.
We don't know that.
What?
I'm supposed to believe she's gone
just because they say
her dental records match?
- Yes.
- No.
No, man.
Evie did it before.
Maybe she did it again.
I am trusting you with this, and I know
you'll do the right thing, Garvey.
I haven't put your baptism in yet,
but it's pretty much up-to-date.
You're insane.
There's, um, glass in your hair.
I was worried you'd forgotten.
Don't usually get so many
so close together.
Love is in the air.
Um...
A little extra for your trouble.
Sarah,
does the name "Kevin"
mean anything to you?
No.
English - SDH