Previously, on From...
- Anghkooey.
- No, no, no.
- Anghkooey. Anghkooey.
- Don't touch me! Don't touch me! No!
No! Don't!
Hey, hey, hey! You okay?
- Did you see them?
- See what? See who?
We heard a voice on the radio.
He knew my name, knew what my wife
was doing in the house, in the basement.
- Jim?
- I think people are watching us.
We've gotta start
working together on this.
I gotta go, Jim.
You were on your way to rehab
and you ended up here.
Did you take anything?
- Yeah, just a little bit of morphine, so...
- Marielle.
Okay, fine. Do whatever the fuck you want.
They're coming. You have to get out
before the music stops.
I'm sorry. My blood...
"...is your blood now."
Look, I got worms under my skin
and it feels like
something's coming for me now.
I can't have new people
stealing what little food we have!
- Get outside.
- Dale, come on.
Get off me!
Open the door!
Boyd, Kenny, I'm gonna need you out here.
- Breathe in, okay?
- Ellis, what's happening?
- We're gonna relieve the pressure, okay?
- Okay.
- You can't put my blood into him.
- Boyd.
Whatever's inside me
is going to go into him.
- Boyd.
- I got an idea.
My blood is your blood now, motherfucker!
- I almost lost him.
- But you didn't, okay?
I need to ask you something.
Yeah, of course.
Do you have any pregnancy tests?
Are you sure?
As sure as I can be
given the circumstances.
Have you said anything to Ellis yet?
No. No, not yet. I...
I know these
aren't the most ideal conditions,
but women have been giving birth
for thousands of years.
Right.
And...
not all of them
have a third-year medical student
to guide them through.
Look, talk to Ellis, the three of us can...
I can't.
I don't wanna say anything to him yet.
- Hey, sun's coming up.
- Yeah, we'll be right there.
Fatima, what's going on?
- Fatima...
- We should go.
I'm telling you, we should go.
All right.
Jesus.
You really did it.
You killed one of them.
What do we do with the body?
- We should burn it.
- No.
We take it inside.
Tell me you're joking.
No, he's right,
this is our chance to learn about them.
We can study them, open them up,
see what they look like on the inside.
We don't even know
if it's safe to touch this thing,
you're talking
about operating on it.
You guys?
Kristi.
It's your call.
Let's bring it in.
I'll get a sheet. We can drag it.
Thanks.
- I'll grab some sticks.
- Ellis.
I need you to head back up
to Colony House.
No, I wanna stay.
You do that, we gonna have dozens
of people coming to check on you.
And we gotta keep this quiet.
At least until we have a chance
to get a look at it.
Hey, Kristi,
are you good if we head back?
Yeah, but you gotta take it easy.
You come back to me immediately
if you have any trouble breathing, okay?
Keep the bandage nice and dry,
and I'll check on you later.
Okay.
- Let's go.
- Yeah.
- Elgin.
- Yeah?
What?
You all right?
I'm fine.
- Be careful.
- Yeah, always.
Let's go.
You guys.
All right, can we please just stop
and talk about this for a second?
Kenny, what is there to talk about?
You are about to willingly
bring something evil into your home.
Do you understand that?
I do.
I also understand that we may never
get this opportunity again, so is that it?
Okay?
Let's go.
Is Ellis gonna be okay?
How the fuck should I know?
I spent the whole night
putting food in salt water.
Well, what are you gonna do with me?
You gonna put me in the box?
That's what they do down there
in town, right? Is that who we are now?
I'm sorry about what happened to Ellis,
I really am. He's a...
He's a good kid.
But I'm not wrong
about those people from the bus!
There's too many people here.
And I saw how much food
you brought down yesterday.
There are some hard choices coming
and no one here
seems willing to make them.
I'd be careful how much you lobby
for people to make hard choices.
No one gets in or out.
Right.
So what happens now?
- We see how Ellis is doing.
- And then what?
You can't honestly expect us to live here
with someone who tried to kill us.
He wanted us to go outside
in the middle of the night.
He was ready to put both of us out...
Yeah, I heard the recap.
And I'm asking you
what you're gonna do about it?
Donna! The van just pulled up.
Ellis and Fatima are back.
Listen, I promise you, you are safe here.
And we are gonna figure this out.
You're one of us.
The fuckwad in the room notwithstanding,
we take care of our people.
Okay. Everyone, come on.
Give him room. Okay?
Come here. Okay, okay. Lean right on me.
Okay, I got ya.
Okay, here you go. Easy does it.
Easy does it.
- I think we should flip them.
- No.
- But they're ready.
- Not ready.
Hey, never argue with a master chef.
You've given away
the secrets of the trade?
I wanna see Victor today.
So do I.
- I don't think that's a good idea, buddy.
- Why not?
I can take him.
I was gonna go up there anyways.
Nobody's going to Colony House.
Hey, Jim.
I think it's okay for them to go.
Could we talk outside for a minute?
Save me some pancakes, okay?
What's up?
I don't know what's going on with you.
Excuse me?
We have to be a team here.
So when I say no one goes to Colony House
and you immediately undermine me,
- it doesn't help.
- Okay, what do you wanna do?
Do you wanna lock them in the basement?
Two days ago, you took Ethan to confront
the person that tried to kill him.
- That was different.
- No, it was you and I accepting the fact
that we can't just lock them away
until we find a way home.
You want them sneaking out?
Because that's what will happen.
This way, we know where they're going,
we know they're together.
I just don't want our nine-year-old son
hanging out
with some emotionally-stunted freak
who walks around town
with a gun in his lunch box.
Wait, wait, wait, no.
That emotionally-stunted freak
saved your daughter's life.
And he saved mine.
Or maybe that's what
they want you to think.
I heard a voice on the radio.
- Why is that nothing to you?
- Because I think you're wrong.
I know you want all this to make sense.
I know you want there
to be a rational explanation,
but if you had been down in those tunnels,
- if you'd seen what I saw...
- Maybe that's what they wanted you to see?
Oh, God.
Okay.
How did they do it?
How did they...
create monsters that come out at night?
Because I've seen those things.
Up close, Jim. I've seen them.
You are so sure
this voice you heard on the radio...
is the answer
to all those impossible things.
Have you ever stopped to wonder
if that voice was even a person?
Of course it's a person.
- What else do you think it was?
- I don't know.
And that is fucking terrifying.
You know what? But for now,
I'm gonna go back inside
and have pancakes with my children.
You're welcome to join us if you want.
Okay. You got it?
All right.
Okay, so...
how's this work?
What do you need?
It looks like
it has some sort of rib cage,
- so we'll probably need a saw.
- Okay.
There's a few
of those in the tool shed by the bar.
Gloves wouldn't be a bad idea, either.
All right.
Hey, Kenny, you think your mom
has anything in storage we could use?
Kenny?
You had worms or something
crawling underneath your skin,
and you put them inside
this thing and now it's dead.
Yeah.
So what happened to the worms?
Huh? Are they dead too?
- What do you...
- Excuse me.
Mari, hey!
Hey.
Mari.
- Hey.
- I'm sorry.
- You okay?
She's going through withdrawal.
- Is there anything we can...
- I need gloves
and something to cut through bone.
I don't want this thing down here
any longer than it needs to be,
so let's just do it and get it done, okay?
Please.
Hey, come on, let's go back here.
I'll go down to the shed.
Hey.
I'm sorry about the flyby, I was just...
- fucking around.
- That's all right.
You're pretty good with that thing.
It was supposed
to be for my nephew's birthday.
Figured I'd get my money's worth.
Hey, I...
I never thanked you for...
what you did the other day.
Helping out down in the basement.
You're welcome.
Though, seeing as your wife
wasn't even down there,
it kinda seems like you got those two
other guys killed for nothing.
That feel good just now saying that?
Buddy, fuck off, okay?
You said thank you. You're welcome.
Now, what else do you want from me?
- How much you think that thing can carry?
- What? Why?
Take a walk with me.
I wanna show you something.
- Where?
- Just down the road, outside town.
Oh, you want me
to help find your dog, right?
- What?
- You sound like one
of those fucking perverts
that hang out at playgrounds.
What is wrong with you?
Just leave me alone, okay?
What if I told you
that drone might get you home in time
for your nephew's birthday?
Did they move again?
What are you doing here?
- I came to see you.
- Go away.
Why are you being so mean to me?
I thought we were friends.
We are friends.
It doesn't feel like it.
I'm trying to protect you.
It's just...
It's safer for you to stay away from me.
Why?
Because bad things happen
to my friends here.
Well, what's the point
of being friends if we can't be friends?
Okay.
Bye.
The orange was dry.
What?
The markers you gave me.
The orange was dry. It was a bad gift.
Sorry.
There's a lot of measuring to do.
I guess you can help if you want.
They need you out there.
They can wait.
- Just go.
- There.
I'll be fine.
You're shivering. Here.
Just do what you need to do.
Just try to drink some water, okay?
Yeah.
I'll be right back.
- She okay?
- Not great. She's trying to sleep.
Okay.
Let me help you with that.
I'm...
She's gonna be all right,
you know. She's got you.
When I met her,
she'd been sober for almost a year.
She worked so hard. She was so proud.
And then I...
- disappeared.
- Hey.
Hey, listen...
this is not on you.
I didn't even notice
she was going through withdrawal,
because I was so caught up
in that fuckin' thing.
- I...
- No. Kenny's right.
We have no idea what we're in for
once we open that thing up.
I know.
Are you scared?
Yeah.
Yeah, me too.
Okay.
Yeah!
You know it's a bar, right?
You don't have to knock.
What are you doing?
Well, you have arrived
at a fortuitous time.
I think I figured out how to make
the alcohol not taste like stomach acid.
I needed a project that wasn't terrifying.
Hey, come on.
Could you give me a hand with this?
No, I actually need to ask you a question.
When you found me in the woods
the other day, I was...
rolling on the ground and screaming.
You were not surprised.
Why?
I like you a lot better
when you're not yelling at me.
Oh, come on, Jade.
Just answer this question, please.
Your husband found me like that
once before.
He ever tell you that?
No. No.
Well, to be fair,
I wasn't entirely forthcoming
with the details.
If I recall correctly, I got up...
I told him to fuck off
and then I ran away.
What happened?
I was being attacked
by a very angry Civil War soldier.
What?
That's all you get.
You want more,
you gotta help me with this.
And you're not allowed to yell at me.
So you sent out a call for help?
Someone actually answered
and no one's doing anything about that?
Yeah.
And you think this is one big
mindfuck designed to...
Designed to what? See what we all do?
Experiments have been going on
like this for a long, long time.
And when you see the ones
that finally get declassified,
you start to wonder about the ones
they still manage to keep under wraps.
Holy shit.
- This where you and your...
- Yeah.
Fuck.
Come on.
The key is the antenna.
Yeah, I can get
the signal up over the treetops.
That's why
we put it on the roof the last time.
Yeah, if we can strip
this thing down, get it light enough,
- this drone can carry it up...
- Yeah, I get it,
you can get the antenna up
as high as you want, right?
This radio's pretty trashed.
Radio's not the problem,
I can handle the radio.
You sure about that?
- You think I'm crazy?
- I don't think you're crazy.
Shit, with everything
I've seen here so far,
you're the first person
that's making any sense. I'm just...
wondering why you haven't asked
yourself the obvious question.
And what's that?
Well, you think this place
is one big experiment, right?
And it never occurred to you
that some of the people here
might be in on it?
I mean, they'd have to be.
How else do you keep
the experiment on track?
Jesus. He stabbed you?
Yeah, things have been
a little intense around here lately.
But you guys are both okay?
- We're fine.
- Yeah.
Really, we're fine.
Okay.
Okay. Well,
I'll let you get some rest then.
Hey.
I miss you guys.
We miss you too.
You're always welcome here.
- You know that, right?
- Yeah, I do.
And you guys are
always welcome at the Liu House.
We'll keep that in mind.
Sorry.
- Leaving so soon?
- Yeah.
I gotta make sure
my brother's not building a spaceship
- or something with Victor.
- Best get on that then.
I thought you two might be hungry.
I thought
we were in the middle of a food shortage.
We are in the beginning stages
of a minor and temporary shortage.
But you need to get your strength up.
Donna...
I am fine.
Really, I am.
But it never should've happened
in the first place.
I should have been here.
- I'm sorry.
- Well, I'm...
so glad
that you finally decided to apologize,
because another grown man losing his shit
and stabbing me is clearly your fault.
You know what I mean, smart-ass.
You did good.
Getting him down to the clinic.
Hey, Julie?
- Hey.
We have to stop meeting like this.
On the porch.
- Yeah, right.
- Yeah.
What's up?
You said if I ever wanted to talk...
Yeah, yeah, yeah, of course.
You have time for a walk?
Okay.
These were all I could find, so...
Yeah, they're fine.
All right.
- How can I help?
- Catch me if I fall.
Sorry, bad joke.
- I'm gonna open up the shirt.
- Okay.
I'll take...
Okay.
I'm just gonna make an incision
across the chest, okay?
Here we go.
- The fuck!
- It's fine.
I just...
- Think I hit a nerve or something.
- No. Let's stop. Stop.
- It's fine.
- Kenny, Jesus Christ!
Stop!
All right, we shouldn't be doing this.
We should have fucking burned it.
We shouldn't be doing this!
- Hey!
- You're fucking crazy.
- Hey, hey!
- I got it.
I got it.
Kenny.
Kenny, stop.
Fucking stop!
Are you really gonna walk away right now?
We never should have brought
that thing inside.
It's dead, how is it going to hurt us?
I'm not worried about the monster.
Kristi, I'm worried about the thing
that fucking killed it.
Boyd brought something back with him.
He had worms crawling underneath his skin.
He put them inside the scariest thing
I have ever seen in my goddamn life,
- and now that scary thing is dead.
- But that's why we need to...
Look, whatever Boyd brought back
is like a poison to those things,
and now it's in his blood.
If we could extract it and use it,
we may finally have a way
of fighting back.
Or there's something
in there that'll kill you
the moment you open that thing up,
how do you not see that?
Fine, I'm willing to take that risk.
Look, Kenny, all I do here
is put broken things back together.
This is a chance to just finally...
And yeah, I'm scared.
I'm fucking terrified,
and that's why I need you
in there with me.
I can't do this without...
We're in this together, remember?
You and me.
No.
No, we're not.
Not anymore.
Are you fucking kidding me?
No, I... That's not... I'm saying...
Look, it's okay.
It's okay.
I'm glad she's here.
Truly, I am. I...
Kristi,
I love you.
And all I want is for you to be happy.
But I can't go in there and watch you
do something that might get you killed.
I just... I can't do that.
I just can't.
I'm sorry.
Kristi?
No.
No, no, no.
Kristi! Kristi!
You feeling okay?
- Where is it?
- What?
The body. The fucking body.
Run.
Marielle, run!
Hey, Donna.
Hey.
You all right?
The plants keep dying.
It's like they're growing
in poisoned soil.
Boyd, all he ever wanted
was to find...
I'm pregnant.
Oh, sweetie! Oh, this is...
Oh, I wish I could've seen Ellis' face
when he found out he was gonna be a dad.
I haven't said anything to him yet.
- Is he not...
- No, of course he is.
Donna, I was told I can't have kids.
What's happening right now
is medically impossible.
And all I can think is
what if this place
is trying to torture me?
Mock me?
Like those things that come out at night.
The way they smile at us.
What if this is just...
What's happening?
I'm standing here thinking
I'm at the end of the line,
that everything
I thought about this place was...
We have seen
so much unbelievable shit in this place.
Roads that lead nowhere.
Monsters that come from the dark.
According to Boyd,
there are evil fucking trees
that trap you in dungeons.
Don't ask.
The point is...
we have seen a lot of horrible
impossible shit here.
So we just assume
that anything impossible
that happens here is bad.
But look at you.
Sweetie, you met the love of your life
in the middle
of your worst fucking nightmare!
You're gonna have a baby,
that you were told you could never have.
That sounds like a pretty good
impossible to me.
Donna, it's impossible.
What, you're gonna sit here
and tell me with all you've seen,
that you can't
wrap your head around a miracle?
Because a miracle
is just the other side of a nightmare.
What if you're wrong?
I've got a different question for you.
What if I'm right?
There we go.
So first it was the guy crushed
by the rock in the root cellar.
He was stuffed inside
that giant armoire in the back.
And then...
And then it was the Civil War soldiers.
Then the other night, Christopher,
which was easily the creepiest
fucking thing
I've ever experienced in my life.
Wait. Christopher?
Oh, yeah.
Christopher's the guy holding the journal.
And you see that kid in the background?
Yeah, that's Victor.
Wow, you caught that
a lot quicker than I did.
Okay, so...
For you, what you see
is different every time?
I mean, except for the symbol.
Why, what do you see?
I just see children.
What, like, little kids?
Yeah. Yeah, but...
They're fucking terrifying.
I thought I was losing my mind
or I was being punished.
Punished for what?
Oh, my...
My son, Thomas,
was a few months old when he died, so...
You know.
Fuck.
God, I'm so sorry.
Well, look, I mean,
the good news
is you're not being punished.
Maybe this is just a fucked-up place,
where scary shit happens.
And there's no explanation why.
Yeah.
I'm gonna go home.
I appreciate the help.
Wait. Is this the symbol
you were talking about?
Yeah, that's Christopher's
incel book of crazy.
I've seen this.
- Yeah? Like in a vision or something?
- No.
No, on the walls in the tunnels.
What?
What tunnels?
How many times do we have to do this?
A lot.
We have to be thorough.
We have to be sure.
They're losing their leaves.
What?
The trees.
So?
- That happens every year.
- Well, not here.
It's always the same here.
Is it bad
that they're losing their leaves?
When things change here, it's usually bad.
Well, if it's never happened before,
maybe it's good.
Almost got it.
There.
Okay.
- Now we have to remove the sternum.
- Great.
What?
- Okay, on the count of three.
- Okay.
Hold that hand steady, okay?
One...
two, three!
What the fuck?
What's wrong? What is it?
It's human.
I mean, at least it was.
It's got the exact same anatomy.
There're the lungs. The heart. Liver.
But they're shriveled.
Desiccated. It's like some shit
that you see at a museum.
Okay, hey, hey.
Look, slow down. Just talk to me.
It's supposed to be in the blood.
"My blood is your blood,"
that's what you said to it, right?
Right, but maybe their blood
is different than ours.
This thing is bone dry inside.
There's no fluid, there's no lymph,
- there's nothing we can...
- Hey, it's okay.
No, it's not okay. This was our chance.
This couldn't have been for nothing, okay?
There's gotta be something.
There's gotta be something in here.
All right, be careful.
You fucking piece of shit.
- Okay, stop!
- Fuck you! You fuck!
- You fuck!
- Kristi, stop.
Hey, Kristi, stop!
Okay, just... Kristi!
Hey, hey, stop!
What is that? What's that stuff?
That's the gallbladder.
That's...
- That's bile.
It's good, right? It's liquid.
It might be something we could use, right?
Yeah. Maybe, it's something.
Maybe? You goddamn right that's something.
- Bile is something.
- Can you go get me one of the...
- Yeah.
...droppers, so we can collect it.
You did good. You did great.
Wait, what do you mean he killed it?
I'm telling you,
he went outside and did something,
and the thing started screaming.
When we went out this morning,
it was dead.
Jesus.
Hey, you can't tell anyone.
Not even your parents.
- Why?
- I don't know.
Boyd said he doesn't want
anyone to know yet
and I really don't want him
pissed at me, so please.
Okay. I won't say anything, I promise.
Look, this is a good thing.
I mean, if we can hurt them,
if we can kill them.
Everybody here
is gonna be a whole lot safer.
- I know.
- So why are you upset?
You know that dream I had?
On the bus?
Yeah.
I can't shake this feeling,
like there's something
I'm supposed to remember.
Something that...
When I seen that thing lying there
in the dirt this morning,
it was like I could...
it was right there. And I...
It's like before I could move
my head, it was gone. And I...
I don't know
if what I'm supposed to remember is real
- or if my mind is just so messed up that...
- No! No.
Everything about this is crazy.
I get it.
This place, it's like...
As soon as you start to think,
"You know, maybe today I won't go insane."
Something new comes along and it's like,
"Hey, wait till you see this."
We all go through it.
You seem pretty together.
Seriously?
You must be in pretty bad shape then.
I do have a little trick though,
for when things really start to get to me.
I fill up the bathtub,
and I sink down just enough,
so that the water is level with my ears.
And the sound is like,
when you're standing by the ocean.
And I just sit like
that for a while and I breathe.
It's peaceful.
I don't take baths.
Okay. Well, then I don't know how
to help you.
- Hey.
I have just accepted
that I'm never gonna be comfortable again.
You okay?
Yeah.
I am.
There's something I need to tell you.
Big day.
Yeah, it was.
You really think injecting them
with that stuff is gonna kill 'em?
Honestly, I got no fucking idea,
but it's the best chance we got.
How are we even gonna test it?
I tell you what.
Let's make that a problem for tomorrow.
I should get home.
Tell Kristi...
You know.
Yeah, okay.
Hey, Kenny.
Hey.
If you ever want that badge back...
I'll see you around.
Yeah.
How'd it go?
I don't really know yet.
- I guess we'll have to wait and see.
- Okay.
How are you?
- I had a bad dream.
- Oh, no.
What was it about?
That thing in the basement...
came alive and...
I think there was a music box.
Your friend Boyd
is giving me his nightmares.
I'll be sure to talk to him about that.
I'm gonna be all right, you know.
You don't have to worry about me.