Previously on From...
You ever wonder if Abby was right?
What if it's all just a dream?
- Who did you come here with?
- My mother.
She was nice.
What are you drawing?
Things that I've seen.
It's good to draw them
when you see them, so even if you forget,
the pictures remember.
When Christopher started seeing
that symbol, things changed.
He changed. Everyone died.
- I've seen this.
- Yeah? Like, in a vision or something?
No. On the walls in the tunnels.
What tunnels?
You heard the voice on the radio.
That means that there are people
out there who can see us.
And what part
of you thinks that that's a good sign?
You already got people's hopes up
with your goddamn tower.
- All the more reason that we...
- To keep our fucking mouths shut.
What if I told you
that drone might get you home
in time for your nephew's birthday?
Experiments have been going on
like this for a long, long time.
This radio is pretty trashed.
The radio's not the problem.
I can handle the radio.
And it never occurred to you that some
of the people here might be in on it?
How else do you keep
the experiment on track?
You really did it. You killed one of them.
- What do we do with the body?
- This is our chance to learn about them.
We can open them up,
see what they look like on the inside.
- You fucking piece of shit!
- Kristi, stop it!
- Okay, stop it! Stop!
- Hey, hey, stop! Stop.
You really think injecting them
with that stuff's gonna kill them?
Honestly, I got no fucking idea,
but it's the best chance we got.
How are we even gonna test it?
I do have this little trick,
though, for when things
really start to get to me.
I fill up the bathtub,
and I sink down just enough
so that the water's level with my ears,
and I just sit like that
for a while and I breathe.
Ma.
Where's the family?
Everyone's still asleep. Are you hungry?
A little.
Sit down. I'm making your favorite.
Can I help?
You can set the table.
You should answer it.
Hello.
Hello?
Here they come. They come for me...
Who is this?
Is everything all right?
I don't know.
What is that?
They're not ready yet.
Hey, Son!
You were yelling.
I had a bad dream.
I'm okay.
What the fuck?
So, what's the point?
Well, I told you, once we re-establish
connection, we can start asking...
No, no, no, not the antenna.
I'm talking about this.
Let's say this is
one real big experiment. For what?
Well, there's a lot of value...
in seeing how far
you can push someone before they break.
Look what this place did
to that girl Sara.
The one who tried to hurt your kid?
Yeah.
I'll tell you,
the fact that she's still breathing...
you got a lot more restraint than I do.
I'm not gonna let
this place turn me into something I'm not.
Shit. If they really wanna break people,
I got a few ex-girlfriends
they could hire.
- All right. Let's give it a shot.
- All right.
There we are.
- Keep going.
- Yeah.
- Well, go... go higher.
- Yeah. That's it.
- What?
- That's it.
All right, bring it down.
I got it, I got it.
Look, let's say this thing works,
why would the people running
this thing wanna talk to you?
They already did it once.
Were they tryna help
or just tryna fuck with your head?
I mean, look at this,
look at where we are.
- Listen, if you don't wanna help, you...
- I'm not saying that. I just...
Look, if someone out here really wanted
to help, they would find a way to help.
But I still think we'd be better off
looking at the people in here.
Something this big?
You'd have to have someone on the inside.
Nah. You can't just start
throwing around accusations.
Look, I'm not saying accuse, I just...
Look, when you got here,
who told you what was what?
Who laid out all the rules?
Boyd, Donna,
- Father Khatri.
- Father who?
Khatri.
He died.
That night they got into the Colony House.
- Did you see it?
- See what?
Did you see the priest get killed?
No. Happened outside the sheriff station.
I wasn't there.
Right.
And of all the people
that died since you've been here,
how many times
have you actually seen it happen?
What's your point?
What if the people these "monsters"
are killing, what if they're all in on it?
I mean, you wanna scare
the shit out of people,
you need a body count, right?
Maybe that's why
they say when you get here,
you gotta keep your blinds down.
'Cause God forbid
you're looking out your window at night.
What about that guy Brick?
What about Tom?
I didn't see it happen. Did you?
I mean, yeah, I saw a body the next day,
but I didn't get close enough
to see if that shit was real.
Have you seen one ounce of proof
that anyone here has actually...
Nathan.
- What?
- Sara's brother.
You know, she killed him.
Slit his throat.
Or she didn't.
Let's just imagine
for a second that I'm right...
and everyone here that dies is in on it,
it's gonna mean one of two things.
One,
that they pushed Sara so far
that she actually killed someone,
of which, you know, maybe she did.
Or... like everything else,
that whole thing with Nathan,
him arriving just in time
to save your kid...
what if that's all just for show?
Maybe poor little Sara's
not as broken as you'd think.
Hey, Sara,
I was gonna come by and check on you.
I wanna go back out.
Excuse me?
To the woods. I wanna go back.
I'll pack a bag. Take a talisman.
What if you were right?
What if the answers are out there?
Maybe we just didn't go out far enough.
Well, we went far enough
that whatever's out there
put us right the fuck back here.
So, that's it? We just give up?
I didn't say that.
I get it. People need you here.
You shouldn't be out there.
But I can... Just let me do this.
Okay. Why?
Why'd you wanna go out there?
Because I wanna help.
I'm sure you do.
But that's not why you wanna leave. So...
There's no place for me here.
No one even wants me here.
And they're right, I shouldn't...
This is something I can do.
There's a difference
between going out there
and running away from here.
Leaving? That'd feel good. It'd be easy.
We don't get to do easy anymore.
I can't just sit in that church anymore.
There's nothing for me to do,
nowhere for me to go.
Okay, good.
Now we're talking
about problems we can fix.
Down there.
That's where I saw
your symbol, and it's...
also the first time I saw the children.
And those things that come out
at night, they're down there too?
- Yeah.
- All right.
This has to mean something.
It can't be a coincidence.
- Why?
- How much do you know about chaos theory?
A butterfly flaps its wings in Wyoming...
a month later, there's a tsunami in Japan.
And on the surface,
the two events appear entirely unrelated,
but in reality, there is
an intricate set of connections...
Jade, what the fuck
are you talking ab...?
It's not an accident! We just...
We need more information
to see how they're connected.
Well, I'm not going back in there.
Yeah, no shit.
I mean, you'd have to be crazy.
Motherfucker.
- What?
- Did Victor see it?
You told me Victor was
down there with you.
- Did he see the symbol on the walls?
- Of course!
- He was the one that pointed it out.
- Of course.
I asked him! I asked him point blank.
He promised to tell me everything
he knew about that symbol, yet somehow,
he manages to leave out.
You know, in the entire Venn diagram
of crazy that you and I have seen,
there's one single point of overlap.
Hi.
Is Ethan home?
Yeah. Yeah, yeah, come in.
I'll wait out here.
Okay.
Ethan, Victor's here!
You know, I never got to thank you
for everything you did
that night at Colony House.
I mean, getting me
out of there, you saved my life.
Okay.
- Hi.
- Okay, I'll be ready in two minutes.
- Okay.
We're gonna help Mrs. Liu at the diner.
I brought you something.
Are you gonna come in?
No, you have to come outside.
- Why?
- Because you have to try it on.
Come.
It's getting cold.
You'll need a coat soon.
This used to be mine.
Let me see if it fits.
Yeah.
Here. I drew this for you.
I don't want this.
Why?
Because pictures are
for things that are gone.
But what if something happens to me?
You forget a lot of stuff.
I wouldn't want you to forget me.
I said don't talk like that.
Well, if you don't keep it,
I don't want the coat.
Hey, you ready? We gotta go.
Wanna come?
- Okay.
- Come on.
- Nice jacket.
- Thanks.
- Are you sure you shouldn't be in bed?
- I mean, no, I'm fine.
You know, I'm not gonna be doing
any push-ups anytime soon,
but I feel great.
Seriously.
Did Kristi check you out?
Yeah, yeah,
and she was more surprised than you.
And what about Dale?
Donna's locked him up in his room.
Dad, everything is fine.
What are you smiling about?
I have some news.
- Corey said you were looking for me?
- Oh yeah, I'll... One second.
Yeah.
I'll tell you later.
I...
Okay, get some rest.
A'ight... Yeah, look, Dad,
I'm good, but go ahead.
Hey.
Are you out of your fucking mind?
I really don't need this today, Boyd.
I have a headache
like you would not believe.
I'm not asking you to let her stay here.
Look, just throw me a bone.
Give her something
to do, anything. I don't care.
- She just wants to feel useful.
- Okay, I'll do what I can.
Thank you.
But we have bigger problems
right now than Sara being bored.
I got a house full of people
on their last nerve,
a madman locked in the bedroom,
and last night,
Elgin almost drowned in his sleep.
Wha... He what?
Come in.
Hey.
I heard about what happened last night.
- What are you doing?
- I found these in one of the closets.
- Helps me relax.
- Good.
You wanna tell me about it?
This nightmare of yours.
I was...
I was sitting in the bathtub...
in my dream,
and something pushed me under the water.
Then I guess...
someone shook me awake,
and I started spitting up water, and...
How is it even possible?
You didn't tell anybody about anything
that happened at the clinic, did you?
Well, I got some good news.
We... pulled something out of that thing.
Something that might help us.
So, you think it's like a poison?
It could be. The only problem is
we gotta figure out how to get this
inside another one of those things
without getting ourselves killed.
You have a gun, right?
Yeah.
So make some silver bullets.
- No, you're making that up.
- I'm not.
Julie, tell him it's real.
- What's real?
- The Internet.
Oh! Yeah. Yeah, that's a thing.
- Told you.
- Victor. You come carry.
You're up.
Are you just gonna wear
that thing all day?
I like it.
Smells musty.
Ethan, you put here.
What's this?
Where did you...
- Where did you get that?
- It was in the pocket.
What's wrong?
I need you to be brave.
There you are. He's in here!
- Listen, we gotta talk.
- I have to go.
- What are you doing? Hey!
- We had a deal, remember?
I play you the song,
you tell me about the symbol!
Hey! Leave him alone.
- I told you about the symbol.
- You sure you told me everything?
You didn't tell me you saw it
on the wall down in those tunnels!
- Hey! Relax!
- What tunnels?
- Victor, we just wanna talk to you.
- I have to go.
- Hey!
- Mom, what's going on?
- Give me one reason... right?
- Stay here, honey.
- One reason why you wouldn't mention...
- Jade!
...that you saw this symbol
on the wall down in those tunnels.
- Just give me one!
- It's not important.
- It... Yes, it is! Goddamn it, stop!
- Hey, Jade, stop it!
- Stop it!
- No! No, I have done fucking around!
You... Hey! Look at me. You don't get
to pick and choose what you tell us.
Everything, everything you know,
everything you've seen, it all matters.
Because that may be how we go home.
Don't you want that?
Wouldn't you like to go home?
This is my home.
What is wrong with you?
Is it just physically impossible for you
not to be an asshole
for longer than ten minutes?
- Great, you're yelling at me again.
- Fuck off.
That didn't take very long.
Victor.
Sara... we were wondering
if we could talk to you for a minute?
About what?
We're just tryna get
our head around a few things.
- This is Randall. He came on the bus.
- I know who he is.
What do you wanna know?
You came with your brother?
Where were you going?
Back to Boston.
Where were you coming from?
Why does it matter?
What's going on?
We're just trying
to figure out if there's any pattern
to how people end up here.
We just want your help.
Pennsylvania.
I was living in New Hope, but it wasn't...
Nathan came to bring me back home.
So, you guys were close?
He was my best friend.
That day, at the barn...
No, I don't want to talk about that.
Sara...
I know you didn't want to hurt Ethan.
I know that.
And what this place did
to you, it isn't fair.
- But please...
- Is your brother still alive?
- What?
- It's a simple fucking question.
- Ease up.
- The hell is going on?
This is convenient.
Excuse me?
You just show up here out of nowhere
the moment we start
asking fucking questions?
- The fuck are you talking about?
- Nothing.
Boyd says you're looking
for ways to be helpful.
I got a bunch of clothes
that need stitching. You sew?
- Yeah.
- Great.
Here you go. Start with that.
You two, get the fuck out.
Who are you?
You think you're some kinda big shot?
Got a little power? Little pull?
'Cause you'd like that, right?
You know what you are?
You're a fucking tollbooth operator.
- You're gonna wanna leave right now.
- All right.
Everything's fine. Everything's okay.
We're gonna go right now, let's go.
You okay?
Why were they talking about Nathan?
Why do they think he's alive?
- What was that?
- What was what?
You wanna figure this thing out,
or do you wanna be everyone's friend?
I saw the look on her face
when you asked her about Nathan,
she doesn't know anything.
- Donna might.
- No. That's exactly what we cannot...
We cannot go around assuming
every little thing, okay? But look...
we need to watch.
What?
It's what you said about people
keeping their shades drawn at night.
These things that come from the forest,
we need to see what they do
when they don't know
they're being watched.
And how do we do that?
Go back to the bus. Go about your day.
When it gets closer to dark,
you sneak out, you meet me at the RV.
We'll stay the night out there,
maybe see some things
they don't want us to see.
Hey.
- Dad!
- Hey, how's it going in here?
Good.
We're just getting ready to clean up.
- Where's your mom?
- She said she was going to Colony House.
Victor and Jade were in here,
and Jade started yelling at him,
so I think
Mom just went to go check on him.
Are you okay?
Yeah, come here.
I wanna talk to you for a second.
- This one?
- Ethan, come.
- What's up?
- I'm not gonna be home tonight.
I got an idea.
Something that can get us out of here.
I just need some time to figure it out,
but I'm gonna be fine.
- I got a talisman, I'm gonna be inside.
- Inside where?
I'm gonna stay the night in the RV.
I'm telling you this so you won't worry.
When you see your mom,
you tell her I'm all right.
Okay?
Please be careful.
Always.
Jim... can I have a word?
- Look, if this is about before...
- Are you some kind of moron?
What?
What is wrong with you?
I'm just looking for answers,
same as everybody else.
- By taunting Sara?
- Come on.
You asked if her brother was still alive.
Look, I tried to talk to you about this.
Jesus Christ! Is this about
that fucking voice on the radio?
Why do you say it like it's strange
that I don't wanna just let it go?
Don't even tell me
you put this shit in Randall's head.
- Listen...
- No, you fucking listen.
That guy is a fucking powder keg.
If you start putting ideas in his head...
I didn't tell him about the voice. Okay?
Talking to Sara was stupid. I get it.
We all just wanna go home.
Are we done?
- Yeah.
- Okay.
Victor, I need you to be brave.
- But I'm scared.
- Everything's gonna be okay.
You just...
You just draw your pictures.
And no matter what happens,
you do not come out
until morning. I love you.
Mom!
- Hello.
May I come in?
Yeah.
I just wanted to say thank you
for the coat you gave Ethan.
That's very thoughtful of you.
I remember these.
Ethan said he found it in one
of the pockets, that you were upset.
Can I have that, please?
Yeah, of course.
Yeah. I hadn't seen it in a long time.
Victor...
why didn't you tell Jade
we saw that symbol in the tunnels?
Because it's not good
to ask questions. It's not good.
- People shouldn't go looking for answers.
- Why not?
Because they don't come back.
But looking for answers
is our only way out.
I don't think there is a way out.
I know you're afraid
that bad things might happen, but...
but Victor, bad things happen here,
no matter what.
If you know something that could help us...
My mother said that we were going home.
The night
that the bad things happened, she's...
she's... I don't know.
What? What did she say, Victor?
I don't remember.
- Come on, Victor, please.
- I don't remember.
The pictures might.
Well, your pictures were
inside the house when it collapsed.
No, not these pictures.
I put them somewhere else.
Put them away somewhere
where I would never have to look at them.
So I would never...
have to remember.
So that no one else would die.
Do you know where you put them?
Hey. I...
What happened there?
I...
I don't know. Somehow,
I managed to burn myself in my sleep.
It's nothing.
What?
Nothing.
Elgin, that kid from the bus,
he had a pretty interesting idea
about how we test our theory.
- Okay.
- Silver bullets.
What?
You take the bullets,
dip them in the bile, coat them,
fire from a safe distance. Then we see.
We're gonna need the rest of that bile.
I'm heading there now.
Deep breaths, okay?
We gotta get the fuck out of here.
What's going on?
Something's happening downstairs.
Okay, deep breaths.
Are you sure the sound
was coming from the boiler room?
- Okay.
- What were you doing down there?
Does it matter?
I haven't... This just happened.
- Do you really think that thing could...
- I don't know.
But if you see anything
coming from... up these stairs, you run.
Do you understand me?
- Yeah.
- Okay.
You don't need to be down here.
I'm good.
Go upstairs.
No.
Come on.
What the fuck?
Boyd.
- No, Boyd, wait...
- Hey.
Get her some water. Okay?
No, I mean,
this is what I was talking about earlier.
- What?
- I saw those things in the dream.
I saw those, I...
In my dream, I hung up the phone,
and I heard the exact same buzzing.
All right? And I looked
inside the pot, and it was full of them.
- Jesus.
- Look, okay, let's just try to calm down.
Wait. Elgin said that he had a dream
that he was drowning,
and then he started spitting up water.
And you had cicadas in your dreams,
and those bugs are swarming
in that thing downstairs?
No, it wasn't just the bugs.
When the music box started playing,
one of them jumped out,
and it burned my arm.
- Is that what you...
- Yes.
I'm sorry, are you honestly saying
that our fucking dreams can hurt us now?
- Marielle.
- Kristi?
- Hey, hey.
- You here?
I was hoping I could borrow some...
You look glum.
What the fuck's going on?
Victor?
You're a nice lady,
and Ethan is my friend, and I wanna help.
I know you do.
But I'm afraid to remember.
I know. But I need you
to be brave, Victor.
That's what my mother said
to me that night.
It's right through here, so...
I saw you less than two hours ago,
when the fuck were you planning
to tell me about this?
I'm telling you now.
No, I walked in on you
and caught you, it's not the same.
I needed time to...
I just didn't want anybody
jumping to conclusions.
- And since when am I just anybody?
- Donna.
No, no, no, don't give me
that patronizing bullshit.
You came to my house this morning,
looked me straight in the eye,
and you asked me for a goddamn favor,
knowing full well
this thing was down here.
Okay, you're right.
I should have said something. I'm sorry.
Okay, it won't happen again.
And you think you pulled something
out of it that can help kill the rest?
Well...
we found something that's worth trying.
All right.
Well, let's get a look
at this thing, then.
Okay.
Just watch your step.
This...
The fuck?
Jesus.
Piece of shit.
There were bugs.
Hundreds of them,
crawling out of the body.
Look, Kenny saw them too.
They probably scattered.
We closed the door.
You need to burn this thing.
Now.
Make sure you get it out far enough,
people don't see the smoke
and get curious.
Right.
Just push.
- So, look, this stuff with the dreams.
- Yeah?
We burn the body,
and that should take care
of whatever has...
has been...
But still, it's probably
a good idea if people sleep in shifts.
Just in case.
What about Sara?
I'll bring her to the sheriff's station.
You and Marielle should come too.
Hey, look, I've seen withdrawals before,
and that's about to get
a whole lot worse before it gets better.
I'm not staying
under the same roof as Sara.
We'll stay at Colony House,
if that's okay?
The more the merrier.
All right, then.
I forgot, do you have any aspirin?
No, sorry.
Great. You have fucking monster bile
and no aspirin.
- Try a warm compress.
- Fuck right off.
- Hey, come on.
- Jesus.
Would you...
Are they in there?
Do you want me to look?
Victor, I need you to be brave.
I'm counting on you.
No, please...
Hey, it's okay.
- Victor, Victor, what's wrong?
- No, no, no, no.
No matter what happens, you cannot leave.
You need to protect your sister.
Please don't go, Mommy.
These aren't mine. They are not mine.
- What?
- They were hers.
You just draw your pictures, okay?
And you stay here all night.
And when I come back,
we're gonna go home. I love you.
No!
Oh my God, Victor. It's okay, it's okay.
Okay. Okay. Protect your sister.
- Mommy, no, no!
- No, don't go!
- No...
- Victor, it's okay, it's okay, it's okay.
- No!
- Yes, it's okay.
Mommy, wait!
Please, I wanna come with you!
Eloise, no!
Okay, it's okay.
It's okay.
Eloise?
Eloise. Come back.
Donna...
I come in peace.
What do you want?
To apologize.
Sincerely.
Look, I know we got off on the wrong foot...
I was just hoping that we could talk.
We're all in this together.
Okay.
You wanna do the honors?
Yeah.
You know, I thought I'd gotten
so used to being scared that it just...
felt normal.
This feels different.
I know.
I mean, it's one thing
having monsters come out of the forest.
They start coming out of our dreams?
That's a kind of scary
I can't even imagine.
Yep.
Mama told us to hide, and I...
I was supposed to take care
of her, protect her.
But she was so scared
that she ran, and I...
I was so afraid that I...
I should have run after her, and...
Victor, you were just a little boy.
I didn't come out until morning.
We should go.
Victor, what is this?
That's...
Eloise said that that's
where my mother went that night.
The night the bad things happened.
She went to save
the children locked in the tower.
- See, that was fun.
- Yeah.
You do good work. You come back tomorrow.
Hi, Sheriff!
How you doin' there, young man?
Good.
Good. You guys working?
- Mm-hmm.
- Yep.
Hi.
Do you hear that?
Oh God! Help, somebody!
Help me! Please!
Please, I need help!
Oh God!
Randall?
Jim?
Randall, what the fuck?
New plan.