- Nothing?
- No, ma'am.
Her oxygen ran out two minutes ago.
John said she's here, so she's here.
Oh, Henry.
- You're gonna fall, Henry.
- Oh, God.
Please.
- Where's Mia?
- I don't know.
Where is she?
Nothing.
Living room!
For God's sake, there's a
panel behind the plasterboard.
Please!
John?
Living room, there's a panel in the
plasterboard.
Living room. Living room!
- Come on!
- Living room!
Help me with this.
Please, I'm gonna fall, I'm gonna fall.
What if you're lying to me?
What if you are lying, because
you've done that before, haven't you?
You've lied. And lied and lied!
I'm not lying, I swear.
She's there. Ahhh.
- Please.
- Ahhh!
- John, she's here.
- Is she alive?
I can't tell yet.
Come on. Oh, come on, please.
Please!
Good girl. Good girl.
- We've got her.
- Oh, thank God.
Get me up, please!
- Thank God.
- Please, please.
Please!
Well done, you're all right now.
- Henry, tell me about the others.
- Please!
- How many more were there?
- None.
Henry, can you tell me
how many more were there?
How many were there?
Because there was Adrian,
and there was little Gabriella,
and of course there was Emma!
Emma. I dug Emma out with my own hands!
But it was too late.
Please, please.
Please.
Please! Please!
♪ Love is like a sin, my love
♪ For the ones
that feel it the most
♪ Look at her
with her eyes like a flame
♪ She will love you like a fly
♪ Will never love you again ♪
This may turn out to be
the first time I actually beat you.
Got to go.
Emergency, which service?
Police, please. Please.
Go ahead, caller.
You're through to the police.
It's my mum.
Hurry, it's my mum.
- What's happened to your mum?
- Oh, God.
Oh, God.
Oh! I think my mum and dad are dead.
Mum.
Oh, God. Oh, God.
Please, please. Please.
Listen to me now.
Stay on the line but make yourself safe.
Boss.
So, Reed was right.
This is where you spend
your gardening leave, is it?
Staring down a big hole.
We have the Madsen verdict.
Given the exceptional circumstances,
the inquiry have found
no grounds for disciplinary action.
Which means you're back.
If you want it.
I want it.
Rule number one, don't get
yourself into this situation again.
Which means you observe
case management protocol.
Any pro-active strategies are
to be signed off by me.
I don't sign, they don't happen.
- Is that the speech?
- That's the speech.
- It's a good speech.
- Thank you. It's one I prepared earlier.
- You and Zoe, you spoken?
- No. Not for a while.
- And?
- It was a trial separation. I tried it,
- didn't like it.
- She feel the same?
Rose, I did everything she asked for.
Got myself together.
So now we'll see.
Well, that's the difference
between her and me.
She talks about taking
you back, I actually do it.
DCI John Luther, DS Justin Ripley.
- Good morning, sir.
- Nice to meet you.
So... Welcome back and whatever.
- Yes, shall we?
- All right.
So, do we need to have the chat?
What chat?
I was sick, I got better, I'm back, etc.
Um, then, no. We don't need the chat.
Good.
I've lobbied to be stationed with you.
I put in the request nine months ago.
Chased it up
three times a week in writing.
- So, what we got?
- Um, home invasion.
Murder. Victims are
Douglas and Laura Morgan.
Who called it in?
The daughter, Alice Morgan.
She was out when it happened.
Doing?
Buying bread and milk.
She live there?
Uh, no, she's a research fellow
for some department of Physics.
- She lives in a flat near campus.
- Why the family gathering?
- Douglas Morgan's birthday.
- Right, let's go.
Sir.
First responders have
this down as point of entry.
The daughter left it unlocked
when she went out.
So we need to look for any indication
that the shooter was watching the house.
Possible vantage points,
any hiding places.
Good line of sight.
You might want to keep
your hands in your pockets.
Reduces temptation to touch anything.
Sleeping pills.
Separate bedrooms.
What does that tell you?
Husband snored?
Anything else?
It's hard to say. Sometimes separate
beds make for a happy marriage.
That's a very generous thought.
It's good.
He didn't hear it coming.
He's a published poet. Small press.
So, no sign of burglary. No attempt to
stage the scene and no sexual assault.
- Contract killer, maybe?
- Well, it's workable.
I mean, the shooter
has done his homework.
He knows the layout of the place.
He eliminates
any physical threat, the dog.
Douglas, what kind of weapon was it?
Some kind of low-calibre handgun.
- Some kind? No gun?
- They are still searching.
House, grounds, drains. Nothing so far.
Yes, see, someone that efficient,
you would expect him
to ditch the gun at the scene.
Am I missing something?
Does that seem right to you?
- None of it seems right to me.
- Because it's not right, is it?
It's not right.
I'll, uh, meet you upstairs, yeah?
Yeah, sure.
Zoe Luther.
- Hey, babe. It's me.
- John, hi.
- Guess what?
- What?
Sir.
The Board of Inquiry's
came down on my side.
Oh, John! Oh, really good news,
that's great.
I mean, I knew they would,
obviously, but...
- Yeah, and I'm back at work.
- Already?
Well, they missed me.
What's wrong, babe?
Nothing's wrong, I'm just
on my way to a meeting, that's all.
Look, can we talk a bit later?
That's why I was calling, really.
So, you know,
‘cause I think that we, uh...
Well, we need to have that talk.
Ah. Tonight I... I've got a dinner.
After dinner. Um, I'll come round.
Okay, tonight.
Look, I'm sorry,
I really do have to go.
Um...
- So...
- What?
I've got myself together. All right?
I'm back, and I feel great, I'm good.
You know.
I know.
Welcome back.
For you.
Thank you.
What does it say?
"You don't have to be mad
to work here, but it helps.”
Good to see ya.
Well, uh, thank you.
So they welcomed you back
with a weird one?
Yeah, they did welcome me back
with a weird one.
- You?
- Honour killing.
- Ouch.
- Hmm.
So, how are you?
Splendid.
Excellent, then. Good.
- Miss Luther, I'm Mark North.
- I remember, yes.
Did you tell him?
Zoe, he needs to know.
All this sneaking around, it's mad.
You've been separated for months.
He's the only one
that doesn't seem to know.
I know, I know, I know.
I wasn't going to tell
him when he was...
You know, getting better.
Now I wake up, I feel sick.
I've got this permanent knot
in my stomach.
It's gonna kill him.
You can't keep lying. It's cruel.
- Miss Morgan?
- Alice, please.
Alice. Hello, I'm John Luther.
Senior investigating officer. Can I?
You must be very tired.
Yes. I am.
I don't think I've ever been this tired.
It's shock.
It's the way our body reacts,
it's one of those strange things.
Alice, I know this has been a terrible,
terrible day for you.
Things look bleak,
and you must be feeling very alone.
But believe me when I say
we will do everything we can
to find out who did this.
Thank you.
So, these things I'm going to ask you,
I have to ask.
I'm sorry. Let me turn this on.
Do you have any idea who would
wish harm on your parents?
Hmm?
Even if it's just a feeling,
a sense of unease about someone.
Something you heard your mum or dad say.
Something that didn't sit right.
No.
There's nothing, my mum
was a very kind, very...
Very gracious woman and...
- Can I get you a glass of water?
- No, I'm sorry.
- A cup of tea?
- I'll be okay, I'm just...
It's okay, it's okay.
And your dad?
He was a very admirable man, he was...
The thing is, Alice,
this was a very singular crime.
No sign of robbery.
And no apparent, and I'm sorry,
sexual motivation.
Now, I've been a police officer
for a very long time,
and one of the things that I've found is
that crimes like this aren't random.
And never without motive.
So, as painful as this is,
I'm gonna ask you to dig deep
and really think
about any money issues
your parents may have been experiencing,
any marital difficulties.
I've done nothing but think,
all I do is think. There's nothing.
There's absolutely nothing.
- Guv.
- So, he's back?
From outer space.
You do know the man is nitro-glycerine?
With respect, sir, a comprehensive
investigation under your edict
cleared him of any wrongdoing.
Not least because the only other witness
is in a coma,
measuring three on the Glasgow scale.
And Mia Dalton's in school today,
and not in the ground.
Rose, if you bet too heavily on Luther,
then you stand or fall with him.
And with you goes this unit,
and my credibility as its architect.
Haven't you worked too hard for too long
to take that big a risk
on such a wild card?
- I don't consider him a risk.
- Then what is he?
An investment.
And if Henry Madsen wakes up,
gives his account
of what happened that night?
Will Luther drag us all down?
Let's hope not.
So just one more time
so I'm absolutely clear.
You saw nothing or anyone unusual?
I'm sorry.
I wish I could tell you I had.
I've got this feeling,
this strange feeling like I'm looking at
it down the wrong end of a telescope.
Like it happened years ago.
That can happen with stress.
Different parts of the brain take over.
We remember things in different ways.
I'm so sorry.
It's been a long day.
Really, it's fine.
It's very tiring going
round and round like this.
You must be exhausted.
Can I get you a coffee?
Tea would be nice.
She did it.
She did it. Look at this.
Hmm? Watch.
I'm so sorry. It's been a long day.
There, she didn't yawn.
She didn't yawn. Yawning is contagious.
Someone in a room yawns, you yawn, too.
See, even talking about it.
It's to do with parts of the brain
that deal with empathy.
She didn't yawn. She did it.
And he's back.
Nothing in her affect points
to survivor guilt.
"Why them? Why not me?"
That's pretty atypical.
So her affect's off.
It could be medication, shock. Whatever.
Could be. Except it's not.
This kind of scenario, an offender
typically tries to stage the scene,
make it look like murder, suicide,
a burglary gone wrong.
- But...
- She did none of that.
- Exactly.
- Exactly how?
'Cause she's proud of this!
I mean, why give anyone else the credit?
- To alibi herself?
- She doesn't care about alibis.
She's a malignant narcissist.
This is about prestige, power,
self-affirmation.
The timeline doesn't work.
Three minutes before
she called 999 she was at the shops.
- There's not enough time.
- There's not enough anything.
Absence is the point.
It's a way of her saying
to us, "Look at me!"
So where's the gun?
It's got to be somewhere.
- Everything's somewhere.
- I don't know.
Say that again. That was special.
I don't know where the gun is.
No, she doesn't look the type.
Yeah, well,
that's the thing about people,
they always find ways to surprise you.
Tea.
Is your chair okay?
Comfy?
It's fine, thank you.
Only sometimes,
we like to shorten one of the legs
so the suspect
can never get comfortable.
Never relax, always unbalanced.
Is it too hot?
Really. It's fine.
I see you got
your PhD at 18 years old.
Astrophysics, was it?
Dark Matter
Distribution in Disc Galaxies.
Dark Matter. That's the stuff that
makes up the universe.
But it doesn't interact
with the things we know
and in the way we expect.
No, but its presence
can be inferred from
gravitational effects on visible matter.
We know it's there.
We just can't see it.
Would many police officers be able
to gain my trust
by having this conversation?
I don't know, I just like to read books.
It beats burning them.
No but you're the one
that's practically a genius.
- Only practically?
- So you went to Oxford at what?
- Thirteen.
- Wow, that's young.
These child prodigies,
they're not one thing or the other,
they're sort of freaks, really.
But I expect your parents were proud.
Very.
There were newspaper articles.
Pictures of mum, dad and me,
smiling in the library.
When I was nine,
I proved tangent minus 1x.
They bought me a dress.
Got me on the news.
I wonder what that was like?
You know 13 years old,
classmates were what? 20, 22?
No friends your age.
- No boyfriends.
- Quite a presumption.
Actually, I matured very early sexually.
Alice, are you familiar
with Ockham's razor?
"All things being equal, the simplest
solution is the best solution.”
That's right.
And what that principle tells me
is that the only other person
known to have been
at your parents' house this morning...
It was you.
I... I don't see how it's possible
to arrive at that conclusion.
Well, there was no evidence
of an intruder.
But absence of evidence
isn't evidence of absence.
I know. I'm making a leap.
It's a little leap, though.
It's more of a hop.
Is this where you ask me
if I hated my parents?
- It is about that time, yeah.
- Did they make me a freak? Yes.
Did I hate them?
Absolutely. Did I kill them?
- No.
- Can you prove that?
I can't prove a negative.
It can't be done.
Innocence is a negative.
It's the absence of guilt.
Meaning the burden of proof
is entirely yours.
If you think I did this, then you need
to demonstrate how and when.
I know, and I won't
be able to do that, will I?
- Well, you can certainly try.
- Because there is nothing.
You don't interact with the things
we know in the way that we expect.
Your presence, your actions,
can only be inferred by a certain...
- absence.
- Is that a compliment?
- Absolutely.
- Ah, are you trying to beguile me?
No, I wouldn't be so foolish.
But I will tell you this,
Alice, you can revel in your brilliance
for as long as you like.
But people slip up.
Happens time and time again.
Well, that's just faulty logic
postulated on imperfect data collection.
What if you only catch people
who make mistakes?
That would skew the figures,
wouldn't it?
- Yes, it would.
- Hmm.
But criminals aren't as smart
as they think they are.
Oh, that must get monotonous.
For someone as brilliant as you.
Ian, am I wrong?
- You're not wrong.
- No.
Guyv.
There's got to be something
we can find to charge her with.
Such as? Being a space oddity?
Such as, she killed them.
Look, right now she's little girl lost.
We've got no real motive.
- She hated her parents.
- Seriously, who doesn't?
There's no forensics, no witnesses.
Timeline alone gets it
laughed out the CPS.
You saw her in there.
It excites her that we know she did it.
So prove it. Bring me
something of substance.
Find me the gun, put it in her hand.
Until then, cut her loose
and send her home.
Thank you very much,
Miss Morgan, you're free to go.
Well, I enjoyed our chat.
You're very interesting.
:::::: www.hiqve.com ::::::
Wow! Nice dress.
Just come from dinner?
Come in.
Hi.
What's wrong?
You look tired.
Me? Oh, no, I'm all right.
Why, what's wrong?
John, I know... I know
what you came here to discuss.
But before you say anything,
you need to know that I've met somebody.
- Sorry?
- I met someone.
What do you mean? You met...
Someone, who?
Someone.
What do you mean, um, Zoe?
When?
A while ago.
- Who?
- It doesn't matter.
It does matter.
Are you sleeping with him?
No! No! No! No! No! No! No! No!
Zoe, no! Zoe, no!
Why would you do that?
Why, Zoe? Come on. Why?
Hmm?
Go home, John.
This is my home.
No.
Zoe called.
There we are. All right?
Are you gonna say anything?
Anything you'd like me to say?
No.
Well, then why say it?
Where you going?
Do you ever get
a song stuck in your head?
And it just keeps going
round and round and round?
T'Pau. China in Your Hand.
Cool, deep strangeness, that song.
- High weirdness.
- I've been thinking.
She's a narcissist, isn't she?
She needs constant recognition.
Needs to exaggerate her accomplishments.
How does someone like that keep secret
the most perfect thing she ever did?
You don't need to be thinking
about Alice Morgan right now.
Why? What do you suggest
I think about, hmm?
My wife? Henry Madsen?
I don't know. Normal stuff. Breakfast.
The way Alice Morgan sees it,
is this world is full of people
that have offended her,
embarrassed her, let her down,
and those people deserve to be punished.
She's already gotten away with it once
and she's eyeing her next victim.
And she won't stop until
someone stops her.
Until I stop her.
- All right, so be patient. Build a case.
- There is no case!
She didn't leave one.
She didn't leave anything.
Well, so what you thinking?
Well, she's compelled
to impress, isn't she?
People in general,
but right now me in particular.
She needs to show me
how brilliant she is.
She needs to be admired.
- John...
- And I give that to her.
I take it away, I make her angry.
And then I watch her get careless.
- Slow down.
- I'll call you later.
- They burned my dog.
- It's protocol. It's what happens.
He was only a dog.
It seems unduly pitiless to me,
to burn someone's dog.
It seems kind of pitiless
to shoot the dog in the first place.
Oh! You look exhausted.
Would you like to come in?
Are we being listened to?
- Would it make a difference?
- Who knows?
No, we're not.
So, you're not here to interrogate me.
No.
Liar.
This is a black hole.
It consumes matter, sucks it in
and crushes it beyond existence.
When I first heard that,
I thought, that's evil at its most pure.
Something that drags you in,
crushes you, makes you...
- Nothing.
- I love to talk about nothing.
It's the only thing
I know anything about.
Don't you believe in evil?
- I have to. I've seen it.
- Ah.
- Henry Madsen.
- Henry and others like him.
Me?
Conceivably.
- What's happening to your marriage?
- Huh?
Last time I saw you, there was a ring.
Today, no ring.
Is someone else involved?
I'm not here to discuss that, Alice.
Is he handsome?
If you like that sort of thing, I guess.
Are you in pain?
You don't understand love, Alice.
It's not your fault. You can mimic it
and I guess you can
recognise it in other people,
but you will never be able
to understand love.
Did you come here for sex?
No.
Because you'd be surprised
how many men do.
Do you think they have any idea
how fatuous they look?
Well, some of us
are afraid of that, yeah.
- Then why?
- Why did I come here?
‘Cause I wanted to tell you
that I know you kept the gun
and sooner or later I'll find it.
Well, why would I do that?
Ah, you just couldn't help yourself,
could you?
Wouldn't it make things easy
for you if that were true? But it's not.
There's no gun to find.
See, keeping that gun
wasn't a rational decision.
It was a compulsion.
You did it "cause you needed to do it.
And it's that compulsion
that makes you weak
in ways that you
can't see or understand.
And it's that compulsion
that's gonna get you caught.
And it will bring you down, Alice,
it always does.
Just like clockwork.
Are you threatening me?
Because honestly, I wouldn't.
- And why's that?
- Come now, really.
Because I'd be hurt and angry.
I wonder.
Why did your wife turn her
face from you, John?
Why would she do that?
Is it because you shine so bright?
- I'm coming for you.
- Not if I come for you first.
Good morning.
- Out, you two. Go on.
- John!
- Raus! Raus! Come on.
If you're thinking of calling security,
don't bother.
Call the police. Let's go.
Arriba! Arriba! Andale! Andale!
This is his sense of humour.
Everyone, this is my husband, John.
That's right, I am her husband.
Way to get me sacked.
John, the people in this office,
they don't know you.
They're scared.
They think you're gonna do something.
Do I embarrass you?
Right now? Right at this moment?
Absolutely.
- Yes!
- Is that what this is all about?
- No!
- Am I boring?
Hmm? Boring? "Cause, personally
I don't think that I am boring.
You're not boring.
You're the opposite of boring.
And him?
His name's Mark.
Does a woman
just get to a stage in her life
when she says, "You know what?
I'd like my man to be boring"?
Because I have to tell you,
no one warned me about this.
He's not boring.
Is the sex good?
- It's not about the sex.
- It's always about the sex.
You enjoy sex with him. You must.
And that image just goes round and round
in my head like a train.
The trouble with you,
that train in your head never stops!
- You really frightened me last night.
- Come on, Zoe,
you know I'd never, ever hurt you.
- John. Why are you here?
- Well, I couldn't help but wonder
if perhaps you'd like to
come home and be married to me?
- Some men bring flowers...
- What, this was a grand gesture.
This is professional ruination,
is what this is.
Next time, think flowers.
Next time?
You know what I mean.
- I just need to know why.
- You always do.
But not everything has a motive.
Sometimes things just happen...
That's not true, everything has
a reason. There are physical laws,
I mean how did we...
How did we get here?
One minute I'm one place
and then next minute
I'm 15,000 miles away and
I know that I've travelled,
because I'm dizzy and
I just want to throw up.
I just can't remember
the bits in between.
You tell me.
How do you think we got here?
What happened?
Okay.
You're the reason.
- You are. You left.
- But I'm here.
Now. Look at me. I'm here.
Only part of you. But never all.
Because you care more about
the dead than the living.
- That's where your heart is.
- That is not true.
All those years spent up to your neck
in malignancy.
All those months
looking for Henry Madsen.
All the months that came after.
And you were just gone.
And you weren't coming back.
Not, not my you. Not my John!
Then him?
When he's with me, he's with me.
Is that all it takes, Zoe? Eh?
Do you love him?
Yes.
I'm sorry.
Um...
And me?
Always.
But not like that. Not any more.
Look, I know it's a cruel thing to hear,
but you need to accept it, John.
If you love me, you need to accept it.
I don't know how to do that.
Could you open
the door please, sir?
Could you open the door, please?
I'm a policeman.
- How did you know I was here?
- Your phone was off.
- DI Reed said, "Try the wife."
- Oh, yeah?
Any news on the gun
that killed the Morgans?
No, we're still looking. But ballistics
came back on the bullets fired.
They were .9mm Parabellum.
Designed for ultra-compact weapons.
Good work.
Sod it.
"Raus, raus." ” Mother of God.
- Don't look at me.
- Okay! Okay!
- Shh. Shh.
- Okay. Okay. Okay.
- Your husband assaulted me.
- What?
He touched me. Intimately.
He made me do things.
He hurt me, because of you.
What do you mean?
Well, as he touched me,
he talked about you.
He said you were dead, that
you'd been very badly burnt.
Your face was gone
and your skin was gone.
You'd been abducted off the street
by a man, a very sick man.
He kept you alive for days.
He used knives.
A blow torch. He kept pieces
of you for souvenirs.
I'm worried that someone might
want to hurt you like that.
- Please, please don't.
- Shh. Shh.
Don't turn around.
DCI John Luther.
Zoe? Hey, hey, hey, what's wrong?
Bloody hell!
I mean, honestly, guy,
you should have just let me hold her.
You didn't give me enough to hold her.
And you can't prove
it was her this afternoon.
Zoe didn't see her face.
No CCTV, no eye witnesses, no nothing.
You do know this makes me
Alice Morgan's next project?
I questioned her brilliance,
offended her.
Do you know what she could do?
To me? To Zoe?
I know what you say she can do.
I also know we can't prove
what she already did.
And you can't detain people on suspicion
of crimes yet to be committed.
Be nice if we could.
So, what do I do to stop her?
Bring her in the right way.
- Ah, mate, mate, mate, thank you.
- Yeah, well.
- It's only a gun.
- So, tell me what I need to know.
All right, so what you've got, this is
a Glock 26, lightweight compact pistol.
Weighs less than 16 ounces.
Carbon steel spring and barrel,
polymer frame and components.
Polymer frame. Let me see it.
- Polymer. Plastic.
- Yeah, it's light.
- It's easy to carry.
- Plastic melts.
Plastic melts. Why am I thinking that?
Of course.
- "Knock knock?"
- What?
- Never mind. What's this?
- So.
Her parents get one shot to
the head each. Boom. Boom.
And the dog gets four.
Four shots spent killing the dog. Why?
It's a dog. It bites intruders.
- Why the overkill?
- Perversity. I don't know.
No, no. Four bullets in
the dog to maximise the mess.
To make the cause of death unambiguous.
She needed to blow the dog's head apart
to access the digestive tract.
She disassembles the gun, shoves
the pieces, the gloves, shell casings,
down the dog's gullet, into its stomach.
And then they cremate the dog.
- All right!
- It'll burn, watch.
- I have absolutely no doubt.
- Look at that, it's melting.
John, fine.
It's not enough.
The gun was in the dog.
Section 8, Police
and Criminal Evidence Act.
"A magistrate may issue a warrant
authorising the search of a premises
"provided there are reasonable grounds
"for believing
the location contains material
"with substantial evidentiary value.”
It's my assessment that saying,
"the gun was in the dog"
will not be judged by the issuing
magistrate to have met those criteria.
It's in there. On the mantelpiece.
And even if that were true, we can't
prove that Alice Morgan touched it,
let alone fired it. We need more.
We've got to trace the gun,
put it in her hands.
It won't be traceable.
She doesn't leave evidence,
just an evidence-shaped absence.
And after everything else,
that just infuriates you, doesn't it?
Come on!
She kills her parents and walks.
She threatens Zoe's life,
we can't touch her.
- This is Zoe we're talking about...
- John.
Who sat with your kids
the day your father died.
So take the chilly bitch down.
But slow down, calm down,
find another angle.
There are no other angles.
She left us nothing.
What do you need to prove more,
that Alice Morgan's guilty
or that you're right?
John!
Give me your wife's address.
What? Why?
I'll stay on her. Make sure she's okay.
You take down Alice Morgan.
I told you, boss.
The gun was in the dog.
‘Cause she needs it.
Alice.
That would be mine.
Hello, Alice.
Do you know why
the gun fragments in that urn
can never be
used as evidence against me?
One, the cremation melted
away their forensic value.
Because those ovens burn very,
very hot.
Two, you could never prove that
I ever knew the gun was in there,
let alone that I so much
as touched it. And three,
most dazzlingly, you broke in
to my apartment and stole it.
In the process you committed
a crime that will cost your job.
-So, congratulations.
Well done. -I know that.
This urn. This isn't evidence.
This is what you need to remind
yourself of who you really are.
That's why you followed me.
I know you. I see you.
And you think that I'm that weak?
- Yes.
- Then you don't know me at all.
Okay.
No, John! No!
- Stay away from Zoe!
- Is this what you did to Henry Madsen?
So, go on. Kiss me.
Kill me.
Do something.
Here's what's gonna happen.
You're gonna stay away from my wife,
or I'm gonna arrest someone else
for the murder of your parents.
Oh, yeah, by the time he's found guilty,
you'll have been forgotten about.
There will be no enigma
with Alice Morgan at the heart of it.
No one will wonder how you did it,
no one will think how clever you were.
I'll just plant the evidence.
I don't need the gun.
You'd degrade the law you serve,
just to protect some woman
who cast you aside like offal?
In a second.
And you think I'm the monster?
Love is supposed to
dignify us. Exalt us.
How can it be love, John, if all it does
is make you lonely and corrupt?
Answer the question.
Don't turn your back on me!
All right, Justin.
You can go home now, all right?
- You sure?
- Yeah, yeah.
- I'm good. All right.
- Okay.
Sure, yeah?
Very sure.
Go on.
20?
He'll leave. Let him go.
- Zoe!
- No. Sod him. He doesn't get to do this.
Zoe?
I hate to do this, it's my ex-husband.
He's, he's, um, I don't know...
Zo.
Zoe.
- It's Mark, innit?
- That's right, yeah.
John, you need to go.
We called the police.
Come on, this is mad. What do you want?
I want to speak to Zoe, that's what.
Well, it's not gonna happen.
It's not gonna happen. Not today.
It's not gonna happen.
You need to go, come on.
Um, I know, I understand all of that
but I really do need to speak to her.
Okay? So can you just...
Just give her some time,
she needs some time.
- Maybe give her a call...
- One minute. That's all I need. Zoe!
I know I don't have the right,
but I want to speak to you,
just one minute is all I need.
No, no, no. You need to go.
Please, John.
- I can't listen to you.
- No, no, no. Just leave.
- Just leave her alone, okay?
- I gave you a chance, didn't I?
I didn't ask you for it, did I?
Chill out! I don't want to talk to you,
I want to talk to her!
Listen, get off me, yeah? I'm
a policeman, all right? I'm a policeman.
See there, what does it say? It says
I'm above your rank, now back off!
I just want to talk
to my wife, that's it!
Wait, wait, please wait.
Zoe, I just want to talk to you,
that's all.
Just you. I don't want all this.
Okay.
Look.
I know you have to be
where you need to be.
All right? I can accept that.
I'll respect it, okay?
I still love you.
And I'm sorry, all right?
Don't apologise.
Don't be sorry. I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
All right? All right, mate?
Take me away.
- Hello, John.
- Alice. You may be very, very clever.
But you're wrong.
There is love in the world.
So you lose.
- Excuse me, miss. Can I help?
- No.
Thank you.
♪ Every day I see you looking in
♪ I'll be the smoothest thing
to touch your skin
♪ You're longing to be loved
but you're alone
♪ And your longing makes you
shiver to the bone ♪
These are good cops doing good jobs
being gunned down in the streets.
Everyone take cover!
He's gonna keep killing until
someone finds him and stops him.
How are we doing?
I'm going to send my boys for you.
Do not proceed unassisted
to the Kings Hill Estate.
Negative.
:::::: www.hiqve.com ::::::