- Cheers.
- See you later, mate.
How you doing in there?
I'll be fine. Did they go?
Mmm-hmm, all gone.
I had to.
Mmm.
You sure you've got the passports?
I've got the passports.
Show me the passports.
Oh!
I don't believe it.
Did you give them a tip?
Yeah, I gave them a tip.
No, this is a different lot.
Sure.
On the floor! Floor now!
Shut up! I said shut up.
Don't move.
James Carrodus.
Dealer of fine art.
Quite the reputation,
but not above the odd
privately brokered deal,
selling fakes to Russian billionaires
who don't know any better, huh?
And this cash,
James, was liquefied in the form
of 18 cut diamonds
of outstanding quality.
'Cause that's the best way
to carry serious wealth, am I right?
Now you're off
to start a new life in Rio
with your beautiful bride, Jessica.
The limousine arrives in,
what, James? 15 minutes?
- Ten.
In 10 minutes,
you could both be in that limo.
All I need you to do
is give me those diamonds.
I don't have them.
Okay.
There's nothing.
You go get me those diamonds, James.
In two hours. Let's call at 10:15.
I've got those 18 diamonds in my hand
or we start cutting
the lovely Jessica here.
All right. All right.
At this point, I'm sure you're asking
yourself, "Is he bluffing?"
I know you'll appreciate,
that it's in my best interest
to prove that I'm not.
Apologies in advance, Jessica.
You don't... You don't have to do this.
- No, no, no. No, please!
- Look you don't have to...
- I'll get you the...
- No!
♪ Love is like a sin, my love
♪ For the ones
that feel it the most
♪ Look at her
with her eyes like a flame
♪ She will love you like a fly
♪ Will never love you again ♪
Guyv.
Justin.
Hello, sir. Can I help?
Ian Reed?
I need to see Ian Reed.
Er, I'm afraid DCI Reed is elsewhere.
I'm DCI John Luther.
I share an office with Mr Reed.
This is DS Ripley.
Can I help you? Come on.
It's her tongue.
You sure you want to play it this way,
Dan? It's pretty hardcore.
The police, they get involved.
Kidnap, it's going to be.
Did you just use my name
in front of the victim, Tom?
James, the fact of it is
most kidnappings don't come
to our attention
because when it comes to family members,
people pay up pretty fast.
You think I don't want to do that?
You think I don't want to give them what
they asked for and get my wife back?
- Do you think that?
- James,
I just need to understand
what's happening.
I came to see you because
I haven't got what they want.
And I've no way of getting it.
What are you saying?
Jessica swallowed them.
The diamonds are inside her right now.
If I'd have told them that,
they'd have cut her open on the spot.
Sorry.
Oh, yeah, well, that's,
er, Bill Winingham.
He sent Carrodus directly to you.
- Oh, yeah?
- How well do you know him?
Yeah, pretty well.
He's a money launderer, basically.
Bit of a gent, as it goes.
Never involved
in any bloodshed, not to my knowledge.
Right, thing is, he was the one
that procured the diamonds
for Carrodus in the first place
and he's the only third party
to know that they even exist.
So if anyone set this up,
I think he's our man.
Turns out, no one's seen
Winingham for three or four days.
So we can't find our sole lead?
No. And the kidnappers
want their ransom in just over an hour.
You think they'll make good
on their threat?
Absolutely.
Um, listen, Bill knows me,
so do his friends and family.
Do you want me to go out
there, see if I can round him up,
find out what the hell's going on?
Yeah, see if you can do that.
So, they won't give us what we want.
We can't give them what they want.
No, we can't give it to them,
but we can lend it to them.
Meaning?
- Let's visit the evidence safe.
- Don't want to hear it.
Boss, these are
very special circumstances.
Same rules do not apply.
Chain of evidence
is like the Ten Commandments.
It applies unto time and all eternal.
Anything in the evidence
safe is sacrosanct.
We tamper, we risk voiding active cases.
Only if we get found out.
Am I actually having this conversation?
Are you actually saying this to me?
Boss, listen.
Listen to me carefully. If we do not
have any security to play with,
then Jessica dies.
- If I start stealing evidence...
- Borrowing.
If I start borrowing evidence
to use for my own purposes...
It won't be out of my sight
for a second.
Of course I understand.
He's your husband.
Oh, no. He's not.
Let me say it. Let me get it out.
And then it's said. It's said and done.
I don't want to ever have
this conversation again.
I'm gonna go away for a couple of
days and give you time to think.
- There's nothing to think about.
- Yes, there is.
And if you decide to stay with me,
there'll be no recrimination,
no blame, no nothing.
We pick up where we left off,
and we carry on.
- But?
- But,
you can never see him again.
Not ever. That means
no phone calls, no emails, no nothing.
It's necessary for me.
I can't let you do this
to me again. I can't.
- Babe.
- John.
Can I see you?
Absolutely. Erm...
I just got a lot of stuff going on here.
Can I call you later?
Okay, but I really need to see you.
It needs to be today.
No, me too. All right?
Erm, I'll call you the moment
I get a chance.
All right.
How much are these worth?
I don't know, about £3.5 million.
I appreciate the effort, but these
people want something very specific.
They want 18 diamonds
of a particular size, quality and value.
That's the best we can do.
- It's not what they want.
- James,
I'm gonna need you to understand that
unless we find a way to open up lines of
communication with the kidnappers,
they're going to kill Jessica.
Not tomorrow or the next day,
but before this hand gets here.
So you will deliver these diamonds.
But you'll attach a note that says,
"Give me Jessica
and you'll get the rest.”
- They won't go for it.
- No, they won't go for it.
But we'll have given them
a good enough reason
to keep Jessica alive a little longer
and we will have made
our first contact.
Once we can achieve that
then we can think about the next stage.
Hmm.
Ian. It's not my fault!
It's not my fault.
Look, we all know the rules, all right?
You rob a thief of stolen money,
he thinks of that as cost of business.
He's not going to the police,
nobody gets hurt,
no innocents are involved.
And that's the way these things have
worked since I was a woodentop.
Now this is kidnapping, Bill.
They took his wife.
They cut out her tongue.
Oh, sweet Mary.
- So what happened?
- I don't know.
All I know is that they're
supposed to call with the all-clear,
but I've heard nothing.
- Where are they now?
- I don't know.
No, that's not good enough.
Okay, you need
to listen to me, all right?
You need to forget
about the money. The money's gone.
The money doesn't matter.
You need to tell me what you know.
Who did your nephew recruit for the job?
Some...
Some American he hooked up with over
there when he was at school.
He's a bright boy. He's a clever boy.
Some American? That's it?
I don't know where they are!
Bill, they are going to kill her.
Oh, Jesus.
Okay? And I can't
be responsible for her death.
Not because the chance to make
a few easy quid went wrong.
So I have to make sure she gets through
this. Do you understand me?
Whatever it takes, I have
to get her through this.
Of course.
- Do you have it?
- Yes.
All right, Westfield Shopping
Centre. Central Hall. 20 minutes.
20 minutes, er...
I don't think I can make it. I need...
Entrances and exits covered.
Received.
Echo 1 in position.
Echo 2 in position.
Affirmed.
Carrodus coming into position.
Eyeball on Carrodus.
Okay. Here we go, people.
What... What's this?
Couple of hoodies.
- Subject's been handed something.
- It's a note. Instructions.
Pick 'em up, Ripley.
Yeah, I'm there.
All right.
John, stay on Carrodus.
I'm gonna move then.
Visual on the coffee bar.
Nope. No visual.
Thank you very much.
Diamonds are in the bag.
Received.
Benny, track the hoodies.
Tracking.
Ah!
Are you getting this, Benny?
A wasp in a wheelie bin.
Yeah. Have uniform pick 'em up,
they're no kidnappers.
Just kids that'll have been given money
to give Carrodus that note.
Well, go.
Eyeball on Carrodus. Level 2.
What's he waiting for?
I'm watching. Benny, what's he doing?
I don't know. But we don't like it.
He's made his drop.
Yeah.
Cover all second-floor
stairs and escalators.
Okay, I've got an eyeball. Two live
ones. One male, one female.
Here we go, here we go.
Subjects approaching drop point.
They have the bag.
Son of a bitch!
What's wrong?
She's not happy. Something's wrong.
I don't know.
Get in closer, can you?
- No diamonds.
- What do you mean, no diamonds?
I mean, run the bastard down. Go! Go!
Justin, if she makes
that call, Jessica's dead!
Don't lose him.
Hey! Hey!
You're under arrest
for the kidnapping of Jessica Carrodus.
You do not have to say anything.
Benny, Benny, come on.
Boss, come on.
John, I've lost him. I'm sorry.
We've lost him? We've lost him.
Oh, shit.
Listen, I don't know
who you are or where you are.
You're still in control here,
so don't put the phone down.
Prolong the situation.
Ensure the safety of the hostages.
Foster relationship between
negotiator and hostage-taker.
But most importantly, keep things calm.
Look, I know you're no amateur.
All right? So I'm not going
to try and play you here.
Yeah, I will try and trace the call,
but it's gonna take me a
couple of minutes to get in motion.
By the time I do that,
you'll be long gone.
You've got one minute.
Carrodus kept the ransom.
He did, huh?
Last-minute calculation.
The way he sees it,
Jessica was going to die
even if he gave you the money,
so why give you the money?
Looks like we both lost him, right?
Look, I don't care about him.
I want Jessica back. That's all we want.
No, it's not. No, you want to arrest
me and send me to prison.
Yeah, I do want that.
But that's not an outcome I can expect,
not right now,
not given the circumstances.
So I'm going to go for plan B,
right, which is get Jessica back alive.
What's your name?
John. But don't doubt
that I can get you what you want.
I just... Just give me three hours.
I tell you what,
you give me a number
and I'll call you on it in one hour.
- I'll need proof of life.
- You won't get it, John.
You see, this is a game
of trust now, John.
Do you think you can manage that?
All right, take this number down.
Uncle Bill, it's gone bad.
What do you mean?
There's no ransom.
There's hot and cold running police.
- Shit.
- What?
They've nicked Evie. Daniel's lost it.
If I go back to him empty-handed,
no diamonds, no Evie, right, that's it.
That's it. I've had it, I've had it.
Tom, I've got somebody here
that needs to talk to you.
Jesus, Bill, who've you got there?
Don't panic. He's a friend,
all right? He's a friend.
Who's there?
Okay, Tom. You need to listen to me
now. Okay? Are you listening?
- Who are you?
- Are you listening?
Yes, yes! I'm listening.
Where are they keeping her?
I'm not going to tell you that, am I?
Okay, Tom,
you can still get out of this,
with the money, do you understand me?
No, no, look, I'm sorry, no, I don't. I
don't understand, I don't get it.
The woman, okay, the woman,
Jessica Carrodus.
She has the diamonds.
Just get her away from
wherever she's being kept.
Get her away safely
and you can have it all.
I can't!
If you don't do this...
If you don't do this,
hand to God, I'll kill you myself.
Anything?
Not a word. No prints on record.
No nothing.
You know, she may not have been
our problem up until now,
but she'll have been someone's.
You don't start off at kidnapping.
You work your way up to it.
Why don't you send her details
to Detective Munch in New York.
He's Special Victims Unit there.
Sir.
"The evidence won't leave
our sight for a second"?
We'll get it back.
We'd better, because right this second,
I'm peddling thin air
like Wile E. Coyote.
I'm sorry.
- Can I get five minutes?
- You can have two.
How are you? Good?
Nice to see you. Bye-bye, then.
- Hello.
I haven't seen you in here forever.
I know, it was a long time back.
I need a moment.
I can't.
It's a madhouse today.
Can I see you later?
Not really.
Are you really going
to do this to me today?
In front of everyone?
I can't make a scene, yeah?
‘Cause you're safer here.
What do you want me to do? Beg you?
- 'Cause I've done that.
- I don't want that. I don't want that.
You want... You want me to ask you why?
You already know why.
Zoe, you say that. And I... I don't.
I mean I think about it and then...
I really do think and just nothing.
I don't know why
you keep doing this to me.
You and me, these
last few days, it's just been...
It's just been a way
of saying goodbye properly.
And I think we both knew that deep down.
We knew it, didn't we?
Zoe.
I didn't know.
Do you know who she is?
Do you have any clue what she might
be going through right now?
Where she is?
Do you want to see her tongue?
‘Cause I have it somewhere
here in a napkin. Get out.
- John...
- Get out! Get out! Get out!
Oh! Whoa!
All right, back to work!
The clock is ticking!
- Did you speak to Munch?
- Er, yeah.
Evangeline Nixon. Long history of
violence, extortion, suspected kidnap.
Married to this man,
Daniel Sugarman, 36.
Even longer history.
Armed robbery, extortion, kidnap.
More than one murder.
Yeah, that's him.
No facial tattoo.
No, I bet it's fake.
Just look at his face.
That's all you're going to remember.
- When's he due to call?
- In about four minutes.
Oi, Winingham?
No sign of him.
All right. All right.
All right. I'm here.
Do you have it?
Most of it.
Most of it is not what
we agreed, John. Deal's off.
What about Jessica?
You have to get
this into your head, all right?
I don't care about her.
If I no longer believe
her to be of sufficient value to you,
then her value to me
diminishes sharply. Do you understand?
And right now, it seems to me
that she's verging on worthless.
Well, okay, we've got
Evangeline. I mean, what's her value?
To you, Evie's an asset of very limited
benefit. I know she's safe.
I know you can't hurt her.
I know she's strong and won't say a damn
word about me. So keep her.
She's not in play here.
She's just a captured piece.
You bring me the money. Last chance.
All right, okay, I can get
£3 or £4 million.
But it's going to take some time.
You have one hour.
Plus, here's a revised deal.
You give me 100% of what I want,
you get back 100% of Jessica.
You bring me 80%
of what I want, you get 80% of Jessica.
And so on. You take longer than an hour,
you don't get to know
how she died or where I dumped her.
- All right, how long?
- Two to three minutes.
Make it two minutes.
Shh! Shh!
Please, Jessica. Hey, I'm trying to get
you out of here, all right?
I'm trying to get you home.
Please.
I know they're inside of you.
If you do not let me help you,
he's gonna cut them out.
So, please, please help me here.
Thank you.
We offered Daniel a swap.
You for Jessica. Do you want
to know what he said?
We've got Evangeline,
I mean, what's her value?
You have to get this in your
head, all right. I don't care about her.
I no longer believe her
to be of sufficient value.
Right now it seems to me
that she's verging on worthless.
So keep her. You bring me the money.
Now, I neither have the patience or the
time to feel sorry for you,
so this is a one-time offer.
You tell me where Daniel's staying and
I'll make sure you're looked after.
You've got 10 seconds.
Then after that, I walk out of that
door and you never see me again.
I want to serve my time in the States.
I can arrange that.
That was the burn code.
That means he's on his way.
- That worked.
- So what now?
Jessica's being held alone,
at worst being guarded
by a third kidnapper, Tom Meyer.
Come on!
Get down.
Come on! Come on!
Almost there.
Shit!
:::::: www.hiqve.com ::::::
You okay?
No, I'm not.
Are you?
No.
Yeah, it should be.
What a God Almighty mess this is.
Have we, um, put it together?
Well, best guess?
Jessica sees Meyer as a nice guy.
You know, her best way out of here.
Classic Stockholm response.
So she tells him about the diamonds.
Meyer decides to rescue her,
maybe keep the diamonds for himself.
Then, just as they're leaving,
Sugarman comes back.
He turns on Meyer.
Tortures him until
he gives up what's happening.
So the only possible link to all this
is the money launderer,
Bill what's-his-name?
- Winingham.
- So, track him down.
Throw accessory to multiple
murder, kidnap, extortion.
In the face of that,
he'll give it up in five minutes.
Mate? You all right?
Yeah, yeah, yeah. I'm fine.
It's just, er,
what a mess, eh?
Yeah.
Erm, so, listen, do you want me
to, erm, track down Winingham?
Yes. And I'll go for Sugarman.
He'll have vanished, John.
You know that, he'll be gone.
No, he won't.
No, he knows we'll be
watching the airports and the ports.
He'll probably go underground
somewhere, lay low.
Are you sure you're all right?
Yeah, yeah, I'm fine.
You don't look it.
No. No.
Bad day.
Bad, bad day.
Your nephew's dead.
Sugarman cut off his fingers
and his ear.
Oh!
And then they gutted Jessica and they
took what was inside her.
Do you understand what I'm saying?
Tom only did what he did
because I told him to.
If I'd said nothing,
my friends would've got there in time.
They'd have got to Jessica.
Tom would still be alive.
I made a really bad mistake, Bill.
I made a really, really bad mistake.
That's all right, son.
You didn't mean to, Ian.
I know you didn't mean to.
Okay.
All right, so I... I need you
to concentrate, okay?
I need you to concentrate
because I have to start trying
to clear up this mess, all right?
Does Daniel Sugarman know about me?
He asked if anyone else knew
and I told him no.
He knew I was lying.
It's okay. It's okay.
That's okay. You know what?
I know you had no choice.
What did you tell him?
I told him I knew a copper who could
smooth things over for us if we needed.
As long as nobody gets hurt.
I told him, I said...
I said, "That is a deal-breaker."
No violence, no bloodshed.
Did you give him my name?
No, I wouldn't do that.
Is there anything he asked you to do,
anything that might help me
find him before my friends do?
I don't know.
He said something about passports
and I told him to get in touch
with Patrick Holguin.
That's good, Bill.
That's really, really good.
That might help us.
Will you be okay?
Oh, Bill, this is not about me.
I'm nothing.
Jessica Carrodus is dead,
and I'm gonna have to try
and live with that somehow.
But you've gotta understand
that this has grown.
And if I go to prison for this,
then every case that I've ever convicted
will be questioned.
And all the murderers,
the rapists, the predators,
they might get out.
They might be back on the street.
And whatever they do after that,
whoever they hurt...
..that'll be my fault.
And I can't live with that.
I can't. I just... I just can't.
I'm sorry, son.
Do you want a drink?
Yeah.
I'm so sorry, son.
Me, too.
Thanks for coming.
How could I not?
- You sounded...
- This is such an interesting place.
John Milton was buried here.
- You know Paradise Lost?
- Mmm.
Very well.
He wrote it to justify
the ways of God to men.
But even he couldn't do that.
God emerged as a tyrant.
Satan as a hero.
Where is this leading?
All those things you said to me
about Zoe,
about me, about us, about all of us.
You were right.
There is no love, not really, you know?
Most of its just cruel and deceitful,
just matter.
I saw a lot of matter today.
Matter all over the place.
There is nothing.
There's absolutely nothing.
You know you hurt me very badly.
Don't. Okay?
- No games.
- No games. Listen.
I did what I did to Henry Madsen
because I wanted to help you.
I put my liberty at risk
because I couldn't...
bear to see you hurt.
So what I did, I did for...
..wholly unselfish reasons.
- I don't...
- Yes, you do.
"The mind is its own place,
"and in itself
can make a heaven of hell,
"a hell of heaven."
The universe isn't evil, John.
It's just indifferent.
That hasn't changed. It can't.
But what I did for you
proved something to me.
Something I hadn't...
..believed...
- ..until that moment.
- What?
It's you who's right.
There is love in the world.
Thank you.
Any progress on Carrodus?
No activity on the credit cards
or the mobile.
Right now I need to see
Evangeline's stuff.
It's fake.
Em, how quickly can we
find out who made this?
Batches of forged passports tend to have
defects specific to the forger,
so Benny should be able
to identify it pretty quickly.
All right, cool.
- Do you want me to come with?
- No. Stay here.
Stay on Carrodus.
Oh, get the diamonds back
in the evidence room,
save the Duchess's sanity.
If I get a line on Sugarman,
I'll call you.
- Patrick, yeah?
- Yeah.
Can you make me a passport? A good one?
- Best you'll get.
- Yeah?
- There, you see that?
- Oh, no, not again.
All right, now I don't have much time,
so I'm not going to drag this out.
How many fingers
do I have to break before I...
He's staying
at The Renaissance. The big hotel.
How do you know that?
He wanted a total
of nine passports for three people.
- So0?
- So nobody buys in that volume,
except terrorists and whatever.
They have a lot
of aircrews at The Renaissance
and I thought, I don't
want anything to do with any of that,
thank you very much.
- So then what?
- So I followed him.
What? You were going to make him pay for
the passports, then grass him up?
Too right. I've got to live
in this city, you know. I've got family.
Not even forgers are honest these
days. Go on, get out of here.
Wait a second.
What did you mean, "not again"?
Hey, John. What's up?
Zan. Don't do it.
Don't do what?
I know what you're about to do.
And what am I about to do?
Look, I saw your face
at the crime scene, all right?
I know it did something to you.
I know how that feels.
But if you hurt Sugarman,
you'll go down for it.
All right? It'll finish you.
Who says I'm going to hurt Sugarman?
I spoke to the passport forger.
I know you're looking for him.
So?
So, look, if you want two minutes with
him alone, break his legs, whatever,
but just let me be there
to tell you when to stop, mate.
All right. Okay, listen,
let's meet at The Fountain.
Fountain, yeah, all right.
Erm, I can be there at 3:00?
All right, but just you.
Not Teller. Not Ripley.
- Just me and you, okay?
- Yeah, yeah, yeah. Just me and you.
No Ripley, no Teller.
All right, 3:00 at The Fountain.
Okay, bye.
You're not going to be
at The Fountain, are you, Ian?
Excuse me,
no time to bullshit. Is this man here?
Erm...
Oh, you lying bastard, John.
You lying bastard.
Which room?
Listen!
Listen to me, listen to me,
listen to me, listen to me!
Listen, someone's coming here
for you, okay?
He's coming. He'll be here very
soon if he isn't here already.
Now, ordinarily, I'd let him
do whatever he wants to you,
but he's my mate, okay, and I don't
want to see him go to prison,
so if you want to live,
Daniel, I need you to listen to me.
Come with me. Whoa! Ian, Ian, Ian.
Ian. Ian, listen!
If you kill this man,
that's it for you, you know that, right?
What are you going to do, John?
Arrest me?
No! That's not what I mean
and you know that.
No, I've known you too long, mate.
I know how your mind works.
Ian, this is not a play.
All right? This is not a tactic.
Do you have any idea of the lies
I've told for you over the years,
for all the shit you've done?
Yeah, well I've never
killed anyone, have I?
Yeah.
Not for lack of trying.
And it was you, Ian,
that stopped me every single time.
So here I am, all right,
returning the favour.
Don't do it.
No matter how much
he's earned it. It's not worth it.
- Hold on...
- What did this turd say to you?
- What?
- What did he say about me?
- What do you mean?
- What did he say?
What?
Now it makes sense.
- You must be...
- Shut up.
Shit. Whatever.
Oh!
What did he say?
- I don't know what you mean.
- What did he say?
I don't know what you mean, Ian!
I don't know what you mean,
all right? Help me here, I'm lost.
I'm just lost.
Whatever this is... Whatever this is,
all right, we can make it go away.
I was here to make an arrest.
Sugarman was armed, all right?
You thought my life was in imminent
danger and you took appropriate action.
Don't say that.
- Why?
- Because you don't know what I've done.
I do know what you've done and I don't
care about it, mate. He is nothing!
- No, not him.
- He's nothing.
What?
Look, I knew
about the robbery, all right?
You... You what?
Yeah, I let it go ahead
for a percentage.
And that's why I'm here.
Not for revenge, but to shut him up.
Now, still want to help me?
Still want to make it go away?
Did you know about the kidnapping?
No.
All right, well, then, good,
‘cause I don't care.
We can still make this work.
I didn't want any of this, John.
You know that.
I tried to make it right.
I wanted it to be right.
I know. All right. I know.
How can I believe you?
You know how much I want to.
Because you know
when I'm lying.
And right now I'm not lying!
Take it.
All right?
- You lying, bastard. You set me up.
- Whoa, whoa!
No, I didn't, Ian!
Ian!
Did you see him? Did you see anyone?
No? Ian, look, it's just the maid!
Shit.
Ugh.
There were no diamonds found,
and the concierge...
..says that, er,
- this is the gunman.
- Yeah.
I don't know.
All right. That's enough.
Go and get yourself checked out.
Eat. Get some rest.
Ian. Ian, listen to me,
listen to me. We need, erm...
We've got to start talking, mate.
We've got to start talking,
otherwise this is going
to bring us both down, all right?
I need you to talk to me.
Put these away in the safe, would you?
Ah. Hello, sir.
You were going to value
some diamonds for me.
Yes, erm...
They're fakes, James.
They're good fakes, but they're fakes.
Evidence in a fraud trial.
Best we could do at short notice.
Jessica?
Thanks.
Hi, it's me. I'm not going to stay
at Heather and Allan's.
It's silly. I'm going to come home.
I'm going to get in the car
now and I'm going to come home.
I love you.
See you soon.
- Ian?
- Hi. Can I, erm...
- Yeah, of course, of course. Come in.
- Thanks.
Erm, tea?
Er, yeah, yeah. Tea sounds...
Tea sounds great.
Er, unless you've got anything stronger.
Oh, so what's wrong?
Oh.
Bad day.
For everyone, apparently.
Er, listen, Zoe, I need you to...
I need you to call John
for me and, er, ask him over.
- Why?
- Just do it, please. Would you?
But you can't tell him I'm here.
Why not?
- It's complicated.
- And it's my house.
So what's going on?
Okay. You, er...
You ever have
one of those days you wish it would end,
but somehow it never does?
More than my share.
Well, that day's today. Cheers.
And if you do this for me,
all right, you're going to
help end it, so please...
Please, will you just call John?
I can't.
Why not?
Because, actually, you're scaring me.
Look, I don't mean to, I don't mean to.
You know me and John are friends, right?
Well, so call him yourself.
I can't. I can't. I just can't.
It's just things have got
really complicated.
Look, Ian,
I can see things aren't right,
that you're in trouble.
All I can do is tell you to trust
him because he's your friend
and that means a great deal to him,
but I can't call him up and lie to him
and pretend you're not here.
I can't do that.
- You have to.
- No, I don't!
Just do it.
Just get your phone.
Zoe, please. Please get your phone.
I don't want to hurt you.
That's not what I'm here for.
I just need you to call John,
all right, and ask him over.
And when he comes, will you
be pointing that thing at him?
Yeah. I might have to. Just for a bit.
Just so I can sit him down
and make him hear what I've got to say.
All I want is to trust him.
And if I don't?
Don't make me answer that
question, please. Look at me.
Hear what I've got to say.
Don't make me answer that question.
- Ian, please don't.
- Just do it!
I can't find my phone.
Zoe.
John?
Yeah.
John, can you hear me?
Yeah, I can hear you. What's up?
- Ian Reed's here. He's got a gun!
- No, no, no!
- Don't do that. Put it down!
- Help, call the police!
Zoe!
- Shut up! Shut up! Just shut up.
- Just get out of my house!
Listen. Are you there? Zoe?
Zoe, can you hear me?
Shut up. Will you shut up?
Shut the fuck up!
Get out of my house!
Ian, listen to me, this isn't you.
I'm begging you, leave her alone.
- Come on, Zoe, come on.
- Please!
Zoe, Zoe, listen, listen.
Please!
No!
Zo? Babe?
Babe?
Babe, are you there?
No!
Ian? Ian?
Ian, what have you done?
Ian, Ian,
I will kill you, I will kill you.
If you've hurt Zoe, I will kill you.
I swear I will kill you
if you've hurt Zoe, Ian.
This is your fault, John.
Ian, Ian.
This is your doing.
Please be there, please be there.
Rose, Rose!
It's me, John. Listen,
I think Ian's hurt her!
As soon as you
get this message, send a medic!
Zoe!
20?
No, no, no, no, no.
Oh.
No, no, no, no.
Babe, babe.
Baby.
Ahhh!
What have you done?
No!
He killed his wife!
Wake up! Stop protecting him!
I am coming for you.
All I have to do is stay free
long enough to see you dead.
- Alice, I need you to help me.
- Where do we start?
- I can bring him in.
- He's gonna kill you.
It's not gonna come to that!
You won't hesitate
to give the kill order?
Absolutely not.
John, run! Run!
:::::: www.hiqve.com ::::::