BP's dropping.
- He's bleeding.
- I can fix this.
Can you believe it?
It's finally fucking happening.
Yulia's tracheas,
they're defective.
Sorry.
Just wait
a little bit longer.
Okay.
You were right about him,
about all of it.
Andy Beyene.
He just died.
I wanna see it--his trachea.
I wanna see it
with my own eyes.
Now, when you remember
this day,
will you feel shame?
Don't have a solution.
Welded wrong.
Clearly not working.
I don't have a solution.
Welded wrong.
We have to change
the material.
Clearly not working.
What of the ones
we used on Mr. Beyene?
The endoluminal surface
is barren.
We should be seeing anastomosis,
blood vessels developing
around the implant.
It looks like
the trachea ate away
at the surrounding cartilage.
Here, take a sample
of the tissue
near the left main bronchus.
Oh, holy--
That's advanced degeneration. Necrosis.
We'll test it.
You test it all you want.
That is rotting flesh.
I tend to agree.
I see no evidence
of vascularized neomucosas.
This is--this is gross.
Stay with us, man.
Just be quick, please.
We need to be out
before the morning shift.
- Shh.
- Hmm?
Okay, go.
The stem cells,
they were supposed to--
they were supposed
to come alive.
It's a bad time to find
enlightenment, Lasbrey.
Come on, let's go.
Anders, breathe.
I'm good. I'm fine.
I'm totally fine.
Nate, look.
It's barely attached.
He coughed
the damn thing loose.
How the hell was he breathing?
Oh.
All right, pal.
Just keep an eye on that door.
Hedley's already got
a hard-on for us.
The last thing we need
is for him to find out
we went behind--
- Wait, wait, wait.
Ah, shit.
Ah.
Yahoo.
Can you go like this?
Like that?
And then.
Macchiarini.
Did you see the email?
Yeah, we've worked around
the clock for--
we still don't have
a solution.
The material because these
are clearly not working.
Are clearly not working.
To change the material
because these--
clearly not working.
I got you,
you son of a bitch.
Yo, time's up, toots.
No, no, no,
I found something.
You said
you needed two hours.
You're rounding up to six.
- Yeah, yeah, but hold on.
Hold on.
- You gotta get out of here
before the morning shift.
Listen.
Yeah, we've worked around
the clock for two weeks,
and we still don't have
a solution.
And I'm very unhappy.
When I felt the tracheas,
they were
completely welded wrong.
They dried out too quickly.
They were like the ones
we used on Mr. Beyene.
Yes, I mean, definitely,
we have to change the material
because these are
clearly not working.
His tracheas don't work.
They don't work,
and he knew, Kim.
B, you don't work,
not here, not anymore.
They don't work, and he kept
putting them in people,
in real people,
in Hannah Warren.
I thought it was just me,
but it's his patients too.
Fuck, Kim, the fog. The fog.
This is the way out.
I have to expose him.
Okay, you can expose him
all over the place,
but right now, the "Today Show"
people are coming in,
and if anyone sees you--
Wait, wait, wait, wait,
what time is it?
Oh, shit.
I gotta go. I gotta go.
Sorry. Sorry.
Thank you so much.
- Wanna run the noble gases?
- Nah, I got it.
Lizzi!
Sorry, guys,
I don't know what happened.
One minute it was midnight,
and the next--
Mom, it's fine.
Your hair looks
really cute today.
Did you finish your homework,
'cause I could check it
for you before--
oh, honey, I know it's your day
to bring snacks,
so I got a whole assortment
of different muffins and--
We picked up some on the way.
- Oh.
- Sorry.
No, no, no, no, no,
that's great.
I appreciate it.
Bye, love.
Mom! Mom!
Sorry. Sorry. Okay.
Go ahead and give the extras
to your teachers or classmates
or whatever.
All right. Phone?
Keys?
Look, this is
completely unacceptable.
This is why we have protocols.
You're the head of security.
You tell me how it happened.
I don't care what was signed.
Was it worth it?
Oh, the entire posterior
quadrant is ruptured.
Trachea ate its way
right through his goddamn neck.
We have the samples
I smuggled out
from the autopsy.
I can run
most of the tests myself,
but some I need
to send out to the labs.
We should have results
within a few weeks.
Sure.
Is it Hedley?
He can threaten disciplinary
action all he wants.
We have the science
on our side.
No, it's not Hedley.
It's just this--
it's all too familiar.
Yesim.
Ah. Any word?
She made it through
her transplant in the U.S.
Donor lung, donor trachea.
But after everything
she's been through--
Tracheas were
just the beginning.
We had more organs
ready to go--
animal testing, prototypes,
all of it.
- Where?
- Russia.
In a lab overseen by you.
I'm here now.
Yeah, and your sudden urge
to give back
is truly inspiring.
"Two months after transplantation,
"the patient is asymptomatic,
breathes normally,
and is tumor free."
Anders, this is
what we published.
Our names are on this.
After what we just saw...
we have to expose him.
How many papers
has Macchiarini published
since his time at Karolinska?
Six,
with more in the pipeline.
Uh...
No, that's fine.
Just use my wall.
Macchiarini used
these publications
to build his name.
Perhaps they'll lead
to his ruin.
Six papers, three patients
from here on out known
as patients A, B--
Ah!
Sorry.
We'll repaint it later.
C.
We'll write our own paper.
A report
contrasting the results
Paolo released
with his patients'
actual clinical outcomes.
We show the discrepancies,
show that he knew, proving--
Fabrications. Falsifications.
Scientific misconduct
at the very least.
And we walk this straight
to the board of directors.
This implicates
Karolinska as well.
They'll try to bury it.
Yeah, and dig three more
holes while they're at it.
They'll crucify us.
Not if we do this
by the book.
We keep the patient anonymous.
We'll need permission
from the families,
access to their files--
Karolinska will make
our lives miserable.
Hedley warned us.
Fuck it.
We see this through.
You wanna blow the whistle
on one of the most powerful
medical institutions
in the world.
Well, I'd rather take a bullet
to the back of the head
than get one of those tracheas.
All right, let's go,
before Macchiarini adds
another letter to our alphabet.
Open your eyes.
Yulia.
Welcome back.
Can you speak?
Say something.
Is--is it--
The operation is a success.
See, I told you.
I told you
it would go perfectly.
Aren't you glad
that you changed your mind?
Is it--
is it working?
Of course it's working.
Something's not right.
It hurts.
You have to remain calm, Yulia.
It will help you heal faster.
Yulia, everything is fine.
Will I be able
to play with my son?
Yes.
Everything is
as it should be, my dear.
Everything.
Paolo Macchiarini
is a con artist.
Google him, and you'll find
a sea of good press,
good intentions, a miracle man.
But it's all just a con.
This is a story
about who he really is,
and the more I learned
about him,
the more questions I had.
He left a trail of bodies
behind him
from Italy to London.
Before that,
it was Hanover, Germany.
Paris, France.
Every two or three years,
he suddenly relocates his work.
Why?
He's running,
trying to distance himself
from the lies
he leaves behind him.
House arrest--
charges of bribery,
extortion,
except none of them stick.
And it all comes back to this
little piece of plastic,
this little piece of plastic
that turns into a windpipe,
but none of it's true.
Here, here, listen to this.
Used on Mr. Beyene.
Yeah, well, definitely,
we have to change the material
because these are
clearly not working.
That man that he's
talking about in the video,
Mr. Beyene, died.
But Dr. Macchiarini
keeps on operating.
And I'll admit I bought
into this fiction myself.
I wanted to believe that he was
a man who could perform
all of these miracles,
but Paolo Macchiarini is
more mirage than man.
And this story proves
just how deadly
a mirage can be.
There's a story here,
all right.
I told you.
But it's not the one
you're selling.
Back in Detroit,
you and me and John,
we had quite the little rivalry
going, didn't we?
A three-way tug-of-war,
and you, you were merciless.
When you had a story,
you had a story.
You weren't sharing it,
let alone giving it away.
All these years, Percy,
and you really haven't gotten
any better at getting
to your point, have you?
Like I said,
there's a story here,
and there's a reason
you're bringing it to me,
to anyone, for that matter,
same reason you don't have
half the 27th floor
of 30 Rock on this right now.
I feel like this is
a much stronger written piece,
and with your magazine
behind it,
I know we could--
- Bullshit.
You're neglecting your lead.
You, with this guy,
that's the story I'd publish.
Yeah, I don't know
what you heard,
but I have not--
- Okay, okay, fine, fine.
Let's break down
what you're pitching.
Synthetic tracheas,
no one gives a synthetic fuck.
Stem cells, people are either
for 'em or against 'em.
They don't wanna read
about 'em.
He's--he's killing people.
Maybe, but at the end
of the day,
you don't have any proof
of what you're claiming.
Like you said,
a sea of good press
is all that I'm seeing.
Maybe no one has the balls
to print anything else.
This version of the story
is too complicated,
too medical.
We need a road
into this world, Benita,
and that boulevard is you.
Don't go there.
It's the only place to go.
Deception, crossed lines,
secret affairs--
I mean, that's the through line
to this other sciencey shit.
Am I wrong?
You wanna expose him, you said.
- Yes.
- To save lives.
Yes. That's what this is.
I have
a journalistic responsibility
to tell this story.
It doesn't seem
you were too worried
about your journalistic
responsibility before.
Thank you
for your time, Percy.
Okay, let's review complications.
Tussis.
- Patient A, yes.
- Patient B, yes.
Patient C...yes.
You spelled sepsis wrong.
What? No, I didn't.
Is that a P?
Don't worry about me.
Worry about patient A.
This is going to be hell.
Okay,
tracheoesophageal fistula.
Patient A, yes.
B, yes.
C, yes.
Hey, Dr. Lakshmi,
I'm having flashbacks
to JV basketball here.
I'm sorry?
I can't seem to find
my name on the roster.
Nothing for you this week.
You've got me working six-day
shifts without any surgery?
So I'm, what, changing IVs?
Perhaps you can
help your colleagues
with their paperwork.
They're sticking us
in the rubber room.
It's not what it sounds like.
I've been on call
120 hours straight,
and all I'm doing is
other doctors' paperwork.
I'm clocking 110.
Honestly, I'm surprised
they even let me touch a case
since I came back from Russia.
I'm not touching cases,
only case files.
I haven't done a surgery.
I haven't done an intake.
I haven't seen a patient's face
in weeks.
I received notice today
my emails are under audit.
What does that mean?
They're tracing back
through every email
I've sent and received
over the last two years.
I expect you two will be
receiving the same request.
What are they looking for?
Slip-ups, mistakes, breaches
in patient confidentiality,
whatever they can find
to justify our dismissal.
All this extra scrutiny,
the unending hours...
They're trying to break us.
Is it working?
The sooner
we complete our report,
the sooner we can get back
to our regular work.
Patient A, tracheal materials
were made from POSS-PCU.
But Paolo found the initial
materials to be too dry,
so patient B was pure PET.
Time-out.
Pure PET?
Where are the trials
to back that up?
You switched materials
between Beyene and Lyles
without any prior testing
in place?
We switched materials
with every patient.
- B?
- Yes.
More tea?
No, I do not want
hot plant water.
The fuck do you think
coffee is?
Who keeps opening the window?
It's 30 degrees in here.
I need air.
If it's 30 degrees, then--
Don't make a Celsius joke.
You should be cold.
Oh, my God,
you live in Europe.
You live in Europe.
Sweet baby Jesus,
my seven-year-old is
better behaved than you two.
He's so stubborn.
It's ridiculous.
Oh, no, she just gets pissed
when she doesn't get
what she wants.
Nathan, stop.
You've been difficult enough
on her.
Why are you always
sticking up for her?
She's the reason
we're in this shit.
What's done is done.
We can't continue on like this.
Thank God.
Hello.
We need to get
out of this apartment.
That can't be.
What can't be?
I had Macchiarini's
stem cell solution tested.
The lab found elevated traces
of TGF beta 3.
No, that's a mistake.
It's right here in the labs.
What is it?
It's a growth factor.
But it's barred for use
outside of the lab.
- It's a known carcinogenic.
- Jesus.
Who on ethical approval board
would have allowed this?
They were probably all
just as blinded
by the miracle man
as everyone else.
They have no idea
what they approved.
Ministry of Health.
How can I help you?
Hi, yes, I'd like
to speak to someone
in permits and approvals.
Yes, I'm--I'm looking
for an application
for ethical permission.
Dr. Paolo Macchiarini
out of Karolinska.
No, that can't--are you sure?
Where are you located?
To the Karolinska
Board of Directors,
we hereby request--
No, demand.
No.
We hereby demand a inq--
Investigation.
No.
An investi--
Do you want me to type?
When I'm in need
of numerous typos,
I'll be sure to let you know.
Investiga--
I would have chosen
a different font, but whatever.
What--
...gation.
"It is our opinion
that these articles neglect
"to address the fatalities
"associated
with these procedures
"and omit the majority
of complications,
which these patients
have endured."
"We have analyzed
the medical records
"of three patients transplanted
with synthetic trachea
"and compared them
to the outcomes
published by Dr. Macchiarini."
"The claim that a synthetic
tracheal implant
"can develop
into a functional airway
is unsubstantiated
by our findings."
"We found
that all six articles contain
falsified information."
"That crucial data
had been omitted or"...
There was
no ethical approval.
- What?
- He never applied.
Didn't even try.
He just skipped it.
That's impossible.
You can't--that's--
that's the first step.
You can't conduct studies--
that's--that's felony.
You can't--
You can't, but he did.
Everything he did
to those people,
everything I did--
Can I have a drag?
Actually, I don't smoke.
Neither should you.
What's the matter with you?
I started back up in Russia.
Vodka and cigarettes.
Only way to stay warm--
stay numb.
- Hey, so--
- Don't.
I keep thinking about Beyene
on the table.
I saved him.
My first operation with Paolo,
and everything went wrong
until I stepped in.
I was brilliant.
I spent days studying
the science, his physiology.
I hear it's called preparing.
Maybe it would have been
better if he died.
Then none of this
would have happened.
How can I still call myself
a doctor
when I think like that?
There was a moment
in the OR with Yesim.
All those surgeries--
I started to lose track
that she was real.
We're all animals
after a while.
Body parts, organs, meat.
I couldn't shake the feeling
that I was
some kind of butcher.
And I...pushed things further.
I crossed lines
that I didn't ever think I--
The more I tried to save her,
the less I could.
None of it had
anything to do with him.
We all get lost
in the dark, Ana.
And there will be time
to grieve,
you know, to figure out
how to forgive ourselves,
but what we're doing,
this could help
set things right.
But in order to do that,
we need you with us.
Got a minute?
How's school?
You guys still working
on the periodic table?
They didn't invent some magical
new element to rewind time,
did they?
'Cause there's a few things
I would do differently.
Okay.
You know, we are gonna
talk about this, right?
Maybe not tonight, maybe...
at some point,
we're gonna talk about it.
I know these last few months
have been really hard.
And I'm sorry, but I'm trying.
It's just--it's not easy
to untangle your--
Papa?
Mom--
Mom, give it back.
- He's been texting you months?
I don't--
I don't even answer.
- Lizzi--
- Please--
How could you talk to him
after everything he did to us?
I don't even text back.
Give it.
Okay. Nope, sorry.
You lost your phone.
You lost your laptop.
You lost your iPad.
It's all mine now.
- Mom, you can't do that!
Yes, I can do that.
None of what he's saying
is true.
They're all lies.
So?
All you ever do is lie to me.
I lie to you?
How do I lie to you?
Well, about Dad,
about how sick he was.
And you lied to Kim.
You think I don't see
this stuff?
Mom, I'm not blind.
I know you did.
All he ever did was lie.
Every goddamn word out
of his mouth was a lie, Lizzi.
You think he cared about you?
You think you're special? No.
He's got women
all over the world.
He's got little Lizzis
You're not special.
We were never special.
Well, no turning back now.
I'll make the personal delivery
to Hedley's door.
You're a very gifted doctor.
There will be
other opportunities
far away from the polar circle.
I was the right hand
to a fraud.
My most notable paper
is a sham.
No serious institution
will ever touch me.
Oh, I wouldn't be so sure.
How many researchers publish
a revolutionary thesis,
then succeed it
with a new treatise
that's designed to dismantle
that very thesis?
It shows versatility.
Huh?
This will make a difference.
It has to make a difference.
My last patient in Russia
was a young mother.
Her name's Yulia.
He was going to put
one of those in her.
I convinced her to wait
before I left.
Wherever she is, this Yulia
owes you a debt of gratitude.
You didn't just save a life.
You saved her from a fate
worse than death.
Gentlemen, we have had
a tremendous breakthrough
that will help us
not only to enhance one's life
but to extend it.
Here she is.
May I present
the beautiful Yulia Tuulik,
the very first recipient
of a bioartificial implant
here at this facility,
and with
your generous new grant,
the first of many to come.
Yulia.
Here.
Death came for Yulia
after a tragic accident,
but little did death know
that he messed
with the wrong Russian.
Oh, gentlemen, come on.
You're making her afraid.
I'm not afraid of anyone.
Mama.
- Sasha.
- Mama.
See? This.
This is why I became a surgeon.
Through all the delays,
through all the setbacks,
moments like this
keep me going.
And I promise you I--
I will never stop.
Andre.
This man hurt
a lot of people,
and they deserve the truth.
My daughter deserves
to know the truth.
So I'll give you the story.
But you leave her
out of it, all right?
Lizzi is off-limits.
Paolo loved
playing the martyr,
the selfless doctor
who was, you know, so busy,
so caring, so lonely
without a bed to call his own.
But it couldn't have been
that much of a surprise.
Meaning?
There were plenty of signs--
your wedding, celebrities.
I mean, drown me in wine,
you could maybe feed me
that one,
but the Pope?
I did my homework.
It happened before.
For two divorcées,
a non-Catholic?
Paolo knew people
at the Vatican.
You still believe that.
It's so easy
sitting in that chair,
never believing
it could happen to you.
Paolo could make
any person in any room
feel like they were
the most important soul
in the entire world to him.
It's a really wonderful gift
for a doctor
and a potent weapon.
Once someone believes that
you mean something to them,
they just let their guard down.
They trust you.
That's why so many of Paolo's
patients trusted him.
And why you trusted him
that night
at the Russian hotel.
- I never told you about that.
- He operated on you.
He probably saved your life.
You talked to him.
I'm obligated to get
both sides of the story.
You know that.
He said you contacted him
from the ER
when you had your episode.
Of all your friends,
your colleagues,
you chose to call him.
Why?
I was scared.
And I felt really vulnerable
'cause I had just lost John.
Paolo made you feel safe.
At the time, he did, yeah.
You loved him.
I did.
He offered you
security, stability,
then he took it away,
just like your father.
Excuse me?
He kicked you out,
your father,
right after your mother
ran out on your family.
It's understandable
why a man like Paolo
would fill a paternal void
for you.
But then he turns out
to be just the same.
Man after man,
betrayal after betrayal,
after all that, one can imagine
you might want some revenge.
Go fuck yourself, Percy.
Any intern doing
a five-minute background on you
would find this,
and you're smart enough
to know that.
Ana.
Paolo.
I'm so happy to see you.
I have to admit
that your departure
was a complete surprise for me.
I just feared I would never
have the chance to thank you
for everything you've done.
I--
I've encountered
many surgeons over the years,
but you?
You possess something that gets
driven out of most doctors.
Imagination.
Oh, yes, you do.
I realized that
the moment we met
because you reminded me of me.
I'm nothing like you.
I read your report.
You and your partners crafted
quite a page-turner.
I'm just surprised that you
would go so far to undermine
what you and I built together,
after all
that you have sacrificed.
But that's why I'm here today.
Karolinska has given me
the time
to refute these allegations,
the opportunity
to defend my name.
To defend what, a lie?
That's all it ever was,
and you know it.
I always thought
you understood.
Why else would you cheat?
Why else wouldn't you seek--
Ethical approval?
Because my surgeries were vital
to saving patients' lives.
A loophole.
Loophole?
Our entire history is
built on loopholes.
On lines that we must be
willing to cross
so that we can give
desperate people a chance
when no one else will.
That's compassionate use.
There is nothing compassionate
about what you do.
You know, I meant to tell you
Yulia sends her greetings.
She's doing exceptionally well.
She's back home
in St. Petersburg
with her family...
with her new trachea.
No.
You almost had her convinced,
but luckily,
she changed her mind
before it was too late.
Dr. Lasbrey, we have
a few questions for you.
Would you come with us, please?
Ciao, Ana.
It was a mistake.
I don't know
what I was even thinking,
why I thought this would work.
We've seen it happen
over and over.
People who try to speak out,
to tell the truth...
They're the ones who suffer
in the end.
Heads down, mouths shut.
That's the moral
of the fucking story.
The system is rigged.
Good people,
they learn to stay silent.
And men like Paolo, they win.
- Not always.
- Maybe.
But this time.
You want me to come over?
No.
I think I need to be
by myself right now.
Okay. Try to get some sleep.
Okay.