Do you trust me?
I need to get her
away from me.
I found a surgeon
in the States who might be
able to help because I can't.
It's finally
fucking happening.
I already have a song.
I picked out the first one.
"May There Always Be Sunshine."
I was wary when you first
reached out to me.
Some ethical rules
are meant to be breached,
especially in service
of the truth.
Yulia sends her greetings.
She's back home
with her new trachea.
Something's not right.
It hurts.
He's killing people.
Maybe,
but at the end of the day,
you don't have any proof
of what you're claiming.
Is somebody going
to interrogate me?
What's up?
- This way.
This way where?
What the hell is going on here?
Don't say a word, okay?
Let's go.
Hey.
You're up early.
I'm meeting Aubrey.
And her dad?
Yeah.
Do you want me
to walk with you?
No.
Okay, well,
have a great day at school.
I love you.
Love you too.
Holy shit.
A claim has been made--
a breach of internal confidentiality.
What does that even mean?
They're claiming
we shared privileged
patient information.
Who the hell is they?
Well, right now,
they are the police.
So far,
no charges have been filed.
But they didn't
even question us.
That doesn't mean they won't.
They held us in a fucking
police station overnight
over doctor-patient
confidentiality?
Which is a criminal act
in Sweden.
You could face prison time.
This is a joke.
Why are you so
goddamn breezy?
Because Ana is right.
This is a joke.
Our process
was beyond reproach.
We had permission
from the patients' families.
We kept names
and identifying data anonymous.
They don't have
a case against us.
You don't seem to understand.
You're right, Nathan.
They just held you in a fucking
police station overnight.
You sent your report
to 13 board members
at Karolinska,
handed it over, hard copies.
How the hell do you think
that info landed
in the hands of the police?
It seems to me
Karolinska wants you silenced.
These are scare tactics.
Hedley tried this before.
They're not
just scare tactics.
There are real laws cited here.
If they want to find something
to charge you with,
they'll find it.
And we would win.
Even if you do win,
an institution like Karolinska
could tie you up
in legal battles
for decades if they have to.
That could bankrupt you,
destroy your reputations.
Where would
your careers be then?
Jesus Christ. This is insane.
Listen to me.
They made a show
of bringing you in.
It's very important that
you do not speak to anyone--
no press,
no colleagues, no one.
I'm talking to you, Nathan.
Fine.
You two will have
to hand over your passports.
What? No, I can't.
- This is insane.
- I have to go.
I have to go back to Russia.
What? Why?
Yulia Tuulik.
Paolo told me he performed
the surgery on her.
You can't leave right now.
She's sitting there
with a bloody time bomb
in her throat.
I have to get it out of her.
And replace it with what?
Another tracheostomy, something.
Assuming he didn't
remove a fucking lung.
She's healthy.
I can fix this.
You shouldn't be
leaving the country.
Then let them arrest me.
Three blocks--
three blocks, okay?
You're cutting it close.
The deadline
to print is in like--
Seriously, Percy.
I'm a journalist.
I know when
the deadline to print is.
Come on.
Okay, I'm two blocks.
Are you east side or west side?
- West.
- Seriously?
Just cross the street.
Come on.
Okay, I'm here.
I'm here. I made it.
You did.
This new source--
it better be good.
Hello?
You see this shit?
How can I possibly
see what you're seeing?
This little warrant
they've sent out for us.
"The three doctors,
after various verbal warnings,
"will appear
before the Karolinska board
to defend their findings."
We're being summoned.
It's a fucking tribunal.
After everything we uncovered,
after all the shit
that they put us through,
that goddamn butcher
is still out there cutting,
and we're the ones on trial.
It's not a trial.
Oh, like hell.
Have you heard from Ana?
No.
I think they're watching me.
- Who?
- I don't know.
There's a car that's been
parked outside my building
for the last day and a half.
Nathan, try to,
you know, chill out.
Chill out?
Now, good night.
Hey, Burt.
Dr. Gamelli, how are you?
You know.
Lucky I look good in stripes.
Yes, I heard
about the whole ordeal.
Wait till you
read the report.
The shit he got away with,
it's nuts.
I don't need to read it
to know it was a mistake.
What are you talking about?
You should retract before you
make the situation any worse.
What situation
am I making worse?
We have spent our entire
careers in this institution.
You and I both came here
to find something better.
And now your actions--
no one will take Karolinska
seriously ever again.
Our reputation, our funding
will fade into dust.
You watched
Yesim Cetir wither away.
You saw what he did to her.
- This isn't about one patient.
This is about hundreds
of people's jobs,
all of their patients.
I can't believe
you're taking his side.
His side is our side.
You didn't just go
behind the back of the board.
You blew the whistle
on all of us.
You have no idea
what we found.
Well, it doesn't matter now.
You've caused an uproar.
Whatever your report uncovers,
whatever truth there is,
it's just a whisper
up against all this noise.
You should have
handled this another way.
Any other way.
Fuck this.
Yes, of course.
I'm looking for Yulia Tuulik.
Is that Sasha?
Who are you?
I'm a friend,
a doctor of Yulia's.
Is she here?
I was hoping
to speak with Yulia
about her operation.
If you want
to speak to Yulia,
you will need
a phone line to heaven.
I'm so sorry.
You seem surprised.
The rest of the doctors
didn't seem to care so much.
Was--was there any pain?
There's no such thing
for my Yulia.
My daughter was strong.
She'd fight and fight.
But that thing in her throat...
Would you mind
telling me what happened?
She had the cough,
terrible cough.
The things she would spit up--
blue stitches, blackness.
And her skin, it smelled.
Like rotting meat.
She would spray perfumes,
all those lotions,
but you could still smell it
coming from inside of her.
The death.
The trachea decayed
inside of her body.
She just wanted to sing to him.
Oh, she did sing.
She did.
I only got, like,
two hours of sleep.
You slept?
I used to love
coming to this place.
Sorry. Sorry.
I'm here.
Thank you.
Yulia?
The allegations
against Dr. Macchiarini,
as outlined in the report
dated October 4, 2014,
and submitted to this board
by doctors Gamelli,
Lasbrey, and Svensson,
are serious in nature.
At Karolinska, our reputation
speaks for itself
and must be above reproach.
As such, any claim
of scientific misconduct
must be evaluated
and considered
in the strictest
possible terms.
Doctors, you may proceed.
Did you have any specific
questions or concerns
about the report or--
More of a novel, really.
428 pages.
It's all there.
Most of it, anyway.
We actually gave you
the abridged.
Right.
So, to summarize,
three patients,
all implanted
with biosynthetic tracheas
that Macchiarini misrepresented
as viable for transplant
based on the claim
that these organs
had been successfully tested--
they hadn't--
and that the procedure itself
was grounded in science.
It wasn't.
In the case of Mr. Lyles--
Whose transplant
you performed, Dr. Lasbrey.
I assisted, yes.
You also assisted
at Mr. Beyenes' surgery.
Is that correct?
- That is correct.
As well as that of Ms. Cetir.
If we want to go
around the room,
I think we can agree
that all of us
bear some degree
of responsibility
for aiding and abetting
Dr. Macchiarini, no?
Mr. Beyenes'
successful transplant
was the focus
of a prominent research paper
published in "The Lancet"?
Correct.
Of which you, Dr. Svensson,
and Dr. Lasbrey
were coauthors,
ranked one of the ten
most important studies
in regenerative research.
That's quite the achievement.
Any other
rhetorical questions?
I find it interesting
that none of you
voiced your reservations
about Dr. Macchiarini's work
until now.
I did.
Yes, Dr. Gamelli.
We're all aware
of your personal misgivings
towards Dr. Macchiarini.
I doubt you're aware
of the half of it.
We were all led to believe
that Dr. Macchiarini's work,
though experimental,
was substantiated
in legitimate research.
From an outside perspective,
it may appear
that you chose to benefit
from Dr. Macchiarini's
reputation and achievements
until it no longer
served your interests.
From any perspective,
the man falsified
information knowingly.
He misrepresented delusions of
grandeur as scientific theory.
He lied to his patients.
Why are we talking
about anything else here?
I'm not a doctor,
so please forgive my ignorance.
But it's my understanding
that these patients
were terminally ill.
If there was hope,
however slight,
that the procedure gave them
a chance to survive,
what was the harm in trying?
Mengele felt the same way.
The patients agreed
to these procedures.
Under false pretenses.
They were aware
of the risks involved.
No, they weren't.
They couldn't have been.
Look, the bottom line is,
these were experimental
treatments approved for use
through compassionate care laws
in the service
of saving lives.
And how did that bottom line
work out for you, Provost?
It doesn't matter
if a surgery
is experimental or not if you
don't have ethical approval,
which he didn't.
The use of TGF Beta-3,
in itself, is criminal.
TGF Beta-3?
The cytokine compound
Dr. Macchiarini deployed
in his stem cell formulation.
There's a section
dedicated to it, I believe,
around page 140, 150?
- 155.
Oh, my God.
They haven't read it.
You know, we really did try
to keep this professional.
Professional?
You've been accused
of violating
doctor-patient confidentiality,
sharing privileged information.
Professional
by focusing our report
only to include Macchiarini's
patients at Karolinska.
Or did you think
there were only three?
Keziah Shorten, 20 years old.
She died six months
after receiving
a cadaveric transplant
in London--
choked to death.
She's the one that Paolo used
to justify all
of his work here.
Thank you, Dr. Gamelli.
This is hardly the time
or the place to--
Then we get
into his greatest hits.
Ande Beyene, his trachea
rotted inside of him.
Then Christopher Lyles--
he had six months
to live when he arrived.
We cut that luxurious
prognosis in half.
Then Macchiarini
heads off to the U.S.,
where he uses these surgeries
to ask the FDA to give him
approval to operate
on Hannah Warren in Chicago.
You'd recognize her
from the TV.
She was two years old,
never left her hospital bed.
Are you finished?
No, he's not finished,
so neither am I.
We welcome him back
to Karolinska with open arms,
where he proceeds
to butcher Yesim Cetir,
22 years old.
She's in the U.S. now,
holding on to life by a thread.
Then the global expansion.
He operates
on Yulia Tuulik in Russia.
She had a son.
He watched her coughing up
rotting plastic and flesh
until she died last week.
And he got away with it.
He got away with it
because it took time
for these implants to fail.
He got away with it
because he promised money
and prestige and a Nobel.
He got away with it
because we let him.
It's easy for us to forget
what it's like to be a patient.
Imagine you're 22
with a hole in your neck,
or your kid can't breathe
on her own,
or the cancer is terminal.
And so you go to the doctor,
and you're just--
you're desperate
and vulnerable,
and you're just looking for
someone to tell you what to do.
And they trust us because we
take an oath to protect them.
Part of that includes
telling them the truth
because we all want to believe
a miracle is possible.
But he saw that
in his patients,
and he took advantage of it.
He gave them hope.
He sold them the promise
of a new life, and...
They trusted him.
And now they're dead.
The man experimented
on human beings!
He violated every principle
of medical ethics
and human decency
for which we have laws,
and we're all to blame.
We all could have done more,
including me.
But, right now, we don't
have time to soul search
because he's still out there
practicing medicine.
And so we owe it to
our patients and to ourselves
to hold that man accountable.
Otherwise, none of us deserve
to call ourselves doctors.
- Should we just walk?
- To yours?
Any fucking place but here.
Doctors, a word.
Look, this has certainly
gone quite a ways.
But there are still forks
in the road.
Why the fuck are you
talking in riddles?
Okay, look, I'm sure
you've read Dr. Macchiarini's
response to your report.
Were mistakes made?
Possibly.
But there is still a way out.
Look, papers get retracted,
diagnoses reversed,
inquiries withdrawn.
And the alternative?
Well, in the unlikely event
that the board chooses not
to press charges...
without the support
of the institution,
without funding,
do you understand what would
happen to your careers?
It's up to you.
I wanted to be
a fighter pilot.
- Really?
- Mm-hmm.
I felt a need,
a need for speed.
I wanted a bakeshop.
Do you bake?
No, no.
Not me, my ex.
She would make--oh, the things.
The things,
what do you call them?
She made rhubarb,
passionfruit, matcha.
Oh, fuck,
what do you call them?
Anyway, she would bake,
and I would manage,
whatever that means.
But as fate would have it,
"Ana Lasbrey,
welcome to Oxford."
I wanted to be a rock star.
both: We know.
Mm.
Macarons,
that's what they're called.
- Ah.
- Oh, so delicious.
I should call her.
Uh... I don't think
you should call her.
No?
And at the end of the day,
what was the point
of any of it?
Oxford,
residencies, internships,
scholarships, student loans,
fucking ramen for breakfast--
I mean, it is, objectively,
a miserable line of work,
and yet--
It's impossible not
to wonder what it says
about us to choose it.
The anxiety,
the 48-hour shifts,
the utter absence
of a social life.
Ah, yes, but look at us now,
on the right side of history,
a clear conscience,
and so extremely unemployed.
What? Shelabetsh--
- Albet--
- De arbetslosa.
The arbetslosa.
Oh, fuck.
Why is it so hard
to do the right thing?
Where are you going?
Home, to pack.
There's nothing
keeping me here, is there?
Anyway...
It's not like I ever want
to see you people again.
Nonsense, you love us.
You know, it's funny.
I was wondering when one
of us was gonna ask.
Ask what?
Where the fuck
is Macchiarini?
Maybe English is easier.
I wasn't aware we had
an operation scheduled.
Da, I'm implanting
a biosynthetic trachea today.
But I haven't prepared--
I prepared
the trachea myself.
I need you to keep working
on the catalog expansion,
the new organs.
Of course,
the work is happening.
But I thought we might wait
after Miss Yulia.
We're falling
behind schedule.
We need a breakthrough
if we want
to secure additional funding.
There is a German TV crew
filming a special here.
When the world sees
what we're doing--
"Miracles."
Exactly.
Miracles.
Don't you have work
to complete?
Yes, sir. Of course.
So imagine if, instead
of waiting for months or years
for someone to donate an organ,
you go to the supermarket
and say,
hey, can I have a new liver?
- Incredible.
- Yeah.
It's never been done before.
It's the future.
So you are creating
new body parts?
Yes.
Yeah, yeah,
like Dr. Frankenstein.
Or God.
So...
So-so-so from here to there?
- Mm-hmm.
- Okay.
Okay.
The work I do is not easy.
Innovation is never easy.
But I do believe
that we don't evolve
from a place of comfort.
Maybe the Earth is not
the center of the universe.
Maybe disease
is caused by germs.
Those were
revolutionary ideas once.
I want to change
the way we think about how
we repair the human body.
That's how we change the world.
And what inspired
such a revolutionary piece
of technology?
I don't know.
But when I look at it--
this was the first model.
Do you see?
It's a cross.
You actually suffocate
when you're crucified.
Not many people know this.
But without air,
we're just dust.
And maybe this is its purpose,
my purpose, the will of God.
You believe
you were divinely inspired?
No, no, no.
No, but I do keep
my faith in mind.
So you are a religious man?
Yes, I am.
You know, the Pope
has these red shoes,
and I also have a pair of red
shoes that I wear in surgery.
They were a gift
from my mother.
Your mother must
be very proud.
Yeah, I think so.
She keeps a portrait
of San Luca in her house,
you know,
the patron saint of surgeons.
Surgeons, bachelors,
and butchers, correct?
You mentioned earlier
that your work wasn't easy.
This medicine,
I hold it on my shoulders.
I have to keep pushing it
up the mountain.
Some mornings,
I wake up in my hotel
all alone, away from my family.
In fact, I spend most
of my year like that.
And this can be difficult--
sleeping in hotels,
on pillows that never
feel quite--you know?
My patients are my priority.
Room service for dinner,
sometimes just the minibar.
Maybe there's a movie on TV
in a language that I know,
maybe not.
Sometimes I wake up alone,
and I don't know where I am.
This could change the world.
The will of God.
And it's difficult.
It's difficult.
It is truly difficult,
and no one truly
understands that, no one.
But, to answer your question,
the work I do--
is it easy?
No, it's not.
But to save someone's life--
that is my purpose.
Oh.
So what do you think?
Suspensions, licenses revoked,
death penalty?
I think there's a possibility
I may still be intoxicated.
You guys see
the news vans outside?
What vans?
Something's different.
Who is that?
That's Ebba Blomberg.
She runs--
- The Swedish Research Council.
All right,
as many of you already know,
the report that is the focus
of this hearing
has been leaked,
and an article referencing
its contents was published
this morning to public outlets.
Due to the increased
public attention,
the Karolinska board
has decided
to hand the investigation
over to a third party.
Ms. Blomberg and
the Swedish Research Council
will assume charge
of the review from here.
Let's please begin.
Let's please turn to page 143.
143.
There was a question
about the shift
from POSS-PCU
to pure PET materials
without additional
testing in place.
Perhaps I am
still intoxicated.
What the hell was that?
Our report was leaked?
Did he say leaked?
- What does this mean?
Oh, my God.
"Love, Lies,
and Human Experimentation:
a Celebrity Surgeon Exposed."
Listen to this, near the end.
"Macchiarini has been
credibly accused by a group
"of colleagues at Karolinska.
"A whistleblower's
report details
"Macchiarini's long history
of scientific misconduct
"resulting in the death of
at least two of his patients.
"Add these claims
to the history of lies
"and deceit
in his personal life,
"and we are painted
a picture of a man
who is wholly untrustworthy,
perhaps even sociopathic."
Oh, my fucking God.
The news vans out front.
Outlets are picking this up.
American outlets.
Sweden is pissed.
Well, that's it.
You saw them in there.
Karolinska can't stand
behind him anymore.
Did we do it?
It seems this woman did it.
Who the hell
is Benita Alexander?
"The Pope?"
Sorry, it's all caps.
"The Pope?
She seriously believed that?
What a fucking idiot."
I mean, it's fair.
Hold on, hold on.
This one's good.
"Was this bitch drunk
or something?"
- Uh, you think?
- Yeah, you were.
And a little crazy.
- Drunk and crazy.
We all got to be
something, right?
Yeah.
Oh, what about this one?
"How could she let that man
near her daughter?
What a terrible mother."
- All right, you know--
- No, no, no, no, no.
I'm not even...
Have you heard back
from Lawrence?
Oh, no.
I mean, yes, I did.
It was a no.
Oh.
I'm sorry.
God, you would have been
perfect for that job.
Yeah, they're all
gonna be no, Kim.
- What do you mean?
- I'm un-hirable.
- Oh, stop it.
- It's true.
Turns out no one wants
to hire a reporter
who slept with their subject,
especially when that subject
turned out to be a con man.
Oh, well,
you know the golden rule.
both:
You don't fuck your sources.
Right, they should put me
on the poster.
Yep.
♪ "The More You Know" ♪
I mean, I knew
it was going to be hard.
But some of this,
I just didn't expect.
You getting
symptoms of regret?
I'm having symptoms
of wondering
whether it was worth it,
whether any of this
is ever worth it, you know?
Put yourself out there.
Tell the truth.
Fuck.
Why is it so hard
to do the right thing?
But you did.
We'll see.
Hello?
Yes, this is he.
I see.
Thanks.
Thank you for calling.
Do you know what
you want for dinner?
Whatever.
What did you think
about the article?
There's no point in pretending.
It's on the internet.
You should see what
people are saying.
I know what they're saying.
I believed him too.
I have been trying
really hard to figure out
how to explain all
of this to you,
what was real, why he lied.
But I just don't think
we're ever going to know,
and we have to be okay
with that.
But it doesn't even matter
because as long
as I have you, kiddo, I'm good.
People can say
whatever they want.
You kinda kicked his ass.
We did, didn't we?
Yeah.
I'm proud of you.
I love you.
I love you too.
- Benita?
- Allison?
- Yeah, hi.
- Hi.
Sit, please.
Thank you for meeting me.
Yeah, of course.
Your message was
a little vague.
What can I do for you?
I'm an ad exec at IPG--
a good one.
I read people.
I can tell the public what they
want before they even know it.
Then I give it to them.
And six months ago,
I was conned
by my fiancé--
former.
It was like this fog
all around my head
just wrapping up the truth and
the lies until it all just--
I didn't have anyone
to talk to, be honest with.
And then I read your article.
You just told it.
You put it out there,
haters be damned.
Well, there
certainly are haters.
Who gives a shit?
You're owning your story.
When I read it,
it just made me feel...
seen, I guess.
Well,
if it could happen to you,
and it happened to me,
at least we're not
the only ones, right?
Yeah. Yeah.
Actually,
would you be interested
in me telling your story?
Yeah.
All right, yeah.
Yeah?
Yeah.
Is it okay if I record this?
Sure.
Okay.
All right, so...
Crowds have gathered today
to hear
the verdict of the Swedish
Police investigation
into celebrity surgeon
Paolo Macchiarini,
who has been accused
of medical misconduct.
Officials are hoping
for an indictment
to be issued today in the case
that has taken the global
medical community by storm.
My daughter.
I'm so sorry.
Hello.
After months of investigations
and deliberations,
we, along with
the Prosecutor General,
are prepared
to announce our findings.
We have found that there was
a clear and real
scientific misconduct
that took place--
negligence
and surgical misadventures--
during Dr. Macchiarini's
tenure here in Sweden.
However, we do not
have the grounds
to charge Dr. Paolo Macchiarini
with any criminal conduct.
In our conclusion,
in terms of the criminal law,
there are no grounds
for legal liability.
This investigation
has now been closed.
It's Wednesday.
Hump day happy hour?
First pint's on me.
What about the second?
The second is on you.
I can't get it.
I can't afford it.
The fifth is on me.
"I'll be back."
It must be, it must be.
I don't know, man.
What do you think it is?
Yippee kayak, motherfucker?
Yippee ki-yay.
He's very serious
about these things.
Please don't get him started.
- I'm with you.
- No, no, no.
Don't argue on this with me.
Sure.
He didn't win.
Not really.
No?
I'm glad we did it, though.
Me too.
Yeah.
But if you could go back,
if you found a DeLorean
right now,
would you do it again?
Oh, absolutely fucking not.
But that's the thing.
Science is not perfect, right?
Far from it.
But, for some reason,
we think that
the medical system can be.
And we can't fight the system
because we're all a part of it.
So I suppose all
we can do is this:
fight for it.
And that's why
you stayed, right?
I guess you're right.
Aw, well,
that is lovely, Dr. Svensson.
Such a sap.
I really--I can't with this.
Where do you think
I get it from?
Who, me?
- "We owe it to our patients"...
- No.
"And ourselves to hold
that man accountable."
both: "Otherwise,
none of us deserve
to call ourselves doctors."
Come on. All right.
You know, there is something
that's been bugging me.
We were so careful.
Fucking hard copies--
who the hell leaked the report?
I suppose we'll never know.
Let's just be thankful
that someone did.
- Skol.
Skol.
both: Skol.