All I can hope is
when you walk out
of that church,
when you listen
to those bells ringing,
that you will be happy.
Hi, my love.
I'm here missing you
in Barcelona.
The lemon trees
are ready for you.
- Hey, Paolo?
- Yeah?
What do I call you
after the wedding?
What about Papa?
Papa. OK.
You want us to move
to Barcelona?
It's an incredible place
to raise a child.
Paolo was arraigned
for extortion.
This guy--
this guy was in Italy.
Why me, Paolo?
You don't want to go
digging in there, Benita,
because it's dangerous.
You need to leave.
Yulia, my dear,
for you, only the best.
So this is an
elective surgery.
- Yeah.
- Oh.
This grant has everything.
It's all based on a lie--
the patients are, the trials--
he's experimenting on people.
He just took it out.
The issues
that arose afterwards
are completely unrelated
to my procedure.
Gentlemen,
welcome to Krasnodar,
the world's
premier destination
for the most
cutting-edge procedures
in regenerative medicine.
Today, we will show you
what we have built
this past year under
the leadership of Dr. Lasbrey.
We realize that the delays
have been trying,
but the results we've seen
are revolutionary.
The upcoming patient trials
are the final step
before full medical approval.
These are young,
healthy adults
who are electing to be
a part of the future.
In just a few days,
we will perform
our very first procedure
on a young woman
named Yulia Tuulik.
In Karolinska,
we operated to save lives.
Here in Krasnodar, we will
operate to improve lives.
And now, I leave you
with Dr. Lasbrey,
who is going to show you
around our facilities.
Thank you.
Right this way.
In tandem with
the trachea transplantations,
we've made significant headway
in our expanded research.
We've just entered
the testing phase
for our next biosynthetic
organ, the diaphragm.
Vasia, Mila, may we interrupt?
- Ana.
- Welcome back.
It's good to be back.
How was Sweden?
Are they all dead?
What?
No, no, they're anesthetized.
They cannot feel a thing.
If it seems cruel,
that's because it is.
We began with the trachea.
Now we've made headway
with the diaphragm,
a much more complex organ.
But these were
just the beginning.
Next, we conquer the liver,
the lungs,
the heart.
Dr. Lasbrey,
we have waited longer
than we wished for progress.
But this facility
does not disappoint.
- Knock, knock.
- Ah, it's you.
Can you believe it?
It's finally fucking happening.
No more silk chokers for you.
Ah, I'll be able
to fucking shower.
What, you don't like
Andrej's bubble baths?
This is going to make
everything right.
We have one last hard part.
Are you ready?
- I am.
Are you going to tell me
what you're doing back there?
Or are you going to make me
guess, like my husband?
Well, this is technically the
first part of your procedure.
We're going to extract
bone marrow from your hip,
separate the stem cells
from the bone marrow.
Then later, I'll give your
new trachea a nice bath
with the stem cells.
Thank you.
Well, don't thank me yet.
This will be
a bit uncomfortable.
I mean it. Spasibo.
Tiny prick.
You're going to feel
a series of pinches.
OK.
How was your trip
from Saint Petersburg?
I sat next to a big fat guy.
Andrej's not that fat.
Ow.
Aisle or window?
Window.
I watched the country pass by.
You doing OK?
This is nothing.
Really?
When I was in my car crash,
I was pregnant with Sasha.
They had to re-break my bones,
pick my teeth up
from the street.
My whole body was broken,
but that little boy survived.
After that, I--
I promised
I would keep him safe.
Through all the surgeries,
I never took the painkillers.
I didn't want
to put him in danger.
This?
This is nothing.
Ow.
OK.
Maybe this is something.
How is little Sasha?
I miss him already.
But after this,
I can be a real mother.
You are a real mother.
Not like I want to be.
We can go swimming.
Oh.
I can sing to him.
I already have a song.
I picked out the first one.
"Poust Vzegda Boudyit Solnse."
Oh, my Russian's
not that good.
It means,
"May There Always Be Sunshine."
That sounds beautiful.
OK, this is the last one.
And we're done.
Why so many?
Since we're using a new
material for your trachea,
Dr. Macchiarini wanted
to be extra careful.
We're preparing three tracheas
for your surgery,
just in case.
Hey, Lizzi,
please don't make a mess.
I need my gloves.
What do you need
your gloves for?
It's summer.
Well, we have to
unpack it anyway,
so what difference
does it make?
I know this is hard
to understand.
Well, then,
why don't you explain it to me?
Because it's complicated.
Hmm. Whatever.
- But it's for the best.
- How?
Paolo's the only good thing--
- The only good thing what?
- Nothing.
The only good thing what?
The only good thing that
happened to us since Dad died.
I know...
This sucks for both of us.
- Then fix it.
- I can't fix it, Lizzi.
It's not something that--
Why not?
I had to pack all my stuff,
have a goodbye party,
take stupid Spanish lessons.
Well, we live in New York.
It's probably good to know
a little Spanish.
Oh, my God, Mom,
you're not listening to me.
Oh, God.
Don't move.
He wasn't even playing.
I just saw what
I wanted to see--
with the arrest,
with the wedding, all of it.
His CV--
he lists a fellowship
in thoracic surgery
at the University of Alabama.
They don't even have
a thoracic program.
He was never the Pope's
personal doctor, obviously.
Confirmed that
with the Vatican.
It's just
the personal life stuff
that seems to be more
of a black hole.
Born in 1958.
Lived in Switzerland--
at least I think that's real.
Married 1986 in Italy,
no divorce record on file
'cause he never actually
got divorced.
It's just lie
after fucking lie.
We've got to get you
out of this house.
You need to work, real work.
I'm going to start
making some calls.
You know what?
It's one thing to fuck with
my life, but with Lizzi's?
I want to tell her
the truth so badly.
But how can I when I don't
even know what the truth is?
But I really want
to figure it out.
Fuck it.
I'll go to him.
- Go where?
I don't know,
wherever I have to go.
I'm not going to watch you
do this to yourself.
Come on, Kim, I have to know
who this guy really is.
- Do you?
- Yes.
And this is why.
Another fucking article calling
him a rock star surgeon?
Well, how the hell are you
supposed to move on
when you still get
Google Alerts on the guy?
The entire world thinks he's
a miracle man because of me.
* Life is funny ♪
- Hey, hey, hello.
- * Skies are sunny ♪
♪ Bees make honey ♪
♪ Who needs money?
No, not poor me ♪
Where have you been
the last few days?
I checked work, the bar,
the linen closet.
Then I ran out of places
that you'd go.
I just needed
some time to myself.
Well, time's up, I think.
We have work to do.
- Oh, do we?
- Yes.
To stop Macchiarini.
Going to have to pass
on that endeavor, Anders.
I--I--
I thought you would
be more, more.
OK, I know I turned my back
when you needed me.
But I'm here now.
We have to figure out
a way to stop this guy.
Maybe you were right
to turn your back.
I don't understand.
After Yesim--
What?
After Yesim, what?
I kept my promise to her.
It didn't make a difference.
He still got to walk away.
No, he's not walking.
He's publishing about Yesim.
While she was flatlining
on your table,
Paolo was writing a paper about
her successful transplant,
called it "a huge advancement
in the field."
He's being praised for it,
"a rock star surgeon."
Not only did he
destroy her life,
now he's profiting
off her pain.
If that sits right with you,
by all means,
let it sit that way.
♪ Oh, yeah ♪
I heard that
you were interested
in seeing your new trachea, correct?
This is a prototype,
an exact replica
of your natural trachea,
or more precisely,
what it looked like
before the accident.
It is built from
all the X-rays and CAT scans
that you and Dr. Lasbrey have
taken over the past few months.
Here, take it.
Yeah?
It looks like plastic.
Wouldn't it be better
to use a natural material?
I thought you might ask
something like that.
You will have heard
of Mr. Andemariam Beyene.
Do you know that a few days
before his operation,
he asked me and Dr. Lasbrey
the same question?
And then he had
the very same procedure
that you will receive.
And today, two years later,
he's thriving.
, Yulia.
You will be in the most capable
hands every step of the way,
starting with Dr. Lasbrey,
who has already begun
preparing the implant
for transplantation.
All right,
all right, all right.
No need to feel me up.
Ciao.
I'm sorry.
My Italian is not very good.
Do you s--
- My English is fine.
Oh, OK.
My name is Benita Alexander.
I actually saw you
a few months ago.
I--I was here with
Dr. Paolo Macchiarini.
And you two exchanged
some words.
What the hell do you want?
I--I wanted to talk to you
about him, actually.
About what he did to you.
How'd you find me?
I'm a journalist.
Did he send you?
No. I sent myself.
And I'm so sorry.
When we--when you saw Paolo,
your son was with you.
What's his name?
- Nico.
I have a daughter a little
older than him, Lizzi.
So what--what happened?
What did he do?
Why you interested?
No one was interested
when it mattered.
Because I want the truth.
I want any kind of truth
about who he really is.
And you two seem
to have a history.
Was this about his arrest?
'Cause I read about it
in the newspaper,
but then I couldn't find any--
I giornali,
no, there wouldn't be.
You'll find it is very easy
to hide things away here.
Then tell me. Please.
Well, Paolo was a...
I trusted him,
trusted his prognosis
when my wife
was diagnosed with cancer.
Trusted in his research,
the future he promised us.
I trusted when he asked
for 150,000 euros
to skip the waiting list
for a donor.
I trusted far too much.
After she died,
we no longer seemed
to matter to him.
I tried to speak the truth,
but the code of silence here...
I'm surprised he was
arrested at all.
But then, of course,
he was cleared.
So I lost my work,
my savings,
and my wife.
Stay away from
Paolo Macchiarini.
Men like him,
they get away with murder.
Hello.
Hi.
Beautiful, isn't it?
It really is.
It's like a cocoon of color.
Hmm.
What brings you here?
Honestly, I don't--
I don't even know anymore.
Well,
this is good place to be
if you are lost.
Are you lost?
I'm on a mission.
That sounds really nice
and clear cut.
So where did this
mission of yours start?
South Korea,
a small neighborhood
called Yongsan-gu.
Yongsan-gu?
Mm-hmm, yes. You know?
I do. I do, actually.
I, um...
I knew a little girl
who was really sick, and...
she and her family
were from Yongsan-gu.
Hmm, a small world.
Yeah.
It's nice to be reminded
of how connected we all are.
Connected by God, you mean?
Mm, God,
a greater purpose,
coincidence--
call it what you like.
Just reminds me
we are not alone.
Ah,.
I sound like priest now,
don't I?
Would you mind
if I say a prayer
for the little girl
and her family?
No, I don't mind.
Ah, excuse me a moment.
I'll be right back.
We have a problem--
three, actually.
Yulia's tracheas,
they're defective.
- Which?
- All of them.
What is the issue?
They're flawed.
They're not--
What is the issue?
Number one is too soft.
- Mm-hmm.
- It's almost soggy.
OK.
Number two has several holes.
It's unusable.
- And number three?
- It's too short.
- How short?
- 3 millimeters.
Sod it.
We'll use the short one.
You don't think
we should postpone?
I can build a new implant,
recalibrate the bioreactor--
- No.
- It will only take a few weeks.
We cannot wait.
That trachea could fail.
Keep your voice down.
We cannot postpone.
We do not need to postpone.
It will be difficult.
Difficult, but not impossible.
So now, you can continue
with the preparations
for the surgery, Dr. Lasbrey.
Thank you.
Come in.
Hi.
Hi, um...
I just wanted
to check in on you.
How are you feeling
about your surgery?
Are you scared at all, worried?
Well, you asking me
all these questions
is making me nervous.
If you asked less,
I would be calm.
Should I be worried?
It's just, I've been thinking
about it more and more.
And this new
synthetic material,
it hasn't been tested.
Yes, I know this.
So maybe you'd like to wait
until we can conduct
some proper trials.
Where is this coming from?
And why now,
after I've waited for so long?
I know that you've waited,
but we--
But you said
the procedure is safe,
that because I'm healthy,
I'll be OK.
I know what we told you.
But the new material--
New material or old material,
I don't give a shit.
I promised my son
that I would come back
and sing to him,
to run with him,
to laugh with him.
I want to be myself again.
Dr. Macchiarini is giving me
a chance to be myself again.
Do you really want
to be a human guinea pig,
a rat like all the others
we have caged up in this lab?
Look, I am begging you.
Just wait a little bit longer.
Even in a few months,
we'll know so much more.
I just want you to be safe.
OK.
I'll wait.
Oh, hi.
Sorry, excuse me.
Uh, perdóneme, un cafe de...
I cannot believe you're here.
I figured you needed
an interpreter.
Oh, my God, Kim.
He told me Andrea Bocelli was
going to sing at the wedding.
Like, in what world?
- In our world, B.
Stop beating yourself up.
OK, you're going to stay
to the right up here.
We're doing this.
I didn't say a thing.
But if I said one thing,
this journey you're on,
I'm all for it.
I just--I hope you know
what you're looking for.
We were supposed
to come to this house
a dozen times while
we were together,
and we never made it.
He always had some reason.
And you think there's
some sort of answer here?
I do.
I think there is a part
of him here that's real.
How do you know
he's not going to be home?
He's in Russia--
big surgery,
very important patient
who I helped convince.
OK, it should be right up here.
This isn't it.
This can't be it.
No, no, no, no.
I've seen the videos
and pictures of this.
I have an entire house packed
of boxes ready to send here.
To this--
this empty fucking lot!
Come on,
what was the plan, Paolo?
What was the plan, seriously?
300 people flying to Italy for
a wedding that doesn't exist.
I packed my entire life up
to send to a house here
that doesn't exist--
my entire fucking life
committed to a man
and a future
that doesn't exist.
Oh, it's like...
it's like I'm in this fog, Kim.
It's like there's this fog.
And I just keep
running through it--
not even through it, to it.
And I'm just--I'm just, like,
completely fucking lost.
Like, I--I'm reaching out,
and I can't--
I can't hold on to anything.
I can't see anything.
I can't even see myself.
Like, am I here?
Do you see me?
- I see you. I see you.
I see you.
And he's got you exactly
where he wants you.
I don't know what I would do
if you weren't here.
The tickets for the wedding
were non-refundable.
Don't say I never brought you
anywhere nice.
He's really good.
He's really, really good
at this whole fucking
lying thing.
Well, he was probably well
practiced before you met him.
When I met him...
Hold on.
When I met him.
I think I have...
the contract that he signed
for the show.
Ah, there it is.
OK, hold on.
Lemon trees.
- Lemon trees.
There it is.
That's the house.
OK, OK, OK.
OK, OK.
OK, so, um, what if there
are security cameras?
I wave and say hello.
Wow, my heart's actually
beating really fast.
OK.
All right.
Oh, God.
Oh, shit.
Oh.
Paolo.
Hola, Paolo.
What are you doing here?
I'm on holiday.
The tickets to the wedding
were non-refundable.
So I thought, what the hell,
why not see Europe?
And also,
I am so sorry about
what happened with the wedding.
I just--I had to come in person
and give you a gift.
That's very nice.
Thank you.
Something I picked up
in a gas station.
Very kind.
Where is your car?
Your car.
Oh, I--it's such
a nice day, I just--
I wanted to take a little walk.
So, uh,
I hope you enjoy your wine.
I'm sure you'll like it.
It's right up your alley.
Go, go, go, go, go, go.
Are you OK?
"An incredible place
to raise a child."
Pull over here.
You.
Do you remember that day,
the day you convinced us?
Lava tubes.
He was so impressed with you.
And do you remember
when he came back,
and he told you
how terrible he felt?
And you said,
"It's all normal.
Nothing to worry about.
Now smile for the cameras."
From the beginning,
we have meant nothing to you.
And now, as I stand here,
forced to end
my husband's life...
once again, here you are.
Now, when you remember this day,
will you feel shame?
Good.
All these data sets
are making my eyes cross.
I can't believe
you do this by choice.
Shh.
I feel like
I'm getting a hunch.
Am I getting a hunch?
- I'm getting a hunch
you'll be kicked out of my lab
if you cannot focus.
Come in.
Ana. Uh...
How can we help you?
You were right about him,
about all of it.
Ande Beyene--he just died.
What the fuck
do you want, Ana?
I want to see it--
his trachea.
I want to see it
with my own eyes.
You've got to be joking.
An autopsy?
I have permission
from Mrs. Beyene.
I need to know the truth--
what this thing
really does to people.
We know what it does.
We have to go now.
He's being cremated
in the morning.
I went down that dead end
with Christopher Lyles.
Hedley won't--
We don't need
Hedley's permission--
not medically, not legally.
You won't get
into that morgue.
Paolo said his name
would open doors.
At least that much was true.
I still have full privileges,
for now.
Are you coming or what?
Hi.
How was your day?
Whoa.
And another cartwheel.
This is where
we stopped the endoscopy,
at the first suture.
He didn't look any further.
Afraid of what he might find.
Oh, Mom, Mom, Mom, look.
Whee!
Have to change
the material...
not working.
the ones
we used on Mr. Beyene.
Whee!
Change the material...
clearly not working.
Yeah, they
we used on Mr. Beyene.
Oh, God.
So definitely, we have
to change the material
because these are
clearly not working.
Yeah, they're all like the
ones we used on Mr. Beyene.