I have been looking for you.
Announce yourselves
and the village lives.
[SCREAMS]
[TAMACTI JUN] The witches have escaped.
A message from Jerlamarel.
It is a message for eyes.
"My dear children,
the river is the first step of
your long journey back to me".
I'm missing something.
Something very important to
me. We have to get it back.
I think I know who
took our things. Look.
There are new whispers about you.
Who whispers? Lady An? Lord Dune?
Her death must involve no struggle.
No evidence of human hand.
I've decided I won't die for this
city. This city will die for me.
[WHISPERING] Jerlamarel,
you did not come for me.
So I am coming to you.
[BIRDS TWEETING]
- Synced and corrected by Firefly -
- www.addic7ed.com -
[BIRD SQUAWKS]
[SOFT METALLIC CHIMING]
[BIRDS TWEETING]
[RIVER RIPPLES]
[BIRDS SCREECHING]
[BABY BURBLING]
[RIVER RIPPLES]
[ROPE BRIDGE CREAKS]
[MAN] Chet-chet!
[BIRDS SQUAWKING]
- [WINGS FLUTTER]
- [HORSE NICKERS]
[MAN CHANTS IN FOREIGN LANGUAGE]
[CROWD] Chet-chet-chet!
[RHYTHMIC CHANTING]
[SNARLS]
[SILENCE]
[RECORD PLAYING, CRACKLING]
[MAN SINGING "PERFECT DAY"]
[SOUND WARBLING]
[SONG CONTINUES, WARBLING OFF-KEY]
[SLOWING, STOPS]
[RAIN POUNDING]
[THUD]
[OBJECTS POUNDING]
[WHISPERS] There you are.
[SIGHS]
Look what happened.
Look what I did. [GASPS]
[EXHALES] Your story is over now.
All of you... I ended it.
But mine is just beginning.
[CREAKING IN DISTANCE]
Goodbye, Father.
I always loved you...
even if you never did me.
[NYRIE] Please, my queen.
[METAL CREAKING]
[GASPING]
[GRUNTING]
God has abandoned us!
[STRUCTURE CREAKING, RATTLING]
We are Payan. We are
holy. We are chosen...
[QUEEN KANE] Come on, boy.
Okay. Good boy.
[RATTLING, CRACKING]
The beast has slept for too long.
And now it is awake.
Everything is ahead of us...
everything that matters.
[PEOPLE SCREAMING]
[PARIS] Ooh.
Ooh.
[STICK TAPPING, SCRAPING]
[SIGHS] Thank you.
What have I done?
You gave me some time alone.
Resisted the urge to push for
answers you know I can't give.
[PARIS SIGHS]
What could be so important
about some trinkets your father gave you
that you would risk your children's
lives, your husband's life...
just to retrieve it?
I'm sure if there were
more to that story
than you've already divulged,
you would've told them
before you would tell me.
I will say, though...
there is a different question...
I have spent the last little while...
unable to silence in my mind.
What question is that?
The day you arrived in our lives...
do you remember the last thing
Jerlamarel said to me as he left?
I don't.
He said, "Be careful".
In that moment, and
in every moment since,
I assumed he meant...
"Be careful with this woman I love,
with the children she's soon to bear".
His words have been like a rock to me...
something solid to hang
on to all these years.
But with all that has changed
since we left the waterfall
and set off up this river...
I wonder if I
misunderstood what he meant.
What else could he have meant?
Now your husband and children,
they have walked unarmed into
grave danger because you said so.
They hardly hesitated.
Nor did you.
I feel something growing in you
since we started
upriver on this journey.
Something in your voice,
in your way, Maghra.
Something formidable.
Something dark.
I am the same person you've
known for almost a lifetime.
I understand your confusion,
and I tolerate your curiosity.
But please do not
suggest that my husband
or my children are in grave danger
because of my sinister motives.
Or that I am indifferent
to their welfare.
Hold my hand.
Pray with me...
that they'll all come
back safe and unharmed.
[HANIWA] These might be tracks here.
[KOFUN] Where?
This is ridiculous.
[WHISTLES]
[CLICKS TONGUE]
What do you hear?
Nothing.
I hear humming.
Yes.
A bunch of people, and they're humming.
Coming from that way.
Humming? Who's humming?
[FOOTSTEPS CONTINUE]
[WIND WHISTLES THROUGH CHIMES]
Humming.
What is this?
Opayol. Scavengers.
There's no one down
there. It looks deserted.
It isn't.
They're about by night,
and they sleep by day.
They're the ones who took our things.
They're most definitely down there.
What I can't say is how many men.
I'm guessing there's a lot more
of them than there are of us.
- Easily.
- We're not turning back.
I'm also guessing they're a
lot less unarmed than we are.
Whatever the significance
of your mother's possessions,
I am certain she would not
want either of you dead over it.
[HANIWA] Me too.
But I can get in and out of there
without them even knowing I was there.
No one's going anywhere alone.
I have to go alone.
I'm least likely to get caught that way.
I can slip in and out.
You said so yourself,
they're probably asleep.
But if you wake one of 'em, the
other ones will come out quickly.
Then I'll avoid them.
Mama knew how difficult
it would be to find this,
and she's asked us anyway.
Are we saying that we don't trust
her to understand what that means?
Are we saying we think she's incapable
of making that kind of decision?
Okay.
You're both right here.
I'll call out if I need help.
But I have to try.
[CREAKING]
This is a... terrible idea.
No, we should've stopped her.
How?
She would've done
this for any one of us.
She would not have been
stopped by any one of us.
Honestly, I don't think this
has anything to do with us.
I think the moment that
Mom mentioned her father,
her connection to him,
Haniwa's decision was made.
You know, there wasn't
even a decision to be made.
It was unavoidable.
The idea of an absent father,
the chance to reconnect,
it was just...
It was too much for her.
[RAGGED BREATH]
[SIGHS]
And I'm just afraid that
there's not gonna be...
[SHRIEKS]
Oh, no.
[BABA VOSS] Haniwa!
Haniwa!
Haniwa. Haniwa.
- Is she still breathing?
- Yeah.
- Where's she hurt?
- I can't see.
- [FOOTSTEPS RUNNING]
- Dad!
[GROWLING]
[GRUNTS]
[GROANS]
Wait. No. Wait. No, no, no, no, no!
[GRUNTS]
- [KICK LANDS]
- [GROANS]
[MEN GROWLING, GRUNTING]
No. Stop. Stop! You
don't know who he is!
I don't care who he is!
[HANIWA] His-His chest.
- [MAN GRUNTS]
- Look. Feel. Feel.
[GRUNTS]
[PANTING]
Get up. Get up.
[GRUNTS]
[RAGGED BREATH] He can see.
[WIND HOWLING]
[JINGLES]
So empty here.
I was born into the
sound of the engines...
thunder, power...
meaning.
I spent my entire life bathed in it.
Never ventured far enough from the
capital that I couldn't hear it.
I always wondered what
the world would sound like
if I'd ventured a little...
further.
Turns out, sounds like nothing at all.
How unbelievably boring.
Listen to the water, my queen.
And the wind.
And perhaps if you listen, it
might whisper its secrets to you.
[SCOFFS]
There are no secrets here.
No information being bargained.
- Hmm.
- No stories being woven.
No strength, no fear.
Nothing.
Is this really how people
go about their lives...
in the absence of
anything of any importance?
I suppose so, Your Majesty.
This journey may require it,
but I don't think I'll be
very good at being that person.
[NYRIE SCOFFS]
I don't believe there's
even the smallest part of me
that is built for it.
I'm hungry.
[WOOD SCRAPING]
[WIND HOWLING]
I'm hungry!
I'm ready to take my dinner.
Did you find eggs? 'Tis the season.
Driver?
I hear the fire dying.
Did you find food?
Driver, where are you?
[INAUDIBLE]
Save the fire. It's
choking on its own smoke.
Driver?
Driver? Fucking answer me.
[THUD]
[STICK RATTLES]
Nyrie!
[FIRE CRACKLING]
[WIND WHOOSHING]
[LOUD CLAP]
[GROANS]
Nyrie.
[SCREAMS] Nyrie!
I have whatever you want.
I have whatever you want. I
have rings. I have God bone.
[WOMAN] So soft.
Exquisite fingers.
No rings.
No God bone.
[WHISPERS] We take you.
Nyrie?
[SHRIEKS] Nyrie!
Mama, it's us.
Haniwa.
Come.
[MAGHRA SIGHS]
Did you find it?
[SIGHS] Thank you.
I count four.
Who is our new friend?
They call him Boots.
[PARIS] Raccoon hides.
This is the creature
who took our things.
Yes.
But he didn't know who we were,
and he didn't have a choice.
Let me explain, please.
All right.
When Jerlamarel left us,
left us to go to the House of
Enlightenment as he promised...
it seems he didn't go there directly.
He made a stop for the winter.
He approached the Opayol.
He lived among them for a year.
A year?
But... once his child was born...
he resumed his journey.
Boots is that child.
Boots is Jerlamarel's son.
Our brother.
After Jerlamarel
continued his journey...
the Opayol treated Boots like a slave.
Forced him to scavenge
and steal for them.
Once word came that the Witchfinder was
campaigning through this area,
the Opayol left to
seek safety elsewhere.
And they abandoned him
here to fend for himself.
Child! Child!
Are you suggesting we
bring him along with us?
[HANIWA] Yes.
Aside from offering him a way out
of being treated like an animal...
aside from him being an asset
to us, a skilled fighter...
He can see.
Can't he?
Yes, he can see.
You... You two, you are in agreement?
Why is everyone being like this?
He is family. We're
not leaving him behind.
I've asked all the
same questions you have.
I have expressed the same concerns.
And?
And if I was gonna forbid
this from happening, Paris,
I imagine you would have
heard me do it by now.
Don't you?
What else do you know about him?
Aside from his skill as a thief.
Do you trust him?
I have never had anyone to look after me
as you do for each other.
To be a part of that,
I will do whatever it is you ask of me.
Then let him come.
Let us begin to build for
ourselves an army of the sighted...
[HANIWA EXHALES]
so long as its newest recruits are
willing to swear their allegiance
to the only general we have amongst us.
I swear it.
No. Show us.
[CLICKING TONGUE]
[QUEEN KANE] Such a perfect day.
[HORSE SNORTING]
Your total silence I find far more
interesting than her total silence.
You know, I will be there
when they slit your throats,
reminding you what a fucking
mistake you made today.
[FIRE CRACKLING]
[BABA VOSS] Too many times
separating from you...
and worrying it'll be our last.
Let's never do it again.
[FIRE CRACKLES]
I never told you much about him...
about my father.
I never asked you to.
It's never mattered to
me where you come from.
I know. Nor I you.
He gave this to me the day he died.
Been in his family for as
long as he could remember.
Open it.
All of that for this.
Must've loved him very much.
He was a very good man.
Kind, wise.
I think he would've liked you.
Let's not get carried away.
I wish I'd known him.
Perhaps you can tell me
more about him sometime.
I think I'd like that.
Kofun is right.
I should get moving.
Of course.
That boy, Boots...
you don't trust him, do you?
I haven't planned on trusting
anyone new for a while.
I see.
Then why did you choose to allow it?
I'm flattered you thought I
have any choice in the matter.
I'm being serious.
- I know.
- Why didn't you forbid it?
'Cause at the end of this journey...
they will meet a new father.
And I can't give them any
new reason to want one.
Kofun understands our choices.
He always has.
Doesn't take them personally.
But her...
I don't wanna lose her.
You won't.
Yes.
[SIGHS]
[TAPPING STICK]
[BABA VOSS] Love you.
[BIRD TRILLS]
They don't like me, do they?
They're scared...
and confused.
But they're good people.
They'll come around.
Do they like you?
What did you say?
They yell at you.
They question you, make you feel small.
That is how my people always treated me.
Why did they make you wear the mask?
They said I was not like them.
Not a man, but something else.
They said the mask would remind me.
My family loves me.
They don't always understand.
But I have never doubted for
one moment that they love me.
How you've been treated, it was wrong.
You deserve better than that.
But I promise...
you're one of us now.
You'll never be treated that way again.
Y-Your mother.
Do you think she will have
room to love another child
as she already loves
you and your brother?
That may take some time.
This is complicated for her.
But...
my mother has the biggest
heart of anyone I've ever met.
She does what's right.
She always does what's right.
[BIRD CALLS]
[KOFUN GROANS]
[GRUNTS]
- Why did you keep your secret for so long?
- How do you do that?
Do what?
Sneak up on people who can
see you sneaking up on people.
I wasn't trying to be sneaky.
Maybe you just weren't paying attention.
Will you answer my question?
What are you talking about?
What secret?
You kept it for so long, you don't
even know it's a secret anymore.
Why did no one in the Alkenny know...
that you could see?
Well, given how everyone else reacted
when the Witchfinder turned up,
I think my parents were probably wise
to not trust them with
that piece of information.
Hmm.
Baba and Maghra were
stuck in the Alkenny.
And I guess they kept a
secret to protect you two.
Something like that, yes.
Can I tell you what it's
like to observe people
that don't know that
you're observing them?
They are completely vulnerable to you.
You could keep their secrets.
You could spread them to their enemies.
You could strike at them...
without them ever knowing who did it,
or how, or why.
You could change their life.
Could end their life...
for any reason...
or no reason at all.
That is what gods do.
You might not know what this feels like
because you never made the choice
to hold that power over others.
It was made for you by your parents.
But I know.
And I suspect Jerlamarel knew, too.
For me, it brought me
closer to those I shadowed.
For Jerlamarel...
he fathered a child among
them and abandoned him.
So, what does any of this
have to do with you, anyway?
Maybe I find it amusing that you
can see and still observe so little.
[WIND BLOWING]
Where am I?
The City of Worms.
[QUEEN KANE SHRIEKS] Where am I?
[WIND HOWLS]
[HORSE WHINNIES]
[QUEEN KANE GRUNTS]
Ah, my friends.
What have you brought me?
I have a horse. It needs water.
And I'm tired. I need to sleep.
I've ridden all day.
I need oil for my ass
and a maid to apply it.
After I've slept, I will speak to you.
You've made a mistake... [GRUNTS]
[SNIFFS] Mmm.
Exquisite fingers.
You have done well. Thank you
for this. She will be... perfect.
A silkworm is a fascinating creature.
Would you like to know why?
[CHUCKLES]
She begins so small,
so innocent, unassuming.
But in the course of
her very short life,
she creates a substance of
such beauty, such perfection,
that the wealthiest men in the world,
men who could dress themselves,
their wives, their concubines,
in whatever they desire,
choose... this.
And when her life has run its
course, her usefulness expired,
she spends her final
days sadly grotesque.
A winged creature with the urge to fly
but denied that ability.
A husk of herself, used up,
eager for death.
You will come to know her well here.
You will come to understand her.
My friend, you do not want me in here.
I haven't met a worm in my life.
Yeah. Perhaps for a
time, it'll amuse you.
[SHRIEKS] But soon you will regret it!
[SHOUTS]
[SHRIEKS]
[GROANS]
Is that so?
I wonder who you might
be to make such a claim.
Delicate hands unused to being worked.
An impudent mouth
unused to being struck.
A woman of wealth...
accustomed to wielding authority
or the authority of a husband, perhaps.
But from... where?
[GRUNTS]
The Witchfinder's campaign brought
him through here not long ago.
- [GRUNTS]
- When he was asking for information,
his accent reminded me of
the time I spent in Kanzua,
selling our goods to the
high-born with money to burn.
Your accent brings back
those same memories.
You were a noblewoman, I presume.
Perhaps even a councilor
to that bitch queen.
[GASPS]
But no matter.
Here you will be the same as the
rest, or even less so, perhaps,
as everything must be
learned from the beginning.
[QUEEN KANE GASPS]
If you work hard for
me, you will live well.
If you try to escape,
you will not get far,
and the consequences will be...
unpleasant.
[QUEEN KANE GASPING, PANTING]
You are an interesting one.
I look forward to whatever time
we are able to spend together here.
[RAGGED BREATHING]
[WHISPERS] Hear me...
Jerlamarel.
Kofun?
[KOFUN] Yeah. Here, Dad.
Is the boat free?
It's unmoored, but it's stuck.
What do you mean "stuck"? Stuck where?
Tide's gone out.
[KOFUN] What are we gonna do?
[GROANS]
We're gonna have to wait till morning.
[SIGHS]
[SNIFFS]
[EXHALES]
[HORSE WHINNIES]
[WHINNIES, BLUSTERS]
[RAGGED BREATH]
Come.
[WHISPERS] Run.
[KOFUN WHISPERS] Come.
[BABA VOSS] Run.
- [HORSE WHINNIES]
- [DOGS BARKING]
[DOGS BARKING]
[GASPING]
[DOGS BARKING IN DISTANCE]
[SNAPPING]
[GASPING]
[MAGHRA GASPS]
They can't ride through this, can they?
[BABA VOSS] They can.
But it'll slow them down.
[WHISPERS] I hear them.
- Haniwa.
- Yes.
Take your mother and Paris
and find shelter for them.
[KISSES] I love you. Go. Go.
They're everywhere.
[DOGS BARKING]
Dad, I'll-I'll stand with you.
Yes, you will, son.
[BARKING CONTINUES]
- [WHISPERS] Stay here.
- [PARIS GRUNTS]
Everything will be all right.
[DOGS BARKING]
[METAL CLANKING]
[GRAPPLING HOOK WHIRS]
[TWIGS SNAPPING]
[GRUNTS]
[WHIRRING]
- [BLADE SLICES]
- [GRUNTS]
[EXHALES]
[GRUNTS]
Ooh.
Maghra?
[GRUNTS]
[PARIS] Baba Voss!
[SIGHS]
Where's Mama? What happened?
- She's gone.
- [BABA VOSS] Haniwa!
- [PARIS] Haniwa.
- [BABA VOSS] No.
Baba, I had her by the hand.
They took her?
No, she let go of my hand.
She whispered to me.
She said, "Be careful".
Mama?
Mama!
Tamacti Jun!
Do you hear my voice, Witchfinder?
Do you hear me?
[MAGHRA] Speak.
Witchfinder...
can you hear me?
I hear the voice of a dead woman.
Then listen closer.
Take my hand.
And speak.
Hail...
Princess Maghra...
of the House... of Kane.
[TAMACTI JUN] Give homage!