You want to trade the cache, my cache?
It was the only way
we could avoid a fight
we were more than likely to lose.
- Mr. Scott?
- He told me that he feared
for the safety of his
wife and his daughter.
- Are they still alive?
- Yes, they are.
They revolted. A man
named Julius started it.
Now he's forming an army out there
with designs on taking Nassau.
The damage done to this
alliance was caused by Billy.
It may be that the only
way to repair this damage
is to remove that which caused it.
Stop!
What the hell have you done?
If the British empire will not aid
us in fighting our present enemy,
perhaps a different empire will.
Once you land, I envision no confusion.
I'd simply ask that you
burn it all to the ground.
Synced and corrected by Aaronnmb
www.addic7ed.com
When your people took this place,
it was they who suffered
the consequences.
Reprisals visited upon their mothers,
brothers, children.
Tortured on the other farms
as a result of your actions.
I understand.
Which is why I've come
here to make that right.
If you had suffered such loss,
is there anything you can imagine
making it right?
No. I can't.
But I imagine getting my hands
on the man responsible for it...
would be a start.
He completed the raid when
my friends tried to stop it.
He chained those he felt
most likely to revolt
over the offense.
Though, I imagine they know this.
With what conditions?
Two of them.
They respect you, so
they'll listen to you.
I'd ask your help in
mending this alliance,
both with the men and women here
and those elsewhere on the island.
I understand there's now a
band of armed slaves out there.
I need to know you can
broker a peace with them, too.
And the other condition?
That he's alive at the
end of whatever happens.
You trust him?
Flint.
You've cast your lot with him.
What does it matter to you?
Before this war began, before
everyone's roles changed,
your father mistrusted Flint
as much as anyone in Nassau did.
I assume you were in some
contact with him all that time.
I'm surprised that his
feelings didn't influence you.
You were my sister.
There is very little that I remember
from when I was young,
but I remember this.
You were older.
You were beautiful.
I revered you.
When you were told that
my mother and I were dead,
I have to believe that it affected you.
You had just lost your mother.
But if things were as I remember,
my mother and I were your family, too.
And yet, through all
the years thereafter
that my father cared for you...
counseled you, labored for you...
he never told you that we were alive.
It would have been so easy
to lessen your suffering
by divulging the secret.
And yet, he never did.
Have you yet asked yourself why that is?
My father didn't mistrust Flint.
My father mistrusted all of you.
Lieutenant.
The cache isn't here, so I am leaving.
And as my collateral to ensure
that this deal is consummated,
he'll be coming with me to the fort.
"This deal"?
As in the one in which you
walk away with all my money?
It seems the only means I have
of registering any
meaningful disapproval
of this deal at this point
is to kill one or the both of you.
- How many?
- 12 total.
Eight ships of force.
They'll be in range
in an hour, maybe less.
Grab the ledgers and
whatever coin is on hand.
Where are we going?
You're going to inform Mr.
Silver what's happening.
We're getting onto the Walrus
and we're getting it and us out of here.
If we're still here when
they make their landing,
none of us will survive the day.
You would surrender our
position to the Spanish Navy?
You were prepared to
surrender this position
to Long John Silver
just a few hours ago.
And in this case, our lives
may very well depend upon it.
Spanish forces, sir,
will offer no quarter.
We have no choice but
to defend ourselves!
Quiet, please.
What is it, Lieutenant?
The lead ship that approaches,
she's just posted a signal to us.
It was Governor Rogers' signal
ordering us to stand down.
His signal?
Could it have been stolen?
It's from our most recent signal book.
Then I think our response is obvious.
We will follow his orders.
Obviously, he has
enlisted Spanish assistance
in forcing the pirates out of Nassau.
If we stand down, the
invasion proceeds around us
and we will remain safe here.
And what about Eleanor?
What about her?
She is out there.
Someone must retrieve her
before those troops arrive.
Before we could retrieve her and return,
that invasion would be fully unleashed.
It would be suicide for
anyone to attempt it.
Where are you going?
_
He's in the field with the sign.
I did not want this.
Flint is my friend,
but I know what he is.
I have no illusions about it.
But for all the dangers he presents,
for all his offenses...
the one thing he's never done is
force me to choose between him and you.
That, you did.
But it isn't too late to
find a way to remedy it.
You made a terrible mistake
and you paid a terrible price.
But we're at war...
and you're an asset.
Despite what's gone on,
you are my friend.
And the men out there have
had their pound of flesh.
And our men...
Billy, I could walk out there
and tell them the sky is red...
and they'd believe me.
That's the power you've given me.
But I have to know this is over...
your vendetta against Flint,
your need to see him dead
or departed from our story.
I have to know you'll never put
me to a choice between you again.
Swear it...
and this all ends.
You chose.
Live with it.
They're here.
He speaks for them?
They call him Julius.
- Help me out.
- Won't do it by itself.
Over there.
Pretty sight for you.
I came to find Eleanor.
"I betrayed you, Jack.
"Tried to trade your life
for my own personal gain.
"Lied to Anne to her face about it.
"Please, Jack. Beg of you.
"Is there any way you can forgive me?"
That was the general sense I had
of what I might hear
come from your mouth
were I ever this close to you again.
Spain is here.
A fleet of a dozen ships has
already opened fire on Nassau town.
By now, well over a thousand soldiers
will have likely made their
landing and begun their invasion.
In a matter of hours,
there will be no safe place
to stand on this island,
made all the more dangerous by the fact
that the harbor has been
rendered defenseless.
There will be no resistance
to their landing since...
Since Woodes Rogers was
the one who invited them in.
How did you know that?
Captain! Sails!
The Walrus.
They escaped the harbor
ahead of their landing.
Change of plan! Back to the ship.
Spanish invasion. You're
welcome to stay if you like.
You coming?
I won't ask again.
Keeping an eye on us?
Making sure you don't slit my
throat out of spite, perhaps.
I suppose I chose the right hostage
if they're that concerned
about keeping you alive.
I suppose so.
You know, there was a time...
not so long ago, when
you shared their concern.
When you saw what I saw.
The benefits of being
free of British rule.
To make the new world something more
than just an extension of the old.
Is it so unthinkable
that that might be again?
You were a pirate once.
Stranger things have happened.
We need to get to cover.
Quickly.
Where?
The governor's forces have
been driven out of Nassau.
In a few hours, the last
remaining members of his regime
will be surrendering the fort,
leaving the island
completely under our control.
It is a new day.
But one that demands we all
unite behind a common cause.
What cause is that?
To free the new world.
And we will be your partners...
in the fight to free it?
Yes.
For how long?
How long?
I'm told you removed
the one who governed
the pirates before you.
Sacrificed him in the hopes that
it would remake this alliance...
Know that man was a friend of mine...
before you question the sacrifice.
Amongst pirates,
loyalty changes quickly, it seems.
If a man can be replaced so easily,
how can I know that his
promises won't be, too?
Spain? Here?
12 ships, likely in
excess of a thousand men.
There won't be much time
before we're overrun.
Mr. Featherstone awaits on
the Walrus off the south coast
if we wish to retreat.
If?
A thousand Spanish fighters
are more than three times
our number could withstand.
What can we do but retreat?
We're not leaving.
If it's Madi that concerns you,
we could send someone out to find her.
We wouldn't be leaving her behind.
Madi and Flint will either
find their way back here
or they'll find a place to hide.
But even if they were
here, we cannot retreat.
Not with our numbers.
The Spanish would run us down.
We'd end up facing them
disorganized out there
rather than entrenched here.
So, what do we do?
If we fight them together,
there's a good chance we live,
hold our ground, maybe
even fight them off.
Separate, and we all die.
Retrieve your men,
bring them here,
and make this the last
battle to win the island.
_
No, no, no, no, no.
Where is she?
She left with an escort hours ago
to make the exchange.
You let her leave?
Your men need to know my
wife is not to be harmed.
_
English, God damn it!
Even if that order could be given,
no one would heed it.
They've been let loose.
I opened the gates for you.
Handed you this victory.
Yes, you did.
But what has begun here,
there is no altering it now.
Jesus Christ.
I sent a rider to the
Underhill estate to warn them.
Told them we'd be here to
get them off the island.
But there's a credible
argument to be made
that we ought to leave right away,
while we still can.
Hello, boys.
No. We wait here.
We wait here for whomever,
if anyone, survives the day.
If you have men you can spare,
I can use them on the Walrus.
That's high enough!
If there is nothing left to be
done, I would like to see her.
I loved you.
And I betrayed you.
But I cannot apologize for it.
I did what anyone would have done
when confronted with the
same impossible choices.
If I apologize, you
will know it is a lie.
And I do not wish to
lie to you ever again.
Leave.
No.
I am going to stay with you.
I want to take care of you.
Get the fuck out.
Doesn't make sense.
Spain has been quiet for months.
Why is this happening now?
The governor sailed from here days ago,
frustrated in his attempts
to retake the island.
Apparently, he found
someone willing to aid him.
That's not what happened.
The harbor is still obstructed.
How else would they manage
to enter it so cleanly
unless he was in league with them?
That is not what happened.
Well, whatever the cause, they're here.
We need to prepare a
defensive position here.
We need to send out scouts to
determine the size of their force.
And we need all the hands we can muster.
Already?
They must've tracked us here.
Get inside the house, the both of you.
You saw them?
I think so. Beyond the trees.
Wait.
Now.
Move! Move!
If they report our position,
we'll face 50 more of them.
Stay. Watch the house.
It did affect me.
When Mr. Scott...
when your father told me that
you and your mother had died...
it affected me a great deal.
It must have been hard...
to live hidden away for so long.
It was hard to be away from him.
The rest of it...
my mother did the best she
could with the rest of it.
She must have done well.
I've found myself thinking about it.
Of walking away from Nassau,
from England, from civilization.
One can be happy that way, can't they?
A life of isolation and uncertainty
as long as it is lived
with someone you love...
And who loves you back.
It is possible, isn't it?
It is.
- You've seen them?
- They're right around the bend.
80, maybe 100 headed this way.
If we're lucky and
it's on the lighter end,
we might actually be
able to hold them off.
"If we're lucky" is not a notion
that's worked well for us recently.
You have men positioned by
the south and west gates?
As many as we could
afford, which isn't many.
What's happening out there?
I don't know what chance you'll have.
Their soldiers are likely everywhere.
If you're going to be found by them,
it shouldn't be tied up like an animal.
You cannot stay here.
Good luck.
Need more men, Castro. Let's go!
Reload!
What is it?
Can you hear that?
- Come on, let's help them out.
- I'm out!
How many men are watching the
south end of the cane fields?
I think four.
They're coming!
- Get off the wall!
Horses behind us!
Take positions and go!
The back! Get the back!
Yah! Run for the...
Watch your flank!
Retreat!
Run! Run!
Madi!
Madi.
Don't waste the shot!
Watch out! Watch out!
Keep it down. Move ahead.
Aim at the horses!
Torches!
Aim for the torches!
- Aim for the torches.
- Take him down!
Open the doors!
Hey.
Was he...
Is he with them, my husband?
No.
No, he isn't.
I tried to save her.
Madi.
Let's move him before
he starts stinking.
How many?
A hundred, give or take.
Roughly half withdrew,
but I imagine it was not
without intent to return,
and with greater numbers.
Where's Madi?
We've got about 30 able-bodied
men left, plus Julius's men.
We should be able to
defend the main gate
and have men to spare to prevent
another move through the cane.
- We can't.
- Can't? We just drove them off once.
And it cost you half your number.
Spanish regulars will not allow
themselves to be defeated by us.
And when they return...
with three times as many reinforcements,
what do you imagine will follow there?
We know they're coming
now. We'll be ready.
It's over.
Gather whatever supplies you can.
Anyone who can't make it to
the beach, I want them carried.
I'll not leave anyone behind.
We've done most of what we can
and still be able to depart quickly,
which we may have to do sooner or later
with or without survivors.
We have to assume the Spanish have
men all across the island by now.
Every hour we sit here is an hour
closer to being sighted by them...
if we haven't been sighted already.
She saw Anne?
We'll give them another
hour, then we'll set sail.
Seems a fair amount of
resentment towards you these days.
I just want you to know...
that I remember what you did for me.
Standing up to Captain Berringer.
Jack can be angry. Anne can be angry.
But...
but I remember the
good you've done, too.
It wasn't supposed to end like this.
How can we all have sacrificed so much
and none of us has
anything to show for it?
Captain! Movement on the shoreline!
I can't see anything.
- Get those launches away.
- Aye.
- Is Flint among them?
- I think so.
By the dunes.
Jesus, it looks like
they've been through hell.
It will take some time
before we fully know
all we have lost today.
So, we are leaving?
We, uh, follow Flint south...
to the camp.
We'll regroup,
we'll refit, we'll...
A war against civilization?
What?
Civilization has been winning
that war for 10,000 years
against men richer, braver,
stronger, and smarter than you.
How can you be so blind not to see that?
What the fuck are you talking about?
You mustered a force stronger
than you had any right to hope for.
You hit the governor when
he was at his weakest.
And at what result?
Eleanor is dead, Anne is nearly dead,
and the governor is sitting in
Nassau in my fucking chair victorious!
You cannot fight civilization
from the outside in.
And your plan now is to follow
that man into more of the same?!
"What result?"
That result was because
of your goddamn betrayal!
Just now, that man and
several others wondered aloud
whether the smartest thing to do
wouldn't be killing you
and throwing you in the sea
rather than giving you
another opportunity to fuck us!
For reasons I can't begin to
fathom, I argued against it.
Bark at me again about braver,
stronger, and smarter men,
and I might decide to revisit the issue!
If killing me seems like
the smartest thing to do,
then it is obvious to me
none of you have any idea
how to defeat Woodes Rogers.
- And you do?!
- You're goddamn right, I do!
Eleanor is dead,
Anne is nearly dead,
and I want him to pay
for all of it dearly.
Do you want to help me or not?
When Flint heads south,
we head north.
What's north?
Eleanor Guthrie's grandfather.
We'll be arriving soon.
Still no sign of Rackham?
No.
Do you really think they just...
Abandoned us?
Yes.
I'm sorry.
I need you to know...
that I did everything I could
to keep her safe.
I...
I don't expect that to mean anything.
It wasn't...
your fault.
It wasn't your fault.
They had already begun to arrive
when Kofi came with your
request for the cache.
You can understand why
I didn't let him go.
They came from other islands,
the colonies,
maroons from camps like this one,
pirates from as far
away as Massachusetts.
They heard that Nassau had fallen...
and they came to join us.
The revolution you promised...
has begun!
Synced and corrected by Aaronnmb
www.addic7ed.com