So, let us assume that
the measuring of you
and your proposal are done...
and that we are partners...
in a venture to acquire
and reform Nassau.
Jack went to hunt Captain Flint.
Chances are good you've
seen the last of him.
When Anne was recruiting
spies in Port Royal,
she met a man with an
estate in the wilderness.
This man found it profitable to
offer his services to wealthy families
with a need to make troublesome
family members disappear.
What families?
Flint doesn't need to get far.
All he needs is to bury that gold
somewhere unknown and he's won.
Accept the treaty and John Silver lives.
This war, it will not be
bargained away to avoid a fight.
Even if you could kill me,
how are you going to explain it to her?
She believes in this.
If it costs a war to save her,
you'll have lost her anyway.
Even you cannot construct a story
to make her forgive you that.
Is this war more
important than her life?
Answer the question.
I wanna hear you say it.
What's to be done
with the unwanted ones?
The men who do not fit,
whom civilization must
prune from the vine
to protect its sense of itself.
Every culture since earliest
antiquity has survived this way,
defining itself by
the things it excludes.
So long as there is progress,
there will always be
human debris in its wake,
on the outside looking in.
And sooner or later,
one must answer the question...
what becomes of them?
In London,
the solution is to call them criminals.
To throw them in a deep, dark hole
and hope it never runs over.
I would argue that justice
demands we do better than that.
That a civilization is
judged not by who it excludes,
but by how it treats the excluded.
That is not what I asked.
Many of the men incarcerated
here have enemies, sir.
Such is the nature of being
anathema to the empire.
And the only way I can protect them
is to ensure that once they
walk through these gates,
their anonymity is protected, too.
Here, they must cease to
be... to be able to find peace.
I already said I'm not an enemy
of his, nor is the man who sent me.
Yes, and I believe you when
you say it. But still...
Do you know where I come from, sir?
- No, I don't.
- I come from Nassau.
My name is Tom Morgan.
I come on behalf of Long John Silver.
Have you heard of him?
Yes, of course.
Good.
Then I ask you again
and for the last time,
is the prisoner we
are looking for here...
or isn't he?
Synced and corrected by Aaronnmb
www.addic7ed.com
Come on!
Ready, set.
Come up.
Quick! Get to cover!
Get on the beach!
When we make our landing, pass
word to the men I need Flint alive.
If he departed with the money, he's
the one who knows its whereabouts.
What of the others, my Lord?
There are no others.
No quarter, Mr. Utley.
Come on, run! Go!
Get to cover!
Give me your hand!
- Ready to starboard!
- Starboard!
Bring her about!
Back to the ship!
Jesus.
Yeah.
Make ready to take on survivors.
An hour ago,
we were upon a fool's errand
to capture Captain Flint
and find an island
that does not exist...
you're welcome for that, by the way...
evade a ship full of redcoats,
fight through a ship full of pirates,
and somehow get past Long John Silver.
I don't know if you've noticed,
but this is considerably better luck
than you and I have experienced lately.
And yet somehow, I get the sense
you and I are possessed
of different instincts
as to how to react to this.
How would you like to react to it?
Throw him in a sack,
sail away from here,
let the Guthrie woman and her
lawyers deal with the governor,
and be alive come tomorrow.
He's headed for open water.
I noticed.
He has everything he came for?
We were at the camp.
They told me you brought the
cache to ransom for her life.
It's in the ground.
Ashore.
I'm the only one who knows where.
It comes out when Madi is safe,
when the governor is dead or captured,
and when we are ready to
return together to the camp
to resume the war to which
we all committed ourselves.
Then and only then.
Can you live with that?
She runs or she wants
room to fight this out?
You've met the man. What do you think?
He'll never stop until we're
all hanging in his square.
Unless we defeat him today, together.
Get us underway and ready the guns.
- Make ready the guns!
- We should speak.
The three of us.
Woodes Rogers isn't
going to receive a letter
from anyone's lawyer
informing him I've beaten him.
I'm going to tell him so.
- Jack...
- I want my money back.
If it takes rescuing the girl
to get Flint to dig it up,
then, Augustus, you and I are
in the rescuing business today.
Get us after that ship.
Well, here I am. What
exactly is on the agenda?
Where did you go?
You were to follow us to the camp.
Your ship disappears...
and then you arrive here as
though none of it happened.
Before we discuss anything else,
I wanna know where you went.
I went to Philadelphia...
to see Joseph Guthrie.
You went to see Joseph Guthrie?
I presented him with a
plan to join our cause.
Every rebellion can use a wealthy
convert or two early in the game.
What did he say?
He politely passed.
Anne remained to be
tended to in the city.
Max with her.
Now that we're all caught up,
might we agree there are
more pressing issues at hand?
Namely, what we intend to do from here.
I intend to assume command here,
pursue the governor, and
capture his ship whole.
Is that so?
We'll need to take her without
the use of our great guns.
It will be technically
beyond your capacities.
Without the guns? Why would you...
It would put Madi's
life at greater risk.
Securing her alive is
all that matters today.
Return her, him,
and the cache back to the camp intact
along with the governor
defeated and in chains.
And news of it will travel far and wide.
The war will be fully,
undeniably, and maybe
unstoppably underway.
Victory here today changes everything
for everyone forever.
And it is most likely to
happen under my direction.
Do you have anything to say about this?
He's right.
And you know it.
You people.
We need to watch him.
The governor is the danger ahead of us.
But if he has a chance
to put knives in our backs
for the money, he'll do it.
You don't think I know that?
What the hell is this?
You cannot honestly
believe that placating me
is going to repair
what's been broken here.
I absolutely think
that it is repairable.
And no one is placating anyone.
Then what exactly is it
you think you're doing here?
I know what it's like...
to have lost her.
And then seeing a way to have her back.
I understand what
that must've felt like.
You asked me once what I would do,
what I would sacrifice
if it meant having Thomas back again.
I honestly don't know...
what I would've done.
I honestly couldn't say I
wouldn't have done what you did.
I told you I'd see you through this.
Put things back together again
so that we can move forward.
I meant it.
Please know...
I was so conflicted about
all this when it began.
I knew it would be
difficult to separate them...
Flint and Silver.
They'd grown so close, it was
hard to know where one ended
and the other began.
I worried that the act of separating
them might destroy them both...
when what I wanted was to remove Flint.
And I saw no other way.
But the things I've done
in the pursuit of it...
were intended to honor my oath.
But somehow, here I am now.
What I've just done...
there's no coming back from that.
There is no difference
between Flint and Silver now.
Or between Flint and any of them.
They are all enemies of mine.
Now, I believe they
are outmatched today.
I believe at the end of the day,
there will be no more
of them left alive.
But if somehow...
they are able to prevail
today against us...
fight their way through
the British soldiers above,
through the governor, through me...
I will ensure that at the end of it all,
when they walk through this final door,
there is defeat awaiting them.
You think killing me
means defeat for them?
You will have given them
a martyr to unite them.
Still no sign of her.
Thought he'd try to block us in ahead.
He's out there.
Maybe there, ready to loose his
guns once we clear the mouth.
We should veer to starboard
as far as is possible
and be prepared to take fire when we do.
The captain suggests Eurydice
is likely lying in wait
beyond that headland.
We should take measures
to prepare for it.
In the meantime,
why don't you tell me what the
fuck you're actually doing here?
You presented a plan
to the Guthrie family
to bolster piracy in Nassau...
with Max at your side?
I sincerely doubt you'd
go along with any plan
that promised support for the account.
And from there,
my questions only multiply.
Which is probably not a
state you want to leave me in.
A state of multiplying questions.
I suppose that makes two of us.
Because there is something in the air
between you and your friend up there.
It's just tension between
steadfast partners.
Or it's something else.
We could suffer under the weight
of our respective questions.
Or would you like to
start trading answers?
Helm!
Hard to starboard!
Put the wind on the port quarter.
Mr. Featherstone, set the foresail,
Trim as we alter course.
What's happening?
We're gonna get hit.
My Lord, shall we withdraw
in favor of a wider approach?
No.
I beg your pardon, sir,
but there are easier ways
to attempt to board her.
I do not wish to board her.
I wish to cause confusion
and terror amongst her men.
I wish to shatter their spirits.
I wish to break them.
And then I wish to board her.
Keep her main mast aligned over the bow.
Bow guns we fire at will.
- Fire!
- Take cover!
Helm, prepare to come
hard over to starboard.
hard over to starboard!
Now!
Brace for impact!
Target the rail!
Come on, men, fire at will!
Take cover!
Stay down!
Ready the rest of the men.
And lead them over the
stern. Board them at the helm.
The helm?
Just get them ready.
When you're on-board, get
below decks and find Madi.
Where are you going?
To turn us around.
Musket!
You.
Join the muskets on the foremast.
Musket. Reload!
Target on the quarterdeck!
- We broken away!
- Yeah!
Hooks at the ready!
You load that now.
Come on, men!
Come on!
What are you doing down here?
Are you a fucking coward?
P-please, sir.
I'm just the cook.
You had a prisoner here.
Is she still alive?
Is she still alive?!
Don't worry.
No one's going under the ship today.
Though, the thought had crossed my mind.
No, I'm quite certain I
can do better than that.
I'll need cutting away completely.
Time is of the essence
for what happens next.
Take the better part of a day,
maybe two, to secure the chest.
Captain Rackham will ferry you
back to the camp aboard the Lion
to relay the news.
I'd like to stay, actually.
To help see the chest secured properly.
Mr. Featherstone can see
her back aboard the Eurydice.
Provided the majority of men
crewing the Lion are ours, not yours,
and you remain on the ship
while we retrieve the chest.
Yes?
Let's go.
We'll rest up here.
I can keep going.
We'll rest here.
You really are getting
nimble on that thing.
Pain is an exceptional tutor.
Hmm.
We won't be going any farther.
Won't we?
I won't take another
step towards that chest
until I know for certain that I'm wrong
about what I suspect is happening here.
I don't know what you're talking about.
Please don't do that.
And what is it you think is happening?
I show you the chest,
the chest is brought
out of the ground...
and then...
I don't know what then exactly,
but I doubt it involves returning
it to the camp as planned.
Am I wrong?
Tell me I am and we'll
continue on our way.
And then what?
This war...
your war...
her war...
Julius will be no obstacle to it.
As long as you and she stand for it...
as long as the treasure powers it...
nothing can stop it from beginning now.
Nothing but you.
Why would you want to do that?
This is what it would be.
Time after time after time.
Endlessly.
The measuring of lives...
and loves and spirits...
so that they may be
wagered in a grand game.
How much ransom can be
afforded for the cause?
How many casualties can
be tolerated for the cause?
How much loss?
That isn't a war.
That is a fucking nightmare.
And I cannot take a single step
towards leaving this forest...
till I know it's over.
This is how they survive.
You must know this.
You're too smart not to know this.
They paint the world full of shadows...
and then tell their children
to stay close to the light.
Their light.
Their reasons, their judgments.
Because in the darkness,
there be dragons.
But it isn't true.
We can prove that it isn't true.
In the dark, there is discovery,
there is possibility,
there is freedom in the dark
once someone has illuminated it.
And who has been so close to
doing it as we are right now?
This isn't about England...
or her king...
or our freedom, or any of it.
When I thought Madi was gone,
I saw... for the first time,
I saw the world through your eyes.
A world in which there
is nothing left to lose.
I felt the need to make
sense of the loss...
to impart meaning to it...
whatever the cost.
To exalt her memory with battles...
and victories.
But beneath all of that,
I recognized the other thing...
hiding in the spaces.
The one whose shape you first showed me.
And when asked,
it was honest about the
role it wanted to play.
It was rage.
And it just wanted
to see the world burn.
I see a life for myself with her.
And I will not live it
wondering if tomorrow
is the day your nightmare
finally takes her away for good.
So, what next, then?
What decisions have you made
about what our tomorrows will be?
I made arrangements...
to ensure that when we leave here,
it is with compromises in place
that will diffuse any threat
of widespread rebellion.
All this will be for nothing.
We will have been for nothing.
Defined by their histories...
distorted to fit into their narrative...
until all that is left of us...
are the monsters in the stories
they tell their children.
I don't care.
You will.
Someday, you will.
Someday.
Even if you can persuade
her to keep you...
she'll no longer be enough.
And the comfort will grow stale.
And casting about in the dark
for some proof that you mattered
and finding none, you'll know...
that you gave it away...
in this moment...
on this island.
Left it in the ground...
along with that chest.
This is not what I wanted.
But I will stand here with you...
for an hour,
a day, a year...
while you find a way to
accept this outcome...
so that we might leave here together.
For if not...
then I must end this another way.
Captain Flint is gone.
Gone?
Gone where?
Retired from the account.
He was persuaded that his
efforts were no longer viable,
that those closest to him
had grown tired of them.
And of him.
He then chose to walk away from it all.
He's no longer a concern of ours.
This sounds somewhat less definitive
an end than I had expected.
But far more effective.
For if our intent was
to extinguish his war,
feeding it a martyr
seems like an odd way of going about it.
Flint had allies
who would've only been
emboldened by his death.
Some of whom, had they the desire,
could and would have
fought his war without him
to honor his memory.
Instead of a martyr,
we have fed it a story,
a tragedy that diffused
their fighting spirit,
and enabled the more
moderate voices among them
to press for a more moderate solution.
What is that?
A treaty.
Its terms conceived by Governor Rogers.
Its terms agreed to by
the Maroon leaders...
over a few scattered objections.
I can tell you whatever
it is you want to hear
about Flint's whereabouts.
He's dead.
He's retired.
The truth of it matters not at all.
The truth is there will be no
Maroon War in the West Indies
because the Maroons
themselves have agreed to it.
All that remains, then,
is for you to purchase
Woodes Rogers' debts.
Force his default and incarceration
and see him replaced with a new governor
who will honor these terms.
You asked for proof of
Captain Flint's removal.
I cannot give it to you.
But this is a meaningful assurance
that the pirate threat is no more.
You asked for a governor
I would call husband.
I cannot give that to you either.
But I have given you a candidate
whose trustworthiness I can guarantee.
What candidate?
You want me to administrate Nassau?
These are the terms under
which it will happen.
They are the best I can offer.
Are they acceptable to you?
Just one more thing.
Small favor to ask...
before the ink dries
on whatever it is you've agreed upon.
Once the demand for
repayment has been made
and his default recorded
and the warrant sworn,
there will be a trial.
And at that trial,
the court will solicit
affidavits from his creditors.
Affidavits that will shape the
official narrative of the default.
The failure.
The humiliation.
For a man like Woodes Rogers,
how difficult that will
be... to sit helpless
while history records
such an unflattering end
to what was once such a promising story.
I suppose what I'm asking is...
once the time comes to
submit that affidavit,
I'd so love to help you write it.
Leave.
No.
The treaty is being ratified.
The chiefs from the other
camps will be leaving shortly,
along with the pirate crews.
The war is over.
Yes.
I don't know why you did this.
But I know you did this.
Sent me away from that
island so I would not see it.
Emboldened Julius so
I could not oppose it.
Orchestrated it.
Don't you dare insult
me by denying this.
Flint's war could only have one result.
A life of loss...
and misery...
and fruitless sacrifice.
- I had to stop it.
- You had to stop it?
And I'm not sorry for it.
I lost you once.
I would not do it again.
Captain Flint didn't retire from this.
It was important that they heard that,
but they didn't know him like you do.
I won't insult you by repeating it.
He trusted you.
He was your friend.
And you killed him.
No.
I did not kill Captain Flint.
I unmade him.
The man you know could
never let go of his war.
For if he were to
exclude it from himself,
he would not be able
to understand himself.
So I had to return him to
an earlier state of being.
One in which he could
function without the war.
Without the violence.
Without us.
Captain Flint was born
out of great tragedy.
You know this.
I told you this.
I found a way to reach into the past...
and undo it.
There is a place near Savannah...
where men unjustly imprisoned in England
are sent in secret.
An internment far more humane,
but no less secure.
Men who enter these
gates never leave them.
To the rest of the world,
they simply cease to be.
I don't believe you.
I don't believe this.
Flint would have fought to
the death before allowing it.
He resisted...
at first.
But then I told him what else
I had heard about this place.
I was told prominent families
amongst London society
made use of it.
I was told the governor
in Carolina made use of it.
So I sent a man to find out
if they'd used it to hide
away one particular prisoner.
He returned with news.
Thomas Hamilton was there.
He disbelieved me.
He continued to resist.
And corralling him took great effort.
But the closer we got to Savannah,
his resistance began to diminish.
I couldn't say why.
I wasn't expecting it.
Perhaps he'd finally reached
the limits of his
physical ability to fight.
Or perhaps as the promise of
seeing Thomas got closer...
he grew more comfortable
letting go of this man
he created in response to his loss.
The man whose mind I had
come to know so well...
whose mind I'd in some ways
incorporated into my own.
It was a strange experience
to see something from it...
so unexpected.
I choose to believe it...
because it wasn't the man
I had come to know at all...
but one who existed beforehand...
waking from a long...
and terrible nightmare.
Reorienting to the daylight...
and the world as it existed
before he first closed his eyes...
letting the memory of
the nightmare fade away.
You may think what you want of me.
I will draw comfort in the knowledge
that you're alive to think it.
But I'm not the villain you fear I am.
I'm not him.
You sent a man...
to investigate this place?
Yes.
And he did this and
returned to Nassau...
all before the Spanish arrived?
Yes.
You didn't just betray my trust.
You have planned to betray it...
all that time.
Get out.
The pirates will be leaving here.
The chiefs.
But I will stay.
And I will wait.
A day...
a month...
a year...
forever...
in the hopes that you will
understand why I did what I did.
Get out.
A story is true.
A story is untrue.
As time extends,
it matters less and less.
The stories we want to believe...
those are the ones that survive,
despite upheaval and transition
and progress.
Those are the stories
that shape history.
And then what does it matter
if it was true when it was born?
It's found truth in its maturity,
which if a virtue in man
ought to be no less so
for the things men create.
As this relates to your
question specifically...
I'm sorry. Remind me, what was
your question, specifically?
- Long John Silver.
- Long John Silver, yes.
Please forgive me.
I will go on from time to time,
but generally in the
service of thoroughness
and always with the best of intentions.
I appreciate your indulging me.
No need. I was drawn in.
Long John Silver's story...
is a hard one to know.
The men who believed
most deeply in it...
were ultimately destroyed by it.
And those who stood to
benefit most from it...
were the most eager
to leave it all behind.
Until all that remains of any of it...
are stories bearing only
a passing resemblance
to the world the rest of us lived in.
A world we survived.
A world that is no more.
I hear it ain't altogether over.
I hear there are still
men on the account here
under the blessing of the governor.
I hear he allows for it...
as long as it helps drive up
prices for the merchants here.
I hear he allows you to
continue the practice.
That's why I came.
Two things you must know
if you're gonna be
spending time here with us.
One, the governor.
Lovely man. Dear friend.
Might be the hero given
credit for the Maroon truce,
bringing peace to the West Indies,
and finally, at long last,
bringing law and order to Nassau.
But let's just say he had some help.
And the true power here...
is a little more complicated than that.
And two,
there is, by law...
and strict enforcement
of the administration,
no piracy in Nassau.
Not anymore. Not ever.
It's critical for commerce.
This is known to the world.
Meet me at the jetty.
Are we ready to depart?
Don't remember talking
about bringing on new people.
Ah, we didn't.
Oh, I know we didn't.
He's come from the continent.
Served with the regulars in the war.
Mark. Mark Read.
You could be more
welcoming to new people.
Would it hurt?
Planning on bringing them all on?
All of who?
All the fools that have heard
you may know where to find
Captain Flint's treasure.
The ones thinking you may
go looking for it again.
Thinking you'll make them rich.
The ones I worry might
just convince you to do it.
I've chased Captain Flint's treasure.
I've had Captain Flint's treasure.
It never ends well.
Rather than rush off after it again...
maybe let's just do this a while longer.
Maybe...
Oh, is that it?
Still don't understand what
was wrong with the one we had.
Because what's it all for
if it goes unremembered?
It's the art that leaves the mark.
But to leave it, it must... transcend.
It must speak for itself.
It must be true.
It's fine.
Get us underway.
Synced and corrected by Aaronnmb
www.addic7ed.com