[MAGHRA] I want men posted at their church
and each of their homes
in case they return.
[TAMACTI JUN] I don't believe the
Witchfinders will be returning home soon.
You've outlawed their beliefs.
Well, their beliefs have been outlawed
in all of Paya. Where will they go?
Ah. It's a big kingdom.
My guess is the outer-lying towns,
uh, Lebnin, Altoona,
they'll find a more sympathetic haven.
Have Lords Diego and Torrance sent word?
I want them found.
Already did.
Perhaps we'll have news.
The council is already assembled.
[MAGHRA] Any word on my family?
[TAMACTI JUN] Even if everything at
the House of Enlightenment went perfectly,
they wouldn't be back yet.
When does anything go perfectly?
You said the council
had already assembled?
It has.
Why don't I hear them?
I smell blood.
[GASPS]
[BREATHING HEAVILY]
Is it all of them?
I think so.
[BREATHING SHAKILY]
[TAMACTI JUN] Lord Diego.
[MAGHRA BREATHING HEAVILY]
Witchfinders.
Blood is still warm.
Let's get you somewhere safe.
[MAGHRA BREATHES SHAKILY]
- [HARLAN] Okay, this isn't gonna work.
- [BABA VOSS] What are you talking about?
[HARLAN SIGHS] We don't just need
to get to Pennsa before Tormada.
We gotta get there
with enough time to build an army,
fortify defenses, come up with a plan.
You know a faster way?
Well, yes, actually I do.
There's another route
sometimes used by smugglers.
Why are you only saying this now?
'Cause it's dangerous, okay?
But it'll save us an entire day.
Maybe two.
You wanna take 'em through the lowlands?
Yeah, you're crazy.
What are these lowlands?
They aren't on any maps.
And the terrain is-is... is tricky.
- What do you mean "tricky"?
- We've lost men there.
- [BABA VOSS] Lost them? How?
- We don't know.
- [GUNTAR] There are spirits.
- Not that.
Okay, it's not ideal,
but it's the fastest way back.
And there are seven of us.
Three of us have sight.
I've made it through many times
with far less.
How many times?
Twice.
You'll lead the way.
Yeah, right. Punish the one with the plan.
How did we let these Witchfinders
get past our defenses?
It wasn't a lot of them.
Three or four is all it would've taken.
Those were largely defenseless civilians.
I did this.
Maghra.
I had them in my hands,
moments from the hangman.
And I just let them go.
You showed mercy.
My mercy just killed our entire council.
My sister was right.
Violence must be met with violence.
I'm gonna find these Witchfinders.
They are murderers, and they will pay.
I only ask you leave this with me.
Your hands should stay clean.
It's too late for that.
[DRIVER] Whoa, whoa! Whoa.
Welcome, Councillor.
Made exceptional time.
I received word you managed to lose
an entire battalion to one man.
A man you said you killed.
Yes, yes, yes. Baba Voss.
All my fault, lesson learned and so on.
But, uh, why talk about past mistakes
when we can talk about
how many soldiers you brought me?
[SIGHS] Pathetically few.
I had to be careful.
Until I've bought
the loyalties of the generals,
I cannot reveal my part in all of this.
Hmm, reasonable calculation.
Maybe. But we're a regiment short.
Can we still take Pennsa?
Ah, you still underestimate
the power of my bombs.
I'm concerned about
having enough soldiers to place them.
Ah, soldiers are no longer required.
We've built machines that can
launch these bombs great distances.
- You've tested these machines?
- [SCOFFS] You insult me.
And the sighted children?
How will you continue to operate
without them?
We'll find them.
And there are other sighted ones in play.
In the meantime,
we have more than enough ammunition
to flatten the entire Payan kingdom.
Well, then,
I suppose you should proceed to Pennsa.
- [CHUCKLES]
- You have my troops.
- For which, you have my thanks.
- Commander.
- [HORSE WHINNIES]
- [COMMANDER] Join ranks!
[TORMADA] Back home?
Yes. I have an empire in crisis to manage.
- And you have a kingdom to conquer.
- [CHUCKLES]
Safe travels.
[DRIVER] Hyah!
[CROW CAWING]
[GUNTAR CLICKING TONGUE]
Harlan, in a lifetime of bad ideas,
this is the worst.
Yeah. [CLICKS TONGUE]
There's no turning back now.
[CLICKING TONGUE]
[BABA VOSS]
You should talk to your sister.
She shot a gun at me.
Kofun, do you know why your mother will be
a far better queen than Sibeth?
No. 'Cause she's not crazy?
[CHUCKLES] 'Cause she has compassion.
I could never be king
'cause my compassion is less powerful
than my instinct to fight.
Maybe that's what makes a good warrior.
I don't know.
But what I do know is
that you are your mother's son.
You have had her compassion
and wisdom from a young age.
I know you think that makes you soft,
but it makes you stronger.
Like your mother.
You'll make a great king.
What? [CHUCKLES]
What are you talking about?
I'm not gonna be king.
Spoken like a true prince.
Please, go talk to your sister.
It's not gonna work.
That's the spirit, boy.
[SIGHS]
Hey.
- I'll leave the two of you alone.
- Wren.
- We have to talk at some point.
- [SIGHS] Do we?
It wasn't just me, you know.
Mom and Dad wanted it gone too.
The knowledge stored in that place
could've changed the world.
You think I don't know that?
Haniwa, they were building bombs.
They are building bombs. Not us.
We would be different.
You were pretty quick to pick up that gun.
[HANIWA SCOFFS]
I'm sorry. That was a mistake.
Yeah, it was a pretty big mistake.
Please, as if you haven't
made mistakes. Sibeth.
[SHUSHES]
Papa, what is it?
We're not alone.
This fucking place.
[FIGURE GROWLS]
I saw someone.
- There's another.
- [GROWLS]
There are more.
- [BRANCHES RUSTLING]
- [FIGURES GROWLING]
At least six.
We can handle six. Right?
- [FIGURE GROWLS]
- [BRANCHES RUSTLE]
Hello!
We're passing through.
We mean you no harm.
But... we are heavily armed.
[FIGURES SNARLING, GROWLING]
They have dogs.
Those aren't dogs.
[HORSE WHINNYING]
Whoa! Shit.
[GROWLING CONTINUES]
[HORSE WHINNIES]
[GUNTAR SCREAMS]
Guntar!
[SNARLING]
[SHOUTS]
[GRUNTING]
[ATTACKER SHRIEKS, SNARLS]
[SNARLING]
[GRUNTING]
[SHOUTING, GRUNTING]
- [GRUNTING]
- [SNARLING]
Oh! Fuck! Shit! No! [GROANS]
[GRUNTING]
[SCREAMS]
Fuck! Fuck! Fuck!
Oh, fuck.
[GRUNTS, SCREAMS]
[STRUGGLING]
[WREN SCREAMS]
[SNARLING]
- [BABA VOSS GROWLS]
- [FLESH TEARS]
[PANTING]
- Kofun. Are you hurt?
- [BREATHING HEAVILY] No.
Where's Haniwa?
[STRUGGLING]
- [WREN SCREAMS] Get the fuck off!
- [HANIWA PANTING, GRUNTING]
[WREN SCREAMS] Haniwa!
[SCREAMING, STRUGGLING CONTINUES]
[EXHALES DEEPLY]
- [GROANS]
- [GRUNTS]
[PANTING]
[SNARLS]
- [GROANS]
- [HANIWA SHOUTS]
- [SNARLS]
- [GRUNTS]
[STRUGGLING]
[HANIWA STRUGGLING, ECHOING]
Haniwa.
[HANIWA SCREAMS]
[GRUNTING, PANTING]
[WREN] Baba! [BREATHES HEAVILY]
- Where is she?
- [CRYING, PANTING] They took her.
She's gone.
[BREATHING HEAVILY]
[SHOUTS]
[RATTLING]
Whoa.
- [WHISTLES, CLICKS TONGUE]
- [SOLDIERS] Whoa.
- [CLICKING TONGUE]
- What is it? Why are we stopping?
[LEAD RIDER]
There's someone on the road, sir.
[RATTLES]
- [GRUNTING]
- What is that?
[SHOUTING]
[GRUNTS, SHOUTS]
[BONE SNAPS]
Stand down.
[SOLDIER] Stand down!
[SOLDIERS GRUNT]
Who are you? What do you want?
I'm seeking Tormada.
I am Tormada.
I'll do it.
Get off me.
[GRUNTING]
[GRUNTS, BREATHES HEAVILY]
And who might you be?
Tormada, I am Sibeth Kane.
Your Majesty. It is an honor.
Hmm. I'd heard you were a smart one.
[CHUCKLES]
Now, where are all those wonderful weapons
I've heard so much about?
[SCOFFS]
[WREN] Is that human bone?
- [SNIFFS, GROANS]
- [KOFUN] What are these?
I heard stories about this
when I was a boy.
There's a tribe that lives like animals.
Hunting and eating their own kind.
I heard those stories too.
Fucking flesh eaters.
Cannibals. We read about them.
All right, well, what are we gonna do?
We have to find them.
We should split up.
Search the entire area.
[KOFUN] No, that's gonna take too long.
We'll be too late.
Maybe not.
They took them alive for a reason.
[WREN] What are you trying to say?
They keep them alive
so that they don't spoil.
[BREATHES SHAKILY]
Kofun, I need you to ride back to Pennsa,
tell your mother Tormada's coming.
No. No, I'm not leaving. Haniwa needs me.
So does your son and your mother.
Get on the horse
and ride to Pennsa and warn her now.
Wren, with me.
[BREATHES HEAVILY]
We're gonna get her back.
[SIGHS]
[HORSE WHINNIES]
- [TAMACTI JUN] Remend Skelt.
- Who's that?
Tamacti Jun.
[REMEND] Tamacti Jun.
I'd heard of your return from the dead,
and no sooner are you back
than you disband the army that you served.
I serve the queen.
And you have aligned yourself
with those who would undermine her crown.
I'm a simple blacksmith.
I'm not aligned with anyone.
Well, then...
it's time you were.
My queen.
[BELLS JINGLING]
Hello. Remend, is it?
Your Majesty.
I'm looking for some Witchfinders.
The Witchfinders have all
been disbanded, my queen.
[MAGHRA] Hmm. Are you sure
that's how you want this to go?
Tamacti Jun.
[GRUNTS, GROANS]
[GRUNTING, GROANING]
[SCREAMS]
- Where are they?
- [CRIES] I don't know! I don't!
[CRYING, SCREAMING]
- [SIGHS, PANTING]
- Put his hand on the table.
- [REMEND GROANING, COUGHING]
- This is a whistle sword.
I doubt you've ever made one.
It requires a level of artistry
that few possess.
[REMEND PANTING, GRUNTING]
Its blade is refined
to an almost inhuman level of precision.
These Witchfinders we're looking for
just slaughtered 12 innocent Payans.
If they are not found,
they will keep killing.
So, please,
will you tell us where they are?
[SPITS] I will not.
[GRUNTING, PANTING]
- I understand.
- [WHIMPERING]
[SCREAMS, CRIES]
You can probably keep making
your swords without that finger,
but what happens when I take your thumb?
[SCREAMS] No, fuck! [CRIES]
No! They're at the mason's yard.
There's a house in the back.
They're all in there.
[CRYING]
Thank you.
[PANTING, CRIES]
You fucking heretic!
I hope they slit your fucking throat.
You and those bastard witch children!
[MAGHRA] Take the whole hand.
- [TAMACTI JUN GRUNTS]
- [REMEND SCREAMS, CRYING]
Yes. This way.
[BREATHING HEAVILY]
Edo used to track like this.
My father, he was a Slaver.
He taught us to track this way.
Scared men, they leave marks.
They make mistakes.
But these, these things...
have no fear.
- [GROANS]
- You lost it?
Anything?
They leave no trail.
[BREATHES SHAKILY]
[SIGHS]
They are hunters.
[BREATHING HEAVILY]
We will let them hunt us.
Come.
[CLICKS TONGUE]
[CLICKING TONGUE]
It is Tamacti Jun. We know you're here.
[SHILOH] Witchfinder General.
Have you come to rejoin our ranks?
Shiloh. I might have known.
There will be no negotiating here.
I had no intention of negotiating.
They're on the roof.
[GRUNTING]
Get back!
[GRUNTING, SHOUTING]
Maghra Kane. Where are you?
I'm right here.
[BOTH GRUNTING]
[GROWLS]
[CHOKING]
[GRUNTS] Maghra!
[GROANS]
[PANTING]
Where are the rest of you?
- What are you planning?
- [BREATHING HEAVILY]
You... You think I would betray
my oath to God for a heretic like you?
[GRUNTS]
You have no authority over them.
They serve a different queen now.
What queen? What are you talking about?
[PANTS, CHUCKLES]
You don't know?
[CHUCKLES]
[GASPS, GRUNTS]
Sibeth and the Witchfinders
will rain God Thunder down
on you and your devil children.
[GRUNTS, BREATHING HEAVILY]
[CHUCKLES]
You fight for a kingdom
that is already lost.
[BREATHING HEAVILY]
You better kill me, Maghra Kane.
Or you will live to regret it.
You're a Witchfinder
who can no longer walk.
You're already dead.
Kill me, you bitch!
[TAMACTI JUN] Shiloh.
[INHALES SHARPLY] Tamacti Jun.
Give me my honor. Finish me.
Death must be earned, Shiloh.
Trust me, I know.
Kill me!
[GROANS]
- [FLESH EATERS SNARLING]
- [GASPS]
[EXHALES SHARPLY]
- [HARLAN] You're awake.
- [GROANS, BREATHES HEAVILY]
Where are we?
Well, based on the smell,
I'd say we're in their home.
[GROANS]
Smells like...
[GASPS, BREATHING HEAVILY]
Oh, no. [WHIMPERS]
[HARLAN] What? What? What?
[CRIES] They... They're eating people.
[INHALES SHAKILY]
[CRYING] Oh, my God.
Guntar?
Oh, shit.
[HANIWA STRUGGLING]
We have to get out of here.
Yeah.
I've been trying while you were asleep.
They may be animals,
but they know their knots.
[PANTING]
Well, they'll come for us.
Haniwa, if they could track us,
they'd be here already.
And there's... there's Pennsa to consider.
- What about it?
- Their first order of business remains.
They gotta get home.
They gotta warn Maghra.
My father won't leave me behind.
Even for the sake of an entire kingdom?
[SCOFFS] Yes. Even for that.
Well...
I guess there is some small comfort
in knowing
that either way, we're dead.
[CRYING]
[GRUNTING, SNARLING]
- [HARLAN WHISPERING] Hey, hey, hey.
- [CRYING CONTINUES]
- Haniwa?
- Yeah? [BREATHING SHAKILY]
You know, we've never really talked.
You're choosing now to start?
Oh, I'm sorry,
do you have somewhere you need to be?
[LAUGHS]
[BREATHES SHAKILY, CHUCKLES]
Okay. [EXHALES SHARPLY] Okay, um...
Okay. Behind you, uh, there's some
broken glass about an arm's length,
but you're going to have to move.
- Yes.
- Which way, which way?
[HANIWA]
Um, further back. Yes. [BREATHING HEAVILY]
About half an arm's length now.
Just a bit further.
[FLESH EATERS GROWLING]
- [HARLAN] Half an arm?
- [HANIWA] Yes.
You're very close. Almost there.
- Further, further, further back.
- Okay.
I can't get further. Oh, shit.
Yeah. Yeah, that's close.
- Yeah, almost.
- [HARLAN] Okay.
[BREATHING SHAKILY]
Now he's coming. He's coming.
- Where is it? Where is it?
- Oh, shh. Shh. Be quiet.
Don't... Then tell me quietly. Where is it?
[HANIWA] He's coming. He's coming.
- [SHUSHING]
- [HARLAN] No, I've got it.
- Okay. Oh, fuck.
- [FLESH EATER GRUNTS]
- [HANIWA SCREAMS] No! No! [STRUGGLING]
- [HARLAN] Oh, fuck. Oh, fuck.
[HANIWA PANTING, WHIMPERING]
[SOLDIERS CHATTERING]
[FOOTSTEPS APPROACHING]
Lucien, is that you?
Yes, my queen.
We have the Trivantian scientist.
Bring him.
[CHAINS RATTLING]
[TORMADA GRUNTING, BREATHING HEAVILY]
I hear chains. Why is he in chains?
For your safety, Your Majesty.
That is no way to treat
a new friend and ally.
Unbind him.
- My queen.
- [SIBETH] Now.
I am so sorry, Tormada.
I suppose our nations have been at odds
for so long,
you can hardly blame Lucien.
If I were you and I'd captured me,
I'd have done the same.
So, Trivantes and Paya are moments away
from a peace treaty,
and you have planned an attack.
[TORMADA] Mmm. A treaty with your sister
wouldn't have given me much peace.
And you're going to war
with only a handful of soldiers.
I'm funny like that.
[SIBETH] Yes, I have heard about you.
[CHUCKLES]
Your wonderful new weapons...
[BREATHES SHAKILY]
...like thunder from the heavens
tearing apart the earth.
An almost insurmountable advantage.
Though, you don't speak
for all of Trivantes, do you?
No more than you speak
for all of Paya, I suppose.
Tormada, I think
you and I may very well be friends.
And how am I so fortunate?
The enemy of my enemy is my friend.
Or rival.
I find myself wondering how this ends.
If you're careful,
you just might keep your head.
Oh, I'm certain I'll keep it.
Because without it,
my bombs are just lumps of Godbone
and of no use to you at all.
And without my bombs,
you'll never reclaim your kingdom.
And without my army,
you'll be vulnerable to attack
from Pennsa and Trivantes alike.
Sounds like the perfect foundation
for a deal to be struck. Hmm?
Tell me, my queen,
what is it that you want?
I want my father's kingdom back.
But why stop there?
There's a whole world beyond Paya.
That's what I want.
Once Paya is mine, you may use it
as your base to build new weapons,
to expand your empire
as far as your heart desires.
You don't strike me
as someone who likes to share.
Well, not with just anyone. [CHUCKLES]
But a husband.
A king.
- Is that a proposal, Your Highness?
- [LUCIEN] My queen.
- If so, I accept.
- [LUCIEN] Wait.
Quiet, Lucien.
Can't you hear we're having a moment?
You can't be serious about
aligning ourselves with a Trivantian.
We cannot trust this man.
Perhaps you're right.
Hand me your sword.
[LUCIEN] Your Majesty?
[SNAPS]
[SNAPPING]
[CHUCKLES]
[BREATHING SHAKILY]
What do you say, Tormada? Can I trust you?
It's certainly a gamble.
I'll give you that.
But you strike me
as someone who's spent years
honing her instincts about people.
Hmm?
Indeed, I have.
[TORMADA BREATHES SHAKILY]
[GRUNTS]
[SIBETH SIGHS]
- [LUCIEN GRUNTING, GROANING]
- [BREATHING HEAVILY]
[LUCIEN GRUNTING]
Thank you for your service.
[LUCIEN EXHALES DEEPLY]
[BREATHING HEAVILY]
I ruled alone my entire life.
It's exhausting.
Lonely.
I've just never met anyone
with the stomach for it.
But you seem up to the task.
I am, my queen. I am.
[FLESH EATERS GROWLING]
[SNIFFING]
[GRUNTING]
[BABA VOSS ROARS]
[FLESH EATER SHRIEKS]
[WHIMPERING]
[BREATHING SHAKILY]
[GRUNTS, WHIMPERS]
[GRUNTS, PANTS]
[SNIFFS, SMACKS LIPS]
[PANTING]
[HOWLS]
[ROARS]
[FLESH EATER GROWLING]
[BREATHING HEAVILY]
[GROANS]
[GROWLS]
[GROWLING]
[BOTH GRUNTING, GROWLING]
[HANIWA WHISPERING] Harlan.
- Harlan.
- [HARLAN] Shh.
[GRUNTS]
- This could be our only chance.
- Shh.
[SAWING]
[BREATHES SHAKILY]
[HANIWA] You did it.
[WHISPERING] Haniwa.
I'm here. [GRUNTS]
Harlan.
[BREATHING SHAKILY]
[GROWLS]
Harlan!
- [GROANS]
- [SNARLING]
[BABA VOSS GRUNTS, GROANS]
[GRUNTS, SNARLS]
[BABA VOSS BREATHING HEAVILY]
[PANTING]
[GRUNTS]
[FLESH EATER GROWLING]
[BREATHING SHARPLY]
[WHIMPERS]
- [GRUNTS]
- [OBJECT CLATTERS]
[HANIWA WHIMPERING]
- [SNARLING]
- [STRUGGLING]
[PANTING]
[BOTH GRUNTING, SHOUTING]
[BABA VOSS GROANS]
[SCREAMS]
[CHOKING]
[GRUNTS, PANTS]
[BOTH GROWLING]
[PANTING]
[WEAPON CLATTERS]
[BOTH ROARING, GRUNTING]
[GROANING]
[PANTING]
[SNARLS]
[GRUNTING]
[SCREAMING]
- [GRUNTING]
- [BOTH SCREAMING]
[GRUNTS, BREATHING HEAVILY]
[BREATHING SHAKILY]
Haniwa.
[HANIWA] I'm here.
Okay, okay.
[HANIWA BREATHES SHAKILY, GRUNTS]
[PANTING] You came back.
I never left.
I just wanted to find something
really heavy to hit the fucker with.
[BOTH BREATHING HEAVILY]
Oh.
Okay. All right, we got to go.
[HARLAN SIGHS]
- Papa.
- [BABA VOSS] Haniwa.
[FINGERS SNAPPING]
- Are you hurt?
- No.
- Haniwa.
- Where's Harlan?
Almost sound worried about me, Boo-boo.
- [HANIWA] Harlan.
- [BABA VOSS] Oh, no.
- Ah, shit. Oh, God.
- Help.
Wasn't as fast as I thought, was I?
- [BABA VOSS GROANS]
- [HARLAN BREATHES SHAKILY, GROANS]
[BABA VOSS] His cut is deep.
[HANIWA INHALES SHARPLY]
[STAMMERS] It's okay. We can stop
the bleeding until we get him to a healer.
Oh, Haniwa, g...
Those weren't the last of their kind,
all right?
There are more, and they'll be back,
so all of you are gonna need
to move along pretty quickly.
- We are not leaving you here, Harlan.
- [EXHALES DEEPLY, CHUCKLES]
I don't think you're gonna have
much of a choice.
[HANIWA] No. [BREATHES SHAKILY]
It's okay. It's okay, it's okay.
It's fine, really.
Listen, I've been taking care of myself
for a long time, all right?
It's nice to take care of someone else.
[INHALES SHARPLY]
- Thank you.
- [GRUNTS] No, thank you.
See, this is nice, huh? Nice.
All right, now listen to me.
When you tell the story...
[BREATHES SHAKILY]
...I want you to promise me
you will massively exaggerate my bravery
in the face of certain death.
- [LAUGHS]
- Okay?
Yes, Harlan, you were very brave.
It's... It's good. It was very good.
Do it exactly like that.
[BREATHES SHAKILY]
Wait, wait...
[BREATHING SHAKILY]
Give this to Maghra, okay?
And tell her that... [BREATHING SHAKILY]
...um... Yeah, tell her, uh...
uh, she...
It's okay. She knows.
Go. Come on, you gotta go.
Hanging around
waiting for me to die is depressing.
- Harlan.
- It's all right, Haniwa.
Go on. Gotta go. Go.
[BREATHES SHAKILY] Oh, fuck.
Oh, fuck.
[BREATHES SHAKILY] Oh, shit.
[BREATHES HEAVILY]
Baba Voss.
Yes, Harlan.
[BREATHES SHAKILY]
Please don't let them take my city.
[BABA VOSS SIGHS]
Whoa.
- [HORSE WHINNIES]
- [GRUNTS]
[PANTS]
[GASPS, GROANS]
[SIBETH] Hmm.
I never had to fight for my crown.
I was born into the monarchy,
a queen ordained by God.
I wore the crown,
but it always felt a little light to me.
But now, now that crown will be forged
in the burning flames of war.
And I will be a queen reborn,
anointed by the blood of my enemies.
You have the soul of a poet, my queen.
Are we ready?
We are.
Good. Let's begin.