- Brock.
- Yeah?
Stop!
Better have a damn good reason
for trespassing on my land.
If this is your land,
you must be Sani Crow.
We're looking for
Chayton Littlestone.
He killed our friend.
She was a cop.
Then you came
a long way for nothing.
Oh, fuck.
I blame you for this.
This woman you say
Chayton killed,
what did she do to him?
Nothing.
Then why would he take her life?
'Cause he's
a fucking psychopath.
There was a time when you people
would have called him
a "wild savage" instead.
Yeah, that sounds about right.
Listen, he came to you for help
and you gave him sanctuary.
I understand that.
He's your people.
But right now every cop within a
thousand miles is looking for him.
Not even you can avoid
that kind of heat.
That's why I didn't
allow him to stay.
- When did he leave?
- Hood.
A few days before you showed up.
And where did he go?
My best guess
would be the Quarter.
It's not a big place.
Let's go.
Hundred bucks says he's lying.
- Doesn't matter.
- Why not?
He sent us
to the French Quarter.
Whether he's selling
us out or Chayton,
we all end up in the same place.
Yeah!
Brock, do you see him?
I can't see anything.
The crowd's too damn thick.
Hit that motherfucker.
- Hit that motherfucker.
- Boys, let's up the ante.
Let's get some real
shit up in here.
Yeah! Yeah!
Yeah!
How the hell
did you get down there?
Ladies and gentlemen,
it is time for our main event.
In this corner,
from God knows where,
weighing in at...
who gives a fuck?
Our undefeated champion:
the Slayer!
Is it me, or does this
entire place smell like ass?
And now,
joining us in a surprise appearance,
a favorite here
at the Underground.
Born again.
Oh, yeah.
Chayton!
Hood.
Sorry.
Excuse me.
I can't see you.
Where are you?
Hood, where are you?
Yeah! Yeah, kill him!
Finish him.
Fuck.
Hood, what the hell
are you doing? Hood!
Hood!
The lady cop,
she was your woman?
Good.
Don't move, Chayton.
Fuck you, cop.
The next shot will blow
your fucking face off.
There are no guns
allowed in here.
We're cops, asshole.
This man is wanted for murder.
Not here, he's not. Here, that
man is under my protection.
Fine.
I'll shoot you, too.
Now that'd be a neat trick.
This didn't go as planned.
- Chayton.
- Fuck.
Is that man you're
fighting also a pig?
Yes.
Now, as much as I'd love
to give these fans
the death they deserve,
I think that killing
a police officer
might complicate my arrangement
with local law enforcement.
You're done.
You're done, Chayton!
I'll see you again, cop.
Yeah, you fucking know you will.
Now, what you gentlemen
need to understand
is that Chayton is a beloved
figure here at the Underground.
And it is only my goodwill
that is keeping
these dedicated fans
from tearing you
apart limb from limb.
And I'll wager you got
roughly 60 seconds
before that goodwill fails me.
Starting... now.
Come on, let's go.
Let's get the hell out.
Come on.
Goddamn it, I thought the
plan was to watch Chayton.
I didn't want to lose him again.
I'm pretty sure that's
what just happened.
- Now he knows we're here.
- That's an understatement.
What if he leaves New Orleans?
He's not going anywhere.
What is it, Burton?
There's a small discrepancy
in inventory at the factory.
- What, missing product?
- The opposite.
It seems we're showing
more profit than sales.
Well, that's a good
problem to have.
What would you like me to do?
Look into it.
Tell me what you find out.
Anything else?
No.
Nothing else.
Burton looked worried.
Oh, Burton always looks worried.
It's just business.
Hey, I thought you went out.
You thought wrong, again.
Did you lose something?
Not something.
$125,000.
Apparently some motherfucker
forgot I'm the one
who can count.
What the fuck were you
thinking taking that money?
Now hold on.
It's just a small taste
of what I got coming to me.
Nothing coming to no one until
we all decide how to handle it.
It's not like I'm running
off to Atlantic City.
I'm not an idiot.
Oh, you doing a damn good
impression of one.
Something came up.
- What?
- Something personal.
That's all you need to know.
Hey. Hey!
Let it go, Job.
I ain't sitting on this just
to cover for your fat ass.
You hear me?
You do what you got to do.
So Will I.
Take the bag directly
to the drop point.
You deliver to Morales
himself or no one at all.
- Okay?
- Yes, ma'am.
Is there a problem?
If your uncle finds out...
Some chances are worth taking.
Don't you think?
Yes, ma'am.
Call me when you're finished.
You're violating our
agreement with Frazier
and selling to the Salvadorans.
Yes.
Your uncle won't like that.
Then don't tell him.
It can be our secret.
And in the end...
...he'll thank us
for it.
I'm not going to tell him.
It should come from you.
I'm trying to help him.
Can't you see that?
This woman is making him weak.
He's making bad decisions.
He's risking everything
he's built.
That's not going to happen.
It's already happening.
Fine.
Do what you have to do.
But just know you'll be
making him pick between us.
And do you really think
he'll choose you
over his very special niece?
Again. Good, good.
That's it.
One, two, three, slip.
There you go, baby.
Uppercuts, uppercuts...
one, two, three, four, five,
six, seven, eight, nine, ten.
That's it.
One, two, three, slip.
Stay... keep your head up.
Keep your head up.
One, two, three, slip.
- Oscar.
- Come on... Shug.
What are you doing here?
How's he doing?
He was doing good,
all things considered.
But a few months back,
things got bad, you know?
Between the doctors, the nurses,
all the new prescriptions,
we're drowning, Shug.
Open it.
Jesus.
No, this is way too much.
It's not even close
to what I owe your old man.
Look, Pop took his chances
just like every other boxer
that climbed into that ring.
Could have
just as easily been you.
It wasn't.
Why don't you
stick around, you know?
You could give
some of those young punks
the benefit of your wisdom.
That bag is about
all the wisdom I got left.
You trying to give me
a heart attack?
A girl can dream.
Start talking.
No.
That's real mature, Job.
Now you tell me
who did you give that
motherfucking money to?
His name is Oscar Cruz Jr.
His father was a fighter.
So, what, you forgot his
son's bar mitzvah present?
Senior wasn't ready
for that fight.
The promoters didn't care.
I didn't care either.
I mean, the title
was on the line.
The ref should have stopped the
fight after I landed a few big ones.
Lord knows I couldn't.
By the time his head
hit that canvas,
I had scrambled
his brains so badly
that he would never speak again.
So where is he now?
He's in some overpriced
nursing home out West.
Drooling and wearing a diaper.
Now, could you please
give me my distributor cap back?
Is anyone there?
Oh, looks like you've been
down here quite some time.
They worked you over real good.
Always be prepared.
Don't worry.
I'm not gonna hurt you.
I'll cut you loose.
Just take your time.
I'll be right back.
Let's go.
I saved one for you.
Come on, let's go.
Can I help you?
I am going to help you
become a better man.
What the fuck
are you talking about?
What did he tell you?
You are going to graciously
return all the money he gave you.
That money was a gift
to my father.
Oscar Cruz Sr., died
in November of 2007.
I saw your handiwork
with the forged
hospital forms
and insurance records.
Junior's been collecting
his benefits for years.
Almost as long
as he's been playing you.
Sugar thinks I have no clue
what really happened
in the fight that night.
But I know what he did to my father
had nothing to do with boxing.
He took everything...
Bitch, I ain't come
to hear your sob story.
I come for the money.
Then come and take it.
What you did or did not do in
the past don't mean shit to me.
What concerns me is a colleague
that can't keep to the motherfucking
plan in the here and now.
I just want you to remember
I gave your punk ass a chance.
Float like a butterfly,
motherfucker.
You think you know
what happened, Job,
but you don't.
Who was she?
Well, if it ain't for money
and it ain't for glory,
there's only one thing left.
Who was she?
Her name was Vanessa.
I loved her, but she loved him.
I could hear her in the
stands cheering for her man.
A man who wasn't me.
I never felt that kind of pain.
I didn't know what to do with it.
So I gave it to Oscar
to deal with instead.
For 25 years...
...I sent his family
anything I could spare.
Wasn't much,
but it was something.
Listen to me. Let it go.
I have had more
than my fair share
of Podunk Tragedy Theater.
I do not have the energy.
Hey.
You could have kept
that money, you know?
Didn't have to say
a damn word to me.
So Why'd you give it back?
I didn't give it all back.
Ain't nobody in here
gonna talk to us.
No.
But they'll talk to Chayton.
And he'll find us?
That's the idea.
You know, Hood,
we've been working
together for a while now,
and I realized...
...I don't know the first
thing about you.
You know,
like where you're from.
Originally.
Town full of day drinkers.
That's a concept I can get...
You got something
on your mind, Brock?
Yeah.
Yeah, I guess I do.
You know...
...when we...
...when we killed Hondo,
I swore to myself never again.
And yet... here I am,
a short while later,
on another assassination junket.
Sometimes the law
can't give justice.
Oh, don't kid yourself, Hood.
This isn't justice.
Hondo wasn't justice, okay?
This is cold, hard,
self-serving revenge.
We're killers, okay?
Don't make us idiots.
Keep your fucking voice down.
Who gives a shit?
They're all drunk.
- You need to calm down.
- Fuck that, man.
We drove through five states
to come here to kill a man.
You don't have to kill anyone.
Then what the hell
am I doing here?
Huh?
What am I doing here?
Hood!
Oh, my God.
Oh, fuck.
You can't kill me, cop.
You're just a man.
No man can kill me.
Hood!
Damn it, give me that.
I underestimated you.
You're not a cop.
No.
Your people deal in lies.
You will never understand
the purity of true purpose.
Of a spiritual calling.
You're nothing.
I am a warrior.
I held her neck in these hands.
So delicate.
Felt her pulse
tapping against my fingertips.
The life running through her.
Hey.
We should probably
get the hell out of Dodge
before the locals show up, huh?
Hood, let's go.
I can't go back.
What?
I'm done.
I got nothing left.
So that's it?
You're just gonna walk away?
You know, I've been
driving myself crazy
trying to figure you out,
but I'm done.
Who you are, who you were,
where you're from, I don't care.
I don't care anymore.
The only thing I care
about is my town.
Kai Proctor has been
having his way with us,
all of us, for way too long.
But you, you're the first guy
that bastard couldn't own.
And together, you and me,
we could take him down for good.
No.
Goddamn it.
What do you think she
would have wanted, huh?
I'm not going back
to Banshee without you.
Gotta finish what you started.
Even if I've got to kick your ass
all the way back there myself.
I'm not leaving without you.
Are you done?
I think so.
Come on.
In the name of the Lord
and the Church,
we extend to you
the hand of fellowship.
"I am He who blots out
your transgressions
for my own sake
and remembers
your sins no more."
Rise up and be ye a faithful
member of the Church.
In youth we learn.
In age we understand.
This belonged to your mother.
Thank you, Father.
Thank you.
Kai.
Let's go.
Bacon burger.
Cheeseburger.
I thought you and
soldier boy were done.
We are.
Does he know that?
- Hey.
- Hello, Carrie.
Jesus.
What happened to you?
I got robbed.
Doug, are you okay?
I Will be.
Did you call the cops?
No, I'll be handling
this myself.
Maybe you can help.
I understand your father
was no stranger
to illegal behavior.
Maybe you could shed some light on
the nuances of the criminal mind.
My father and I had a
complicated relationship.
I doubt I'd be much help.
Okay.
I'd like some more water, please.
Of course.
They came in through
the old service tunnel.
A winch was used to breach
the steel door.
They took control of the security
cameras and motion sensors.
These guys used our own
defenses to their advantage.
The biometric lock was bypassed
using a dimensional latent clone
and high-end vocal
replication generator.
Somebody got close enough to steal
your voice and fingerprints.
Once they were inside,
the rolling vault codes
were exploited
by an elite hacker.
After that, all they needed was
an experienced safecracker.
And just like that,
our money was theirs.
Captain Murphy,
we have three unknowns.
Van driver makes four.
Start with the hacker.
He defeated every
encryption I set up,
avoided every malware trap.
And beyond that, he hacked into an
ironclad mainframe to shut us down.
You're saying
he's as good as you?
I'm saying he's better.
Tell me about the safecracker.
The lock was drilled
dead center,
the tumblers manipulated
with a gentle touch.
The approach was simple, elegant.
The work of a professional.
Are you sure I can't
get you anything else?
Not today.
The one I haven't figured out is
the one you fought in the tunnel.
He was well trained.
Lethal, but a little rusty.
He allowed his enemy to live
instead of cutting his throat.
It shows he's gone soft.
Maybe grown a conscience.
Why have his partners blow the
tunnel before he was clear?
Loyalty and a commitment
to the objective.
Number three is
gonna be a challenge.
Dismiss all enlisted personnel.
I want them off the base
within the hour.
Yes, sir.
Notify HQ that as of today
Camp Genoa is officially shut down.
We're gonna hunt them down and
take back what they stole from us.
And then we will make them pay.