Is there anything you'd like to talk about?
Not really.
Every week you just sit
in silence on that couch.
- Do you know why you're here?
- I got caught.
No, why you're here with me.
I have to go through you to get parole.
Well, in a manner of speaking.
It's my job to evaluate you...
the progress of your rehabilitation.
Come on, you really think anyone in here
gets rehabilitated?
I think we rehabilitate ourselves.
You've been in here
for what now, seven years?
- Yeah, something like that.
- You've had your share of fights.
It's kind of what we do in here.
You're eligible for parole in four months.
I would think a man
of your obvious intelligence...
and skill would at least
create the impression...
of cooperation with me to manipulate me
into recommending parole.
Well, maybe I just know
not to bullshit a bullshitter.
Fair enough. But believe it or not,
I am here to help you.
Yeah, right.
I'm just another file you got to process...
before you go home to your cats.
What makes you think I have cats?
Well, I know you have a cat.
Cats was a guess.
What else?
You're wearing a black bra
under a white blouse again.
It's happened before...
so it's not because you
didn't get your laundry done.
If that were the case,
you'd go with no bra.
Your tits aren't that big.
No, you deliberately
project your sexuality.
Maybe because of a recent breakup...
or a divorce.
Either way...
you get off on sitting across from men
who haven't seen a woman in years...
knowing that we're gonna go back to our
cells and rub one out thinking of you.
I mean, why else would
a woman that looks like you...
work in a place like this?
And, yeah, you have cats.
Every time you wear dark clothing
like that navy pantsuit...
that you had tailored to cling
to your ass like a second skin...
I see hairs on you.
You're exceptionally observant.
- Occupational hazard.
- Of a thief.
- Inmate.
- Are you gonna steal again?
- No.
- Are you sure?
- It's a trick question.
- Why so?
If I say no, I'm full of shit.
If I say yes, I don't get parole.
Not everything's a trap.
Never say that to a man
who's living in a cell.
I like you.
Isn't that against the rules?
Yes.
What do you want, Rabbit?
I just wanted to look into your eyes...
for the last time.
Good-bye.
Oh, shit.
I guess you owe me one.
Hey.
Go ahead.
I don't want to play.
But it will sharpen your mind...
teach you patience.
Holy...
shit.
- Emmett, check the back.
- Jesus.
Emmett, check the back.
- Hell.
- We need an ambulance.
Hood, talk to us. What happened here?
We just got here. Been out all night
looking for the kid.
Got three dead bodies.
Hood? Sheriff Hood!
I don't know what happened.
They just started shooting.
These are military grade M4s.
That's pretty high-end hardware
for this neck of the woods.
All I care about now is finding that boy.
No, that's my priority
and that's my jurisdiction.
In my estimation, sheriff, you've become
an impediment to this investigation.
I can make a phone call to a judge...
and have a writ within the hour
suspending you from duty.
Hood. Where the hell
do you think you're going?
If you want to stop me,
you're gonna have to shoot me.
Let me have your weapon.
- What are you looking for?
- I'll know it when I see it.
I can help you.
I've lived my whole life here.
Which explains why you haven't
grasped the concept of personal space.
Just tell me what you got.
This is from the traffic camera
at the county line yesterday morning.
- How do you know that's him?
- New York plates.
And Rabbit usually rolls four cars deep.
I tried calling our friendly
neighborhood sheriff...
to put out an APB,
but he's apparently not taking calls.
At least not mine.
I ran the plates, they're counterfeit.
But I ain't got no picture of them leaving.
- They're here.
- Think he's okay?
He's not okay.
If Rabbit's here, no one's okay.
I told him, man.
I said over and over again...
we need to get the fuck out of here.
This has never been anything
but a terrible idea.
How do we find the boy?
We hack into street cameras,
we look for the cars.
We review security footage
from mini-marts and supermarkets.
Someone had to do a food run.
We reroute spy satellites
from the CIA...
and look for heat signatures
where they shouldn't be.
This is a tiny needle
in a big motherfucking haystack.
Hmm.
There's just too much
ground to cover.
I need 20 men doing this
and I ain't got them.
It's just us two.
Or us three.
Hey, Job.
Long time.
Gang's all here.
Please.
Keep trying.
You know they're just here
to keep us safe.
Hey.
You okay?
Deva, I'm sorry about all this.
Why would she lie to us?
Everything's not going
to be all right, is it?
I don't know, honey.
I honestly don't.
I must admit...
you have an admirable
knack for survival.
I'm already dead.
- I know that.
- Yes?
So why do you resist?
You haven't offered any other options.
Such as?
Surrender.
You would sacrifice yourself for the boy?
No.
For all of them.
So...
finally you admit your responsibility
in all of this.
Yes, I do.
Uncle Kai?
- Hi.
- Hey.
I'm getting a glass of wine downstairs.
I'm actually gonna go to sleep.
So good night.
Good night, Rebecca.
Agh! Unh.
Who sent you?
Fucking Indians.
Go help your uncle.
You've been in a fight.
Just a misunderstanding.
Do you want to tell me about it?
Someone had a crush on me.
I just wanted to be friends.
- Are we done?
- Not quite.
- Must be exhausting.
- Agh.
What?
Being on guard 24 hours a day.
Wondering where the next
attack is gonna come from.
Can you ever rest?
I've been looking at your
initial police report.
There were two of you in that building.
The police said that you
made it as far as the woods...
where your chance of escape
would be much greater...
but yet you turned around. Why?
Your accomplice...
it was a woman.
These sessions are confidential
and inadmissible in court.
You can't incriminate her.
You must have loved her very much.
And you haven't seen
or heard from her since?
I'm so sorry.
You okay?
Yeah.
So where you been?
You know, around.
Will you stay for a while...
now that he's gone?
I could really use you.
Well, that's not really
my bag, big brother.
Ugh.
Well, this is interesting.
Oh, that motherfucker!
This is my home.
So you're upset that the man...
who cut off the head
of the guy you sent to kill him...
isn't respecting your privacy?
What's this?
It's one of ours.
I'm thinking...
maybe I will stick around for a while.
This man will take you home, Max.
It's okay, Max.
Hey.
No one's gonna hurt you.
Go.
You trusted me to keep my word?
You always have.
Your call has
been directed to an automated voice-mail...
- Still no answer.
- Keep trying.
It's okay.
Gordon.
Sugar.
What are you doing here?
We got Max back.
What? What do you mean? How is he?
He's safe. He and Deva are with the FBI.
- He came home a little while ago.
- How?
He just rang the doorbell.
Said that they
dropped him off a block
away from the house.
Uh... I don't understand.
What do you mean? They just...?
They just dropped him off just like that?
No, not just like that.
Your father told him to tell you something.
What?
He said that you were forgiven.
- Hood.
- Max said they have him.
- He traded himself for Max.
- I don't understand why Hood...
- Would think that that's something...
- His cell phone.
- What?
- I got a tracker on his cell phone.
- There you are.
- What is that? Where is that?
The Bottoms near the North Valley Woods.
What the fuck are the Bottoms?
What's out there?
Heh, well, nothing that I can think of.
Wait.
The metalworks.
We've been here all day
looking at these maps...
moving satellites around
in outer fucking space.
And then he says,
"Wait, wait, the metalworks."
Well, the Bottoms aren't on most maps.
Is that it? Is that it right there?
Yeah.
What are you doing?
You call the FBI
and you let them handle this.
- I can't.
- You have to.
Now, I don't know what
Hood's role in all this is...
but we have two children whose lives
have been turned upside down.
Now, nothing and no one else
is more important than that.
Come on, man. Come on.
Now, you lied to me.
You lied to our kids.
I don't know if you can
ever make that right, but if...
If you're gonna try...
you need to come home
with me right now.
Gordon, don't do this.
Don't make me choose.
You go with them,
you're making that choice yourself.
Um, what are you doing?
Look, I've seen you drive. Get in.
We're probably gonna die.
Probably.
If we do die...
I just want you to know
I don't like you very much.
Duly noted.
Well, if you're going to drive, then drive.
I want to be dead or home by morning.
Just drive.
So your parole hearing is in two weeks.
Do you feel ready?
Uh, yeah, yeah. I think so.
I know you're ready to get out of here.
You think they'll let me out?
You present as intelligent and capable...
as remorseful and articulate.
Plus, you have the single
best psych eval ever written...
in the history
of the prison system, so...
Thank you.
I just wish...
What?
Ah, nothing.
- Come on, what?
- Nothing, no. I'm sorry.
- I forgot myself for a moment.
- It's our last session.
You're never gonna see me again.
Um, I was gonna say I just wish...
we had met under
different circumstances.
I know it's pathetic, cliché.
No, no. It's not.
Um, you saved me in here.
Are you scared?
Terrified.
Are you gonna see Ana
when you get out?
Uh, yeah.
Yeah, I've got a few places
I think I can, uh...
look for her.
- Who are you?
- What?
Who the fuck are you?
I never told you her name.
Mr. Rabbit has a message for you.
Mr. Rabbit says there'll be no parole.
You will serve out the
remaining eight years.
And he wants you to know that when
you do get out, he'll be waiting for you.
There's nowhere you can go
that he won't find you.
Aah! Help me!
Guard, help me!
- Get off! Get off!
- Oh, God!
It's funny being here with you.
I think of all that time
we were together...
the three of us.
We were a family.
Aw, don't kid yourself.
We were never a family.
Me and Ana, we were family.
Not you.
I think maybe we both
kid ourselves sometimes.
Oh, fuck you.
You betrayed me for love.
Then you got out of prison
to find your love had betrayed you.
And then a few days ago...
she barters your life for her own.
My daughter is better at punishing you
than I could ever be.
However...
a man can still try.
Oh, wow.
What is it?
Shit. I don't know.
Shit!
Were you speeding?
I knew I shouldn't have let you drive.
Evening, folks.
Mrs. Hopewell,
I don't know if you heard yet, but, uh...
- Your son turned up safe.
- I know. Thank you.
And, uh...
you, uh...
You three are clearly
not going to a PTA meeting.
Can you step out of the car, Mrs. Hopewell?
There.
That's better, right?
You took my only daughter from me.
There are no words to express the pain.
The rage I feel.
Oh, believe me...
she couldn't get away
from you fast enough.
She hated you...
more than she ever loved me.
You're right.
I took your little girl.
And there is nothing...
that you can do to me...
that can ever change that.
At least I can watch you
pay for your betrayal.
Why don't you shut the fuck up
and get on with it?
We got the call. What's going on?
Yeah, she's telling me
that Hood has been kidnapped...
- By the same guys that took her son.
- He wasn't kidnapped.
He traded himself for Max.
And they're gonna kill him
if I don't get over there.
If Hood is in trouble,
why wouldn't you call us?
- I can't involve you.
- An abduction and you can't involve...
the sheriff's department?
- That's kind of strange, don't you think?
- You think that's strange?
Take a look at who she called instead.
Oh, and, uh, Mrs. Hopewell
was strapped with these.
Two Springfield DX9s.
You want to tell us what
the hell's going on?
The man who has Hood
is a gangster named Rabbit.
He and I have a history.
It's me he's here for.
That's why he took Max.
He's got a small army with him
and he's not gonna think twice...
about killing you or me
or anyone else who gets in his way.
Well, what were you and the A-Team
over here planning to do?
He's going to kill him.
He may already have.
- Please, we are wasting time right now.
- This... This is crazy.
Sorry, I don't...
- You're the sheriff.
- I know I am.
- What?
- If it was you they had...
or any one of us,
what do you think Hood would do?
Shit.
I don't care what kind
of gangsters they are.
They picked the wrong fucking town.
Well, all right.
- You sure about this?
- Do I look sure?
Gregor, tell the men to start packing up.
We're leaving soon.
When I was a teenager...
I found two boys in a field.
They had tied a stray dog to a tree...
and they were beating it with sticks.
He was badly hurt, bleeding.
His front leg was broken.
After I finished with the boys...
I decided I would care for the dog.
But when I went to untie him...
he bit my leg.
The dog meant me no harm.
He was acting on instinct. I knew that.
But I also knew I had to kill him.
Because I, too...
was acting on instinct.
We're all animals, really.
Gentlemen.
Hmm.
Who the fuck are you?
I'm going to need you
to open this here gate.
This is private property. No one enters.
Oh, honey, if I had a dollar
for every time I heard that.
Now open the motherfucking gate.
- Fuck you.
- Oh, it's gonna be like that, is it?
Eenie, meenie, miney, mo.
My bad.
Nice shooting.
I've been taking lessons.
I should have killed you 15 years ago.
But there was a part of me
that hoped that you'd...
Both of you.
Would change your minds.
All right, hold up. Hold up.
The only entrance to this place
is on the other side.
We're gonna be outnumbered
and outgunned.
We have to surprise them.
I'll create a diversion.
You guys go up front and
wait for my signal.
- And then what? What's your plan?
- Save Hood, shoot everybody else.
Like you, I was blinded by love.
No.
This isn't about love.
We spent two years...
figuring out how to fuck you over.
And we did.
That's why you're angry.
Because you got played.
So do me a favor.
Stop whining...
about fucking love.
You don't know what love is.
You're wrong.
- Unh!
- This...
- Is love.
- Agh.
- Agh!
- Go now! Go, go!
Fuck!
- Agh!
- Sugar!
Sugar!
Go!
I knew she'd come for you.
Now she can watch you die.
Unh! Yes!
Aah!
- Brock!
- Aah!
- Motherfucker!
- Brook's hit.
I know. There's no way I can get to him.
He's too far away.
Go around and I'll cover you.
Left and right, flanking pattern.
I've got the center.
I'm running out of ammo!
Goddamn it! Emmett!
Agh!
- Shit, I'm running out.
- Unh.
How you doing?
Oh, fuck, that hurts.
- Sugar?
- He's okay. He's over there.
I'm fine.
- Did we win?
- We didn't lose.
Suck my tit.
- Unh!
- Agh!
Stay away from him.
I forgave you.
I gave you back your son.
Well, I never forgave you.
So, what now...
clever girl?
Good-bye, Daddy.
Hey. Let me see you.
- Unh.
- Oh, God.
Oh, my God.
My God.
Max?
He's safe. He's okay.
Next time, I say we just run away.
Hang on, okay?
I missed you.
Buck. Buck.
Bucky.
Buck.
Hey, boss.
Listen, Janie.
I'm sorry that I've been so distant.
You know, I've just been so obsessed
with taking down Proctor.
I never meant to shut you out.
He's everywhere, you know?
I worked with the Kinaho
to try to get this new casino built...
and now he has his hands in that, too.
That's the hotel.
And on the northern side
will be the casino.
That's why Longshadow wanted you killed?
Yeah.
So now what?
Well, I could just get rid of Alex...
but that would create
a power vacuum within the tribe...
and there's no telling
who would take over.
Better let Alex understand
who his friends are.
And how do we do that?
We could start with a phone call.
You just hit send.
Hello?
Is anyone here?
Well, I guess we'll have to settle
for leaving a message.
Any word on Rabbit?
The FBI turned the woods upside down.
Full-on search grids, dogs, the works.
So far, the theory is that he crawled
into a hole somewhere and died.
Hey.
- They'll find him.
- Yeah.
There. Heh.
Now that's what a sheriff looks like.
Uh, when do you have to change it again?
Tomorrow.
All right, then.
I'll see you tomorrow.
Thanks.
Deputy Yawners.
Agent Xavier.
One of the two active officers of the BSD.
How long you plan to keep us on a leash?
I don't like this any better than you do.
All right?
But Sheriff Hood,
his behavior throughout all this...
has been somewhere between
highly questionable and outright criminal.
And what went down at the metalworks...
that's gonna take some time to soft out.
The Bureau is assigning
a special investigator.
Look, in the meantime, you're just gonna
have to deal with federal oversight.
So...
never a dull moment around here, huh?
Couple of hunters found them this morning.
Based on the level of decomposition,
the coroner's ballparking it...
at 10 to 12 weeks
since they were killed.
Who might you be?
Church County Sheriff's Department.
Hi, uh, it's Jason Hood.
I was wondering if you had heard
from my old man at all.
Sorry, Jason. Still nothing.
All right.
Thanks anyways.
Fuck me.