Come this way, come this way.
Turn over.
Mm.
- You good?
- Mm-hm.
Was it okay for you?
Yeah, of course.
Are you sure?
You're usually a little more animated.
It was a quiet one.
Well, that's no fun.
Come on, let's see
if we can make some noise, huh?
Ha, ha. Oh, honey.
It's okay.
Honey, not now.
What is it?
Nothing. I'm just...
I'm just a little spent.
You're sure there's nothing wrong?
It's fine.
I'm gonna grab a glass of water.
Fuck!
Hello. Where's my fucking money?
- I'm in a bit of a bind.
- And you're calling me.
Am I the only one detecting a pattern here?
I'm on a take. I got boxed.
- Where are you?
- State Museum, Harrisburg.
State Museum.
How the mighty have fallen.
I'll bet she could suck the chrome off
a trailer hitch.
It's a Modigliani exhibit.
I don't know which I find harder to
believe, that there's a Modigliani...
in Harrisburg or that you got boxed
in a State Museum.
There was no box
in the schematics, Job.
Well, not in the ones
you were looking at, baby.
Oh, look, the alarm's got a dialer.
- State police are responding.
- Six minutes. Ha, ha.
I'm telling you, you should ask her out.
Job, I can barely hear you.
Can you turn this shit off?
- Is it off?
- Yeah.
Then I'm in there with you.
And I'm gonna get you out.
Okay. Is there a manual release?
Not one that you can reach
without a blowtorch.
- What's behind these walls?
- Solid stone.
Someone knew what they were doing.
Hold on a second.
- Hello?
- Oh.
I figured I'd get your voice mail.
- I keep odd hours.
- We need to talk.
Now is not really an ideal time.
Really? Well, it's the middle of the night
and I'm sneaking out to my backyard...
because I haven't slept
since you showed up.
You're putting me and my family at risk.
Hold on.
- Job.
- I know you did not just take a call...
while I'm trying to save
your pasty, dumb ass.
- Where are the cops, Job?
- Three minutes away.
I am looking for an override.
Look harder!
Hey, mama, you suck any dick yet tonight?
Yeah, like... Like maybe your own?
Well, yeah, yeah.
Wait, do you ever get bored
and tit-fuck yourself?
Ooh, she's getting pissy.
- Oh, yeah.
- I think she's upset.
- I'll be right back.
- What?
Job!
Oh, we pissed him off.
Oh, yeah, we did piss her off.
I think she likes you.
Hey, sweetie.
Sit your bitch-asses down.
Now I am going back to my table.
And the next one of you
that gets up out of this booth...
is gonna be pissing sitting down
for the rest of his life.
It's Zack's Diner,
just off the interstate...
Oh, sure, narc on a sister.
She... I mean, he has a knife.
- Job!
- Now we both on the clock.
Yeah, I'll be right back.
Ana.
It's Carrie.
Listen, we're gonna have to talk
some other time.
I don't wanna have another conversation
with you.
You need to stop this
for both of our sakes.
Hold on.
Job, I need this door open now!
Job? You're talking to Job?
Jesus Christ, you're on a take?
Listen, I'm in a jam.
You're on a take. Oh, my God.
I got boxed. Fuck.
Okay.
It's okay.
Just breathe.
Now, where are you?
State Museum, Harrisburg.
It's okay. Job will back-door it.
Get back to him now.
Okay.
Job, I hear sirens.
One second.
I've got an override.
Nothing's happening. Come on.
- Wait for it.
- Come on!
Now would be good.
Done.
Dispatch, please advise
we're sweeping the east hallway.
Ladies.
Bitches.
Miller, that you?
Shots fired!
Suspect is on the move on foot,
heading down North Street to 83rd.
He's wearing Miller's badge.
Unit 3, respond.
Right there! Right there!
Cover the entrance!
Start moving through here.
Over there!
We got the exits. He's got nowhere to go.
Over there! Go! Go!
Move! Move! I see him.
I like that.
On three!
One, two...
three, three, three!
- Hi.
How much does he know?
Don't worry about Sugar.
He's one of us.
There is no us.
That was some solid driving.
You're still sharp.
Hey, I didn't ask you to come, you know?
I didn't do it for you.
If you go down,
we both end up on Rabbit's radar.
Well, I guess we're in it together, then.
This is my life you're risking.
I had it handled.
Yeah,
everything was going right on schedule.
- Mm-hm.
- Ha, ha.
What is it with you?
You're still the same reckless
thrill junkie you were 15 years ago.
This whole sheriff thing you're doing...
it's one long bungee
jump without a cord.
You're not so different.
I'm not risking
everything for the thrill.
I wasn't the one driving the getaway car.
- Shut up.
- I'm serious.
So am I. Shut the fuck up.
What, sheriff wasn't good enough?
Now you want to be a state-y?
I had to improvise.
You get the painting?
Once a job goes south...
always leave the take behind.
So all that work for nothing.
Maybe not.
What?
Nothing.
- Sheriff.
- Miss Moody.
Kat.
Are we on a first-name basis now?
The Moody boys are gunning for you.
You killed their brother
and they're not gonna let that sit.
Why would you warn me?
- That's not the right question.
- What is, then?
The question is why aren't you scared?
You have a good morning, Kat.
- What was that about?
- Just a friendly chat.
With the widow of the man you killed?
Yeah.
I'm funny that way.
Sheriff, you, uh, sure you wanna be...
showing up to work looking like that?
Pick your battles, Brock.
All right, fine.
Tell it to the senator.
He's in your office.
Senator Schumacher.
There's a lacrosse stick in my bed.
Excuse me?
Syracuse, Hopkins...
all the schools were all after Reed...
offering him full rides.
He was lightning on the field.
Now he's dead, and my wife...
she's got his lacrosse
stick in our bed...
holding onto it every
night as she cries.
I'm sorry for your loss.
I'm not here for your sympathy.
I want justice.
You made enough arrests
that ATF has practically closed the case...
never mind that this guy Hanson
seems to have disappeared into thin air.
- It's federal jurisdiction.
- Fuck jurisdiction!
This happened in your town, Sheriff Hood.
His blood is on your hands.
You sleep with that in your bed.
Alma, get me the number of the high school.
Who are you looking for again?
Your telling us about Hanson was helpful...
but he's disappeared.
So we're looking for anyone else
that might have been involved...
someone who might be able
to lead us to Hanson...
or tell us where that bad E came from.
Hanson was getting his
stuff from somewhere.
God, how can one town
have so many scumbags?
Hey, him.
- I know him.
- You know him how?
Hanson and his guys
beat the crap out of this guy.
I don't know why,
but it was the day before the rave.
Arno Webber. I played Pop Warner with him.
He's pretty small-time,
but no stranger to the penal system.
He lives over in Hitler's Bunker.
Hitler's Bunker?
Some run-down apartments
where the Aryan Nation guys hang out.
What the hell is this?
You have no right to bring her in here
without asking me.
Chillax, Mom. I'm not in trouble.
Deva was just helping us with...
If you want to see or speak to my daughter,
you ask me first.
I'm sorry, Mrs. Hopewell.
Come on, baby, let's go.
Not for nothing, Mom...
but we're trying to catch a murderer.
Now.
Deva.
Thanks for your help.
Sure. I hope you catch the asshole.
So, what was all that with you
and Mrs. Hopewell?
She had a point, I guess.
That was it, huh?
- This the place?
- Yep.
This is where the master race
collect their unemployment checks.
They seem angry.
They don't like to see
a black man with a badge...
stepping into their white world.
- Oh.
- What you doing here, man?
Hey, it's okay, guys. He's one of us.
His wife is white.
- Nice.
- Just saying.
- That's Arno's door.
- Hey, cop!
What the fuck you doing here?
Whatever the fuck I want.
I'll go see Arno.
You stay here with the Hitler Youth.
Hey, Arno.
You stay the fuck back!
Penn State, right?
You're that all-star nigger running back.
Aah! Okay! Okay! Fuck, what do you want?
Why'd you run? Why'd you run?
Instinct, man.
Looking for a guy named Hanson.
Seems to have gone off the grid.
I'm not telling you shit.
Oh, God!
You're a two-time loser, Arno.
What are we gonna find
if we toss your apartment, huh?
- Ha, ha.
- Possession? An attempt to distribute?
Get a warrant, motherfucker.
- Wrong answer.
- Oh, God!
Off the grid. Ha, ha.
You wanna see Hanson?
Well, there he is.
That's Hanson's hand?
Fucking Addams Family, right?
How do you know it's Hanson?
From the tat, man.
I inked him myself.
- A crab?
- He was a Cancer, man.
He was into all this astrology shit.
- Where'd you get it?
- That I can't tell you.
Okay, then you're going down
for Hanson's murder.
What the fuck, man? I'm helping you.
No. You're annoying me.
Where'd you get the goddamn hand?
Okay, okay.
I work at the slaughterhouse
on the killing floor, all right?
Cleaning and shit.
Well, one day last week,
I sneak in a few pops on the job...
get a little loaded,
and fall asleep behind some crates.
I wake up around midnight, hearing things.
I peek out and there's
the boss himself...
and that weird, quiet dude
with the bow ties...
carrying something wrapped up in a tarp.
I hid while they fed it to the shredder.
And when they left,
I found that down in the blood gutter.
I kept it.
Kind of like insurance.
- You saw Proctor himself?
- Yeah, I did.
- And you'll testify?
- Fuck, no!
I'm kind of addicted to breathing.
- I can help you with that.
- Wait, wait.
This is bullshit. It's bullshit.
Proctor would never do it himself.
- Cuff him.
- No, man! Wait, wait, wait!
- Hey!
- Check it out! Check it out!
Uh, modern technology don't lie.
And the Oscar for Best Picture goes to...
Arno Webber!
You guys are gonna protect me, right?
You're a good citizen, Arno.
Dude, seriously, man,
you gotta keep my name out of this.
He'll kill me.
What a loss that would be
to the Nazi gene pool.
- We'll be in touch. Stay by the phone.
- You just took my fucking phone.
- Then stay here.
- Ugh.
Jesus Christ.
And you confirmed the hand's Hanson's?
Prints match.
So we don't get Proctor
for drugs or racketeering...
but we get him on murder
of one of his own.
Guess there's a poetry to that.
So we good to go?
Well, it's not a slam dunk,
but it's actionable.
Okay, then.
Get your, uh...
Get your witness locked up tight.
When his name goes to the grand jury,
he'll be an endangered species.
You got it. Thanks.
Sheriff, could I have a moment?
- It's good to see you, Gordon.
- Yeah, you, too. Thanks, Emmett.
So this guy Webber, Deva identified him?
- Yeah.
- Okay.
But that's as far
as her involvement here goes.
I don't see why it needs to go further.
My wife was pretty pissed.
Well, I'm sorry about that.
Poor judgment on my part.
Don't get me wrong. I get it.
The case was getting cold and...
I appreciate what you did for my daughter.
Carrie and I both do.
I just... I need to keep
Deva safe, you know?
She's only 15.
I understand.
Okay.
So, uh, go get him, huh?
What are you thinking?
I'm thinking
we should have brought backup.
You are the backup.
Sheriff, deputy.
What can I do for you?
You're under arrest.
What for?
Murder.
Who did I kill?
Christopher Hanson.
Yeah. I haven't seen Hanson
in quite some time.
Yeah, that's one of the side effects
of killing someone.
It saddens me that you continue
to hold me in such low regard.
You'll get over it.
Can we get on with this?
You stay right there.
So, Sheriff Hood...
how are you finding the job so far?
Never a dull moment, Kai.
Yeah, you've been kind of busy
since you got here.
I imagine things were a bit quieter in...
Where was it, Oregon?
Deputy Yawners mentioned
your right to remain silent.
Oh, come on, sheriff.
If you're going to be arresting me
every time someone shows up dead...
- We might as well get to know each other.
- I already know...
Come on.
- Where's Emmett?
- The deputy fell out of the car.
We got no business with him.
If he's hurt and you just left him...
Right about now I'd be worried
about my own ass if I was you.
I got to admit...
didn't count on Proctor being with you.
Two birds, one stone.
Our lucky day.
I don't think so, Marcus.
You don't think so?
You knocked every one
of my brother's teeth out.
Looked like a fucking baby
when he opened his mouth.
Yeah, and he cried like a baby too.
Now I'm gonna take your teeth out...
one by one...
real surgical.
Then we'll see who's crying.
What the fuck you laughing at?
A dead man making threats.
Marcus, we need to talk about this.
You
didn't say nothing about
messing with Proctor.
Shut up, Dex!
We get the sheriff, that's fair.
An eye for an eye.
But Proctor? We got families.
What about our brother's family?
Huh? What about Cole's kids?
You didn't say nothing
about messing with Proctor.
We got Proctor in the deal!
God was just saving us a trip.
Get him up.
Get him up!
Get him up, Goddamn it!
Motherfucker!
You tore my fucking ear off!
Stop!
What, are you gonna kill a cop, Dex?
Huh?
I mean, how do you see this playing out?
Shut up.
What, you're...? You're gonna kill us both?
And then just go home...
kick back, fry up some fucking venison?
- I said shut up!
- No, you listen to me!
I was taking Proctor in
when you guys showed up...
and that's what I'm gonna do.
You and your brothers...
you came out for some redneck justice.
I get that.
But you got only one shot
at getting out of this.
That's the one I'm giving you right now.
Go home.
Take your brothers. You do it now...
- I might forget this ever happened.
- You'll let us go?
How do I know you're not bullshitting me?
If I was, you'd already be dead.
I meant what I said.
Get the fuck out of here.
No, no, no. Sorry, boys.
I'm gonna have to keep the truck.
You crashed my car. Fair is fair.
Once you hit the road...
I'm sure you can catch a ride
to the hospital.
You can come get the truck
from the Cadi tomorrow.
Oh.
Marcus.
Don't forget the rest of you.
You're really gonna let them go?
I'm prioritizing.
Help me get him down.
Jesus Christmas.
- What the hell happened to you guys?
- Car trouble.
What the hell is this?
What did you do to my client?
He's been assaulted? Kai, wait.
Have you been assaulted?
If you assaulted my client,
I will have charges brought up against you.
You, too, Yawners. I'll bring the
wrath of God down on this whole...
Quiet.
He's all yours.
Don't even ask.
Ha, ha.
Wait.
I got you something.
- Is it hot?
- No.
I paid for this one.
It's our house.
It's where we're going.
Where is it?
Far from here.
What's the matter? What is it?
Fuck me. Please, just fuck me.
Big day for you.
Why didn't you just shoot the Moody boys?
They gave you the perfect excuse.
Well, if I kill every dumb redneck
that crosses me...
it won't be long before people
outside Banshee start looking at me.
Yeah, you could lose your job.
And speaking of jobs...
I want in.
You want in on what?
Whatever comes next.
No.
- What do you mean no?
- I mean no.
You've been good to me.
You got a good thing going here.
I'm not gonna screw that up for you.
Heh. No, this is screwed up.
You think I wanna spend what's left of my
life pouring beers and breaking up brawls?
I got my life savings in this place.
It's not gonna give it
back to me when I'm done.
I'm 56 years old. That's 70 for a fighter.
I'm black, I got a criminal record.
You have an interesting way
of selling yourself.
Fuck you.
Look, I don't need much...
but I need more than I got.
You have a particular skill set?
You mean aside from saving your ass?
The doctors couldn't get Marcus' ear
back on his head.
Well...
I guess half deaf...
is better than all dead.
Why didn't you kill them?
I'm not a killer.
Ha, ha. I think my late husband
might disagree with that.
I guess he would.
They're gonna keep coming, you know?
Why are you here, Kat?
I don't know.
Oh, you...
Mr. Proctor!
Would you do me the profound courtesy
of shutting the fuck up?
Oh, God.
Hello?
I'm in here.
Got your babysitting duty, huh?
Yeah.
You mind if I have a quick word
with your prisoner?
If it gets him to stop
singing, I'm all for it.
The wunderkind mayor...
here to savor the moment.
Enjoy it, Mr. Mayor.
Because a moment is all you'll get.
Is something on your mind, son?
Don't call me "son."
Ah. I'm sorry.
Forgot about your daddy issues.
Did you know I had to put him in a home?
And when I go visit him there now
in that place and I see him...
and I smell him...
Enterprises fail, Kendall.
Or it dissolves to make way for progress.
- I'm not respons...
- You broke him.
And I'm gonna break you.
As long as it takes.
Hmm.
I admire your gumption.
Most men would just grab
a shotgun and come after me...
but you, you ran for mayor.
It's maybe a little,
I don't know, gutless...
but for someone like you...
a boy who will never really be a man...
You're a blight on this town.
And I'm gonna... Oh!
I was building this town
before you were born.
You have me to thank for all of it.
Your father was weak, barely a man.
And you're no different.
Break me?
You're a gnat on my ass.
You have no idea what real power is,
you little prick.
What the fuck is going on here?
I think he needs medical attention.
What happened? Dan?
Okay, the charge is murder in the first.
Will you be entering a plea now
or waiting on the grand jury?
My client is pleading
not guilty, Your Honor.
Very well.
I assume you'll want to discuss bail now.
- Yes, Your Honor.
- This is a murder charge.
We have an eyewitness, physical evidence.
Mr. Proctor's wealth is public record.
The DA pulls my client
into this courtroom on a regular basis.
If there was
ever a flight risk...
There's a larger political
agenda at work here.
We fully expect this case to fall apart...
as all the DA's cases
against my client have in the past.
Mr. Proctor has never fled before.
- He's not gonna start now.
- It's murder, judge.
Mr. Proctor has a business to run.
He can't do that from a jail cell.
Okay, in light of the defendant's
legal history here...
and the fact
that he's never been convicted...
I'm not going to remand him
until after an indictment.
Bail is set at $300,000.
Defendant will surrender his passport
before being released.
Thank you, Your Honor.
I brought a check with me.
- Eyewitness?
- Already working on it.
Fuck me.
You don't write, you don't call.
What do you want?
Hmm.
What do I want?
I want a steak, fries, and a Diet Coke.
I want the entire Jean Paul Gaultier
fall collection.
Oh, and I want $750,000
for my blown-up business.
I am sorry about that.
What did you expect to happen?
It's fucking Rabbit.
Well, I can get you the steak.
You can start with the steak...
then you can take me shopping
for new digs.
- Digs?
- Mm.
That's right, baby, digs.
You better brace yourself.
Here come the motherfucking neighborhood.
- You know you're gonna hate it here.
- Not true.
I already hate it here.
I know all about witness protection
and relocation.
I've seen it in shitloads of movies.
You gotta set me up with a whole new life
in, like, Topeka...
where I get to be whatever I want...
like a master electrician...
or a guidance counselor.
Don't judge, bro. I got shit to offer.
You are shit.
I'd make a great stone mason.
Is it possible for you to draw a breath
without speaking?
You're an uptight motherfucker.
What's your blood pressure like, man?
Fuck.
I gotta take a piss.
Well, put it back when you're done.
Who's there?
Hello?
What the fuck's going on?
What is it?
They're here for you.
Fucking hell.
Wait, are you just fucking with me?
Wait, wait! Get the fuck off me!
Get the fuck away!
I didn't tell them anything!
Hey, cop, wake up!
Help!